Hide! Quickly!
Run away.
Back. This way.
Quick, this way.
Quickly, come on.
Down to the lake.
- M for Mischa.
- Mischa.
Come on! Come on, let's go!
Come on, Lothar.
- Hurry now. Give me the bathtub.
- Yes, sir.
Hannibal, Mischa,
where have you been?
Hurry now. Quickly!
Hannibal! Come here.
Come on...
Darling, the cart is packed.
Everything is ready.
Hurry up. Come on, come on.
Come on, old boy. Come on.
Hey... Colonel Timka says the fighting
will be close to the roads.
It can't last more than a few days.
We'll be safe at the Lodge.
Come on, we're almost there.
No, no, no, no, no.
The bath has to be for the dirty clothes.
Yes, Madam.
In you come.
Let's see if our toys are still there.
- Hand me the bath.
- I'll take care of that, sir.
No, no, it's fine. But let's hurry.
Cook will have finished packing
the kitchen
by the time you get back.
Mischa.
Hannibal, give them here.
Mama's pearls.
Blow.
Pearls before swine?
Mischa, blow.
Shut up! Shut up!
The Major's here.
You are a Jew.
How could I eat your cooking?
Dispose of him.
How do you deal with locals,
being locals yourself?
You say you want to be SS,
let's see you earn it.
Kill the Jew.
Bring me the peasant.
Move! Move!
Move, you fat fucking Jew.
- Are you a gypsy?
- No, sir.
Are you a Jew?
No, sir.
Good job!
Why don't you show us your dick?
Major! Russian tanks moving west!
Put all their food on the trucks.
Move it!
What's that?
- It's a tank, a Russian tank.
- Get away from the window!
Lothar! Russians!
Everybody out of the house!
We only want water.
The children can stay in the warm.
- Get them inside.
- Go, Hannibal. Look after Mischa.
Start the pump.
Wait here.
Mama! Mama!
- How much longer with the pump?
- A few minutes.
- Stuka! Stuka!
- Shoot! Shoot!
Stay down!
Papa! Papa!
Mischa!
Hannibal!
Mama!
No! No
Mischa! Mischa!
Mischa, go back.
- Go back, Mischa!
- Mama!
No, Mischa, go back!
Hurry! Hurry!
Come on, Grentz.
Kolnas, come on. Hurry!
Come on!
Get in the back.
Put it in the back.
Start the engine.
I told you, Grutas,
we're going to die.
Relax. We're getting rich.
In. In, in, in. Go.
Grutas, isn't that the SS Major?
Major. Kill a few gypsies, you said.
Kill a few Jews,
and we'll make you SS.
If you had kept your word...
I would be saying
'yes, sir' to you now.
But now, I am in business for myself.
- Russians!
- The Russians. Move!
Go, go, go, go. Hurry!
The Commissar has ordered that
all soldiers found looting are to be executed.
They're shooting looters.
Stop and black out.
Come on!
- Put it down.
- Drop it now, you little fuck.
Put it down!
Or we shoot her.
- Give me that.
- Get the radio, Kolnas.
- Milko, check the kitchen.
- Fuck you!
I want Mama.
We're lucky, only kids.
If a patrol comes by...
...we saved them...
...and their family's stuff.
Grentz, check the door...
Pot Watcher...
Check upstairs.
Find some food.
...only rotten potatoes.
- Find something... try the Germans...
- It's breaking up.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I need information, you idiot!
It's not a fucking toy!
Wait! I have found some
thing under Russian frequency.
Road blocks.
Every five kilometers
from here to Vilnius.
So... we are stuck for now.
- Did you get something?
- It's freezing out there.
Open it.
You think these are peppercorns?
These are frozen maggots.
This was rotten before it froze.
I'll put this in your head.
Stop it, Grutas.
The boy is Hannibal Lecter.
And the little girl is Mischa.
We eat or die.
Let's hear you, Little Master.
- He's mute.
- He's not mute at night.
He can scream well enough
and he'll sing.
This is not your father's house any more.
It's the People's Orphanage.
...and you're just one more orphan.
Lecter! I'll see you in my office.
Hannibal, you do not
honor the human pecking order.
You're always hurting the bullies.
I know.
This was your Mother's room.
It must be difficult for you to live
in this house.
Go to bed.
Go to bed!
Everything all right?
Mischa!
Get up!
Now scream all you please.
Every day, you'll pay for this
Every day for the rest of your short
and nasty life.
Lecter!
He's not here.
This way!
Who's there?
Some help you are.
Shoo! Go!
- What is it, Serge?
- A boy, Madame.
He has pictures of you
and your husband.
Your Uncle would have
loved to see you, Hannibal.
It has been almost a year
since he died.
Only you and I are left now.
Mischa! Mischa!
Mischa!
Mischa! Mischa.
Hannibal!
Mischa!
Hannibal, Hannibal! Wake up!
It's all right. It's all right.
When you sleep do you remember?
Do you remember
what happened to Mischa?
You look like your uncle, Hannibal.
Would you like to try?
Use this.
Hannibal!
Speak to me.
Thank you.
Hannibal!
Here is where I pray to my ancestors
for strength, for courage.
I have the honor
only on my ancestor's birthday...
...to polish his armor
with oil of cloves.
This is after the fight
for Osaka Castle.
The samurai display the heads
of their enemies.
There are more suitable parchments
that will interest you.
Be gentle, Hannibal...
and be brave
...like your father.
And like him.
You must be ready for anything.
Come!
Again.
Good... again!
Hey, Japonese.
Monsieur... please.
- Is that all Madame?
- Yes.
Hey, Japonese, tell me the truth...
...does your pussy run crossways?
With a puff of straight hairs
like a little explosion?
Hannibal!
Don't move.
If you've pissed in my fuel tank,
I'll twist your head off.
Paul Momund, the butcher.
You owe a certain lady an apology.
Apologize to La Japonaise?
Boy, you must be crazy to come here,
I'll throw you in the river...
...or maybe I'll slit your pants
and give you something you don't want
...where you don't want it.
You inquired about her... pussy.
You speculated it ran which way?
Jap pussy runs crossways...
You should fuck that little Jap
and see for yourself, huh?
Crossways like that?
Or more tangential to the spine?
Do you see how your mouth
stains the air?
I should add that to my drawing.
Would you like to see it?
Yum!
Wait for me.
This wound was made
with a single blow.
Ah, Inspector Popil,
I'm very happy you could come.
You won't remember me but
I was with the...
Of course,
you delivered De Rais to Nuremberg...
- ...and sat behind him.
- I saw you bring the evidence.
It's an honor, sir.
- What do we have here?
- Paul Momund, or most of him.
You have his dossier.
Yes. Fat and ugly.
He shipped Jews from Marseille.
He fought recently.
And often.
Last Saturday night in a bar fight.
He had many enemies.
A list, please.
His recent opponents.
- You've done nothing to this body?
- Oh, no, no, no, Monsieur.
- The Chief specifically...
- The odor it er...
it's not of anything you use here?
It smells like that toothache remedy.
Yes, oil of cloves.
Let's see the pharmacist.
Look.
The most exquisite bits of the fish
are the cheeks.
This is true for many creatures.
When carving at the table
you give one cheek to Madame...
- the other to the guest of honor.
- Did you hear?
They haven't found
the butcher's damned ugly head yet.
Good evening, my lady.
I hope you don't mind.
I would have used a butcher's knife,
but the sword seemed so appropriate.
Not a nick in the blade,
I promise you.
The butcher was like butter.
You didn't need to do this for me.
Rudeness is epidemic, my Lady.
Police.
They will call it murder.
At worst, a crime of passion.
Wash your hands, quickly. Go!
- Inspector Pop-il?
- Popil, Madame.
Hannibal Lecter?
Good evening.
You fought with the butcher
Paul Momund in the market.
Now he is dead.
I must ask you to come
along with me.
Is your name Hannibal Lecter?
Yes.
Do you have any guilty knowledge
of the death of Paul Momund?
- Guilty knowledge?
- Limit your responses to yes or no.
No.
It's vanilla.
He reacts to nothing.
It's monstrous.
The butcher had been fishing.
There was blood and scales on his knife,
but no fish.
The tape tells you all that?
Remarkable.
No.
The Chef told me
you bought a splendid fish in for dinner.
- Where did you get that fish?
- By fishing, Inspector.
We keep a baited line
in the water behind the boathouse.
I'll show you if you like.
My speciality is war crimes.
And I know they do not end
with the war.
You lost your entire family.
So did I.
But for you, your beautiful Aunt came
and made up for it all.
The very scent of her must have
taken away the smell of the camp.
So, when Paul the butcher
spewed filth at her...
I can understand if you killed him.
Tell me what happened, Hannibal.
Together we could show a court...
The very scent of her
takes away the smell of the camp?
Do you compose verse, Inspector
and keep it under your pillow?
Now tell me, Inspector.
Did you choose war crimes...
- because you lost family in the war?
- Yes.
How?
Some in combat,
some were shipped east.
Did you catch who did it?
No.
But they were Vichy,
men like the butcher?
Yes.
Then we are both suspects.
I can say you were fishing with me,
if you like?
Inspector, you should see this.
I told you, lead these people away.
- That is the butcher?
- Yes, sir.
- How long?
- Ten minutes, no longer.
Father... Mother...
I'm the youngest student they've ever
admitted into Medical School.
It's a work scholarship.
I think you would be pleased.
Death duties on my Uncle's estate...
have finally forced the sale
of the Chateau.
Lady Murasaki will leave
for Paris with me.
Her residency in France
is now under threat.
This work scholarship
means I must spend
much of my spare time...
preparing bodies
for the anatomy class.
My studies are fascinating
and absorb me completely.
Yet I still find myself
thinking about my sister.
and the men who took her from me.
Hannibal!
Do you suppose
God intended to eat Isaac?
That's why he told Abraham to kill him.
Eat him?
Of course not.
The Angel intervenes in time.
Not always.
I have to know about Mischa.
I can see their faces in my dreams...
but I can't remember
what they called each other
with their bloody mouths.
I would give anything to remember.
Hannibal...
memory is a knife, it can hurt you.
I want to stay here with you.
No. You must stay at school.
Louis, I need you to remember...
Who told the Nazis
where the children were hidden?
You must remember.
I can't bear to think about it.
This will help you remember.
Hannibal Lecter?
What are you doing here?
The body.
I'm a medical student now.
Yes, I know.
I followed your progress.
You repeat nothing you hear
in this room.
Please, Louis.
Klaus Barbie shipped
the children to Auschwitz.
Who told him
where the children were hidden?
Did you tell him?
When they broke my fingers
I gave them Pardou.
Pardou knew
where the children were hidden.
He's Mayor of Belleville now.
- Thank you, Louis.
- Inspector?
Where were the police?
No, no, no. No, no, please, please.
You knew at once
what Louis wanted, didn't you?
His crucifix to remain with his brain,
not his heart.
He answered your question,
but you didn't answer his.
Where were the police when the Nazis
threw the children into the trucks?
Hannibal!
Come and play.
One little cheek... two little cheeks.
Cough.
She has pneumonia.
Let's take her.
She's going to die, anyway.
Hannibal!
Come on!
- Get out!
- Grutas, wait!
The dog tags.
Come on!
Pot Watcher, hurry!
Passport.
- Student?
- Yes.
You need a new photograph.
Night report.
Entry visas for Kaunas.
Lecter...
The Lodge.
Kolnas.
Grutas.
Mischa.
Herr Dortlich.
On behalf of myself
and my late family...
I thank you for coming.
Do you remember the bathtub
bubbling on the stove?
She was dead anyway,
I swear it, she was.
So much mayonnaise, Herr Dortlich.
Where are the others?
I don't know.
Yes, I know where one of them is.
Grentz, I know Grentz.
- Grentz?
- In Canada.
He got out on the refugee boat
from Bremerhaven.
- What did he look like?
- Swarthy.
They wouldn't have let him
in the SS.
Oh yes, of course.
He was the one that
always provided the bowl.
What about Milko?
All dead. They're all dead
in the war.
I remember his singing.
And now your leader, Grutas?
I don't know, I don't know,
I don't know. I don't know.
Please, please let me go
and I will testify against Grentz.
Do you remember
'Das Mannlein im Walde', Herr Dortlich?
Mischa loved that song.
Let's sing for Mischa.
You're not singing.
Sing for slack, Herr Dortlich.
It's Kolnas!
Kolnas deals with him!
Kolnas deals with him.
And where is Kolnas?
Fontainebleau!
'Purpurroten Mantelein', indeed.
He picked some wild mushrooms...
and made a brochette.
Mushrooms and cheeks.
Where have you been?
You smell of smoke
and blood.
Where did you go?
I found them.
The men who killed Mischa.
I have their names.
They're here in France.
Where?
Fontainebleau.
Ortolans.
He nets them on their way to Africa
and serves them for lunch.
They're like us.
They smell the others cooking
and still they try to sing.
Kolnas is using the name of 'Kleber'.
It's on the license.
Monsieur Kleber residing
Rue Juliana.
Good Morning, how are you?
Oh, look... here he is.
Come by on his way to church
to check the till.
How neat he is
and plump, this...
...war criminal.
Do you know that song?
Where is Natalya?
Where is she?
Always wandering off.
Natalya, come, come.
We have to go to church.
Hannibal, he has children.
She's wearing
Mischa's bracelet.
Choose your offering
for the Church.
Good, put it in your pocket.
Ah, the shiny one.
Put it safe in...
What is it?
- Good evening.
- They're waiting for you, down below.
I called my Soviet friends.
Dortlich's dog tag was
in his mouth.
That means that
he has all of our dog tags...
- ...and the pot watcher's inventory.
- No, no, no.
Dortlich searched
those ruins before.
Grutas told him to do it.
Poked around with his picnic fork,
the lazy bastard.
Where is he? Where is he?
This poison little boy
who killed Dortlich?
He's a Paris schoolboy.
They say that there is
a passport photograph
but they don't have it yet.
What's his name?
Hannibal Lecter.
You know him?
So do you.
We...
...we had dinner with him
during the war.
Go back to
your restaurant, Kolnas.
Hey!
Bring me a covered dish
next time.
Where the hell is Dieter?
Dieter!
You bruise their face,
you split their lip,
the money goes down.
Come here.
And that one.
That one is mine for now.
Milko, I want you to go to Paris.
Kolnas found me a Bosendorfer piano.
The best.
Oh, and... find the boy.
Lecter...
you know what to do with him.
Thanks.
Inspector Popil...
please come in.
This is not a social call.
- Where is he?
- I don't know. At medical school, I think.
Did you ever see this man?
No.
His name is Dortlich.
He's a War Criminal.
He was found near
the castle Hannibal came from.
Dortlich had some ugly friends,
I want to know where they are.
Hannibal may know.
Don't cut yourself.
I know about you...
I know you lost your family...
...everything,
when the bomb fell on Hiroshima.
Yes.
And you protect Hannibal
because he lost everything too?
That is your bond with him?
Do you see your family,
in your dreams, Inspector?
Yes.
So do I...
so does he.
If your pet snake strikes in France...
I will have to seize him.
He will die under the guillotine.
Sorry.
It was who sent you to kill me.
No, not to kill you.
To give you money.
Let me give it to you.
No!
You killed so many, Milko.
Many more than these.
Do you feel them
in the tank around you?
We ate her...
We ate her to live.
Grutas was very quick,
she felt nothing.
So, Grutas has a house?
Where?
I have difficulty hearing you.
He has a house?
Alright. alright...
Milly-la-Foret.
No! No!
She felt nothing!
No! Please.
Oh! Inspector Popil.
What a surprise.
Found in your room.
If you kill in France...
I will see your head in a bucket.
Do you mind
if I work while we talk?
You killed Dortlich in the woods
where your family died.
His face had been eaten.
I would suspect the ravens.
Ravens who made
a shish kebab?
Cannibalism.
It happened on the Eastern Front.
But you know that, don't you?
You were there.
This is not the face of your subject.
This is the face of Vladis Grutas,
like the pictures in your room.
Did you kill him too?
- No, I didn't.
- Have you found him?
If I found him...
I give you my word,
I would bring him to your attention.
Don't fool with me.
Did you know he sawed off
the head of the Rabbi at Kaunas?
He shot gypsy children
in the woods.
He walked free at
Nuremburg because
a witness got acid
poured down her throat.
I will need your deposition.
Come with me.
Let's begin.
Put it down...
...or I'll shoot her.
Grutas has the eyes of
an arctic wolf.
He knew at once to threaten Mischa
to make me put down the spear.
At first they needed us for cover
in case troops found them.
Later... they crowded around...
feeling our cheeks and arms.
Hold it still.
Mischa!
- Hold it still.
- Not in here, boss.
Not in here.
Hannibal!
I promised Mischa.
Promised to make them
pay a pound of flesh?
To pay skin for skin?
If they'd killed you,
who would punish them then?
The answer is me. I will.
If you swear to share
what you know with me,
then I will let you go.
I swear.
Jacques?
He knows something.
He'll lead us to Grutas
then we'll arrest him.
The court has to
declare him insane...
...and in an asylum
the doctors can study him
and find out what he is.
The little boy, Hannibal,
died in 1944 out in that snow.
His heart died with Mischa.
What he is now...
there is no word for it...
...except monster.
Give these men to the police.
It's Kolnas's children, isn't it?
No.
Promise me.
Hannibal!
I can't.
I can't,
I already promised Mischa.
- No word from Milko?
- No.
Come on, close the gate.
Don't worry,
I won't hit you again.
I like you now.
Maybe I'll fix your teeth.
I want to steam.
Turn it up.
I am glad you're here.
I always felt
I owed you something.
I thought you would be bigger.
I put your face on
every bully I ever hurt.
Kill him!
Answer me this.
Would you have fed me
to your little sister
because you loved her?
Yes.
There- there you have it...
Love.
I love myself that much
and I would never apologize to you.
Cut him!
Wait! Look at me!
And it won't hurt so much.
Bitch!
Get him! Go!
- Call Kolnas!
- Okay.
To continue our conversation...
Do you wish to see
Lady Murasaki alive?
Yes.
Listen to her.
Speak to your little fuck boy!
Listen, listen carefully...
I offer you a life for a life.
Bring me everything you have.
The dog tags,
Pot Watcher's little inventory,
every fucking thing.
- Where?
- Kilometer 36...
...on the way to Trilbardou
there is a telephone kiosk.
Be there at sunrise
and wait for a call.
If you are not there...
I will send her cheeks
in the mail.
A life for a life.
- Ready to sail, sir.
- Come on!
I'm sorry your room
isn't quite ready yet.
I'll contact room service.
Please.
Eva!
Clean up the treatment room.
Our old guests are leaving.
We have a new one checking in.
Get out!
Good evening, Herr Kolnas.
You drink better wine
than you serve.
I'm calling the police.
May I get them for you?
What did I do to you?
Aside from eating my sister?
Nothing.
Are you wearing your dog tag,
Herr Kolnas?
Many people look like me.
Are you sure you have the right person?
I was slave labor
for the Nazis in the war.
I lost family too, I understand.
Well, to improve your understanding,
I went by your home...
...on the Rue Juliana.
I went into the children's room...
...with the sleeping child.
And... I picked up something
for your offal.
It's a beef roast, Kolnas.
Do you see how it feels?
Where is she?
Where is my daughter?
What did you do to her?
Your daughter is safe, Herr Kolnas.
I will give her back to you
when you give me Lady Murasaki.
If I do that,
I am a dead man.
No. Grutas will be arrested.
I won't remember your face.
Help me...
or I'll leave the child to starve.
Where is Lady Murasaki?
Grutas has a house boat.
A canal boat.
He moves around.
Where is the boat?
In the canal l'Ourcq,
west of Meaux.
Where is my child?
- Hello?
- Hello, Astrid?
- Yes?
Look at the children.
- Why?
- Just do it!
The children are fine.
They're sleeping.
Petras...
Hello? Petras?
- You tricked me.
- No.
I kept my word.
I will spare your life
for the sake of your children.
Your boyfriend...
ate Dortlich's face
Jean, tie her up.
I'll go astern.
Help!
- Jean?
- Help me!
Grab it... grab it!
Hold it.
No! Help!
No!
Hannibal.
Shot in the spine,
my little Mannlein.
Can't feel your legs?
Too bad.
You won't feel it
when I cut off your balls.
A present for you.
A velvet bag.
Can you see?
Good.
Look at this.
I can put some color
in her cheeks.
Come on.
Where is Grentz?
If I tell you...
will you kill me quickly?
Yes.
A village in Canada...
...near Saskatoon.
Stop Hannibal.
Give him to Popil.
He ate my sister.
So did you...
you ate her too.
So why don't you kill yourself?
- No.
- Pot Watcher fed her to you in a broth.
- Liar.
- You have to kill...
...everyone who
knows it don't you?
You ate her...
...half conscious.
Your little lips
greedy around the spoon.
No! Hannibal, stop.
M for Mischa.
Stop. Stop now.
Forgive them.
Never.
I love you.
What is left in you to love?
Find me the Captain.
I came as soon as I heard.
Where is Hannibal?
Come on.
Hannibal!
- Call the fire brigade!
- Yes, Inspector.
Take some men, get down there.
Hannibal.
Coming.
Yes?
I came to collect a head.