Are you an accountman
of the firm?
Financial Chief.
You should have one
give me a call.
I never tried as hard at acting
as I did for advertising.
I only want to ensure that
Niegel is enrolled in the fall.
Niegel's enrollement isn't an issue
wether we pay or not.
If I walk out that door, that's it.
That's it.
Your activities last night
have costed us this account.
( theme music playing )
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
( Ringing )
- Hello? - I apologize for the hour.
You instructed me to avoid your officers.
But we have good news.
Oh, thank goodness.
The hansard procedure
negotiations
have concluded as promised.
You need only wire
the full £2,900 by Thursday
and your slate will be clear
with the *-revenue.
As promised?
Your promise
was to extricate me
from this situation altogether.
My promise was to keep you
out of prison.
Thursday...
How am I supposed to find
$8,000 in two days?
That's not possible.
That's no help at all.
Look, Lane, you gave her majesty's
portion to a foreign power
and the tax man is keen to make
an example of an expatriate.
This is the very best news
there could be.
You should get a pencil.
I'll give you formation.
What are you doing out here?
Uh, business.
Go back to bed, dear.
- What are you looking for?
- Go back to bed this minute!
( Sighs )
Scarlett, hold this
and stand here.
No.
Mr. kinsey called
regarding lunch.
- What does he want?
- I think he wants to have lunch.
- What's wrong with him? He's very polite.
- Yeah.
You should have seen him
at Ken's bachelor party.
- I think he was on LSD.
- Really?
Well, he's sort of been
threatening to "spot" by.
Scarlett, here you are.
Oh, I'm sorry, Mr. Pryce.
Do you need me?
Only in that I wanted you
to direct me to Mr. Crane.
Please leave us.
I'll meet him for coffee.
I was hoping we could discuss
the first quarter
media projections.
Sure.
These numbers
are very positive.
Theyojections.
They're derived from reality,
but they're hopes and dreams.
January and february$
look great--
Heinz, Mohawk, Vicks,
all pretty stable.
When will they become
commitments?
I can't predict
the future, Lane.
I don't know what the
Russians are going to do.
We may be living underground
by Lincoln's birthday.
Mm.
Hey, that's my only copy.
Walt: Hope you don't need
any actual paperwork
because everything's
out by my desk
and my desk is out by Chuck.
How's Rebecca?
About the same--
Underfed and underpaid.
And Laura?
She calls me durifg
the day and she's peachy.
But I come home and she's blue.
- To the holidays.
- Cin cin.
So, Walt, o you think
about extending
our credit by $50,000?
I didn't know we were going
to talk real business.
Should I slow down?
( Chuckles )
Well, ahem,
the projections suggest--
No projections.
We're only interested in commitments.
Yes, well,
the commitments are firm,
but no one's been paying
their bills on time.
Hmm, I got it.
Done.
Are you going away?
No. I love Christmas
in Manhattan.
Can you take care of it today?
I'd like to start writing
checks immediately.
Sure.
We're heading to Florida.
I want to fly, but I think
we're going to drive.
- Roger, Cooper's office.
- Coming.
What's the hurry, Harry?
Are you drunk?
- Pearl Harbor day. Show some respect.
- ( Toilet flushes )
How are you doing
with your bombing?
Remember Lane's fool
at Jaguar, Edwin Baker?
- You mean Bazooka Joe?
- ( All laugh )
Three weeks ago, he was
replaced by Hugh Hibbert,
and we are back in the running.
- He called you?
- No, I called him.
In fact, I've been working
a few prospects over there
for months, waiting for
Edwin to self-destruct,
and he did...
Spectacularly, apparently.
He vomited in the lap of the
head of the dealers association.
( All laugh )
Who else?
Well, it sounds like foote,
cone, Ted Bates, d'arcy.
Everyone who doesn't
have a car.
- What is that, nine of us?
- No, it's five.
And size-wise,
we're the smallest,
so let's all start boning up
on the wonders of Jaguar.
We have a meet
and greet next week
and the presentations
are sometime in mid-January.
( Sighs ) That's a lot of work.
Yes. You may have
to stay past 5:30.
I'd live here if I thought it
was more than a pipe dream.
( Bell rings )
Paul: We reject the
material world
in favor of the recognition
of one's true identity.
I don't understand
what you're saying.
Paul?
Harry crane, as I live
and breathe.
What the hell happened to you?
- Krishna consciousness.
- ( Bell rings )
- Hare krishna, Paramatma.
- Hare krishna, Bhakta Stewart.
( Laughs ) Don't pretend
this isn't strange.
That's why I wanted
you to see it.
Well, consider it seen.
I really should be going.
Harry, I've been trying
to get yo down here.
Remember how anxious,
how insecure,
how terrified I was
of living life?
It's gone.
Can you imagine living
that way, Harry?
I'm sorry, this is
giving me the willies.
Please, keep an open mind.
Can we do this
for a few minutes?
Am I allowed to be here?
- Everyone's allowed to be here.
- Hello there.
Harry, this is Mother Lakshmi.
Hare krishna, Harry.
- Oh, I get it.
- Get what?
( Soft chatter )
( Group chanting )
( Sitar playing )
- I should go.
- No.
Chant with us.
You'll like it.
I promise.
♪ Hare krishna ♪
♪ hare krishna ♪
♪ krishna ♪
♪ hare hare ♪
♪ hare rama... ♪
( Whispers ) Hare rama,
rama rama, hare hare.
- ♪ Hare hare... ♪
- Hare krishna.
♪ Hare krishna ♪
♪ hare krishna... ♪
- Krishna krishna.
- ♪ Krishna krishna... ♪
- Hare hare.
- ♪ Hare hare... ♪
- Hare rama.
- ♪ Hare rama... ♪
Roger's not coming.
He's on battleship row.
But I've already told him.
I called this meeting.
Where's Joan?
It's best Joan's not heard
for my announcement.
I don't know about yours.
Go ahead.
Very well.
A recent pass of the books
shows that we have
a surplus of $50,000,
r and I believe that enables us
to distribute
Christmas bonuses.
Equal shares to full partners,
half shares to juniors,
2% gifts to SNC and 4% ENC.
God bless us, everyone.
And I shall see to it that the
checks are distributed immediately.
Actually, let's wait
till the Christmas party.
Someone's not gointo be happy,
and I'd rather not stare
at her for a month.
( Laughs ) Approved.
- Don-- - I have to announce that
we're in the running--
I mean absolutely
this time-- For Jaguar.
So it's time we all
get some learning
on this fine automobile.
I intend to drive
the mark ii this afternoon.
Don, don't you think
the bonuses would make
more of an impact now, hmm?
There's nothing like
a surprise for morale.
Not my morale.
The Jaguar announcement
should be good for morale.
And, as much as
it affects me personally,
I think we should sit tight
on the bonuses.
Jaguar will provide
only a little seed
- and we'll have to supplement.
- Damn it!
We can afford to do both.
- What ghost visited you, Ebenezer?
- Don: Pete.
You asked me to stop
this last time.
Yes, well, other than Roger,
who started drinking
at exactly 7:55 this morning,
no one has given me
the reaction I desire
from this blessed event.
Bert.
They're lemons.
They never start.
Meeting adjourned.
You like my shirt?
It's very festive.
You know it's sacrilege
to say this,
but pearl harbor
was an act of genius.
The only thing they didn't
plan for was success.
The japs won and they didn't
know what to do with it.
Mr. Sterling,
seeing as you're
dressed for fishing,
you'll have more success
if you're quiet.
Don't be like that.
I couldn't care less.
Ahi I know why you're mad.
But Jane's not going
to take everything.
It never oururretotoe.
- Have I asked?
- No.
And you shouldn't
have to and you don't
and you keep sending it back.
Because it's
a short-term solution.
- I told you, I'll cover Kevin
through college. - No.
It's better this way for him.
And if you're not careful,
you won't even be
a family friend.
- Joanie, I had an experience.
- I know, Roger.
Well, it's not about honor.
It's about the fact that
we created a human life.
We made a baby.
Yes.
And now it's some other
lucky girl's turn.
Scarlett.
Hello.
♪ Hare krishna, hare krishna ♪
♪ krishna krishna, hare hare ♪
♪ hare rama, hare rama ♪
♪ rama rama,
hare hare. ♪
- ( Group stops )
- ♪ Hare krishna, krish-- ♪
All of us have
a very close connection.
Krishna...
My head is humming.
And your mind is clear.
Yeah.
I should be getting back.
Holy shit, how long
have I been here?
- Are you hungry?
- I am.
Paramatma, take him
for some food.
Yes, mother lakshmi.
A beautiful idea.
- Harry, will you eat with me?
- Just the two of us?
- Hare krishna.
Guru:
But when we are
in the material,
conditional life,
we forget this, hmm?
( Car horns honking )
It is so good to see you.
It's good to see you, too.
But I'm not gonna join.
I don't want you
but I can tell
you really got into that.
I can tell you really
got into Lakshmi.
I love her deeply, Harry.
Absolutely.
She's my kind of religion.
It's not like that.
Lakshmi lived most of her
life as a girl named Janet
whose promiscuity led
to drugs and prostitution.
The movement saved her life.
So what's your excuse?
I was at rock bottom.
I had really degraded myself.
- At mccann?
- No, damn
listen, I love what the
movement has given me,
but I don't understand why I have
to live like that to love God.
Are they making you stay?
It's just Lakshmi.
- So you don't wanna share, huh?
- You don't understand.
I want to make a life
with her, but not there.
So what does that
have to do with me?
She was a runaway,
and she won't leave
unless she knows she won't
wind up back on the streets.
You want money.
( Scoffs )
You know go eat by yourself.
Stop, stop.
Money solves today,
not tomorrow.
- Up here on the right.
- ( Brakes squeak )
And for your information,
Prabhupad is buying.
I'm sorry I said
I couldn't come
because of the accident.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Man: "Can you help me,
doctor?" I asked him.
"Well, it started--
Well, it started," I said,
"when I was sitting in front
of the television set
with my feet
on the coffee table.
Now, I've sat there
hundreds of times,
thousands maybe, with a
can of beer in my hand.
I like to have
a can of beer in my hand
when I watch the beer ads.
But now, for no reason
I could think of,
the ad was making me sick.
So I used the remote control
to get to another channel,
but each channel
made me just as sick.
The television was one thing,
and I was a person,
and I was going to be sick.
So I turned it off
and had a panicky moment.
I smelled the beer in my hand.
And as I vomited, I looked
around the living room
for something
to grab onto."
- Do you want something to eat?
- Nope.
Well, I didn't have dinner.
- You want a drink?
- Yep.
"Yep. Nope."
Should have been
our wedding vows.
I'm just tired.
No, you're not.
I don't understand.
I've heard you say a lot worse
things about advertising.
The mighty theater punches
its audience in the face
with its subtle message--
There's a challenge.
Let me tell you,
people buy things
because it makes them
feel better.
Well, we could have had
dinner with Charles.
He's an understudy.
That may be his only performance.
I mind picking up
the check for your friends,
- but not if they insult me first.
- I'm sorry.
People make fun of acting
all the time and you love it.
And I didn't think it was such a
strong stand against advertising
as much as the emptiness
of consumerism.
Well, no one's made
a stronger stand
against advertisinthan you.
( Instrumental music playing )
You know, I was scared
when bea was born,
but she's such a joy.
I actually saw her face float
by while I was chanting.
Really?
You had a vision?
I guess.
And you kind of think you're
tied to this person forever.
Noittle girl.
You know, Jennifer.
And now with another one
on the way...
I want a finfly with Lakshmi.
And a farm,
maybe outside Frisco.
You're gonna have to do
a little less recruiting
and a little more working.
About that...
I don't have a job for Paul.
I've thought about that.
It's the whole reason
I didn't wanna see you.
But you can help me
because I have been working.
You've been writing?
I think this is the most meaningful
work I've ever done in my life.
It's a speculative episode
of the hit television show Star Trek.
- Are you kidding me? - I think it should
be their season opener next year.
If there is one.
It's a tough time slot--
"My Three Sons," "Bewitched."
- At thing's a juggernaut.
- It'll be there.
Where the hell do you watcd it?
Through the window of a
Pizza Parlor on MacDougal.
- What, do you lip-read?
- I've seen the show,
and I think I've made a good effort
at matching the moral complexities
tinged with adventure
that draw people to it.
Just read the first 15 pages.
If you don't think it's good
enough for network television,
then you don't have to pass it
along to the executives at NBC
or even think about trying
to get it to Mr. Roddenberry.
That's kind of a line
you don't cross, Paul.
Who do you think
you're talking to?
How much do you buy at nbc?
You don't have any leverage?
Okay.
- Is it about hare krishna?
- No.
Well, not literally, but they
don't tell literal stories.
Look, you had a vision
your first time.
Not that I wasn't in a state of
bliss for the first few months,
but something happened.
I try to clear my head,
but I can't.
It's too busy in there.
Everybody else looks so happy.
You know, I got there and I
started trying to figure out
who prabhupad likes best.
It's the same
as everywhere I go.
He doesn't like me.
No one likes me.
Sometimes I think krishna
doesn't even like me.
No one but Lakshmi.
Will you read the script?
( Sighs )
Can I ask you something?
Why didn't you bring in
Paul Kinsey when you*?
He wasn't submitted.
- You didn't consider him?
- Was I supposed to?
As far as I know,
he was at McCann,
and then Y&R, then he rolled
downhill through K&E and B&B.
And last thing I heard,
he was in-house at AMP.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
The AMP.
Will you read a script
he wrote for "Star Trek"?
Harry, if he asked you
to pass it along,
I don't think
this is what he meant.
I know what he meant,
but I need a second opinion.
Is it going to give me a case
of the "Nee-groan Complex"?
It's really bad.
And it's pronounced "neh-grahn"
because it rhymes with katahn,
which the negron pick under
slavery to the caucasons.
That's a twist.
- No, the twist is that the negron are white.
- ( Laughs )
Great. Now I'm not
gonna get anything done.
He really hopes
this will change his life.
What am I gonna do?
You really wanna
help him, don't you?
So what?
Really, do you know how lucky we a
well, if you really wanna
help, be honest with him
and tell him he needs
to write a better script.
I think it was
really hard for him.
Then he shouldn't be doing it.
- ( Intercom buzzes )
- Mr. Campbell to see you.
Send him in.
So what's your favorite Jaguar?
Did you send over a packet?
No, I drove them.
Well, someone drove me.
I don't know how to
operate a stick shift.
I'll go this afternoon.
See that you do, because your
opinion means a lot more than mine.
Take Megan.
See how they deal with a couple.
We'll see.
You know, if I told you last December
that we'd be in the running for a car,
you would have
kissed me on the mouth.
Maybe you and I should
go as a couple.
Man:
Well, that is good to hear.
Pity having to deplete
the resources this time of year,
but it had to be done.
I've been assured the funds
should be accessible immly.
Very well.
There is the matter of my fee.
Yes, of course.
After the holidays?
Good day.
( Sighs )
Joan, you have
a guest in reception.
He needs a signature.
Are you Joan Harris?
Yes, that's me.
- You're served.
- What?
Damn it.
Why did you let him in?
- He said he needed to talk to you.
- About what?
I don't remember
everything everybody says.
Because you're an idiot!
Don't talk to me like that.
Do you understand
having you out here
is the same as having no one?
He said he knew you.
He said it was a surprise.
A surprise?
Well, thank you for that.
Here's a surprise!
- Joan!
- Surprise!
There's an airplane
here to see you!
You're not allowed to do that.
- Come on.
- Stop it.
- What's going on?
- Nothing.
- Come with me.
- I'm fine.
Oh, don.
Come on, let's go.
It's too early for lunch.
- Not going to lunch.
- I don't even have my coat.
( Elevator dings )
Look at your watch.
Man:
Well, hello.
What brings you in today?
We got tired
of waiting for a cab.
Thought we'd buy a car.
Well, let's see if I can
get out of your way.
What's this one?
It's the mark ii.
It's roomy, quiet,
good for a night on the town,
but can also
accommodate children.
Do you have any?
Altogether, four.
This is a car
for the American road.
It's too much power
for England.
They don't have the space.
Yeah, plus I hear the dampness is
murder on the electrical system.
We've worked that out.
Oh, honey.
What's that?
That's the most beautiful
car ever made,
the XK-E,
or the E-type.
I want one.
I'm thinking about paying to
have you drive around in this.
Go get me the keys.
I'll drive her around for free.
I'll have to take
you out one at a time.
There's no room for three.
Why would we want you along?
She really wants me
to take it for a ride.
I can't.
She can drive it herself.
So you're going
to ride with her?
Can I?
How much is the car?
That one?
$5,600.
Here's $6,000.
If we don't come back,
consider it paid for.
I don't know what it is.
That car does nothing for me.
It's because you're happy.
You don't need it.
Okay.
You do not know how hard I've
tried to ignore this at work.
I know what I'm doing,
I have some control,
but then he found a way
to ruin that, too.
You're gonna need to define
some of these pronouns
want me to keep listening.
Dr. captain Harris served me
with papers in the office.
He's divorcing me.
Like he has
the moral high ground.
It's hard on a marriage
when you're apart.
Really? He loves it.
I'm sorry about that girl,
but, you know...
It used to be if someone
needed to see me in reception,
they were delivering flowers.
Those flowers...
God, my first week here I thought
you were dating Ali Khan.
My mother raised me
to be admired.
But no flowers from you.
You scared the shit out of me.
Burt Peterson told me
you were the one person
in the agency
I shouldn'cross.T
he and Freddy had
a standing argument
that you were a lesbian.
You think they never
brought that up with me?
Well, congratulations.
For what?
For getting divorced.
Nobody realizes how bad it has
to get for that to happen.
Now you get to move on.
To what?
To start over?
On what date
do you share that news?
Right after you go all the way.
You'll find somebody better.
You did, didn't you?
You found someone perfect.
I did.
I feel like
the office misses her.
Maybe I should have
kept her at reception.
( Both laugh )
Give me some change.
I want music.
( Phone rings )
Hello?
There's a lakshmi
here to see you.
She's got a whole story.
Uh... bring her back.
Scarlett, please hold
all my calls.
Ah.
A pleasure to see you.
I hope you understand.
Jennifer wants to be very
thorough in search for a nanny.
Thank you, Meredith.
If this is some kind of shakedown,
let me stop you right now.
I know you're trying
to recruit me.
Can I have a drink?
Isn't that verboten?
Listen to me.
I don't know what it is,
but when you were chanting,
I felt this...
Intensity, you know?
Everywhere on my body...
Especially one place.
Really?
I was in such a state.
Stop it. I thought
you were with Paul.
Nobody's with anybody.
Paramatma does what
he wants and so do I.
It doesn't mean that
we don't love each other.
So there's no reason
for you to say no.
What about the fact
that I'm married?
I'm burning for you.
Does your wife burn for you?
So this is completely allowed?
Take me like this.
( Slow music playing )
Not even a little Sinatra?
Jimmy Durante.
( Laughs )
Look at all these people
dancing to my music.
You wanna dance?
I don't think we should.
You sure look like
you wanna dance.
You and me in midtown?
You with that look
on your face?
What look, baby?
God, you're irresistible.
You know what this woman
said to me once?
I like being bad
and going home and being good.
I bet that stuck to your ribs.
It was a disaster.
And joyed every minute of it.
( Both laugh )
God, I miss that.
Well, there's a gentleman
over at 7:30
who looks like
he wants to dance.
Who do you think he is?
Advertising?
Insurance? Lawyer?
And who do you think's
waiting at home?
I bet she's not ugly.
The only sin she's committed
is being familiar.
So you think it's all him?
Because she can't
giveve him what he wants.
Because he doesn't
know what he wants,
what he's wanting.
He knows.
It's just the way he is.
And maybe it's just
the way she is.
I'm gonna go.
I can still dr I think.
I can drive.
You can stay.
I've been sitting with you
since he walked in.
Poor me, I struck out.
Who's gonna believe that?
Carfare,
in case it doesn't work out.
Mad money.
Thank you.
Good night, sweetheart.
Stand over by the jukebox.
That looked pretty good before.
( Engine roaring )
Are you okay?
I don't know. I--
My heart's beating
like a rabbit.
Smoking's not gonna help.
Don't get all strict on me,
Mother Lakshmi.
But I am strict.
I did this for the movement.
Good to know,
but I ain't joining.
Although your techniques
are more persuasive
than Parma-- Paul's.
You're disgusting.
I'm only here because I don't
want you shaking his devotion.
What?
How does that work?
You're the worst
girlfriend in the world.
And you're the best friend.
That's why you're giving him false
hope for his awful teleplay.
He wants to have
a life with you.
And you know that, even if that
was possible, that's not the way.
Well, he doesn't know that.
So why don't you
just let him go?
Because he's a devotee of the lord.
You're just a ***.
You wanna make him
into a gross materialist
when he's living
in the spiritual world.
And also he's
our best recruiter.
I mean, he really can close.
So I'm confused. Why did *?
Because you're going
to stay away from him
and let him be happy in the
light of krishna consciousness.
You thought I was
some confused little girl?
I'm tr the only thing I have.
But you already gave it away.
Ow!
Stay away from him.
What do I do about the script?
Tell him the truth.
That always works.
( Door opens )
- ( Door closes )
- ( Keys jangling )
You're drunk.
And you left work at lunch.
Where the hell were you?
You wanna get the rolling pin?
- What the hell?
- I wanna know where you were.
I left work,
I test-drove a Jaguar,
had a drink with Joan, drove around
some more and dropped it off.
And you never
thought to call me?
Why did you want me
to think that?
Calm the hell down.
I put a plate
in the oven for you
and sat here like an idiot,
waiting for someone
who doesn't give a shit
about anybody.
- You like to get mad.
- No, I don't.
- That's what gets you going.
- That is not what this is.
Now sit down!
You're gonna eat
dinner with me.
( Oven door rs )
Do you want any cheese?
- No. Do you want--
- I'll clean it up later.
You used to love your work.
Well, it's different there now.
You loved it
before you ever met me.
Rebecca: My mother
is not a good nurse
and he hides his symptoms.
He's a rugged chap.
I do think more than ever we should
pay them a visit at Christmas.
Or I could just take Nigel.
Certainly we can afford t
I shouldn't be sharing this,
but I truly don't
want you to go.
You see, Edwin's left Jaguar.
Oh, that's why
she left in a hurry.
If he had been sacked,
he'd have lost his visa.
Yes, well, it allowed Jaguar
to come crawling back to me.
The firm can't do it without me
and I shan't spend
another Christmas alone.
Oh!
Oh, darling.
I'm so happy for you, so proud.
Of course we'll be here
by your side.
Christmas in New York
will do just fine.
Don't get excited.
Well, get excited,
but they're not from me.
Thank you for delivering them.
I had to. The girl in reception's
too scared to bring them back.
I also had to sign
for them and tip handsomely.
Do you want a tip, too?
How many times have I left you alone
with a card from another man?
Hare krishna.
Great to see you.
Well, I've been meditating on the
idea that you have good news,
especially since
you called me so fast.
Then I realized
it's probably not,
since you wouldn't
tell me over the phone.
I have news,
but it's complicated.
They loved it.
They said it was one of the best
scripts they had ever read.
- Who? - Uh, the reader at
Mike Weinblatt's office.
But he apparently
can't give it to Mike
or anyone over there
because of legal reasons.
And you can never call him because
they've had some lawsuits,
but he said you have a
future and I agree with him.
Did you tell him
I'll get a lawyer?
I'll sign anything they want.
Yes, but he was firmly
diging in every way
except in his unbridled
enthusiasm for the writing.
Really?
What did he say?
- Can I talk to him? Does he
want to talk to me? - Never.
But...
S envelope is your future.
This is your destiny.
- Is it a contract?
- They're not interested...
But I am.
This is $5 a ticket
to Los Angeles.
I want you to leave the krishnas
and go out there and try.
I don't think Lakshmi--
I'm not giving you this
unless you promise
to leave your things
and go from here.
I don't have any things.
Good.
This is all you need.
You don't understand
what it's like out there.
This failure, this life--
It'll all seem like
it happened to someone else.
Harry, you don't
understand lakshmi.
If you go back there, you'll
never be strong enough to go.
And then she'll try
and talk you out of it.
And what does that tell you?
It's $500.
You can call her on the way
from Philly or something.
You know, all these people said
they'd do something for me.
You're the first one
who did anything.
Break a leg.
Everyone's assembling
for the announcement.
Well, there's a little bad
news to go with the good.
Mohawk's machinists
are going on strike.
Despite the fact
that they're flying,
they're suspending
their advertising.
They made so much money
all summer as scabs.
- What's going on?
- Mohawk's on strike.
They're suspending all work.
They're not leaving the agency,
but what they save
by cutting the ad budget
goes straight to the bottom line,
and it's the end of the year.
Well, then there'll be no bonu
no!
No Christmas bonuses
three years in a row?
I know.
They're going to be working all
through the holidays on Jaguar.
Bert: Fine.
Just the partners will defer.
Even the junior partners?
Yes, till the end of January.
That's prudent.
Well, here we go.
Don, you up to joining us?
( Chatter )
( Chatter stops )
Lane, go ahead.
Well, we have
a few announcements,
the first of which is that
we have received
some bad news
from mohawk airlines
that they will be suspending
their work indefinitely.
( Murmuring )
This puts significant financial
strain on the company.
( Sighs )
It was our plan to distribute
Christmas bonuses
this year, but... ahem,
quite selflesslythe partnerd
to forego their share
in the interests
of rewarding the staff
for a job well done.
You're all getting Christmas
bonuses and we aren't.
Now, understand that the
financial straddling required
is for a very good reason.
We've been included
in an elite group of agencies
invited to pitch Jaguar cars.
So congratulations.
Anything else?
Yes, actually, I'd like
to say something.
Would you?
St year at this time,
whether you knew it or not,
I look at the faces
in this room
who have given their all
to this tenuous recovery
and I say...
Prepare to take
a great leap forward.
Prepare to swim
the English channel
and then drown in champagne.
There are six weekends
between now and the pitch.
We are going to
spend them all here.
We will cee Christmas here.
We will ring in
the new year together.
And in the end,
we will represent Jaguar
and it will be worth it.
Every agency on Madison Avenue
is defined by the moment
they got their car.
When we land Jaguar,
the world wiw we've arrived.
( Applause )
Creative, in my office.
( Chatter )
♪ frosted windowpanes ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ painted candy canes ♪
♪ on the tree ♪
♪ merry christmas ♪
♪ may your new year dreams ♪
♪ come true ♪
♪ and this song of mine ♪
♪ in three-quarter time ♪
♪ wishes you and yours ♪
♪ the same thing, too. ♪
www.tvsubtitles.net