Very nearly there, sir.
I have to say your face is familiar.
Have I drawn you before?
- Occasionally. - Of course, I've seen
you in the English newspapers.
- Are you a reporter?
- I'm a journalist.
Be patient, Snowy.
Not much longer.
Oh! I do beg your pardon.
There. I do believe I've captured
something of your likeness.
Not bad.
What do you think, Snowy?
Oh, Snowy ...
There you are Sir..
Now where's he run off to?
- Anything?
- Nothing.
Snowy!
Where have you been?
Chasing cats again?
Snowy. Look at This.
Triple Masted, double
decks and 50 guns.
- Isn't she a beauty?
- That's a very unique specimen that is
from an old
sea captain's estate.
- The Unicorn.
- The Unicorn, man-o-war sailing ship
- It's very old that is 16th century.
- 17th, I would think.
- Reign of Charles the first.
- Charles the second.
That's what I said,Charles the 2nd. as finer ship as
ever sailed the seven seas.
you won't find another one of these mate!
and it's only 2 quid.
- I'll give you a pound.
- Done.
Carefully does it.
There you go. Careful.
- Hey, buddy. How much for the boat?
- I'm sorry, I just sold it to this young gent
Oh, yeah? Tell me what you paid?
I'll give you double.
- Double?
- Thanks, but it is not for sale.
Look, kid. I'm trying
to help you out.
I don't think you realize this,
but you are about to walk
- into a whole mess of danger.
- What kind of danger?
I'm warning you. Get rid of the boat
and get out while you still can.
These people do not play nice.
- What people ?...
- Wonderful!!.
It's just wonderful.
Don't bother wrapping it, I'll take it as is.
Does anybody object if I pay by cheque?
If you want to buy it,
you'll have to talk to the kid.
I see! ... well...
- ..let the 'kid' name his price.
- Name his price? Oh ...
Ten years I've been flogging briq-a-brac and I miss
"name your price" by one blinking minute.
I'm sorry, but I've already explained
to the other gentleman...
American he was.
All hair oil and no socks.
It is not for sale.
Then let me appeal
to your better nature.
I've recently acquired Marlinspike
Hall and this ship, as you know,
- Was once part of the estate ...
- Of the late sea captain.
The family fell upon hard-times.
They lost everything.
They have been living in a
cloud of bad luck ever since
We are talking generations of
drinking and irrational behavior of ...
I'm sorry, but as I told you before...
it is not for sale.
Good day to you Sir.
That young man,
What's his name?
Him! Everybody knows him.
That's Tintin.
What is it about this ship?
Why it has attracted
so much attention?
What secrets do you hold?
Where is that magnifying glass?
I could have sworn,
that it was somewhere.
Snowy, you haven't seen the errr ...
Where is it?
Thank you.
No, Snowy!
Look, what you did!
You broke it. Bad dog.
Something happened on this ship.
We're going to the one place
that could have the answer.
Come on Snowy.
Here it is. Sir Francis
Haddock of Marlinspike Hall
The last captain of
the ill-fated unicorn.
Ship set sail from
Barbados in 1676...
...on one of the most ruinest
voyages in maritime history.
The ship never reached its
destination. attacked by Pirates.
All hands lost except
for one survivor.
When Sir Francis was
rescued and returned home -
He was convinced his
name had been cursed.
The Unicorn's manifest stated they
we're carrying a cargo...
...of rum and tobacco
bound for Europe, but...
...it was long claimed "the ship was
carrying a secret cargo."
What was the ship carrying, Snowy?
"Historians have tried and failed...
...to discover what happened
on that fatal voyage."
But, Sir Francis's last words:
"Only a true Haddock will discover
The Secret of the Unicorn."
Missed something Snowy.
I need to take a closer
look at that model.
Of course, it's gone!
How can I be so stupid?
MARLINSPIKE HALL
How did you do that?
Clever boy.
That Coat of Arms.
Why does it look familiar?
Hang on.
That fish is a haddock.
Of course! Marlinspike Hall is
the old Haddock estate.
Snowy!
Well done Snowy. Good boy.
Well well well.
It seems we caught our thief.
Welcome to Marlinspike Hall.
- I see you let yourself in.
- I came to retrieve my property.
- I'm sorry I'm not sure I follow you
- Oh I think you do.
This ship was stolen from my
apartment less than an hour ago.
I'm afraid you are mistaken,
Mr. Tintin.
- There is no mistake.
It belongs to me. - Are you sure?
Of course I am sure. I took it home.
I put it on the cabinet
in the living room
and then Snowy chased the
cat and knocked it over ...
It fell.
- This isn't my ship.
- No. Indeed.
- Sorry. It looks identical.
- Looks can be deceiving
Yes indeed. But I don't understand.
Why did Sir Francis make two
ships exactly alike?
And you have one already.
Why did you want another?
What is it about this model that will
cause someone to steal it?
Goodness me! Why so many questions?
It is my job. There could be a story here.
- That's what I do you see.
- It's no great mystery.
Sir Francis Haddock was a
drunkard and a hopeless reprobate
He was doomed to fail and he be
bequeathed that failure to his sons.
So it is true.
Haddock line is cursed.
- What else have you found out?
- What is there to find?
-That depends what you are looking for.
- I'm looking for answers -
- Mr. Sakharine.
- You're looking in the wrong place.
It is late.
I think you should go home.
This way, sir.
- It's a pity, sir.
- I'm sorry?
That the mast broke on
your model ship, sir.
I hope you found all the pieces.
- Things are so easily lost.
- Nestor, where are you?
Good night, sir.
"Some things are easily lost."
What did he mean by that Snowy?
What was he trying to tell me?
"Some things are easily lost."
Snowy.
Great snakes!
What is it Snowy?
What's this?
Aha! this was in the mast.
Good boy, Snowy.
Three brothers joined to three
Unicorn in company.
Sailing in the noonday sun will speak.
For it's from the light.
That light will dawn and then
shines forth the eagle's cross.
What are these markings?
It's kind of a secret language
...or code. Makes no sense!
But it does explain why
they ransacked the flat.
They were looking for this
and they didn't find it.
which means...
...they will be back.
I have to go back to my cocoa.
I have got a very good
book and a cup of cocoa.
- It's really lovely.
- Thank you, Mrs. Finch.
I can look after this.
Hey kid, is that you?
open the door.
- What do you want?
- Look, the game is up.
He's going to be back. Now I know he
wanted those boats, but I swear to God...
I never thought he'd
kill anyone over it. - Who?
- Who you are talking about? - I'm trying
to tell you, that your life is in danger.
Answer me! WHO?
Mrs.. Finch! A man has been
shot on our doorstep!
- Now indeed?
- Call an ambulance!
Whoa, Snowy!
Can you hear me?
Can you?
The victim's name was Barnaby Dawes.
He was one of the top
agents at Interpol.
But we haven't got a clue,
what he was working on.
Quite right Thomson.
We're completely clueless.
Interpol doesn't have any other leads?
Steady on Tintin, we are still filling out the
paperwork.
Police work is not all glamour and guns.
There's an awful lot of filing.
Well I might have something for you.
Before he lost consciousness, Dawes tried to tell me something.
...and I think he was spelling out a word.
B, O, U...
D, J, A, N
- "Karaboudjan."
- Karaboudjan!
- Does that mean anything to you? -
- Great Scotland Yard!
- Its extraordinary.
- What is?
Werthingtons have a half price sale
on bowler hats!!
Really Thompson?
It is hardly the time!
- What is it? canes are half price too.
- Do you take charge of this evidence?
Never fear, Tintin.
The evidence is safe with us.
- I'm going down!
- Please hurry?
Well! I am already downstairs.
Do try keep up.
Wait! You dropped this.
Look after the evidence.
Sorry, Thompson.
My mind is on other things.
Oh, yes. Like our light fingered larcenist.
- What? - The pickpocket.
He has no idea what is coming.
Come-on Tintin, take my wallet.
Yes. Industrial strength elastic.
- Very resourceful.
- On the contrary.
- It was childishly simple.
- Simply childish, I agree.
- Tintin.
- Gentlemen.
Mind you, I expect he's
miles away by now.
I presume, you are referring
to the Pickpocket.
We were just a few
steps behind him.
Snowy, what is it boy?
What do you see?
- I don't suppose you fancy a cup of tea.
- You are quite mistaken.
- I got you now!
- Stop!
I got you!
What going on down there?
Come on, Snowy.
- Beg your pardon.
- I am sorry, sir.
Pickpocket
Tintin, he is getting away!
My wallet, it's gone.
Come on, Snowy! After him!
Stop! Wait!
Gotcha! Steady on
I've lost him.
You must find my wallet.
- It's very important, I have to
get it back. - And you will.
Leave it to the Professionals.
We lost the scroll
but we haven't lost the story.
Karaboudjan. It's an Armenian word.
That's our lead Snowy. What Barnaby
Dawes trying to tell us?
- Mr. Tin....tin.
- Yes?
- Delivery for you.
- But I didn't order anything.
Well that's because it's you...for delivery
Get off me!
Shake him off from the bumper!
- He's not here, look your side.
- Hang on, nothing.
- Well, check that pocket.
- I've looked that one already, I'm sure
of it. - Have a look at his socks?
- Have you found it?
- Doesn't have it.
- It's not here, boss.
- Not here! Then where is it?
- Where is what?
- I'm tired of your games.
The scroll from the Unicorn.
A piece of paper, like this.
- Do you mean the poem?
- Yes.
- The poem written in old English?
- Was inside the cylinder.
- Yes.
- Concealed in the mast.
I don't have it.
You don't value that scroll.
Why else would you take it?
I'm confused. Two scrolls,
but the part of a puzzle.
You have one, but you need
the other. That's not it.
It is something else.
I'll find it.
With or without your help.
You need to think about, exactly
how useful you are to me.
- Deal with him on the way.
- Ok.
Hold this course.
Snowy!
It's good to see you, too.
See if you can chew through these ropes.
He's lying. He must have the scroll.
- The question is, what has
he done with it? -
I want you to go back down there
and make him talk.
- Break every bone in his body,
if you have to. - Oh, that's nasty.
You know the stakes. You know
what we're playing for. Just do it.
Mr. Sakharine!
All hell has broken loose!
- It's a disaster, the captain
has come around. - What?
He is conscious.
He is accusing you of mutiny.
He says you've turned the
crew against him.
- Silly fool he's sobered up again.
- Well don't just stand there.
- Get him another bottle.
- Right sir.
- Take to the left. It is just stuck.
- Take a look.
What are you doing?
Get the hell off.
It's not stuck, you idiot.
He's bunged it from the inside.
Do you want to play
like that then, Tintin?
Get the TNT.
Broken crates, broken,
champagne.
What else do we have Snowy?
There are other ways to open this door.
They'll be swabbing the decks with your innards
when we done with you.
Give it here!
- Don't move.
- What!
Let's go.
He's got a big machine gun -- I've been shot !!!!
Hold your fire.
He aint here - he's vanished.
He's hiding. Search the ship.
Quickly.
Ahh a giant rat through the scuttle
So you thought you'd sneak in behind me and catch
me with my trousers down uhh!!!
I'd rather you kept your trousers on,
If it's all the same to you
- I know your game. You're one of those ---
- Sorry?
- They sent you here to kill me.
- I don't know who you are!
That's how he has planned
to bump me off.
Murdered in my bed by a baby face assassin.
Assassin! You got it all wrong.
I was kidnapped.
By gang of thugs.
Oh the filthy swine
- He has turned all the crew
against me! - Who?
Sour faced man with the sugary name.
He's bought them all off. Every one.
Sakharine!
Nobody takes my ship.
- You're the captain? - Course I'm
the captain who else can I be?
I've been locked in
this room for days.
With only whiskey to
sustain my mortal soul.
- I assumed that was locked.
- Well, it is not.
Now you must excuse me. If they find
me here they will kill me.
I've to keep moving. Try and find my way
out of this drunken tub.
Tub?
Tub.
TUB!
Thanks. Hold him.
- I'm Tintin by the way.
- Haddock. Archibald Haddock.
-There's a long boat on deck. Follow me .
- Wait a second, did you say Haddock?
How could you let them escape?
Find them. Find them both.
- Don't worry, we will kill them, sir.
- No,
...you can kill the boy,
not Haddock.
He is just a hopeless old drunk, we
should've killed him long ago.
You think it is an accident
that I chose Haddock's ship
...Haddock's crew, Haddock's
treacherous first mate...
Nothing is an accident.
We go back a long way,
Captain Haddock, and I.
We have unfinished business.
And this time I'm going
to make him pay.
We have to reach the locked
door at the end of this corridor.
This is gonna be tricky.
you wouldn't happen to be related to
Haddock's Marlinspike Hall. Would you?
- Why do you ask? - That's the
story I've been working on.
You know the shipwrech which happened off the
coast of Barbados.
A man-o-war triple-masted, 50 Guns.
- What do you know of the Unicorn?
- not a lot, that's why I am asking you.
The secret of that ship belongs to my family.
It has been passed out from
generation to generation.
My Grandfdaddy himself with his
dying breath told me that they all...
- And ...
- Gone.
What do you mean "gone"?
I was so upset that he kicked the
bucket, I've no choice but to drown my sorrows
When I woke up in the morning
it was gone. I had forgotten all.
- Everything?
- Every last word.
But is there somebody else in your family
May be they would help.
Sir Francis had three sons.
All but my bloodline failed
I am the last of the Haddocks.
Did you say three sons?
What was that?
No, there is nothing here.
- I know what Sakharine is looking for.
- What you reeling on about?
It was written on the scroll.
Three brothers joined three
Unicorns in company...
...sailing in the noonday
sun will speak.
- Really? - Sir Francis did not
make two models of the unicorn
He made three.
Three ships for three sons.
Excellent.
Sakharine is after the
third model of the ship.
- Barnacles, someone has locked
the door. - Is there a key?
A key ?
Yes, that'll be a problem.
Mr. Jaggerman. Top bunk in the
center. Keeper of the keys.
Careful mate, he is a restless sleeper .
On account of the tragic loss of his eyelids!
He lost his eyelids?
Aye that was a card game to remember
Oh you really had to be there!
Would do it myself, but you are a lighter
and less chance of waking the boy
- I'm not sure this is a Good idea?
- You have nothing to worry about...
...provided they all stay asleep.
I would not get too close to Mr. Hobbsin.
He is very handy with a razor.
And steer clear of Mr. Kitzist.
Sacked from a ship on account
of his animal husbandry.
Not the sandwich. The Keys!
You are the brave one, Tintin.
My heart was in my mouth,
don't mind telling you.
That is if was my heart, judging by my
stomach ache could have been anything
Hurry up, Captain,
we have no time to lose.
Ohhho! Just the necessities of course.
The life boat.
Nothing yet, watch it sir.
The boss says he is a handful.
Come on.
- It is Allan.
- Is that  the bridge?
Aye. On the other side
of the radio room.
Radio room? Wait here, Captain.
Sound the alarm if anyone Comes.
Be Careful, Tintin.
- This message has just come through boss.
- What's it say?
"The Milanese Nightingale has Landed,
waiting in the wings for action"
- Milanese Nightingale..
- just pray this cheers him up
Bagghar.
What is this?
The Sultanate of Bagghar
Ruled over by Sheikh
Omar Ben Salaad.
His love of music and culture
is matched only by his love of...
GREAT SNAKES!
Bagghar.
The port of Bagghar.
In Morocco.
Tintin!
Hey! Put your hands up.
And let that be a lesson to ya
Help me !
Here! Here!
Here! by the lifeboats
After him.
- Over there!
- Boy you ...
He's up there.
- Turn this ship!
- Aye Sir.
Get down!
- There he is.
- Get outta the way.
Go! Full ahead!
Full speed!
- I Got You.
- Stay low.
Look down there.
- Idiots! You idiot what have you done?
- We killed them boss, like you wanted.
No! not like I wanted.
I needed Haddock alive.
Wait a minute boss.
There were two boats missing.
yeah the other one must have been a decoy
They are on to us,
and our destination.
Find them. Make absolutely certain
they never reach Bagghar
- We have to get to Bagghar ahead of
Sakharine. - I know! I know!
- Why? - Because he has
the third model of ship.
How do you know?
The Sheikh collects old ships, and
this is the prize of his collection.
Blistering barnacles!
That is the Unicorn.
- Captain, do you see the distortion
around the model? - I can see.
It means, in Bin Salaad exhibits
are going to be in a...
bullet proof glass
case in his palace.
- Sakharine is going there to steal it.
- He Has a Secret Weapon.
The Milanese Nightingale.. But that
won't be enough to solve the mystery,
and, that's why, Sakharine needs you.
That is why he made you his prisoner.
There is something he needs
you to remember.
I don't follow you.
I read it in a book,
that only a true Haddock can
discover the secret of the Unicorn.
I don't remember anything about anything
But you must know that your ancestors
Sir Francis - it's your family legacy.
- My memory is not the way it used
to be. - What did it used to be?
I've forgotten.
Captain, can you get us to Bagghar?
What sort of stupid question Is that?
Gimme those oars! Now you'll see some
real seamenship buddy.
I'll not be hounded by some pipsqueak ginger
and his irritating dof
I am Master and Commander of the seas.
I know these waters better than
the warts on my mother's face.
Look at the pair of them.
Fast asleep.
Typical landlubbers. have no stamina these days
Never mind. I get take you there Tintin.
Look Thomson, that's the fellow.
Oh my!
- Mr. Silk.
- Yes?
- My name is Thompson.
- And Thomson
- We are police officers.
- Oh!
Mr. Silk. Are you Ok?
Are you all right, sir?
- I'm all right, sir.
- No need to runaway sir.
- No.. no, you see.
Yesterday we nearly we
caught the pickpocket...
who has been terrorizing the town.
Pickpocket? -- We pulled his jacket off and
inside we found the wallet.
- A wallet with your name and address.
- That's my wallet.
- Well, it's obvious he has stole
it from you. - No that's my wallet
Are you all right, sir?
We didn't mean to startle you.
Let us help you into your apartment?
Thank you so much. Don't need to come
in, I'll be quite all right
We insist, it's better to be safe than
sorry. Its least we can do
- Oh, thank you.
- Here we are.
- Good grief what's all this?
- It is my collection.
- What a lot of wallets.
- I can't help it.
It started with coin purses.
and went on from there really
You ought to be careful. Haven't you
heard, there is a pickpocket around.
- Yes. Can you imagine.
- What do you mean pick pocket?
A Master Criminal. A bag snatching,
purse pilfering, wallet lifting thief.
I'm not a bad person.
I am a kleptomaniac.
- A what?
- It's a fear of open spaces.
No wonder, he keeps his
wallets in the living room.
Wallets! I just cannot resist
the lovely little things.
It Is a harmless little habit, really.
- Look at this. His name is Thomson too
- What a coincidence.
No Thompson.
This is Thomson without a "p".
No.. no.. no. Its Thompson with a "p"
[all rambling together]
I'm not your sidekick, you are mine.
- How dare you?
- I met you first.
- I met you first
I can't stand it anymore.
Take them! Take them!
Take them all!
Pull yourself together man.
We can't take your wallets.
- Do we look like thieves?
- Good heavens Thompson.
This looks familiar. Tell me.
This is Tintins.
Oh, I'm so cold....
...and thirsty.
My thoat is parched - I'll see if there is any
fresh water.
ahhh what have we here?
Tintin! Tintin!
Come and warm yourself buddy.
Captain, what have you done?
- No Need to thank me.
- What?
You looked a little cold
so I lit a wee fire
In a boat? No, those are our oars.
We need them.
- Yes but not for much longer.
- Have you gone mad?
Quick, Captain. Help me.
Captain help me quick.
Ohh what have I done, what've I done
No. Captain, not that.
Thundering typhoons
This is a fine mess.
Weak, selfish!!!
There is no hope of rescue. Sakharine
and his men are half way to Bagghar.
- Oh! Miserable! Rats!
- All right, that's enough of that.
That was his fault, you see.
It was Sir Francis's.
- Tell me, how did you work that one out?
- Because he was a figurehead of great courage...
bold exploits, no one like that ever
existed in my family.
Why do you think I drink, because
I know, I'll never be like him.
No it's far better I end it now
Put us both out of our misery
What is it, Snowy?
I'm going to lower
myself into the sea.
Into the cold embrace.
The big blue.....
Those are Portuguese markings.
Where is the Karaboudjan registered?
We are saved! We are saved!
We are saved!
- Troglodytes!
- Captain, get down.
The slave traders! mutant malingerers!!!
Freshwater politicians!
Bad news, captain.
We only got one bullet.
- Oh, what's the good news?
- We got one bullet.
You got him!
Well shot boy.
Stay here, Captain.
Tintin! Tintin!
Don't take your eyes
off of them. Hurry up.
just as I thought.
Ignition has been cut.
A lucky shot. One more pass
and we will finish him off.
Put your hands in the air.
Now!
Let's see.
You know what you are doing, Tintin?
More or less.
- Which is it more --- or less.
- Relax.
I interviewed a pilot once?
Which way to North Africa?
Captain, look,
we've caught up with them.
Wonderful. Would you think I might
find another way to North Africa?
that doesn't take us through that wall of death?
We can't turn back.
Not now. Not now.
No, Captain. That's surgical spirit
for medicinal purposes only.
[muttering]
Fuel tank. It's almost empty.
Captain, This may sound crazy,
but I have got a plan.
The alcohol in the bottle
may go a few more miles.
I need you to climb out of the plane
and pour it into the fuel tank.
Can I put on the parachute first?
It's a terrible storm out there.
- And it's raining.
- And you call yourself a Haddock?
Captain?
Captain, can you hear me?
You're doing fine.
Now, pour the bottle into the tank.
We're running on fumes...
Fuuuuumes...
- Captain, I can't see!
- Land! Land!
- We cant land !
- We're not there yet
Do something!
Hold on, Tintin!
I'm coming!
The land of thirst -- the land of thirst.
- Land of thirst
- Oh will you stop saying that..
You don't understand, I've run out.
- You do not know, what that means.
- Captain, we have to keep going.
One step at a time.
Come on, on your feet.
Lean your weight on me.
A man can only handle so long without his vitals
Captain, calm down. There are
worse things than sobering up?
Look, Tintin do you see it?
Water! Water!
Captain, just a mirage.
It was here. I saw it.
It was just your mind playing
tricks. It's the heat.
- I have to go home.
- What?
- I have to go back to the sea.
- Captain, you're Hallucinating.
Look at that. Did you ever
see a more beautiful sight?
She is turning into the wind.
All sails set.
Triple-masted, double decks.
- Fifty guns.
- The Unicorn?
- Isn't she a beauty?
- Yes she is.
Tell me captain,
what else can you see?
She's got the wind behind her. Look
at the pace she is setting.
Barely a day out of Barbados.
Hold full of rum, and finest
tobacco -
and the heart of sailors
set for home.
The Red Pennant.
The blood runs cold in every sea
captain who looks upon that flag
they know they're facing a fight to the death.
But Sir Francis is a Haddock.
And Haddocks don't flee.
Battle stations!
Never seen so many....
Yellow bellied, lilly-livered sea slugs
- Prepare to bring her about.
- Aye, aye, captain.
Prepare to bring her about!
- Mr. Nichols, secure the cargo.
- Right away sir.
Prepare to repel boarders!
Destroy. We need more men.
Then he saw him.
Like a phantom!!.
Rising from the dead.!!
Who, captain?
Who did he see?
The ship is gone.
What do you mean gone?
What happened next?
Oh Jupiter I have beard!!!
Since when did I have a beard?
Something Happened on the Unicorn.
It is the key to everything.
- You must try to remember.
- Unicorn ... I'm so terribly thirsty.
- Captain! - Tintin,
what's happening to me?
And to think,
all it took was a day in the Sahara.
Congratulations captain,
you are sober.
Sober.
Good dog.
- This one is all right.
Check the other! - Yes, sir!
I am Lieutenant Delcourt. Welcome
to the Afgharin fortress.
Thank you, Lieutenant.
We owe you our lives.
- Did you find my friend?
- Yes, but he is not in good shape.
He is still suffering the effects
of acute dehydration.
He is quite Delirious. Why don't we pay
him a visit.
Oh, Haddock, you're awake.
Good. I have a visitor for you.
- Captain.
- Ooohh I think you've got the wrong room.
Captain, it is Tintin. Our plane crashed
in the desert. Don't you remember?
Plane? Oh no, I'm a naval man myself.
I'll never fly, if I can help it. He is
confused with someone else.
What is this peculiar liquid?
- There's no bouquet - Its completely transparent.
- Ah, its water.
What will they think of next?
We suspect, he has concussion.
- From what he's drinking - its delirium.
- He is sober!
- Now captain, out in the desert.
- Desert? - Yes.
- you were talking about Sir Francis.
- Sir who? - Sir Francis.
- and you were telling me about what
happened on the Unicorn...
- The Unicorn!
- Yes.
AAhh the stuff that dreams are made of
wee chidrens dreams
No, the ship. Please try
to remember captain.
Lives are at risk
Snowy, what have you done?
Stand back, if I were you.
He's snapped.
Everybody out of this room.
Show yourself Red Rackham!
if it's a fight you want
you'll be eating rats...
- Fighting with who?
- To the death, Red Rackham.
No, wait.
Wait. Captain.
I remember everything now,
everything granddaddy told me.
The Unicorn was taken
Pirates were now masters of the ship.
- Our crew surrendered?
- granddaddy said that Red Rackham.
called Sir Francis the 'Kings dog'
A pirate hunter sent to reclaim their hard fought plunder.
Why would I waste my time on rum,
tobacco, molasses and dates, -
When you have a more
valuable cargo on board?
- Where is it?
- You have to kill me first.
Not at first. No.
I'll start with the your men!
To save his men, he would give
up the secret cargo.
Where was it?
Four hundred pounds in weight of gold
and jewels and treasure
- Kill His men!
- No, Rackham. No!
You gave me your word.
Rackham! Rackham!
Sir Francis knew he was doomed, -
That he'd be hung from the highest yardarm
But they didn't reckon on one thing.
Sir Francis was a Haddock.
And a Haddock always
has a trick up his sleeve.
And with that he hurls
himself forward!
On the pirates, like that, unarmed.
No. there was a bottle of rum rolling
on the deck, and he opens it up.
- And he lifts it to his lips ...
- Then then he stops.
This is no time for drinking, he says,
I need all my wits about me.
with that he puts down the bottle and ...
Yes, yes, yes. He puts down the
bottle ... And seizes a cutlass!
He makes his way to
the ships magazine...
where they keep all the
gunpowder and the shot.
You dog! you'd blow us sky high?
Well come on then let's have you.
Not this time.
You!
Captain, what is it?
How can I be so blind?
What are you talking about?
This isn't just about the scrolls or....
the treasure that went
down with the ship.
it's me!!
It's me he is after.
You'll suffer a curse upon you
and your name Haddock.
He wants vengeance.
Come back and face me.
- Hurry Tintin. We are out of time.
- Captain!
I curse you. I curse your name...
...and all who come after!
We will meet again, Haddock!
In another time,
in another life.
- It's not over, it was never over
- I don't understand. Who's after your blood?
- Sakharine.
- Sakharine? Why?
He is a Red Rackham's descendent.
He needs to finish it.
That's why he did it --- Did What?
Sank his own ship.
Sir Francis sent that treasure
to the bottom of the sea.
- He would be damned before he let
Red Rackham have it. - And he was.
- But he couldn't let it lie.
- No. - He left the clue.
Three clues wrapped in a riddle
concealing the secret.
- But only a true Haddock will
be able to solve it. - A secret?
The location... to one of the greatest
sunken treasures in all history.
The wreck of the Unicorn .
He means to steal it.
The third scroll.
Blue blistering barnacles!
I swear, as the last of the Haddocks,
I'll find that treasure before him.
- To Bagghar.
He is here.
It's no good. It could be anywhere.
Captain, don't look now,
but we are being followed.
So we are.
What do you want?
Why are you following us?
Who are you working for?
Captain, stop---stop!
- Thomson and Thompson. - Don't
say it now. - We are in disguise.
Oh, I see. You got the message
I sent from the ship
Yes. Bit of a long story there.
The upshot is we caught the thief, retrieved your wallet,
and hopped on the next plane to Bagghar.
That pocket picker has
picked his last pocket.
Don't worry.
He didn't take any money.
It's not the money I'm worried about.
The odds are even
Now to find the next two scrolls.
The Milanese Nightingale.
That's his secret weapon.
Aye.
Welcome, Madame Castafiore.
We are blessed with
your presence.
Oh, yes. Indeed, Senore Salaad.
What charming peasants.
May I introduce my escort.
Mr. Sugar Addatif.
He has been a very...
...passionate supporter
of this concert.
It's my first visit to the third world.
Please forgive me. I must escort Madam
to the dressing room. Excuse me.
Bravo.
After you.
Captain, I want you to look after this.
What are you doing?
- Me? - Yes
- Are you sure?
If I'm caught, I don't want
him to find this on me.
- Just keep it in.
- I will guard this with my life.
Get up!
It's her.
Blistering barnacles!
What's that noise?
My ears.
- They are bleeding.
- No, they are not.
Captain!
Shut up, Snowy.
........make way - medical emergency
That was close
- Hello, Captain.
- You!
Sakharine.
- Stop him, Snowy!
- Tintin!
- Those two there, they're here to steal your ship!
- No. no. we are not!
- Arrest him and the ugly one!
- Who? Me?
Yes. Arrest him.
Captain!
- Sakharine's got the scroll.
- It's worse than that mate
- What do you mean?
- They took your scroll too.
- Its gone.
- How? What happened?
It was Allan. He nobbled me...
in the garden and...
- Then there was a bottle of alcohol.
- There always is.
No! No, no. It's not like that.
I can smell it on you.
Hurry. Back to the boat.
- Tintin, where are you going?
- Going after Sakharine.
- By yourself?
- Yes. Come on, Snowy.
Lose them!
Get him off our tail.
Did you hit anything?
Faster. You idiot, faster.
I'll take those thank you.
Faster!
- Captain, let's go!
- You don't worry.
on three!
Snowy!
Oh no! Not again.
Come here my beauty.
Ten thousand thundering typhoons!
I'll kill you if I find you!
Captain, the bird! Grab it!
Great work, Snowy! l Now don't let it go.
Blistering barnacles!
Snowy, I am coming!
Slow down.
That's right! That's right! Come
to daddy! Come to dadd....
Gotcha. Come on.
No!
Geronimo!
The scrolls are lining up.
these are hidden numbers.
- What does it say?
- I wouldn't do that if I were you!
Let the bird go.
What do you value more.
Those scrolls or Haddock's life?
Don't listen to him.
You will never get away with this
..you sour- faced sassanach
I will kill him.
- Don't worry about me, Tintin...I'm fine
- Let the bird go now...
- Or this man dies!
- No! Wait!
You two timing troglodyte
Perhaps we should put it to test?
Here's mud in your eye
Tintin!
Oh! We are saved!
- I love the beach.
- You said you wanted a holiday.
- Nobody takes my ship! -
- They've already taken it.
But nobody takes my ship twice.
We'll show 'em hey then Tintin.
Right what's the plan?
- There is no plan. - Of course there's a plan.
You always got a plan.
Not this time. Sakharine has the scrolls,
They lead him to the treasure.
He could be anywhere in the world.
We will never see him again.
It's over.
I thought you were an optimist.
You were wrong, weren't you?
I'm a realist.
- That's just another name for a quitter.
- You can call me what you like.
Don't you get it? We failed.
Failed?
There are plenty of others
willing to call me a failure.
A fool, a loser, a hopeless souse.
Don't you ever say that yourself!
You send out the wrong signal,
that is what people pick up.
You understand? If you care about
something, you fight for it.
You hit a wall, you push through it.
There's something you need to
know about failure Tintin.
It can never let you free
- What did you just say?
- You hit a wall, you push through it!
No, no, you said something
about sending out the signal.
Of course! Captain,
I sent a radio message
from the Karaboudjan.
I know what radio frequency
they are transmitting on.
Well, how does that help us?
All we have to do is send that
information to Interpol,
they can track the signals and figure
out which way they are headed.
- And here come Interpol now.
- Tintin!
Any port they enter,
we will know at once.
We can get there first.
What are we doing here boss, I don't get it
We're right back where we started
Speak of this to no one. Keep your
mouth shut.
Don't worry, as long
as we get our share.
- Oh you'll get your share.
- Where are you going?
Guard the ship.
Good evening, sir. I trust you had
a successful trip abroad.
Do I pay you to talk to me?
You don't pay me at all.
This place is messed up.
Nestor!
Tom! Allan! you blithering idiots.....
Don't just stand there -- do something!
Caught him like a rat in a trap.
Congratulations, Gentlemen.
He's all yours.
Yes. We also have an arrest warrant
issued by both Interpol and the FBI.
Your friend who got shot --- Barnaby?
He was one of their agents. Right on
Sakharine's trail from the start.
It still doesn't make sense. He has the
key to the treasure of the Unicorn.
Which is sitting somewhere
on the ocean floor.
Why would he come back home?
Right, Sakharine.
That's Mr. Sakharine to you.
Hold it.
Allan! Get me down.
Not that way!
Not that way, you fool!
The other way!
Right!!
Look out!
Close but no cigar!!!
- Red Rackham !
- That's right. My ancestor.
- Just as Sir Francis was yours.
- It's unfinished business.
Oh I'm glad you know
the truth, Haddock.
Until you could remember....killing you,
wouldn't have been this much fun.
- Who gave you permission to
board my ship? - I don't need it.
I've never needed it.
The legend says, only a Haddock can
discover The Secret of the Unicorn.
It took a Rackham
to get the job done.
So you've lost again, Haddock.
That's right! Why don't you have a
drink? It's all you got left! Isn't it?
Everything which was rightfully
yours, is now mine.
Including the ship.
Thundering typhoons.
Nobody takes my ship.
We have you now, you devil.
- You are under arrest.
- To be precise.......
you are under arrest.
Do you see?
Blistering barnacles!
They're coordinates.
It took all three scrolls
to form the numbers.
Latitude and longitude, that is it.
That's the location of the treasure.
We did it!
Almost there, Mr. Tintin.
- Next to starboard should do it
- Are you sure we are on course?
Stay laddie I know these parts like
the back of my hand.
- Starboard! quick!
- Quickly!
All stop!!!
Marlinspike Hall
Those coordinates lead here.
And this is where Sir Francis hid it?
I thought the treasure
went down with the ship.
Master Haddock, Mr. Tintin,
I've been expecting you.
- Welcome to Marlinspike Hall.
- Look at this place!
I don't think it's changed at all
since I was a little boy.
and may I say sir,
How much I'm looking forward to having
a Haddock back in charge of the estate.
You will be waiting a long time, Nestor.
There is no way I could
afford to live here.
Well, Captain, you know the house.
Where do we start?
Is the cellar still here?
No, no no, no this isn't it.
- I meant the other cellar.
- I'm sorry sir there is no other cellar.
- It was bigger than this.
- Snowy!
Snowy, where are you?
Snowy.
Just like you said, Captain.
- You hit a wall ...
- You push through it.
My grandfather must have walled it
up before he lost the house.
'and then shines forth the Eagle's cross'.
I can see the cross but where's the eagle ?
St. John Evangelist, who is always
depicted with an eagle.
And he is called the eagle of
Patmos. He is the eagle.
What he trying to tell us, Captain?
I'm at a loss.
The island, the one in the middle,
that doesn't exist.
- How do you know?
- Because I sailed those waters.
countless times I've been there.
That is a mistake.
What if it isn't?
Sir Francis wanted his inheritance
to go to a man who was worthy of it.
A man like himself, who knows
the seas like the back of his hand.
A man who could look at a globe
...and tell if one tiny
island is out of place.
Blistering treasure, it is
Red Rackham's barnacles!
What is this?
Just a wee tipple, a toast to our good fortune.
Now that's better.
It's odd, you would have thought, after all the
fuss and bother there would have been more
- More of what?
- Red Rackham's treasure.
By your account he looted half of
South America. I just thought ...
Ach never mind there's plenty to go around
Ohh. it's a funny old life. Now you got
your story for your newspaper!
- All is well that ends well
- It's not ended.
Sir Francis left another clue,
at the bottom of the globe.
- Clue to what?
- Four hundred weight of gold...
...just lying at the bottom of the sea.
How is your thirst for adventure,..Captain?
Unquenchable, Tintin.