Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Hey, it's me!
Yep. We just landed.
Okay. Cool.
The guy's not home
five seconds,
- he's already calling Kristen.
- Oh boy, here we go.
You don't want her thinking
you're dying to see her, do you?
Turtle's right, E.
Let her think you're busy.
She's my girlfriend,
idiots.
I don't care
what she thinks.
I don't have to play games anymore.
Tell them, Vince.
Come on, what do I know
about relationships?
What kind of girlfriend won't come
see you while you're away working?
The kind of girlfriend
in school.
I went to school.
How hard is it to cut out on that shit?
Not that hard
when you're headed for a G.E.D.
Three months without pussy, E.
That's rough.
You're almost
a virgin again.
Why do you think
he's calling?
It's like the guy
got his hymen restored.
Vince, you ever go
three months without pussy?
- Vince ain't never gone three days--
- Wait, that's not true.
Sophomore year.
- Really?
- Well, you had mono.
- Good memory, E.
- That shit don't count.
Yo, Johnny, is there
another slice left?
No, sorry, bro.
Polished it off
over the Grand Canyon.
We need an Eddie's out here.
L.A. pizza blows.
Why is it so hard
to get a good slice in L.A. anyway?
Tap water. That's why you can't
get a decent bagel either.
Except on Fairfax.
There's different water
on Fairfax?
Yeah, Vince.
The Jews import it from Borough Park.
I'm serious.
If that were the case, then why can't you
get a good slice on Fairfax?
Because Jews don't
make pizza, idiot.
So, given your theory,
Drama,
I should get a decent pizza bagel
at Canter's.
- Uh-huh.
- Wrong, E.
Kosher mozzarella
tastes like tofu.
Tofu?
Did you call for a car,
Turtle?
Was I supposed to?
No, we're supposed
to walk home.
Summer break's over, E.
Time to get your soldiers in line.
Guy's not my soldier.
I inherited him.
- Hey, fuck you.
- I hate the new system.
Check it out.
You called them
and asked them not to tow it?
It would be cooler if I left it
for Homeland Security to impound.
Shotgun!
I hate
the new system.
All right,
so, remember--
gardener, pool guy,
newspaper, vet, alarm company,
satellite, Gelson's,
dry cleaning,
and get the MLB package
hooked up.
Oh, call your boy Busey,
Vince.
We're finally gonna
accept that gift.
I hope it's not
a self-portrait.
Turtle, will you do me a favor?
Will you take this stuff in?
Vince, I want his job.
The guy's sitting on Easy Street.
Turtle, please.
You're like a three-time Lotto winner.
Where you going?
Three months, Vince.
Three months.
Yeah, you won't last
five minutes.
He won't last
five seconds.
What are you doing?
You got me thinking.
Take me to Stacy's.
No, Jamie's.
No, Stacy's.
What?
What the fuck
are we supposed to do?
Jerk each other off,
you losers!
Yeah, don't forget
your bag!
- Help me with this stuff?
- Yeah.
I got Arnold.
Come on, Arnold, let's go.
Huh-uh! Huh-uh!
Huh-uh!
What?
I have my period.
Oh, fuck.
Really?
Yeah.
Bad timing, huh?
Uh, you know.
I mean...
- Maybe, uh...
- What?
It's been three months.
Maybe
a little something else.
No.
- Why?
- Because...
that wouldn't be fair
to me.
I've been waiting to have sex with you
for three months also.
Yeah, but it's easier
for girls to hold out.
No. Eric.
I feel gross.
I feel fat and bloated.
Well, you're not.
You're beautiful.
- Saturday night.
- What?
We can get really drunk.
And since you're
this big hotshot manager
making the big bucks, we can get
a room at the Beverly Hills Hotel.
Big bucks?
I made $6,000 on that movie.
Okay, well,
we'll split the room.
We'll have the best sex ever.
What are we gonna do now?
Just kiss.
- She wouldn't even blow you?
- Or give you a nice tug?
That's bullshit.
You act like a priest
for three months,
the least the girl
can do is service you.
That is
a little selfish.
Had I shown up and Kristen
was missing a leg,
I still would have
taken care of business.
You would have sex
with a girl on her period?
Who wouldn't, man?
Hey, I've done it.
It's not something I hope for.
You guys are disgusting.
I don't think I've ever done that.
Well, you should,
altar boy.
Because it's a fact
a girl on her period is hornier.
And there's no need
for a raincoat.
- It's like Flag Day.
- Except it's a week. Hold that!
Hey, what's up?
What the fuck?
Hey, guys.
I'm Lloyd, Ari's new assistant.
What's up, man?
I'm Vince.
I know who you are.
If Ari gives you a hard time
let me know, all right?
What happened to Emily?
I don't know.
Can I get you something to drink?
- Water.
- Water sounds good.
I'm good.
- What are you being an asshole for?
- Yeah?
A bigwig like Ari should have
a hot assistant to look at.
Johnny, some people
probably think he is hot.
I ain't one
of them people.
Come on, Turtle,
let's go.
The only reason we stopped
was to see how Emily treated you.
Peace.
The boys are back
in town!
You like "Gaysian Lloyd"?
He's cute, right?
And he covers two quotas.
- Did you fire Emily?
- I had to.
To make sure you wouldn't
fuck another one of my assistants.
You're not gonna try
to fuck Lloyd?
Did you really fire her?
James Cameron stole her.
She's over at Lightstorm.
So, how was
the little movie?
Ah, honestly...
one of the best
experiences of my life.
That's fantastic. But you got it
out of your system, right?
I wanted to talk
to you about that.
I ran into Neil Labute
in New York.
He wants me
to do his play in London.
Six months,
$300 a week.
But I figure with your negotiating skills you
can get me $400.
And it's very well written.
Okay, Ari, I'm joking.
I'm ready to work.
What do you got?
Hiya, Mary.
Hi, I'm Carla.
Adam's newassistant.
Can I get you guys
something to drink?
You have a "Diet Creamsicle Shasta"
by any chance?
Johnny, Turtle.
Adam!
You have an office!
And you've got
a smoking-hot assistant.
Yep, and it's all
because of this guy.
- Really?
- No, not really.
Sit. Sit.
So, I'm back
and I'm ready.
Great!
Exciting stuff going on.
- Yeah?
- I'm circling something at NBC.
TV?
I thought maybe after "Queens Boulevard"
we could get a movie.
Oh, this is a movie.
A movie of the week.
But I have
a little problem.
Your headshots--
they're setting us back.
I've had those shots
since '92.
They've been great.
What's the problem?
The problem is people
get annoyed
when they expect to see
a 24-year-old.
Does this look
like you?
- You ready?
- Let's go, we're ready.
This kid's got
no patience.
In some countries,
they would cut off your elfin feet
for disrupting
the master's flow.
How about I shove
my elfin foot up your ass?
- You missed me, didn't you?
- Ari, come on.
All right, you ready?
"Aquaman"!
- "Aquaman"?
- "Aquaman," baby!
It is "Spiderman" underwater!
Boom.
- Is there a script?
- No, I know he doesn't like to read,
so I got you something
with pictures.
Tell him, E.
Uh-oh, tell me what?
We know what we want
to do next.
What?
The fucking Belt Parkway?
- Relax. It's a studio movie.
- Really?
It's big.
Show him.
What is this, some Showtime miniseries?
Come on.
No, it's "Medellin."
The Pablo Escobar story.
Sex, drugs
and salsa!
Did you read it?
I know about it.
It's at Universal.
This movie is gonna be
the new "Scarface."
Which was our favorite movie
growing up.
- Really?
- "Here's the story.
I come from the gutter,
that's okay.
I got no education,
I know that.
There will be
no stopping me.
I go straight
to the top, Ari!"
This is the kind of studio movie
we want to do.
- "What're you gonna do about it"?
- I'll get into it.
But I'm also deep
into "Aquaman."
I got a meeting
with Dana Gordon.
Well, should I be there?
Uh, no.
Unless you wanna
pull up her car
- or serve us creme brulee.
- Go fuck yourself.
- Not gonna work this year.
- What're you talking about?
- What did I tell you?
- I can't play with the guy?
What's the deal?
We gotta battle.
- Go easy. He's having a rough day.
- What happened?
- He's not getting any.
- Oh, no. You kidding me?
You want me
to get Lloyd in here
and have him hari-kari you
with his pecker? Or no?
No? I thought the girlfriend
was still in play.
Bad time of the month
to come home.
- You're like me.
- Yeah? How so?
I won't even fuck my wife
after she plays tennis.
Listen,
here's the deal.
I got other things
to discuss with Dana Gordon.
So you set
your own meetings.
But, Vinnie,
the good news is,
Warner's loves you.
Know it.
This year you're going to jump
to the next level, baby.
- Sounds good.
- Sounds fine.
I'd say hug it out,
but I don't want you drawing wood.
All right?
This is your year, baby.
Your year!
Jesus.
Try this side.
Turtle! Turtle!
What the fuck
you screaming about?
- I'm right here.
- What's going on?
Everything.
Just like you asked.
It's fucking chaos out there.
You couldn't
spread things out?
I have my system,
you had yours.
What is this thing out here
on the front lawn?
That's Busey's gift.
It's "a psychedelic totem pole."
I thought he was giving us
a painting.
I told him I liked
that one better.
We don't own this house. What are we
gonna do with it when we move?
Fucking leave it.
It's ugly as shit.
I told him Vince would take
a picture in front of it, though.
Now you're pissing me off.
Maybe you should
try doing my dog shit job
and I should
try being Vince's manager.
- I did your job.
- Not like this.
Vince never yelled at you.
You yell at a guy,
you break his spirit.
- Ah.
- Vince, does his new title
allow him to yell at me
all the time?
That was in his deal.
Sorry.
Don't be so sensitive,
Turtle.
- What day is she on, E?
- Who?
Kristen-- what day
of her period is it?
Day two.
You're in
for a rough week.
- Not as rough as E.
- Can I buy you a blow job?
It would make
both our lives easier.
Nope, I'm fine.
Don't need any of that.
Just gotta make it
to Saturday night.
What?
You made a sex date?
He's got to wine and dine
his own girlfriend?
I thought the whole reason people have
girlfriends is for effort-free sex.
Are you sure she's not trying
to avoid fucking you?
Exactly. Whoever heard of a girl
who cycles mid-month?
- Mm-hmm.
- When do you cycle, Drama?
Hey, Turtle, let's go outside
and take a couple shots.
I already took care
of your head shots.
You can't let Turtle
take your headshots.
- Why not?
- Because you need a professional.
You want me to call David LaChapelle?
He owes me a favor.
The guy charges five grand
to set up a light.
- I already took care of this, Drama.
- So, I'll pay. It's your career.
You can't
fuck around with it.
It's emasculating having
your kid brother pay for your headshots.
And him paying for the rest of your life
is empowering?
Vince don't pay for shit
of mine.
Everything's on my tab.
Tell him, bro.
It's all a loan, okay?
So borrow the money.
It's not the money.
It's the principle.
I can't let them win.
- Who's "them"?
- The conspirators in this town
who force the good actors
out of the business
by draining their resources
with shit they don't need,
Iike... fucking headshots.
Your headshots
are taken care of.
If someone would
just listen to me.
- By who?
- Trust me, all right?
See, I'm a multi-tasker.
You're a regular Martha Stewart,
Turtle.
At any point am I gonna
get any credit from anyone?
We'll see, Turtle.
We'll see.
"California Pizza Kitchen"?
- Did you buy this?
- Yeah, it's New York style.
Not with guacamole on it,
it's not.
You guys are all over me today.
Jesus.
Oh, come on,
don't be so sensitive.
I'll eat the shitty pizza!
Vince, you should take a look
at this "Aquaman."
It's cool
for a comic book.
I don't want
to do "Aquaman."
Afraid you don't got
the body to fill out the suit?
I didn't want to tell Ari,
get the hard sell.
- Will you tell him?
- Sure, I'll lock him into "Medellin."
Gracias, chico.
Excuse me,
was anyone gonna call me
- and tell me you're back?
- You didn't know we were back?
I knew you were back
because Gary Busey told me.
He wants that shot
with Vince.
- Eric Murphy, this is Amanda Peet.
- Hey.
- Eric is Vincent Chase's manager.
- Oh, hey.
- Nice to meet you.
You too. When's Vince
gonna do another movie?
- Soon, very soon.
- Good.
You should find Vince
a movie to do with Amanda.
Yeah!
- That would be great.
- I'm more than a publicist.
I really should produce.
Give me your card,
I'll give you a call.
You know what,
I don't have a card.
What's the name
of your company?
You know what,
I don't have a company either.
- I'm getting that going.
- I'll put you two in touch.
- Okay, great.
- I'll call you.
- Nice meeting you.
- Yeah.
You sound like a fucking moron,
you know that?
Thanks, Shauna.
It's weird.
Your eyes--
they look black in this light.
- You should seriously--
- Hey.
You're not gonna keep me
waiting are you? What're you doing?
- Hey, Shauna!
- Oh, fuck you, Ari!
Hey, hey,
who speaks like that at Koi?
I apologize.
She's in PR.
She knows not what--
You need to be punished.
Let's go.
This is retarded.
Do you wanna drop
two grand on headshots?
This won't be out
for another four weeks.
What do we have to do
to make sure my boy gets picked?
I do the picking.
How do I know this isn't
your signature?
Come on, Christy,
are you crazy?
That's the classic "Vincent Chase swoop"
on the V right there.
Yeah, yeah.
I got the same thing with my J.
Who are you?
I had an unbelievable lunch
with Dana Gordon.
The script is
coming in next week.
And-- Kanpai--
I think I convinced her to attach Vinnie
before they get a director.
I should get
a fucking Pulitzer.
Ari, Vince doesn't want
to do "Aquaman."
What do you mean
he doesn't want to do "Aquaman"?
He hasn't read the script.
He has read "Medellin."
He wants to do that.
Where did you get that one?
Josh Weinstein?
- A little insecure, Ari?
- How did you get it?
Turtle found it on the subway.
What's it matter? We wanna do it.
And I wanttofuck
AngelinaJolie.
The only difference is,
I might have a shot.
- We don't have a shot?
- No-- you want to know why?
They're out to a guy.
I don't know if you ever heard of him.
His name is Tom Cruise.
Tom Cruise is gonna play
Pablo Escobar?
The guy is not
even Hispanic.
Hillary Swank has a vagina
and she won an Oscar
pretending she has a dick.
That's what actors do--
they pretend.
I get it.
I get it, okay.
So, what if Cruise passes?
They go to Brad Pitt.
He passes, they go to Keanu Reeves.
And on down the list.
- Where is Vince on that list?
- He ain't on the list.
How do we get him
on the list?
You do "Aquaman,"
you stupid fuck.
- Let's go.
- All right, let's do it.
Okay, great.
I think we got what we need.
Wait, hold on a second,
pal.
I got a couple of wardrobe changes.
Turtle!
Who is this guy?
- Okay.
- Suck in that gut a little, Drama.
Fuck you, Turtle.
How's the hair look?
Good?
Before he did
"Born on the Fourth of July,"
Tom Cruise did "Top Gun."
Hanks fucked a fish before
he did "Forrest Gump."
We need a commercially viable
popcorn flick,
Iike "Matterhorn" would
have been.
- We can get "Aquaman."
- We can get a lot of things.
Since Vince doesn't want
to do "Aquaman,"
Iet's talk about those things.
Really, we can get a lot
of other things? You know?
- Yeah.
- You know what we can get?
You don't even know the name
of your own fucking company.
"Stop cursing at Koi.
You're embarrassing me."
You know what's embarrassing--
is that you are managing
your best friend
right out of the business.
That would roughly be embarrassing.
That is not true.
You'll be singing a different tune
when you see
"Queens Boulevard."
We need a career intervention,
is what we need.
No more arguing.
No more bullshit.
We're going to sit down,
the three of us,
and I'm going to lay out
for you clearly,
what our options are.
This town is littered
with the trashed careers
of the "once upon a time"
movie stars.
Don't let our boy be
a cautionary tale.
Okay. Well,
I conceptualized this
when I was on a walk-about
in the Badlands.
And I stumbled
on this briar patch of berries.
And I ate every berry
I could see,
because I thought that would be
nurturement from the earth to me.
Vincent. Teeth.
And after I ate the berries,
this came to me.
Each one of these
represents...
Don't ever commit to shit
without talking to me first.
I gotta have some freedom
to operate, E.
You gotta earn freedom.
Why didn't you get this guy
to do my shots? He's a real pro.
All right, you know what?
Fuck you.
And fuck you, all right?
That's it, I'm done. I quit.
What's he quitting?
He gets paid?
I don't think there's a word
in the Earth language
- or in the dictionary to define...
- Mm-hmm.
...what it did to me.
But it was up in here.
It was in my heart, my spirit,
my soul, my mind, my emotions.
- No anxiety...
- Gary, how many pictures do we need?
One perfect one. It comes from the light
of the sun after it's set.
It's 1 1 :30 now, Gary.
I know it is.
But we must wait for this precious time.
Well, we have a meeting.
Your meeting and your future
is meaningless.
Gary, a couple more pictures
and that's it.
Guys, let me ask you
a question.
What's more important...
Oh, great.
Now what?
Got a big one
for you fellas today.
Yo, "H&H Bagels."
All right!
- How you doing, Blake?
- What's happening?
Yo, check it out.
"Carnegie Knishes."
Nice!
What else you got?
Whatever this is.
Oh!
"Eddie's Pizza"!
What a score.
It's like being back in New York.
- Nice, E!
- I didn't do it.
Who did?
Jesus, E.
You never came up with
something like this.
Yo, great job, Turtle.
Come down here!
Yeah, Turtle,
good job!
Oh, any corned beef?
I'm not coming out till
all of yous apologize.
And that means you, too,
Vince.
I'm sorry.
I didn't do nothing.
Sorry, Turtle!
Now the "Lucky Charm."
Come on, E.
Yeah, come on.
This is impressive.
Whose DHL number
is this?
It's Ari's.
I'm sorry.
I knew
you would like that.
Get down here
and help us carry this shit.
Yeah, that figures.
These are great.
- Yeah?
- Yeah!
Yeah, except, what's with
the big apple behind your head?
Ah, itdoesn't matter.
This is our year,
Johnny.
Can you feel it?
So, twice in two days, huh?
Must be important.
E didn't explain
the situation to you?
Did you explain to E
that there wouldn't be any lunch?
I would have waited
for my pizzas to defrost.
You didn't tell him
what I told you?
I told him you wanted
to sit down and talk.
I thought we just
sat down and talked.
What's the situation,
Ari?
- You seem stressed.
- Uh...
Yeah.
We can't get "Medellin."
Why not?
Because they're looking
at other people.
So call and tell them
to look at me.
You don't think
I've been on the phone?
You're the "most powerful agent
in the business."
One of the most powerful,
yeah.
No, you said
when I signed with you
you were "the most powerful."
He said that to you?
- A bunch of times.
- Shut the fuck up, Eric!
Listen, Ari, snap out of it,
all right?
If they're not looking at me,
you call them.
Tell them to look at me.
They'll listen to you,
all right? We cool?
I'm starved.
Let's get outta here.
Vince,
we have to do "Aquaman."
You didn't tell him
any of this?
No, he told me.
He told me, okay?
And Eric also told you
that I don't want to do "Aquaman."
If we can't get
"Medellin,"
then we will wait
for something else that I love.
For the past three months,
while your boy has been sitting
on your indy set pouring creamers
and getting no pussy, I have been scouring
this town for an offer.
It ain't out there.
Come on.
Okay.
Here's an offer
for you to star...
in a new
Olsen twins' movie.
It's a love triangle in which little Mary Kate
and Ashley
use you as an experiment
to see if you can tell
if they are two separate,
distinct people.
This would be mildly amusing
if the producer didn't think
he had a realistic shot of getting you.
It ain't eight months ago,
man.
Listen, you cooled off.
The $5 million offers
do not exist.
But Warner's loves you,
so "Aquaman" does.
What do you think,
Eric?
We should read "Aquaman"
and then see what's what.
Excellent representation.
Nice work, E.
You know what I think?
I would rather quit the business
than to do more shit
that I don't love.
I've done that.
And you know what,
it sucks.
I was only partially joking
about Neil Labute, Ari.
I'll go do a play.
I'd rather do a play
than this bullshit.
Don't forget,
I came from nothing.
As much as I love the toys,
I don't need them.
Well, that went well.
I don't want this
to get to a place
where you start blaming me
for everything.
You guys don't listen to me.
Listen to this--
you tell your boy
to do "Aquaman,"
or you tell him to find
other representation.
Yo!
My headshots were
a monster hit.
This is gonna be
a great fucking year.
- Can you feel it?
- Mm-hmm.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player