Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Gentlemen,
I want you to meet my daughters,
Marie Louise Pauline,
Marie Louise Jeanne,
and from my first marriage,
Marie Delphine Lopez.
But everyone calls her Borquita.
What they may lack
in outer beauty,
they more than make up for
with their many talents.
Borquita is a huge help to me
with the domestics.
While Jeanne excels
in petit point.
My youngest, Pauline,
well, her major talent
has yet to reveal itself.
Perhaps my talent
is in the boudoir,
Mother dear.
I guess we'll find out on your
wedding night, mon petit.
Mon cherie.
When the blood dries,
my skin is supposed to
be tight as a drum.
Just look at this wattle.
This blood's not fresh.
Borquita!
S'ak pase'w la?
Mon cherie, something happened
during the dinner party.
Stupid slut!
I invite all
the eligible bachelors
just to meet you and you...
spread your filthy legs for the houseman!
You might as well rut
with the family dog!
You can't control me, Mother.
The hell I can't!
The hell I can't.
You know what we're going
to say?
We're going to say
he took you by force.
Like the savage he is.
No, ma'am, I did no such thing.
Yes, that's what happened.
Miss Pauline came on to me.
And I told her
I belong to someone else.
Keep that mongrel quiet.
Haul him upstairs.
No. No. No.
Bonsoir, my pets.
Did y'all miss me?
Hush up.
Or I'll rip your lips open
and stuff more shit in there.
Why?
Why are you doing this to us?
Because I can?
Oh...
Now we gonna have
flies up here.
There.
That should do it.
Bastien.
You want to rut like a beast...
then we're going to treat you
like one.
Where's my pickaninny
with the head?
Put it on him.
Darling, you have
outdone yourself.
However did you think this up?
My great literacy began
with Greek mythology.
I used to sit on Daddy's lap
and he would read me
those stories
full of their vengeful Gods
and wondrous miraculous
creatures.
But the Minotaur was always
my favorite.
Half-man, half-bull.
And now...
I have one of my very own.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Are you sure about this?
Come on.
My mom gets home at 6:00.
It just sucks being
somebody's first.
I don't want to hurt you.
I'll be okay.
You okay?
Charlie?
Charlie, Charlie, what's wrong?
Charlie!
Charlie?!
It's a cliche, but like
all cliches, it's the truth.
Your life can change overnight.
Or in a moment.
The official word on Charlie's
death was a brain aneurysm.
But the doctors had never seen
anything quite like it before.
The blood...
all that blood.
It's not your fault, baby.
It's ours.
There's something I should have
told you a long time ago.
I prayed it would skip
your generation.
Your great-grandmother had
the same genetic affliction.
So apparently I'm a witch.
It runs in my family,
but it doesn't show up
in every generation,
or in every girl.
Like my cousin Amanda,
she's just bulimic.
We read about the Salem Witch
Trials in, like, fifth grade.
Guess I should have paid
more attention.
Hang her!
Drown her! Burn her!
Mercy Osbourne,
you have been sentenced
to death.
May God have mercy
on your wretched soul.
Those girls weren't
even witches.
The real witches were cunning
and careful not to be caught.
In fact after that, they got
the hell out of Dodge.
They fled.
As far South as they could.
That's how eventually New
Orleans became the new Salem.
There's a school there.
A boarding school
for girls like you.
You'll be safe.
You're sending me away?
I'm sorry, baby.
We can't keep you here anymore.
It's too dangerous.
What's going on?
Mom, what's going on?
What is this?
Mom! Mom...
No, what is this?!
Mom...
Mom!
We'll handle it from here.
Can't I drive her
to the station?
She's our daughter now, Nora.
You've done all you can.
A long good-bye would
only make things worse.
By the way, these drapes.
I'm just mad for tartan.
Hello?
O dark father,
we offer this flesh up to you,
blood, life, and all.
Get the hell off me!
Jesus,
Sabrina, relax.
We're just messing with you.
Holy shit. Are you...
Madison Montgomery, movie star.
Shit. When's the last time
you made a movie, girl?
I'm Nan. Hi.
Zoe.
Queenie.
So bored now.
So, is this all of you?
At the moment.
Cordelia Foxx, headmistress.
All right, girls,
there's a van full
of groceries in the driveway
that needs unloading.
I'll show Zoe to her room.
Then we meet
for Midday Gathering.
Let's go.
Miss Robichaux's Academy
for Exceptional Young Ladies
was established as a premiere
girls' finishing school
in 1790.
During the Civil War,
it was converted
into a military hospital.
Afterwards, it came under
new management. Our management.
In 1868, Marianne Wharton,
a prominent
East Coast society matron,
early suffragette,
author of several popular
children's books--
and, as it happened,
the reigning Supreme
of that time--
purchased this facility,
retaining the name as a cover,
establishing a safe haven
where young witches
could gather to learn.
In its heyday,
the academy was home
to as many as 60 girls.
Over the years,
those numbers dwindled.
Why?
We're a dying breed, Zoe.
Many of the families who knew
they carried the bloodline
made a choice not to reproduce.
So, what's a Supreme?
An average witch is born
with a few natural gifts.
But in each generation
there is one woman
who embodies countless gifts.
Some say...
all of them.
She is the Supreme.
Are you the Supreme?
No.
I'm like you.
Just a witch.
And a teacher. I'm here to help
you identify your gifts
and teach you how
to control them.
She means to suppress them.
Not suppression.
Control.
She thinks it's still
the 1600s.
No. Back then,
our kind understood the dangers.
Today, so many families know
nothing of their ancestry.
Too many girls aren't
lucky enough to have found us
or weren't identified in time
for us to have found them.
Like that poor Cajun girl
just outside Lafayette
a few months back.
Misty Day.
She wasn't much older
than any of you.
And she had a gift,
the power of resurgence.
Misty could reach
into that place
between life and death
and draw a soul back
from the precipice,
back to this side,
back to life.
It's dark magic!
To some, this appeared to be
the God-touched power
of resurrection.
To cast you in
to darkness and sin!
To others, necromancy.
To cast you
into separation from God!
So what happened to her?
The same thing that's happened
to women like us
throughout the centuries.
Let me go!
It's you that will end
in flames.
I swear it!
We are under siege, ladies.
Our lives,
our very existence
is always at risk.
Know this or face extinction.
This is Allegra.
She is the equivalent of
a human female in her late 80s.
Allegra suffers
from acute bradycardia,
her kidneys are failing,
she's lost the ability
to swallow.
Allegra, in short, is dying.
Now, several hours
after this video was taken,
we injected Allegra
with our Serum RM47.
We expanded on the University
of Wisconsin studies
on induced pluripotent
stem cells.
Meet Allegra today.
I'll have what she's having.
And you will.
Sooner than you'd think.
We should be ready for
human trials in two years' time.
This afternoon.
Preferably
in the next half hour.
I have a dinner engagement.
I'm sorry, but, uh...
well, that's impossible.
I hear you like to get...
sauced
at biochemistry conventions
and brag about how you're gonna
win the Nobel Prize
for the work you're doing here,
research that has been
entirely funded
by my late husband's money.
I have made you rich,
soon to be famous.
I want that medicine.
I paid for it, and I want it.
Now.
You can't smoke in here.
Fiona...
you are a very beautiful woman.
But if you're just looking
for something cosmetic,
I can recommend
a plastic surgeon.
What I need...
is an infusion of vitality.
Of youth.
I want that drug, David,
and I want it now.
Even if I wanted to give it
to you, I couldn't.
What we do here is not magic.
I'm sorry.
Last night,
communities across the county
held candlelight vigils praying
for Misty's safe return.
However, sources close
to the family have declined
to comment on the fact
that authorities now believe
they have found the last known
location of the missing girl.
It is rumored that Misty Day
may have been burned
at the stake,
though no official statement
was released.
You made me leave my daughters'
violin recital early.
You've been
injecting me with your
shitor five days now
and nothing...
nothing has changed.
How do I know you're not
just shooting me up with some
sugar water?
I have risked my career
giving you these drugs.
They could kill you.
I could go to jail.
Double the dosage.
Pull our funding.
Give me more!
We are organic matter.
We are animals. We rot,
we die!
I will tender my resignation
in the morning.
No!
What is this?
How are you doing this?
Get away from...
get away from me!
No.
Please.
My children.
Don't be such a baby.
Hey, Jeeves. Can I get
some iceberg lettuce
with a side of blue cheese?
Girl, be nice to Spalding.
Poor bastard ain't got no tongue.
Is that true, Jeeves?
Did you use your tongue
for something wicked?
Or maybe you just suck
at going down.
Oh, come on, Jeeves.
Show us your stub!
Maybe we can put it to use!
So, new girl...
...what are you in for?
Her boyfriend.
Nan, shut up before you get
your ass in trouble.
Did you kill him?
No. It was an accident.
It was an accident, Zoe.
And you will find love again.
A strange and unexpected...
love.
Girl,
are you deaf or just stupid?
Tell us
about this accident.
And don't spare
all the gory details.
So, why are you here?
My agent staged an intervention.
Ever since my drunk and
disorderly, I get blamed
for all kinds of shit
that I didn't do.
But you did it.
You killed the man.
I get it, bitch,
you're clairvoyant.
Do you want to know
what happened?
Hi, boys. So glad
you all could come.
Gee, is it hot in here?
Cut, cut.
You're still not hitting your mark.
I'm using the space.
That's a light.
If you don't hit your mark,
that light can't hit you.
The light hit him just fine.
All he said was
"hit your mark."
Why don't you just
do the world a favor
and take an acting class,
you D-list,
Botox bimbo.
Ow!
Stop it, you bitch!
Stop what? I don't feel nothing.
I'm a human voodoo doll.
You like this?
Stop!
You're... you're gonna get
in trouble.
Queenie, stop!
I'll do it.
Come on.
Let's take a walk.
A walk?
Fine. I'm not hungry
anyway.
Like anyone believes that.
Well,
that was disturbing.
Given the choices around here,
it looks
like you're my new best friend.
Do you own any clothes that
don't come from the Gap?
Not really.
Why?
You can borrow something
of mine.
Frat party tonight.
Just got the tweet.
Ooh!
You dropped your cocktail.
I thought you were
in Switzerland.
L.A.
It's tragic. The
glamour's gone.
They put a shopping mall
on Sunset and Vine.
I don't have a broom.
That's ironic.
Los Angeles?
Why do you look so jet-lagged?
I happen to look wonderful.
Let me make you something.
It's a restorative
I've been experimenting with.
This will fix you right up.
Delia, with her
potions and powders.
You know, one of my greatest
disappointments in life
is that you never
fully realized
the extent of your power.
I've done pretty well.
You are the only child
of the Supreme.
You have royal blood running in
your veins.
You could be ruling the world.
I like my little kingdom here,
thank you.
Yeah, well, your little kingdom
is a mess.
No! Oh...
You bitch.
It wouldn't have killed you.
Just put me in a coma
for a couple days?
Or weeks. Look, why don't
you just go away?
I don't want you here. How else
do you want me to say it?
You're still angry. I can tell.
My God, you are the Supreme.
I was just on this...
wonderful spiritual retreat
with Shirley
MacLaine in Sedona.
It was all about forgiveness.
You dumped me here.
You were sent
to an elite boarding school.
Boo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
You know, I've often thought
that my big mistake with you
was waiting so long
before sending you away.
Enough.
Show yourself out.
No. I'm not going.
I'm staying.
I'm here to help you.
Do you know that not
50 miles from here
a young woman was
burned at the stake?
It's Salem all over again.
There is a storm coming.
And you are leaving
these poor girls
under your charge
completely unprepared for it.
I am aware of what's happening.
My entire teaching philosophy...
Has been an abject failure.
You teach them to cower.
And to hide in the shadows.
Well, there are no
shadows, not anymore.
Do you really think
with Twitter and Facebook
that a witch does
anything at all
she won't be videotaped
and turned into some...
viral freak show like a dog
who says "I love you"?
No, no, no.
This is my life.
You can't come in here
and piss all over it.
I will call the council.
Do.
Call the council.
And then you can explain to them
why you think it's a bad idea
for the Supreme to teach them.
When are you gonna die
and stop ruining my life?
I'm here.
I'm staying.
So why don't
we make the best of it?
Okay, animals, all
right, let's listen up, okay?
All right, we're gonna go over
a few ground rules, gents.
The no puke rule will be
strictly enforced.
I will not be drinking...
too much tonight,
so if I see any of you are
in danger of hurling in public,
I will send you back here
to the penalty box.
That also goes...
for public urination
and public exposure.
Believe me, Dalton, nobody's
interested in seeing your dick,
no matter how small it is!
Now, we're still on probation
for the slightly
misguided Blue Mooning episode,
and those pricks at the
administration are just looking
for a reason
to cut our balls off, guys.
So I will sacrifice one night
of a drunken stupor
so my brothers can live to party
another day!
The administration
can suck my cock!
Yeah!
One, two, one, two, three!
We are KLG!
Oh, my God,
that's Madison Montgomery.
Now, that's what
I'm talking about.
That's prize tuna right there.
She's way out of your league.
What's a girl got to do
to get a drink around here?
Come with me.
Can't get a bite
if you don't dangle
your bait in the water.
Thought you looked thirsty.
Is that your superpower?
You can sense dehydration?
One of them.
Ah.
Frat boy, right?
I think frats are
full of fascists.
I don't mind being reduced
to a stereotype, but...
I'm on a scholarship.
My mom lives down in
the Ninth Ward. Besides,
didn't you come here with
a movie star?
You want to be my slave tonight?
What's in it for me?
Are you stupid?
Slaves get nothing.
Now why don't you get me
another drink?
It's on.
Really? A finishing school?
Miss Robichaux's Academy
for Exceptional Young Ladies.
Wow.
I don't want to talk
about me anymore, okay?
You're the first hot girl
I ever met
who didn't want
to talk about herself.
There's got to be something
wrong with you.
I know. You have a boyfriend.
No, I don't.
Kyle, I like you.
But it's not gonna work out.
Have you seen Madison?
Hey, I can't find her anywhere.
What, you think she ditched you?
I'll look around upstairs.
Hang on.
Brush her hair back
so I can see her face.
What the hell are you doing?!
Get off her!
Wait your turn, man.
Are you out of your mind?!
Madison?
Shit!
Hey.
Madison, hey. Hey,
did they give you something?
Whoa, whoa.
It hurts.
Okay, look, stay here, okay?
I'm not gonna...
I'm not gonna
let 'em get away with this.
Give me the phone, Brener.
Eat shit, Kyle.
Give me the phone, Brener. That's evidence.
I'm calling the cops.
Hey, hey.
What's going on back there?
Get him off the bus.
Come on, man.
Stop. Stop.
All right, everybody shut up!
First thing, delete the
videos from your phones.
We stick together.
Stop!
The Louisiana campus
is still in shock over
the tragic bus crash last night.
Nine members of the fraternity
Kappa Lambda Gamma
were on board.
Seven of the boys died
on the scene.
Two were rushed to Troost
Medical Center where they remain
in critical condition.
Officials
will not confirm the identities
of the deceased.
Hey, I was watching that!
Why? It's yesterday's news.
They got any Greek yogurt?
We have to tell
somebody what happened.
The one I met-- Kyle--
Madison, he tried to stop it.
Shh.
Okay, and he was on that bus.
What are we talking
about? The college boys?
Taken in the prime
of their lives.
Such a tragedy.
Almost makes you want to cry,
doesn't it?
But, then, the world's not
gonna miss a bunch of assholes
in Ed Hardy T-shirts.
Who are you?
You know, I've got
to hand it to you.
A bus flip? That's not easy.
But you were a sloppy,
little witch bitch.
Go to hell, you stupid hag.
Say that.
Now, I've read all your files.
And you're never gonna become
great women of our clan
sitting around here at Hogwarts
under the confused instruction
of my daughter.
We're going on a field trip.
Jesus. Go change your clothes.
Wear something...
...black.
Where are we going?
It's too hot.
My freaking vagina is sweating.
To Popp Fountain.
A kind of holy place
for our order.
Back in the 1970s,
Mary Oneida Toups led
an alternative coven down here.
She and her sister witches
would gather there,
proudly and publicly,
very much in the spirit
of the times.
But it was damaged
during Katrina.
And the authorities used
this as an excuse to declare
this sacred space
a safety hazard.
- It's been closed off ever since.
- I don't
understand. What are we supposed
to do if we can't get in?
Tear the wall down.
When witches don't fight,
we burn.
This is seriously
the worst field trip ever.
Each one of you
has a unique gift, but
that's not nearly enough
to be a real witch.
And you're a real witch?
She's the Supreme.
You know that one--
she's smarter than all
of you put together.
Help me.
- Help me.
- The New Orleans Preservation
Foundation is proud to present
the haunted home tour
of the notorious
Madame LaLaurie.
This very house,
the center of New
Orleans high society,
was also a place of
abject horror.
You want me to get her?
No.
Oh, excuse me. You can't just
barge in on the tour
without purchasing a ticket.
You're giving us
a tour for free.
For free. Of course.
The Code Noir,
a decree that dictated
the conditions of slavery,
did not exist on these grounds.
It was replaced by
the Madame's own code of terror.
And the torture she inflicted
on her slaves would spawn
179 years of hauntings.
Wasn't this house owned
by the guy in Face Off?
Correct, the actor Nicolas
Cage was a previous owner.
Madame LaLaurie was
infamous for her vanity.
She fought the rigors
of age with a sacrament
of expensive creams from Europe
and something else
far more exotic.
Oh, I'm running out.
We gonna have to get some more.
No! Please
don't make me.
You think I want
to do this?!
You can blame your father
and his fresh-faced whore.
Unless you'd like to
split your inheritance
with an endless parade
of colored bastards.
The secret ingredient
to the Madame's beauty ritual
was a poultice made
from human pancreas.
This is the infamous chamber
of horrors.
No flash photography, please.
The attic where Madame LaLaurie
inflicted heinous torture
upon her slaves.
And where she ultimately met
her own demise.
Get off my property!
I've heard that you are
in need of my services.
What could a Negress have
that I would ever want?
Mo pélé Marie Laveau.
I have the cure
for your husband's affliction.
His compulsion for young ladies.
I'll have you flogged
for your insolence!
A love potion
to ensure fidelity.
If the potion entrances as you
promise, your future's assured.
To our future together.
Salud.
Mmm.
It's like honeysuckle.
Oh.
Ooh.
Ooh, yes.
Oh, no.
Oh, God!
What did...?
Get it...
Get it out of me.
Unbeknownst to Madame
LaLaurie, a slave she had brutally
mutilated was
Marie Laveau's lover,
and she came
to exact her revenge.
Mo Cher,
what has she done to you?
The potion inflicted
its cruel justice, and she got
what she richly deserved.
But her body was never found.
To this day, no one knows
the final resting place
of Madame LaLaurie.
What do you hear?
The lady of the house.
Please. Please let it be him,
please.
It should have been you,
asshole!
It's the second door
on your left down the hall.
Make sure you stack
'em vertically.
I'm responsible for those girls.
What if something had happened?
Well, nothing did.
Where's Zoe Benson?
How would I know that?
Oh, that's my taxi.
Here, darling.
Make sure you tip them
generously when they're done.
Where are you going?
Out. Don't wait up.
I have half a mind to enchant
the locks after you leave.
Don't make me drop a house on you.
When the levees broke,
the people
of New Orleans were tested.
Those who stayed,
stayed for a reason.
With that came a sense
of purpose and community.
That's what happens
in a crisis.
All the bullshit falls away,
and what's left is just
so raw and vulnerable.
It's agony to let
people see you so exposed.
It takes a huge amount
of trust,
and for most of us, that trust
was shattered long ago.
But, like it or not,
we need each other.
And we need each other
desperately.
My mother was right.
The world isn't safe
for a girl like me.
But maybe I'm not safe
for the world, either.
And since I'll never be able
to experience real love,
might as well
put this curse to some use.
Excellent work, gentlemen.
Just set it down right here.
Well, I'd thank you,
but you're never gonna
remember any of this anyhow.
Come on, Mary Todd Lincoln.
I'll buy you a drink.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player