Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Oh. Morning.
Here.
Coffee?
Yeah, with a little
milk and sugar.
My daddy let me try it
on my first hunting trip.
You get a little older,
we'll add a little hooch
in there.
That'll really keep us warm.
Hey.
There's nothing
to be nervous about.
Hank...
Keep your hands steady.
Just like we practiced
on the range.
I just...
I don't want to miss.
Well, then, you won't.
I was the same way
when I was your age.
Worse even.
I couldn't keep
my breakfast down.
Ruined my shirt.
Damn near ruined everything.
Here you go.
We've been hunters
for generations.
You'll be fine, son.
Yes.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
You stay here.
I'll flush her out
through the brush.
You be ready.
You'll get a clean shot.
Put her down!
Please.
No!
Put her down.
No! Please!
Do it! Put her down!
Put her down!
Do it!
I'm sorry.
I'm-I'm sorry.
No mercy.
Never forget what they are.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Delores Davis,
when is the last time
I had your head in my chair?
We need to talk.
You and I ain't got nothing
to say to each other.
Take your skinny ass and
that filthy thing and get out.
You don't want to
talk to me? Fine.
Then give what's in
this box a wash and set.
Trina!
Get Mrs. Davis started
for me, will you?
I won't be long.
Jesus Christ.
This better be good.
I got six more heads
waiting for me
up front. That one
you can keep.
What makes you think I want it?
You the one dug it up.
For information, that was all.
Then why'd you keep her around?
She amused me.
Hmm... You thought you could
use her as a bargaining chip.
What did she say? I can't hear!
You shut up!
I came here to talk terms.
Terms?
You think it's so easy.
Stroll in here and expect
we gonna fix this truce?
Oh, to hell with the truce.
What I'm looking for
is an alliance.
Your tribe, my coven, joined.
Are you insane?!
Uh! What the head said.
I told you to shut up!
You can't make a deal
with a darkie!
You can't trust 'em
as far as you can spit.
Like I told the governor. I...
Shut up!
Now, we need to stop
this petty quarreling.
We've got bigger problems
than what goes on between us.
Last night, outside
our academy...
witch hunters.
- How many dead?
- None dead.
They missed.
Hmm. Too bad.
This concerns you
and your people
as much as it does mine.
Don't concern me a bit.
Witch hunters
is white women's worry.
You're making a mistake.
I can live with that.
Not too sure about you, though.
That's good work, that wig.
But it's a wig.
What kind of cancer you got?
Shit.
Come down here
'cause you're weak.
Can't protect your own, and
expect me to do it for you.
You're kidding yourself
if you think
that after they're done with us
they're not coming after you.
I'll fret about that
when the time come.
Right after I pop
the champagne.
Queenie?
Take this filthy thing
out back and burn it.
I don't ever want
to see it again.
You, neither.
Sweet release!
At long last!
Goddamn it!
Could people please
not move things?!
Some of us are blind!
Here it is, Delia.
Let me help you.
Let me do it!
It's my mess!
Delia, there's a...
I need to say something,
or I'll simply explode.
I need to know for certain
that you don't think
I did this to you.
I remember the first day
Fiona dropped you off here.
You were like a baby bird,
pushed too soon from the nest.
Do you remember
what you asked me?
Will you be my mother now?
I've always loved you
like a daughter.
Wrap your arms around me,
dear girl.
Use your power of sight,
and you'll see that I could not
have done this terrible thing.
No. I won't.
I don't need magic to tell me
what I already know.
I know you would never hurt me.
I never doubted you
for a second,
and I told my mother that.
My mother set you up.
My blindness gave me
real vision,
but it's of no use to me now.
Not when there are witch hunters
right outside our door.
Darling...
if I could pluck my own eyes
out of my head
and gift them to you, I would.
I know.
Hank.
David.
Good to see you.
I thought you were in Europe.
We had a flare-up with the
Cromwell Coven in North Hampton.
Nothing a few silver bullets
couldn't take care of.
Oh. Corporation
keeps you busy,
now that he's made you
the official right hand.
I know you were hoping
to be named,
- but your father has other plans
for you, Hank. - Right.
Am I still in the will?
You'll always be his son.
Come on.
He's ready for you.
Hello, Father.
Coffee?
No, thanks.
Never acquired a taste for it.
Well, I'll get right to it.
We're not happy with your
progress in New Orleans.
David tells me you're
no longer living at the academy.
A lot of things have happened.
Some of them out of my control.
Allying yourself with
Marie Laveau, the Voodoo Queen,
that was out of your control?
I took some initiative.
I had a plan to bring
them both down.
The Witches and the Voodoos.
You don't take initiative, Hank.
You follow orders.
Your only job is to
gather intelligence.
You don't get your hands dirty.
You're the man on the inside.
That's why you're married
to Cordelia Goode.
Yes, Father,
I-I just thought that...
Don't think.
You'll just end up
getting somebody killed.
I thought that was the point.
I'm much more capable
than you think.
You're referring
to the firestarter
you terminated in Baton Rouge?
I found the witch, killed her,
then got rid of the body.
In a hotel room!
You used a credit card!
It could have been traced
to The Corporation.
I had to send David down there
to clean up after you.
An innocent desk clerk and
a maid lost their lives...
because you were sloppy.
Hank... you need
to understand,
your father's not only the
head of The Corporation,
he's the CEO of a major
financial institution.
The liberals in Washington are
just looking for an excuse
to sic the FEC
on companies like Delphi.
Your recklessness
puts everything
we've worked for at risk.
I thought we were
still Witch Hunters.
The hunt isn't only
about the kill.
A good hunter stalks his prey
with care,
and only strikes when
the time is right.
We need you back
inside that house.
That may be a problem.
Somebody blinded Cordelia,
a-an unknown attacker
threw acid in her face.
Not unknown.
We authorized that.
We wanted to make sure
she needed you.
You disfigured my wife?
Your wife?
Tell me you don't actually
have feelings for her.
Tell me, son!
You haven't forgotten
what she is.
What you are?
I'm part of a Sacred Order.
A soldier in a shadow war.
A war that has been raging
since before the time of Salem.
We are a Brotherhood
pledged in blood,
dedicated to stamping out
the pestilence of witchery
on the North American continent.
Don't think I don't appreciate
the sacrifices you've made.
I know how confusing it can be
to pretend to love someone
who is your enemy.
But you can never
lose yourself to the lie.
'Cause someday...
she will have to be put down.
What a marvelous invention.
So clever.
So, before we move on
to our lobster poché beurre,
a little melon ball
palate cleanser.
Remember back
in the day, Pembie?
We'd always be served
a palate cleanser
at Sunday supper.
Such a sensible tradition.
Nobody bothers anymore.
Now, Myrtle,
Pembie and I were just saying
in addition to
how thrilling it was
to get your phone call,
we-we...
I've... we've...
just had such terrible regrets
about the whole
misunderstanding.
And we...
cannot get over your skin.
Ah.
No burn scars.
You look younger than ever.
We-we've got
to hear all about
this Misty Day
and her magical mud.
Should we be looking into it?
Selling it, perhaps?
Oh! My God...
You miss the point, darling.
The swamp mud is a metaphor,
her metaphor.
She's a sophisticated witch
with extraordinary gifts,
hiding out as
a hippie swamp rat.
From humble
hillbilly stock,
she's been a witch since birth,
her power and humanity
separating her from
everyone around her.
In fact, those around her
have tried endlessly
to destroy her,
in order to mask
their own evil purposes.
Yet she rose from the ashes,
stronger than ever,
more fully realized.
A living testament
to the greater ideals
of our coven.
Power, compassion,
and uniqueness.
We are lucky to have
found her, and she us.
It resonates with
my own story, doesn't it?
Myrtle, I want to toast you
for your spirit
of... f...
...give...
Forgiveness, you say?
Forgiveness is,
and always will be,
the high road...
...the preferred road.
Would that we had such luxury.
Oh... Quentin.
Not to worry.
It's just a bit of monkshood
in your balls.
Causes temporary paralysis.
"Human Statue Syndrome,"
we call it.
I believe it's
the nervous system first.
You lose control
over your limbs,
the muscles harden into cement,
and it feels like
ice in your veins.
Then the respiratory system.
Or is it the other way around?
Well, no matter.
It's supposed to be
quite terrifying. Is it?
Are you terrified?
You should be.
At any rate,
I'm not going to kill you.
Well, maybe after dessert.
I put a lot of effort
into the key lime pie.
I do love a key lime pie,
even more than
a ile flottante...
call me a Philistine!
Enough chit-chat.
You've both wanted
to eliminate me for years,
so you could dominate
the Council.
But I was never worried
you'd be hapless enough to try.
Quentin!
You're a fatuous fool
and a drunk!
Pembie, you're even worse.
You're weak-willed,
boring, and your
fashion faux pas
give me nightmares.
I invited you here
not to chastise you
or exact revenge,
but to help out the coven.
To help out my beloved Cordelia.
I bet you thought,
"Oh, she left
the melon baller in there.
She's growing old
and forgetful."
I had a Turkish Angora cat
who was born with one brown eye
and one blue.
She was absolutely gorgeous.
Oh, my God...
I can see.
I know you had
the best of intentions,
but you could've
asked me first.
Delia, does one ask
a drowning man
before throwing him
a life preserver?
Who let this charcoal
briquette back in?
Oh, sweet Jesus.
He gets no credit.
It was I who restored
our beloved Cordelia.
You're not witch enough
to pull off something
this delicate.
Oh, but you're wrong.
I'm more witch now
than I ever was,
and I've got you
to thank, Fiona.
Being burned at the stake
was an empowering
experience.
There are secrets
in the flames,
and I came back with
more than a few.
You couldn't find
two that matched?
Why do they look so familiar?
The generous donors wish
to remain anonymous.
Well, if she gave
you two new eyes,
it's out of guilt
for having blinded you.
Hurl your baseless accusations.
They have no power now.
You could still end up
in an ashtray, you know.
You're the one that should
be put to the stake.
You murdered
Madison Montgomery.
Well, that's going to be
a hard one to stick, Myrtle.
The girl's not dead.
Not anymore,
and no thanks to you.
You were the one
found guilty of a capital crime.
I don't care if you
did survive the stake.
I could have you banished.
Permanent exile.
You know what
that means, Myrtle--
Paramus, New Jersey--
toxic waste...
outlet malls...
You wouldn't dare.
Ha.
I could call
an emergency meeting
of the Council right now.
Good.
Call the Council.
Good luck.
I hear they're not
seeing anyone right now.
Stop it! Stop it!
Right now.
Like it or not,
Fiona is your Supreme,
and you need to start
treating her like one.
And you...
You need to stop
accusing Auntie Myrtle.
We both know she's not
the one who blinded me.
The real danger
is outside these doors,
not inside.
I'm tired. I need to lie down.
When the girls get in,
make sure they
stay in.
It's dangerous out there.
Of course, baby bird.
You go rest your new eyes.
We'll see to
absolutely everything.
Wait...
Hug me again.
Of course I will,
my darling girl.
Nothing.
My visions...
They're gone.
You can't smoke
in here, Madison.
Why don't you go tell someone?
Ugh, sick people
really gross me out.
We've been looking everywhere for you.
Nan, it's time to go.
Cordelia wants us all
back at the house.
I need to see Luke.
You haven't seen him yet?
You've been here
since last night.
His mother won't let me.
That's bullshit.
Luke?
Who said you could
come in here?! Get out
before I call security!
She just wants so see him.
Absolutely not.
It's your fault
my son is in a coma!
You brought this darkness
into my home!
Luke says, "Calm down.
"Don't have a fit.
Like at the lake last summer?"
When did he tell you that?
Now.
You're a liar... or a lunatic.
No, bitch, she's clairvoyant.
"Regard not them that have
familiar spirits who consort
with demons to be
defiled by them."
Nan's not
talking to a demon.
She's talking to your son.
I don't believe it!
You're mocking my grief.
Not your grief.
Maybe the outfit.
God works
in mysterious ways, Joanie.
Roll with it.
He likes that song.
The one that
you sang to him before.
That proves you're a fraud.
I didn't sing.
I read to him from Deuteronomy.
When I was eight...
When he was eight...
when I broke my arm...
when he broke his arm...
"A Closer Walk"?
How can you know that?
We told you,
she's a mind reader.
We're witches.
Haven't you figured
that out by now?
Come on, Nan.
She doesn't deserve your help.
♪ I am weak...
♪ But Thou art strong
♪ Jesus, keep me
from all wrong ♪
♪ I'll be satisfied
as long as I walk ♪
♪ Let me walk close to Thee
♪ Just a closer walk
with Thee ♪
♪ Grant it, Jesus, is my plea
♪ Daily walking close to Thee ♪
♪ Let it be
♪ Dear Lord, let it be
♪ When... my feeble
life is o'er ♪
♪ Time for me will be no more ♪
♪ Guide me safely,
gently o'er ♪
♪ To Thy kingdom's shore,
to Thy shore. ♪
Ooh, hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo.
You bring nibbles?
I'm starving.
Girl, you ain't got no stomach.
What are you gonna do,
chew it and shit it
out of your neck?
Time for some sensitivity
training.
What fresh hell is this?
Roots: The Saga
of an American Family.
You are gonna watch
all eight hours of it,
followed by the sequel ,
Roots: The Next Generation.
Why don't you just throw my head
in that fire pit?
I wanna die!
I'm ready.
Believe me, I'd love
nothing more than to melt
your ugly face
right off your skull,
but you are ignorant.
And you're not leaving
this earth
until I educate you about those
people you tortured: my people.
We're gonna have ourselves
a little film festival.
You're gonna watch Mandingo,
The Color Purple,
and then my personal favorite--
BAPS,
starring Miss Halle Berry.
But first, based on
the best-selling novel
by the great black writer
Alex Haley--
one family's epic story,
from slavery to freedom--
Oh, God...
Roots.
No, no, no,
not that jungle music.
Enjoy.
No, wait a minute!
No, no, no, turn it down!
Oh, Lord! Oh, no!
♪ Oh... I wish I was
in the land of cotton ♪
♪ Old times there
are not forgotten ♪
♪ Look away! Look away!
♪ Look away, Dixieland...
Marie Laveau sends her regards.
What's happening to me?!
You're feeling the wrath
of broken promises.
Where are the heads
of the white witches?
I'm trying!
They die tonight
or the next needle I use
will put a hole in your heart.
You understand me?
I understand.
♪ Temptation falls
in your path ♪
♪ No hesitation,
"Why?" you ask ♪
I didn't know bay leaves
had magic in them.
They provide protection.
Asafetida...
banishes evil.
Oh, wow,
that's some stinky shit.
Now, you never use this
unless under
extreme circumstances.
Looking good.
♪ Kind of woman
that loves you... ♪
Hey, can I try the
incantation this time?
Go for it.
Bagahi laca bachahe.
Lamac cahi achabahe.
Karrrelyos.
Stronger intent.
Lamac lamec bachalyos.
Cabahagi sabalyos Baryols.
Damn! That is so cool!
We make a great team.
Now we need to make
some more of this...
for everyone.
Go get some more
of that mud back there.
♪ In heaven... kind of woman
that'll haunt you ♪
You're such an awesome leader,
Miss Cordelia.
I've got so much
to learn from you.
Fiona is the leader
of this coven.
♪ Is to be in heaven
♪ I know, I know...
Hey.
Well, shit.
I meant to change the locks.
You have your sight back?
Oh... oh, my God.
Did Fiona do this?
Let go of me.
I said let go.
You're drunk.
Yeah, I needed the courage
to come back.
Hey, hey...
what do your eyes see?
Can you see my heart?
Can you see it's bleeding?
That I'm living in a hell
of regret
and remorse?
My life has no meaning
without you.
What will it take, Delia?
More than you've got.
Who's this?
Hey. I'm Misty.
Can we have this conversation
alone, please?
Don't leave, Misty.
She and I have much bigger
concerns than this conversation.
I've told you how I feel.
Take your stuff and leave.
No, I'm not going anywhere.
I'm your husband!
This is my home!
Not anymore.
I've spoken to a lawyer.
I'm filing for divorce.
That's bullshit!
You got to listen to me.
All I want is to protect you.
I know you don't believe it,
but that's all
I've ever wanted to do.
Your shit's in a box
in the closet.
Get it, and then get out.
Endora, heel.
Good girl.
You got a dog?
Well, one dog moves out,
another moves in.
You know, it's
the cycle of life.
But you hate animals...
and all other living things.
Well, that's true,
but we needed some protection
around here.
I know that.
Why do you think I came back?
You?
Protect? Really?
You know why I got
a female attack dog?
Because bitches stick together?
Because females are more loyal
and aggressive
when it comes to protecting
their families.
Good to see you, Hank.
What is it, girl?
What's in there?
It's another goddamned boy.
Jesus, these girls.
Dog...
You have to leave now.
Come on. Come on.
You're a miracle, Nan.
I'm not certain
I know how to thank you.
I'm sure this isn't enough.
But in truth,
nothing could ever be enough.
You've given me a gift
that can never be repaid.
I confess I had dark moments.
The thought of losing my son
shook me to the core.
I questioned my faith
in the Almighty.
But you have given me
a ray of hope.
Luke says there is a God.
And that he's judging you.
For my lapses of faith?
For what you did to his father.
His father?!
God says my father's death
was no accident.
Why does he say that?
Dennis died
of anaphylactic shock.
God knows all.
He's shown me the truth.
Joan, I've said
all I have to say.
I can't accept that.
Well, you'll have to.
I want to be a good father.
I... I still want
to be in Luke's life.
But... we're done.
Maybe one day you'll understand.
God told me you put
the bees in the car.
You knew Dad
was allergic to bees.
You knew you'd
get away with it.
You killed him
because he was leaving you.
Dad was in love
with Mrs. Martone.
She was in your book club.
She wasn't younger or prettier.
She just loved him
for who he was.
And that was the last straw.
God says you're going to pay.
You don't speak for my son.
He's been in that bed fighting
for his life.
This has all been
some dark-sided trick.
You leave us alone.
Get out!
- My turn.
No, now it's your turn.
- Christ.
Gin.
Shit!
Would you like
to play another hand?
Yeah, you just keep dealing
till I win my money back.
And yours, too.
Kyle?
What did you do to him?
Well, since none of you girls
can play cards worth a damn,
I took the liberty
of sprucing up your boy.
- Just a touch.
- You mean you fixed him?
Well, I wouldn't go that far.
I mean, he's not all there,
but he's okay.
What we need
is a guard dog.
One who will attack on command.
Deal!
Yeah! Kept my eyes shut tight
the entire time, foul negress.
I didn't see a bit of it.
I'm not surprised.
You kept your eyes closed
your entire life.
Can't keep
your ears closed though.
Not without no hands
to cover them.
♪ Oh, freedom...
What is
that heinous caterwauling?
Something my grandma
used to listen to.
If this doesn't touch your soul,
you don't have one.
When will my perdition end?
When you learn something.
♪ And before I'd be
your slave... ♪
You're one stubborn
old lady head, you know.
I got to go.
♪ Buried in my grave
♪ Go home, my Lord
♪ And be free...
Okay, all right, love.
Now, what we gonna do?
Meet me at the wash bowl.
Queenie.
In my shop, when you early,
you on time.
And when you on time, you late.
Now, what you been
doing upstairs?
Watching TV.
Sit your ass down
and get yourself to work.
That phone ain't
gonna answer itself.
♪ And be free
♪ Oh
♪ Freedom
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh
♪ Freedom ♪
♪ Freedom
♪ Oh-oh, freedom. ♪
♪ Oh, freedom ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh, freedom
♪ Over me ♪
♪ Over me, yeah...
♪ And before I'd be a slave ♪
♪ Be a slave ♪
♪ I'll be buried in my grave ♪
♪ Buried in my own grave
♪ And go home ♪
♪ Home
♪ To my Lord and be free ♪
♪ Oh-oh, freedom
♪ Oh-oh-oh
♪ Freedom ♪
♪ Freedom
♪ Oh, freedom ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh, freedom
♪ Freedom ♪
♪ Over me ♪
♪ Over me, yeah
♪ And before I'd be a slave ♪
♪ Before I'd be a slave
♪ I'll be buried in my grave ♪
♪ Buried in my own grave
♪ And go home to my Lord ♪
♪ Home
♪ And be free ♪
♪ Oh-oh, freedom
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh-oh
♪ Freedom ♪
♪ Freedom
♪ Oh-oh, freedom ♪
♪ Oh, freedom
♪ Oh, freedom ♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh, freedom
♪ Over me ♪
♪ Over me, yeah
♪ And before I'd be a slave ♪
♪ Be a slave
♪ I'll be buried in my grave ♪
♪ Buried in my own grave
♪ And go home ♪
♪ Home
♪ To my Lord and be free ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ No more weeping
♪ No more weeping ♪
♪ No more weeping over me ♪
♪ No more weeping
♪ Over me
♪ And before
♪ And before I'd be a slave ♪
♪ I'll be buried
♪ I'll be buried in my grave ♪
♪ And go home to my Lord... ♪
You murdered Dad.
No.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Go back to sleep, baby.
Go back to sleep.
♪ I'll be buried in my grave ♪
♪ I'm going home
♪ And go home to my Lord ♪
♪ And be free. ♪
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player