Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
I'll be home around 4:00.
I need help
carving these pumpkins.
Who is that?
It's Marie Antoinette.
I'm doing a famous
French figures theme this year.
I'm hitting the gym.
Well, make sure
you wear a condom.
And pick me up some Gala apples.
I thought these Golden Delicious
would look dramatic
in the bobbing bucket; they just
look dull and depressing.
There's no contrast.
Why would I wear
a condom at the gym?
Maybe because you're screwing
that twink trainer of yours.
And I need gourds.
I'm going to hang them
on the tree out front,
spray-paint them,
and they're going to be these
clever little organic ghosts.
You know what? I am.
You are what?
Screwing my trainer.
You know what else?
He's a power bottom.
He loves it.
First of all, please
remember our agreement:
don't ask, don't tell.
Secondly, is this crass
admission supposed to...
hurt me?
At this point with you,
I'm bulletproof.
And I need some dry ice.
Have you picked out
a costume yet?
Why are you doing this?
Because there's gonna be
a party here in three days.
This is all bullshit,
this is all bullshit!
Everything we've become
is bullshit!
I don't give a shit
about carving pumpkins.
I want love,
I want passion, I want
a relationship with a man,
not Martha Stewart!
Then leave!
Oh, I forgot, you can't.
Because all of
your money and mine
is in this house that we agreed
to flip and make a mint on,
and now we can't because
the economy is in the shitter.
Do you think I like
carving 20 pumpkins
and getting squash guts
under my nails?
I am trying here!
I'm trying to make
this place warm
and inviting and spectacular
and have this Halloween party
shot by Elle friggin' Decor
so someone will see it and
swoop in and take this place
off our hands, and
then I can feel free
to fall in love with a 25-year
old who has great biceps.
So get off my back,
carve a goddamn pumpkin,
go get a goddamn
outfit and man up.
I can't believe
this is who we've become.
Halloqueens arguing
over pumpkins.
We wanted to have a baby.
We were going to have this...
great life.
(sighs)
Red is wrong.
It has to be green.
(laughs)
Funny.
It's good, actually.
It's very... scary, sexy.
Come help me with these bats.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for everything--
my attitude, my low sex drive.
It's probably low testosterone
from stress.
I'm seeing a doctor next week.
Did you get the apples?
(neck snaps)
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
This is unacceptable, Marcy.
One person has seen
the house in two weeks.
And she didn't even stay
for the whole tour
because she was
so spooked out by it.
You need to do something.
Don't put the blame on
Mame here, Mr. Harmon.
This house has an image problem,
it's as simple as that.
Fix that problem and this property
will sell real fast.
What are we supposed to do?
I think we need a fluffer here.
A what?
Fluffers.
People we can hire
to come in at a nominal fee
and give a dash of style
and élan to this place.
We have style.
Everybody thinks
they have style,
and everybody thinks
they're funny.
Most people aren't.
That's why in my business
we have fluffers.
They come in,
they rent some accessories,
karate chop a few throw pillows,
make this home look
like a magazine spread.
It's Halloween.
Imagine the mileage
you would get
if you could decorate
your front porch
with divine cheery pumpkins.
Lots of happy
trick-or-treaters
means parents who talk
to their friends,
means more looky-loos,
means better PR.
I heard you were egged
last night, Mr. Harmon.
(boys laughing)
Hey!
Happy Halloween, asshole!
Get out of here! Huh?
Little shit!
Why did you tell her that?
You know, on this one topic,
I agree with her.
We have an image problem.
We are on the murder house tour,
for God's sakes.
Marcy, do you know
any of these fluffers?
Can you get one
for us immediately?
Yes, a wonderful English
lady, a real pro,
but she's more expensive than
the young gay fellow I know.
Let's go with the gay fellow.
Gay fellow.
I'll call the fluffer.
Halloween comes from
the Celtic holiday of Samhain.
It commemorated the end
of the harvest festival.
They celebrated it
to ward off their fears.
The Celtic dudes believed that
on October 31,
the boundary separating the
realms of the living and dead
disappeared and the dead could
walk amongst the living.
That's why people dress up,
to scare away the ghosts.
No way I ever want
to be a ghost.
It's so sad.
What are you going to dress up
as this year, Addy?
(whispers)
Are you blushing?
(laughs)
Look at you.
You know what?
I think that's
a hell of a costume.
I tell you you could
eat all my chocolate chips?
I was gonna make cookies
out of those later,
but now someone's
gonna have to run down
to the Korean to get some more.
I'll go.
Get me a carton of Pall Malls.
I'll use the change
to fill up my bike, cool?
Hmm?
(whispers):
Bye.
(chuckles)
What do you think you're doing?
You know how to read.
You just like mooning over him.
You remember what
happened to the last one?
It wasn't like that.
He was just reading.
Oh, one minute he's reading,
the next minute his hand
is down your pants.
He smells better
than the last one.
What did you say?
Now, you listen to me
good, little girl.
I have given every inch
of my life to you
for the last 30 some years.
I would kill or die for you.
But I will not
share the affections of the men
I bring into this house
with any woman.
You understand?
Hmm?
What's this?
Halloween.
What did you tell him
you wanted to go dressed up as?
Hmm?
You and your boyfriend
keeping secrets now?
I want to go as her.
As a pretty girl.
(chuckles)
You can go as Snoopy again.
The costume will still fit
if you lay off
those chocolate chips.
Not Snoopy again.
You'll go as Snoopy
or not at all.
And when Travis comes back,
send him upstairs.
And no more of this.
The dead can walk freely
on Halloween.
(chuckles softly)
We've always known that.
(doorbell rings)
Trick or treat!
(laughs)
What are you doing here?
Um, trick or treat?
It's Halloweek.
I do the full seven days.
It's the only time I
can really be myself.
So, uh, just pop the thousand
dollars in the pumpkin here
and nobody will be the wiser.
Get off my property now.
Or what?
You'll call the cops?
You know what?
I just might.
I didn't do anything.
No? Well, that gazebo
in the backyard
sure went up pretty darn quick.
I have to wonder if you got
all the proper permits.
Maybe somebody should place a
call to the city's inspector
and have him come down
here and check it out.
What's under that gazebo
is what you did.
But what's inside
what's under that gazebo
is what you did.
That is not my baby in there.
Vivien finds that out,
your family is over.
(sputters)
Now... give
me my treat.
You don't want the trick.
I'm done talking.
I have a patient.
And I have patience.
But there is a limit.
BEN:
I've agreed to this meeting
because we need to clarify
a few things.
Firstly, the psychiatrist
that I recommended to you,
Dr. Goldman,
said you never showed up
for the first appointment
and you never called to cancel.
I don't want to see
anyone but you.
We've discussed
why that won't work.
Which brings me
to my next question.
We're very grateful
to you, Tate,
for how you helped my family.
But you need to explain
here and now
what you were doing
in this house
at the time of the break-in.
The truth is
I was just, like,
hanging around outside,
and I was, I was throwing
pebbles at her window.
But she blew me off.
And then I noticed that the door
was unlocked,
so I... went inside.
It's not cool, I know.
I understand.
But this is why
I can't treat you.
It's inappropriate
for everyone concerned.
I really need your help.
I don't want to be like this.
I want to be a good person.
And I know that
you can help me.
You're the one, okay?
You're the only one
that I can trust.
I cannot see you in this house.
(sobs softly)
Look, I have an opening.
I'll meet you someplace
for coffee, but you have
to promise me...
I promise you. Promise.
No more weird shit, okay?
This is your control panel.
It operates one of the 15 window
and door sensors.
You're also gonna get
this infrared motion detector.
It goes in your foyer.
This is your panic button.
Okay, I'm gonna hide one
of these in your nightstand,
probably put one in
the kitchen somewhere.
Now, if something
goes bump in the night,
you hit this button,
and I'm on my way, all right?
Now given what you've gone
through lately,
I'm expecting some false alarms,
so don't be shy.
All right, if you say so.
Oh, I do.
Questions?
I'm sure I have
a hundred questions, but
I can't think of anything
right now.
I mean, the system in
this house is so...
Ah, yeah, it's from
the Reagan era.
Yeah.
(both chuckle)
You know if your power goes out
or someone cuts
your phone line,
something like that...
Yeah, we would be in
so much trouble.
Yeah, exactly. Right.
Did Marcy bring these pumpkins?
Yes.
Oh, that's nice.
Thank you. I enjoy crafts.
Mrs. Harmon, a question.
Hmm?
May I have Halloween off?
I'd like to visit
with my mother.
Of course.
Done.
I'll put that one outside.
CHAD: Ugh!
The roses have whitefly.
Jesus, what an eyesore.
Hi.
Love the house,
so much potential.
Thank you.
Are you Marcy's fluffers?
I'm Chad Warwick.
This is my ball
and chain, Patrick.
Welcome.
This is actually kind of fun.
I never got to do this when I was a kid.
Why not?
So this is what you guys do
for a living.
That is amazing to me.
And wonderful, you know.
I think style is so important.
It's everything.
(snickers)
(scoffs)
It's so great that I get
to help you guys have
the best Halloween ever.
I love Halloween.
So does Patrick
because the bars are
just awash in twinks
with six packs in
revealing outfits.
Isn't that right, Pat?
The Abby, The O Bar, Rage.
That's where he was last year
instead of helping me
with the trick-or-treaters.
Have another drink, dear.
Crafting brings out
his inner George and Martha.
So, in addition
to Halloween night
and making everything look
inviting, which I get,
do you guys have any other
suggestions for what
we might do to the house
to make it sell faster?
Actually, yes.
That gazebo's got to go.
The lattice is wrong.
I agree.
Oh, no, we just put it in.
Did you put that gazebo in yourself, Ben?
Yes.
Well, let's get through
tomorrow night,
and then we can tear it down,
and put in an organic
cutting garden.
Ow! Shit!
Oh, my God!
Let me see.
I think I'm gonna need stitches.
No. No, it's okay.
I can fix this up.
Pat's an EMT.
Oh, I thought you were
a fluffer.
You're hilarious, Vivien.
And I love the hair color.
I can barely see any root.
It's my natural color.
Where's your first-aid kit?
Upstairs.
Look at that.
It's a work of art.
Thanks.
What are you doing?!
Come on, Ben, we're the same.
I can tell.
You play the role
of the dutiful househusband,
but you like having that cock
sucked often and well.
I can do that.
Four minutes. No one will know.
I'm not gay.
Neither was I until I got head
from a guy.
No.
Sorry. It's just...
been a long time for me.
Don't tell Chad, okay?
We're not doing well.
Your husband seems very...
Handsome?
Nervous.
I don't know.
It's just a feeling I get.
Um... darkness.
Seems like you and Pat are
having problems.
Yeah. He can't keep his dick in
his pants.
You caught him cheating?
Yes. I'm a sneak and a snoop.
How?
It's easy.
Cell phone records.
You can delete a text,
but you can't erase the bill.
Vivien, that bat is terrible.
Let me finish it.
(rustling)
(shrieks)
Trick or treat, smell my feet,
give me something good to eat.
Addy!
I want to be a pretty girl for Halloween.
You want what?
Make me a pretty girl
like you, Violet.
I'm actually not
very good at this.
I don't care.
I'll like it.
Close your eyes.
How old are you, Addy?
(a la Constance):
A lady never reveals her age.
Is Tate your boyfriend?
Wait. You know Tate?
I talk to him when he comes here
for his head shrinking.
He likes you, I can tell.
He thinks you're a pretty girl.
Are you a virgin?
Yes.
Aren't you?
Hell no.
You can't keep breaking
into our house, Addy.
But I like it here.
My friends are here.
Wow! Violet, I'm beautiful!
Goddamn it, come here!
Now, who did that to your face?!
Violet!
Violet, that girl's got
another cupcake coming.
Now wash that smut
off your face!
No! I wanna be a pretty girl!
Well, you're not a pretty girl
and you know it!
But I wanna be!
"Oh, put her in a home,"
they said. Even Daddy.
But no, I couldn't do that.
I don't want to be Snoopy!
I want to be a pretty girl!
Do you know what they think when
we walk down the street?!
"There but for the grace
of God go I."
You make them feel lucky.
And they think I'm a hero.
As though I've had some choice!
No, wait!
Tate?
You said she wanted
to meet at midnight.
Come out, come out
wherever you are.
(gasps)
(laughs)
You asshole!
I scared you.
No, you didn't.
Where'd you get this thing?
My dad threw it out.
Finders keepers.
Really?
I didn't scare you?
I said no.
I bet I can.
You have to put your fingers
on the other side.
I don't believe in that shit.
Charles is gonna answer
all your questions.
He used to live here.
Is Charles going to tell me
what happened to those assholes
that tried to kill us?
What'd you do to them?
I told you
I didn't do anything.
I had some help.
What's in this basement?
I want the truth.
What I'm about to tell you
might scare you...
to death.
I can take it.
Dr. Charles Montgomery built
this house.
And here in this basement
is where he worked.
Charles was a doctor
to the stars,
but he was also drug addict,
and his wife Nora wasn't gonna
let that get in the way
of her lifestyle.
So she set up a little secret
side business;
he would take care of
girls who didn't want
to be in trouble anymore.
This went on and on until one
day, one girl couldn't keep
the secret to herself,
and she told her boyfriend
what happened.
(ringing)
Montgomery residence.
Whoever this is it's past 10:00.
You shouldn't be calling
at this hour.
MAN:
An eye for an eye.
Who is this?
A tooth for a tooth.
I won't tolerate this nonsense
any longer unless...
(receiver clicks, dial tone)
Charles, I've just had the most
peculiar conversation.
Charles...?
Oh, my God...
Charles!
The boyfriend wanted revenge,
so he kidnapped Charles'
and Nora's baby.
Terrified, the Doctor
and his wife waited
for the ransom demands.
This is your fault, Charles.
(knocking)
What is the meaning of this?
Charles? What is it, Charles?
Madame, there's no need for you
to see this.
TATE: Driven insane by grief, the
doctor used all his experience
and surgical skills to try
and cheat death.
I want to bury our son in this.
Charles?
What are you doing?
What have you done
to our baby?!
(sobbing)
But what he created was ungodly,
and monstrous.
And even after their tragic end,
that "thing" remained,
down here, to this day.
Oh my God...
You are so full of shit.
I don't believe a word that
has come out of your mouth.
Forget it.
Forget I ever asked.
And I'm tired that
we keep hanging out
in this dark, dank place.
Why can't we go somewhere,
like on a real date?
All right.
Tomorrow night.
We'll go out.
(gasps softly)
Your father agreed
to see me again,
but I'm not supposed to be here.
Come on, I'll be your lookout.
Wow.
There's so many different
flavors, it's freaky.
I don't know half of them.
What did we say?
No eating until we
inspect 'em at home!
She reminds you of Violet,
doesn't she?
VIVIEN:
Violet?
BEN:
Wow...
Oh, I'm so scared!
You look amazing.
She had to be scary.
My fierce little girl.
Just like her mom.
Smart and beautiful...
no need to be like anyone else.
The thing is, I was a...
I was a troubled kid, too.
I was kinda like you, Tate.
I didn't hold out too
much hope for myself.
Not many other
people did, either.
It was a total shock to
everyone, including myself,
when I became a doctor.
But somehow I was given this...
amazing gift of family.
Hey, it's gonna be
okay, Dr. Harmon...
I'm sorry. Oh, God.
(sniffles)
I'm sorry, Tate.
CONSTANCE:
Addy? Addy?
Well, where's your costume?
I'm not trick-or-treating
this year. I'm too old.
It's Halloween! Everyone gets a
chance to be someone else,
let their hair down for awhile.
I thought you wanted to be
a pretty girl.
Hmm?
Ta-dah!
And now you don't have to worry
about makeup or anything like that.
Come on, let me see you smile.
Come on, little honeybear.
Let me see you smile.
(chuckling)
Okay? Let's go see if Mama's got
any clothes that'll fit you.
Come on.
Maybe one of my old
maternity dresses.
Have you seen my... my fangs?
Ah...
Fangs a lot!
Oh, come on, Viv, you're the
one who wanted to do this.
Can you at least try
to enjoy it?
How's Hayden?
What?
I swear to Christ, Ben.
I told you if you lied to me one
more time...
that we're done.
I can't do this.
Vivien...
Viv?
I read through the phone bills.
Her number is on there
20 times-- more.
Yeah. Because I don't answer.
And when she does get me, I tell
her not to call back.
Did you see her in Boston?
Vivien, no.
She keeps calling,
harassing me.
I told her I'd call the police
if she doesn't stop.
And did she?
Yeah.
She won't be calling back.
Well, she might, 'cause I left
her a message.
Well, I wouldn't expect
a call back.
I was pretty forceful.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you,
but...
after everything that happened,
after the-the break-in, I-I...
I didn't want to
add more stress.
Hey, you had
every right to react exactly
the way you did.
But believe me--
Hayden is over.
(cell phone rings)
It's Hayden.
I'll call her back.
(fierce howling)
What is that racket?
The spooky sounds of Hallow...
Really?
What?
Let's see. The first impression
that anyone is going to have,
before they ever experience
my meticulously-appointed
candy/scare station
is of you going
to the front door in
that Rite Aid witch outfit.
Ugh!
But never fear, Count Chocula's
here to really add some class.
What's the matter?
He doesn't like our costumes.
Well, there's nothing that can
be done about it now.
The doorbell's gonna be ringing, and we
still have to decorate the bobbing station.
What the hell is this?
VIVIEN:
What?
Chad?
Gala apples.
We specifically talked about
Granny Smiths.
They didn't have any Granny
Smiths at Gelson's.
Then you go to the
farmer's market
or an off ramp in Valencia and
you buy a bag from Pedro.
Where's the effort?
I think you're overreacting.
Because I'm the only one who
actually gives a shit?
I think you should just leave.
You think we should
just leave our house?
It's not your house.
We know it, you know it
and the house knows it.
Frankly, you don't deserve it.
Get out!
Yeah, leave.
We are not leaving this house.
Get out!
Get out! Get out!
I don't care about any of this.
Just go!
You shouldn't have
to watch this.
Get out of here!
Are you okay?
I don't believe you, Ben.
You tell me your story,
but there's a little glimmer in
your eye, a little...
lie, a little darkness.
And I don't want to live
with suspicion anymore,
so I want you to go.
(whispers):
I want you to go.
Oh, God.
Aah!
What's wrong?
What is it?
It feels like the baby's
kicking.
That's impossible. It's only
eight weeks old.
(groans)
Okay.
I got to go to the hospital.
What's going on?
Stay here,
and don't answer the door.
VIOLET: Don't answer the door?
It's Halloween.
(doorbell rings)
Trick or treat.
(scoffs) It says "Take One."
Can't you read?
I'm a pretty girl.
I want Violet to see.
(laughing)
Shortbus!
ADELAIDE:
Hey!
Wait for me!
♪ ♪
No, no, no,
not his face, that's fake.
He broke his leg.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Are you presently feeling any
pain in the abdominal area?
I just feel really sick.
I haven't been feeling any of
the... the kicking since we left
home about a half hour ago.
Well, I'm sure it's not kicks
that you're feeling.
The baby's only the size of a
kidney bean at eight weeks.
I know. That's-that's why I'm
concerned.
I think... I feel like
there's something wrong.
Well, I'm sure it's just gas.
So let's just take a look, and make
sure that everything is perfect.
(device beeping)
Okay...
And you're sure about
the time line?
Yeah, eight weeks. Positive.
The baby seems to be
a lot bigger.
Okay, here we go...
Oh, my God.
I'm gonna get some help.
What's going on?
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God. Oh, my baby.
Oh, my...
Oh! What happened?
What happened? What happened?!
She just walked
into the street.
It was a
hit-and-run, ma'am.
Oh, no! Oh...
Is she dying?
We're doing everything we can.
Okay. You gotta...
We gotta get her to the lawn
over there
while she's still with us.
EMT: Yeah. We need to take
her in, stabilize her...
No! If you can't help me,
then get out
of the goddamned way!
Ma'am, just... just let us...
(screaming):
No!
Addy, come on.
We're gonna get you home
with all your friends.
Come on, honey.
We're almost there.
Stay with me, Addy.
It's just a few more feet.
Aw, geez.
Oh, my God. Addy?
Oh, no!
(gasps)
Oh... no.
Oh...
(sobbing)
(sirens approaching)
(Constance screaming)
(monitor beeping rhythmically)
Oh, Mother,
you always had the
most beautiful hands.
What have they done to you?
This is my fault.
I wasn't there for you.
(voice cracking):
I'm so sorry.
(sniffles)
(sighs)
(air hissing)
(Molly breathing heavily)
(Molly gasping for air)
(monitor beeping rapidly)
(flatline tone)
Come with me, baby.
I want to, but I can't, Mother.
I can't.
(crying)
(flatline tone continues)
(sobbing quietly)
(knocking on door)
(insistent knocking)
LARRY: My tenant Ben,
I want my money!
(growls)
(pounding on door)
I'm not leaving here
till I have my thousand dollars!
(banging on door)
Hello!
Ben Harmon!
(pounding)
I am not leaving here
till I have thousand dollars.
Screw you!
You owe me!
Oh, here, here.
Take one and go!
(Larry shouting)
(children screaming)
Come on, come on!
Hey, honey.
Dad, there's some freaky dude
at the door
screaming about money.
I think he might be one of
your patients. I don't know,
should I call the cops?
No! No. Just...
just keep the door closed.
Is it locked?
Yeah.
(pounding on door)
BEN:
We're on way home right now.
Violet? Just...
just keep the door locked.
LARRY:
Oh, aha, oh.
I know you're in there.
Is that your daughter?
(knocking on door)
(insistent knocking)
(house alarm blaring nearby)
Violet!
(alarm blaring loudly)
(keypad beeping)
Violet!
Violet?
Ben!
She's not here!
Call her cell phone!
(knocking)
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player