MAN (drunkenly):
♪ Meet you all the way
♪ Yeah, ah
(humming)
♪ Take you all the way
♪ Do-do-do
♪ Rosanna, yeah
♪ Take you all the way
(song plays in the background)
♪ Ooh-hoo-hoo
(laughs)
♪ Oh, yeah
♪ Take you all the way
♪ Oh, yeah...
Seriously.
Toto is amazing.
Toto sucktitude.
I will not argue
about this, bro.
Toto is amazeballs.
Shut up about your incredibly
gay crush on your incredibly
gay band and get over it.
(scat singing)
Seriously. Kyle,
what are you gonna get?
Look, check mine out.
I see.
It means "Beginning and End."
You know, dude,
most of those don't even mean
what the chart
on the wall says they mean.
You might have "I'm a freaking
idiot" on your leg right now.
(laughter) Seriously. You're
going to go out for Chinese food
in a pair of shorts, and the
whole wait staff is gonna be
laughing their
asses off at you.
BILLY: What the hell does
"Beginning and End" mean,
even if that is what it says?
JIM:
It's my life philosophy.
It means, live
right goddamn now.
You're full of shit.
(laughter)
Yeah, seriously,
Kyle, get something.
No, dude. My mom would kill me.
Oh, it's cool.
Oh, I'd totally bang her
to take her mind off of it.
(laughs)
Oh, I got plans.
I'm not going to grow up
and work for Daddy,
or sell pot
to undergrads all my life.
You guys know why the levees
broke during Katrina?
'Cause the little Dutch boy
ran out of fingers?
The levees were built by the
U.S. Army Corps of Engineers.
But they built them for shit.
And where I'm from
still hasn't recovered,
and probably never will.
BILLY:
What in the hell
does you getting a tattoo have
to do with Katrina?
I'm going to be an engineer.
And I'm going to make sure shit
like that never happens again.
I don't want to walk
into some big meeting
with a mayor or a governor
and roll up my sleeves
and have a little Saints logo
or a... or a Wile E. Coyote
or anything
that's gonna make him think
that I'm anything other than
his knight in shining armor.
I got one life,
and I'm not wasting it.
I think
it's a pretty cool idea, Kyle.
Thank you, Jimmy.
Thank you.
Yeah, I do, too.
That's why I want to wish you
the luck of the Irish.
I didn't know you were Irish.
I'm not.
You can't drink or fight.
You're a little bitch.
It looks good, right?
(crying)
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
(grunting)
(crying)
(loud sobbing)
(whimpering)
(yells, mutters)
(crying)
I... (panting)
Ooh. Wh...?
(panting)
(slow, labored footsteps)
What am I...?
(crying)
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
MADISON: I am a Millennial.
Generation Y.
Born between the birth
of AIDS and 9/11, give or take.
They call us
"the Global Generation."
We are known for our
entitlement and narcissism.
Some say it's because
we're the first generation
where every kid gets a trophy
just for showing up.
Others think it's because
social media allows us
to post every time we fart
or have a sandwich
for all the world to see.
But it seems
that our one defining trait
is a numbness to the world,
an indifference to suffering.
I know I did anything
I could to not feel.
Sex, drugs, booze.
Just take away the pain.
Take away my mother and
my asshole father and the press
and all the boys I loved
who wouldn't love me back.
Hell, I was gang raped,
and two days later,
I was back in class
like nothing happened.
Most people never get over
stuff like that,
and I was, like,
"Let's go for Jamba Juice."
I would give everything
I have or will ever have
just to feel pain again,
to hurt.
Thank God for Minor League
Fiona and her herb garden.
One advantage of being
kind of dead is
that you don't have
to sweat warning labels.
There was this one brown liquid
that I thought made my nipples
tingle for a second,
but I think
it was psychosomatic,
because I polished off the rest
of it and didn't feel shit.
I tried every eye of newt
and wing of fly
until I found something
that made me not
look like Marilyn Manson
anymore.
(sighs)
And that's the rub of all
of this, isn't it?
I can't feel shit.
I can't feel anything.
We think that pain
is the worst feeling.
It isn't.
How can anything be worse
than this eternal silence
inside of me?
I used to not eat for days.
Or eat like crazy, and then
stick my fingers
down my throat.
Now, no matter how much
I binge,
I can't fill this hole
inside me.
I can't take it anymore.
I think I'm going batshit.
I need to do something.
(crying)
Hey.
(muttering)
(whimpers)
You know how this has
to go, right?
(quiet muttering)
You were a great guy, Kyle.
But you died.
(grunts) I didn't let you
go when I should have.
(panting)
I don't understand my power yet.
(gasps)
It's new.
I used it to bring you back.
(crying)
You killed your mother, Kyle.
(sobbing)
There's only one way left
to fix this.
(grunting)
(gasps)
(yelling)
(grunting)
(whimpering)
(mutters)
No!
(grunting)
(panting)
(muttering)
(crying)
No.
(sobbing)
I don't want you to die.
(Kyle groans)
Goddamn nothing!
I heard a noise.
Thought we had vermin.
Ain't no self-respecting rat
gonna live here.
Ain't nothin' to eat.
Nonsense. These larders
are bursting to full.
Well, that is disappointing.
I was feeling
a tad peckish myself.
MAN: Welcome to Jumpin' Jacks.
May I take your order?
Who said that?
Girl, relax. It's just a guy at the window.
Let me get two Jumpin' Jacks
with cheese, two fries,
large, and two
strawberry cyclones.
Would you care to super size
your order for $1.99?
Do we dare?
(laughs)
Hell, yeah!
Lord in heaven, the
most delicious food
I have eaten in my entire life!
And that's saying something.
(laughs)
I know, right?
I'm starting to understand
why you're so enormous.
You're not exactly
svelte yourself, okay?
I didn't mean to give offense.
Yeah, but you do, Miss Daisy.
All the damn time.
It's this century.
It still does perplex me so.
You think I'm any
less perplexed?
I dragged my ass
all the way here from Detroit
to be with my, quote,
"sister witches."
And instead, I'm sitting
in a fast-food parking lot
at 3:00 in the morning
with an immortal racist.
(laughs)
How did that happen?
Those girls-- they're never
gonna see you as their sister.
Let me guess.
'Cause I'm fat?
No, ma chère.
'Cause you're black.
Black as coal.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
Shit. It's late.
Hank.
I miss you, baby.
I want to come home.
Go to bed, Hank.
I'll see you soon, baby.
CORDELIA:
Delphine?
(soft thudding)
(footsteps)
Spalding?
Who is it?
I know you're there.
Whoa! Whoa! Hold it there!
Madison.
MADISON:
Stop yelling at me!
Do it! Do it! Do it!
(screaming)
(gasps)
Oh, my God.
(gasps loudly)
Fiona.
I wasn't expecting company.
I wasn't expecting
Buckingham Palace.
A woman like yourself
deserves to be surrounded
by beauty and grace.
(jazz plays)
Sit down.
All I have to offer
is some decent bourbon,
and hopefully, good company.
The reason for living
was to get ready
to stay dead a long time.
Faulkner.
As I Lay Dying.
I get it.
You're not just any old
broke-down sax man,
you're a college-educated one.
I've led a...
solitary life.
(laughs)
Come on, you don't
really expect me
to believe that.
You know, when I was coming up
in the clubs, uh...
musicians weren't so respected.
Hmm.
They were considered, uh,
poor, indigent,
and had to be content, uh,
being the
back-door man...
never invited
to stay the night.
It's more dangerous that way.
Yeah.
And you like danger.
I can tell that about you.
And I like it.
Who's he?
We call him Prince.
Prince of the Ivories.
I hope you understand, Fiona,
that this is a...
a rare night, uh,
a celestial creature
like yourself, uh...
gracing this humble abode.
In short...
hot damn.
(both laughing)
You're gonna have
to excuse me a minute.
It's not very
inviting in there.
Yeah.
Ugh...
AXEMAN:
Another bourbon?
Absolutely.
AXEMAN: Is the bourbon
smooth enough?
(chuckles)
Women don't usually
like a harsh whiskey.
Well, never assume
anything about me.
My taste in whiskey,
or... men.
May I assume...
that you'd like to kiss me?
(whispering):
This was a mistake.
I ran out of sleeping pills.
It was a bad idea.
Don't go.
This is not just
a one-night stand.
That is exactly what it is:
It could be our destiny.
(laughing):
No...
Do you actually think
my destiny is here
in this roach-infested
shithole?
Well, life is full
of surprises.
Well, I've had enough surprises
for two lifetimes.
I'm through with surprises.
Were you surprised
that you wanted to kiss me?
Oh...
No, you don't want
anything to do with me.
I am a wretched human being.
A miserable, mean
goddamn bitch,
I always have been.
I've had three husbands.
I've destroyed every
decent relationship
I have ever had,
including one with my daughter.
Love transforms.
Come on, you don't
believe in love.
Okay, let's table love, then.
What about sex?
Good, old-fashioned,
great sex.
(laughs)
You know, that's why
I took up the saxophone.
You really are
good with the ladies.
Oh, I'm good.
(laughs)
The joke was
they always watched
the bass player.
But they should've
watched my fingers
on the keys...
(giggles)
(playing jazz melody)
...my body in perfect
synchronization...
(laughing)
...an extension of
my instrument...
(plays low notes)
...no effort at all,
just one with it.
The way my lips and tongue
wrapped around my instrument
was... impeccable.
My embouchure...
(laughing)
...that's how I calibrate,
hit those clear, high notes.
(playing upbeat jazz)
(Fiona laughing)
(grunts)
I want to trust you, Kyle.
You need to learn
how to communicate.
When you're hungry,
when you're tired, when...
when you feel like you
might do something bad.
When you're hungry,
I want you to say
"food."
"Food."
Food.
Good.
When you're tired,
you can say...
you can say "bed."
Not!
S...
stupid.
I know you're not.
You're not stupid.
Mm-mm.
Everything you know, it...
it's stuck in your head.
I'm trying to help you,
so you can function
like a person.
(screams)
No!
Stop. Shh.
(grunting, shouting)
Jesus, who's this?
Don't you remember?
It's Kyle.
We used a spell,
brought him back to life?
You killed him.
Oh, uh... Cordelia
wants to see you.
Uh, actually,
that would be impossible,
but she does want to talk.
She knows you're alive?
She knows a lot more
than you think.
Go. I'll take care of him.
Huh?
Looks like we had
to put you back together.
Lucky I picked out
all the best pieces.
(shouts)
(yells)
You were dead.
So was I.
I didn't see a light, did you?
Mine was cold
and dark...
and then nothing.
But we both came back.
To this.
Somehow, it feels
more empty here.
You know exactly how I feel.
(sniffs)
You've been wondering if
it was worth the trouble.
And I've been
wondering the same thing.
(sniffling)
♪ You say you're leavin'
♪ Won't be back no more
LAVEAU:
Here, Walter.
You got some good
ones for me today?
(chuckles)
Ooh...
Yeah... give me
three of them.
(laughs)
Are you gonna come in?
Or you just gonna stare
from the doorway, Queenie?
How do you know my name?
Black witch come to town,
I'm gonna hear about it.
Surprised it took you this long
to come see me.
You doin' some kind of
voodoo with them fish heads?
It's Sunday night.
I'm makin' gumbo.
♪ You have somebody else
I never even had gumbo.
Not surprised.
Livin' over there
in wonder bread land.
They probably feed you
Shake 'n Bake
and watermelon for dessert.
Hmph.
They don't care that I'm black.
I just think that...
they just don't like me.
Oh... they care plenty.
Hmph.
Their power is built
on the sweat of our backs.
The only reason you
and I in this country
is 'cause our
great-great-grandpas
couldn't run fast enough.
We'll never be welcome here.
And those witches
are the worst.
They're not so bad.
No?
Even right now,
they got evil sleeping
under their roof,
eatin' alongside of 'em.
I locked that horror in a box
and buried her in the ground.
Fiona Goode digs her up,
gives her a warm bed
and three meals a day.
Delphine?
Fiona made her my slave.
Slave's too good for her.
You heard the stories,
I'm sure.
That ain't the half of it.
Ask her what she done.
You ask her.
Then you see.
You want to come live with us?
With your own people?
The price of admission
is Madame Delphine LaLaurie.
Bring her to me,
and you will have a home.
I never said I wanted
to come join you.
Voodoo doll belong
in the house of voodoo.
And I know you didn't
cross the line
and break the truce
for no bowl of gumbo.
Every man, woman
and child in this house
know what it feel like
to have to live as second best
to some pretty
little white girl.
You come here,
and you ain't never got
to feel that way again.
More than that,
you mix your witch
with our voodoo...
and even the Supreme
won't be able to touch you.
I should get back.
What are you gonna do to her?
If I bring Delphine to you?
Oh, don't you worry
about that, child.
Now you just get you home
'fore it get dark.
(liquid bubbling)
You go into the hospital,
and you wonder if you'll
ever come out again.
You come out, and you wonder,
"Goddamn, what have I been
doing all these years?"
Tea?
No, thank you.
I would say everything
is different now...
but it's not.
Everything around here
is exactly the same.
Only difference is...
now I see it.
The Axeman was a bad spirit.
You not only brought him here,
you sent him packing,
which means you are one
hot shit witch.
Power like yours does not go
unnoticed.
Which means you've got a
bull's-eye on your back, kiddo,
and our biggest enemy is locked,
loaded, and looking at you.
Marie Laveau.
My mother.
But she's on our side.
Fiona Goode has been on the same
side her whole life: her own.
Now, I don't know
if you are the next Supreme,
nobody does,
but if she jumps to that
conclusion, right or wrong,
she will slit your throat
just like she did to Madison.
Nobody knows who killed Madison,
not even Madison.
She doesn't, but I do.
My mother killed her
because she thought
Madison was the next leader
of our coven.
She wanted to absorb
her power, her life force.
So if she even thinks
you're next...
you're next.
Holy shit.
Right?
Fiona is fading, growing weaker.
Which only makes her
more dangerous.
A wounded animal
will rip you apart
if it's cornered.
So what do we do?
It's simple.
We're going to kill my mother.
Kill her once, kill her good,
kill her dead.
(Kyle grunting)
Where do you think
you're going?
We've only just begun.
(chuckles)
You know, it was
a charming evening,
but, uh, that dead body
in your bathtub
is going to start putting off
some very noxious odors soon.
Just a few fumes.
You're no angel.
(chuckles)
Although you always
did have someone
tidy up after you, didn't you?
It was fun,
our little romantic game,
but I've called the police,
and they're gonna
be coming shortly.
Oh, you'd never do that.
You hate the coppers.
We're one and the same,
you and me.
When was the last time
that your body made
a light show,
huh?
My guess is never.
You're afraid.
You're afraid
of your own pleasure.
It makes you feel weak,
like you need somebody.
That's why you're going.
You're drawing
ridiculous conclusions.
I don't even know your name
and I don't care to.
You don't know me,
but there's nothing
I don't know about you.
Your secrets, your dreams,
everything.
I've been watching over you
since you were eight years old.
You think you're special,
little witch?
What's your name?
Fiona Goode.
Do you know what happens
to scrawny little girls
who stick their heads
up above the others?
They get it chopped off.
I'm not afraid of you, Helen.
Pick it up.
Now hold the glass
above your head.
You know what to do.
No!
You little shit!
(girl screams)
That was you?
That bully had it coming.
I knew I didn't do it.
Why did you help me?
Who are you?
What are you?
At first, I saw you as
the daughter that I never had.
I wanted to protect my,
my little flower.
But you are no hothouse orchid.
There's nothing fragile
about you, Fiona.
As you, as you grew,
I began to see
the-the fire in your belly
and the steel running down
your back.
You were the most fearsome
thing that ever lived.
And while others only saw
the ruthless manipulator,
I saw so, so much more.
And my feelings...
became complicated.
And I fell in love...
But not like a father...
like a man.
I don't believe in ghosts.
Nor did I feel like one.
I felt like I was locked
in an airless closet
for eternity.
And when you arrived,
you gave meaning
to my endless, tortured days.
All I want to do is
give you pleasure.
You deserve it.
Baby, you've lived through so much.
(both moan)
(grunts)
Jesus Christ...
you call that a seduction, huh?
What an idiot,
telling me my life story,
how you watched me grow old.
What was that, a mercy lay?!
It was a, a culmination.
Zip me up.
No, you keep your distance,
lover boy.
Go haunt someone else's life!
(gasps)
Hey, Spalding.
How are you feeling?
Fine.
I feel fine.
How am I...?
Whose tongue is this?
Yours.
I found it the other day,
hidden away.
At first, I didn't realize
what it was.
I mean, a severed tongue,
stored away for 40 years?
You'd think
it'd be shriveled up
like a slice of beef jerky
by now.
(gasps)
But it wasn't. It was wet,
alive...
because someone enchanted it.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
"M.S."
Myrtle Snow.
She wanted you
to tell the truth.
But that was the last thing
that you wanted to do.
So you cut it out
of your own head.
Answer me!
Yes!
Bet you didn't know
that she kept it.
But Myrtle wasn't
witch enough to restore it.
But I'm not Myrtle.
Infernales, curare hominem.
Restitue eum ad naturam.
(chuckles)
What do you want from me, hmm?
The only thing
that you can't refuse me.
The truth.
Did you kill
Madison Montgomery?
M-Madison Montgomery...
is alive.
That wasn't the question.
No!
I didn't kill her.
But you know who did.
Yes!
I do!
Say the name.
Please don't make me!
(groaning)
Say it.
(spitting sound)
Fiona!
Fiona Goode!
I say her name.
I bless it!
As long as there is a tongue
in this head, I will say it!
I will always say her name!
Fiona Goode!
Our Supreme!
She's not your Supreme,
Spalding.
She's your employer.
You're not a part
of this coven.
My family has served
this coven...
for ten generations.
I have devoted my life to it.
Not anymore.
(yells)
(groans)
You're done talking.
Care for a nibble?
I'm not here for that.
I need to ask you something.
What's the worst thing
you ever did?
The past is best left buried.
I feel like
maybe we have a connection.
And my mama always said
that in order to
be a true friend,
you have to see the ugly
to appreciate the good.
You think we could be
true friends?
I perhaps had...
one slight regret.
LaLAURIE:
Sally?
I've missed your presence
for the last fortnight.
Rumor has it that you gave
birth to a baby.
Yes, ma'am, a healthy baby boy.
Oh, Ida says
he's beautiful
with a complexion
as light as cream.
What's the boy's name?
Haven't settled on one yet, ma'am.
Hmm.
I've always been fond of
"Pierre" as a boy's name.
(chuckling):
Have you now?
Kitchen's too hard
for a new mother.
Now that Borquita is serving
her punishment,
I need a new handmaiden.
Would you come
to my boudoir tonight?
Help me
with my beauty treatments?
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you, ma'am.
Elixir de jeunesse.
This little jar came
all the way from Paris.
Madame Lafayette swore
it took ten years off her face.
I could've saved a fortune
if I'd only seen
the bitch in broad daylight.
They're all worthless.
Every single one.
Except this.
My own concoction.
The formulation of which
I will carry with me
to my grave.
Let's play a game.
Can you guess
one of the secret ingredients?
It looks like blood, ma'am.
Very good.
You're a smart girl.
But this batch is extra special.
Can you guess why?
Came from a boy.
Newly born.
Youth begets youth.
I know who's been
between your legs, whore.
You needn't bother
to give that baby a name.
You didn't.
Couldn't have a high yellow
bastard growing up
in my house,
laying claims to our fortune.
The poor girl, next morning
she threw herself
off the balcony.
Cracked her head open
on the pavement.
Cracked it open like an egg.
We buried her with her baby.
It was the right thing to do.
You have no idea
what doing the right
thing even means.
I'm learning, Queenie.
You must understand.
It wasn't only a different time.
It was a different world.
I'm just...
I'm grateful.
To have someone.
A true friend.
To guide me.
(grunting)
(saxophone playing)
What have you been up to?
Nothing. Do you mind?
No, I don't mind.
But you do.
What are we talking about?
Come on, Zoe.
What you walked in on before.
None of my business.
You brought the dude
back from the dead.
You must like him a little.
Brought you back, too.
Starting to wish you hadn't?
Look, it's not like we can
be together anyways.
Why not?
It's gonna be
different with Kyle.
He already died once.
It's gonna take more than just
that thing between your legs
to kill him.
Don't be disgusting.
So, what? You're done with him?
Not even close.
Being with him is the only time
I felt anything
since I came back.
I'm not giving him up.
But that doesn't mean
you have to, either.
Right.
We'll just take turns.
Come here.
♪
(saxophone playing)
Can I buy you a drink?
Yeah.
I must confess my nerves
do flutter a bit
when I think of changing
my hair stylings.
Girl, you had that same
old stanky hairstyle
for over 150 years.
It's time to switch it up, okay?
Uh... oh!
Hello?
We're here.
(gasps)
Ah.
Madame LaLaurie.
Welcome back.
It's been
such a long time.
No.
You don't know this woman.
What she will do to me.
Yes, I do.
It's the reason
I brought you here,
you dumb bitch.
No.
No!
No, no!
(yelling)
No!
No, please!
Please! No!
Mon chérie,
it's been such a busy day,
I forgot to apply my Retin-A.
You care to make the first cut?
I'd love to.
Wha...? No!
You stay away from me!
You stay away from me,
you hear me?!
You stay away!
♪
Beautiful.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player