Drink this, it'll
calm your nerves.
And when you're ready,
I'll cast a little
spell for you.
Help you sleep
through the night.
I'm ashamed...
to show you my weakness.
I might have shed a
tear or two myself
if I'd lost everyone I had.
No, it's not that.
I'm over 300 years old.
Everyone I done ever met done
followed after the Grim Reaper.
Some willingly.
Others kicking and scratching.
I taught myself long ago
not to waste tears for the dead.
It's your kindness
that has touched my soul.
I feel like I've been
alone for so long,
it's a relief
to have found an equal.
Even if that person come
in the guise of an enemy.
We have so much to talk about.
But not tonight.
Tomorrow we'll draw
the battle lines.
After you've rested.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Wake up. Your master calls.
Laveau.
Tonight's the night
you pay me my due.
Not now.
Please.
It's been a hard day.
Hard days...
deserve a harder night.
You drink my torment like wine.
Why you here
in the house of your enemy?
I've come to seek
a lasting truce.
Not before you deal
with my terms.
I want what's coming to me.
Tonight.
Once a year,
you must pay my price.
It's the bargain
you made so long ago.
Ma'am?
Ma'am? Ma'am, it's
the middle of the night.
You'll have to come back
during visiting hours.
Open the door.
I can't let you leave the
hospital with that baby, ma'am.
Mama's had a hard day.
Put the baby down on the ground
and step away from it.
Don't mess with me.
I need this baby.
Put the goddamn
baby down. Now!
I warned you.
Shut up.
I'll give
you something to cry about.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
The police have identified
a man seen here
in this video
surveillance footage.
- If anyone has any information...
- It's my fault.
All of it.
I told him I was filing
for divorce.
He was so angry.
He was determined to be a hero.
He had this look on his face.
I should've seen it.
It ain't on you.
It's on me.
I hired him.
What are you talking about?
Your husband
was a Witch Hunter.
Showed up at my place,
runnin' his mouth
'bout how he been
killing witches
his whole life,
'bout how he had
all this access,
how his mother-in-law
was the Supreme.
Ooh, he hated your ass.
But he gave me a
fair price, so...
You were
my sworn enemy.
You hired him to kill me?
To kill my girls?
Uh-huh.
But he was too soft
on you, he couldn't do it.
He was tryin'
to protect you, all right.
From me.
Lucky for y'all
he was a stone fool.
You're not just blind,
you are willfully blind.
You married Hank to prove
some childish point
and brought a viper
into this sacred house.
It's all water
under the bridge now, mama.
Come on, come on, come on.
Hank was not some...
lone assassin with a grudge.
Witch Hunters never act alone.
They are part
of an ancient order of men
whose sole purpose
is to rid the world of witches.
Black or white.
Now w...
We don't have to waste our time
with worker bees,
what we have to do
is to find the hive.
Excuse me.
...while the search continues
for the newborn baby that was
kidnapped from St. Ignatius.
♪ And it all comes down
to you. ♪
What a lovely shawl.
You keep your distance.
I know your game, lady.
Oh.
Slit my throat like you did Maddy
or the stake like Myrtle.
Don't bother.
I've surrounded myself
with the white spirit light
to protect me.
And even if you do
put me down...
I've already made plans
on how to bring myself back.
Well, now why would I...
want to hurt you?
Of all the girls in the house,
you are the only one
worth a damn, magic-wise.
Bullshit.
Your daughter, she...
she told me how it works
with the Supreme.
You can keep your powers.
But I don't think
you fully appreciate
the power of the throne.
It's a skeleton key.
Anything you wish for
in the world.
The Supremacy comes with a great
deal of power and influence.
You are going to know
the world, and what's more...
they are all
going to want to know you.
You know, I was talking
to an old friend of mine
the other day,
telling her all about you.
She just begged me to come
have a sit-down with you.
She's a White Witch.
And try as I may
I cannot get her
to play in the shadows with me.
Who are you?
You must be Misty.
I'm Stevie Nicks.
Is she all right?
You owe me five bucks.
I told you she was
gonna do that. Mwah.
Well, that was
a morbid field trip.
Queenie's dead.
We don't know that. They
haven't released the names.
She could be at
the Souplantation.
You know how that bitch
loves a bottomless bowl.
Should we go to the morgue?
No.
For witches, you guys
are such squares.
♪ Rhiannon rings like
a bell through the night ♪
♪ And wouldn't you
love to love her? ♪
♪ She rules her life
like a bird in flight ♪
♪ And who will be her lover?
♪ All your life you've never
♪ Seen a woman
taken by the wind ♪
♪ Would you stay
♪ If she promised
to you Heaven? ♪
♪ Would you even win?
♪ Would you ever win?
♪ Oh, Rhiannon, you cry
♪ But then she's gone,
and your life ♪
♪ Knows no answer
♪ And your life
♪ And he says
♪ Rhiannon
♪ He says, Rhiannon...
♪ He says, Rhiannon
I'm a huge Eminem fan.
When's he get here?
Marshall?
You're not his type.
And more importantly...
you're not the next Supreme.
♪ Rhiannon
♪ Rhiannon...
What about the Seven Wonders?
I have no doubt
she'll pass every one.
♪ You still cry out for her
♪ Rhiannon
♪ Dreams unwind
♪ Love's a state of mind
♪ Your love's a state of mind.
That was amazing.
Thank you, honey.
She wrote it in ten minutes.
She heard the name Rhiannon,
and she got inspired, sat
down and wrote the song.
I know everything about you.
I'm honored, Misty.
Thank you.
Did I get
the shawl twirl right? I real...
I want to get it right.
Perfect. It was perfect.
Thank you.
But let me show you something.
One twirl.
Okay.
Oh.
That way.
Okay.
Whoo!
So...
this shawl has
danced across
the stages of the world,
and now it's yours.
And good luck
with the Seven Wonders.
Thank you, thank you,
Stevie, thank you.
That swamp bitch can't even
spell her own name,
and now she gets
the keys to the kingdom?
I mean, I came back
from the dead.
Yeah, Misty brought you back.
I could be the Supreme.
Yeah, the mind reading's a real
party trick, Mumbles the Clown.
My powers are growing.
I can do mind control.
Prove it.
Put out that cigarette.
Now stick it in your vagina.
Nan, stop!
Both of you skanks, enough!
And by the way,
you can't be the Supreme--
you've got a heart murmur.
Hm. Not anymore, bitch.
My little trip
to the afterlife cured it.
I don't believe you.
It's true.
It was clearly my destiny
to die and be reborn,
just like our Lord and Savior.
So let's schedule
the Seven Wonders,
me versus Misty, and we'll see
who the next goddamn Supreme is.
Okay,
so who is he?
Harrison Renard.
CEO of the Delphi Trust,
an asset management company.
One of the richest
men in the country.
And...
apparently, my father-in-law.
I thought Hank
didn't have any family.
No.
What Hank didn't have
were any customers.
No real ones, anyway.
You're sure this man
is Hank's father?
Renard.
The French word
for "fox."
And this.
Important men
get their pictures taken.
His name really was Hank.
Well, Henry.
Henry Renard, the only son
of Harrison Renard.
So, tell me about
this company, Delphi.
It grew out of the Renard's
family business.
They used to be carpenters,
furniture builders,
dating back to the colonies.
Salem.
Now they specialize
in private equity.
Last year they managed
over $50 billion in assets.
So, where do we find them?
Corporate headquarters
are in Atlanta.
Hell, that ain't nothin' but a hop.
- So what we waitin' on?
- Well, before we hop
on our broomsticks,
let's think this through.
This is a multibillion-dollar
corporation.
We have to be smart about this.
They pray
to one god--
a green, merciless god.
Money. So we cut off
their supply,
bring them to their knees,
make them crawl to us
and beg for mercy.
Here, I can do that.
I want to help.
No.
You're tainted.
You let them get
inside your head.
We can fight about this
for the next ten years,
but right now I want
to help you.
No!
Don't you understand anything?
You can't help me.
You can't help anyone.
You're worthless, hopeless.
Get out of my sight.
Come to me, Hecate.
Mother of Angels...
Cosmic World Soul.
Comminuet,
infirmabitur,
submergetur.
Praecipita,
strangulare...
percusserite...
in corde
suo proposito.
Comminuet...
infirmabitur...
...submergetur.
Praecipita...
strangulare...
percusserite...
in corde
suo...
proposito.
Bring them to me
in a weakened state.
Make me strong and cunning,
so that I may destroy...
Are you all right?
Yeah.
No.
I'm fine.
Madison can't be the Supreme.
She's selfish
and she's a whore.
I didn't realize this before,
but we can't survive on our own.
The sisterhood
protects each of us.
If I was the Supreme,
I would only do good.
I believe that. You don't have
a mean bone in your body.
Maybe you're the kind
of leader we need.
I think they moved Luke.
I can't hear him.
Can I help you?
Yes. Uh, we're here
to see Luke Ramsey.
I'm so sorry.
Luke died yesterday.
I want to see him.
The mortuary came
and took the body away.
I want to say good-bye.
What is that hideous smell?
Rattle viper sperm incense.
Clear all
the bad spirits out of here.
Get rid
of their evil intentions.
It's not evil intentions
that's making me sick.
Jadoo toona.
One of these girls is emerging
as the new Supreme,
and as her powers grow,
so does the cancer.
I ain't ready
to say good-bye to you.
We still got work to do.
Have you ever been in love,
Marie?
What has she done to you?
Long time ago.
I found love for the first time,
and it's given me the
passion to keep fighting.
You can help me live, Marie.
I wish I could.
You know the secret.
You gave it to that despicable,
torturing racist.
I gave her a vial of my tears.
If I gave it to you,
you'd still be bald and weak
and living out your last days
over and over for all eternity.
Who... gave it to you?
I don't think
you're ready for that.
Tell me your secret.
I sold my soul...
to Papa Legba.
You conjured him or...
he just appeared?
Mmm...
I thought I was
the shit back then.
I had just come into my prime,
and my magic was strong.
Shockingly strong.
I was pregnant,
and I did not accept
the idea of death.
I was invincible.
Papa must've heard me.
Showed up one night,
said, "You can have
eternal life, Marie.
"I come to you once a year,
and you give me what I want."
I thought he meant
some kind of sexual favors.
Seemed simple enough
at the time.
I wished for it;
it came true.
Unknowingly, I made a deal
forged in Hell.
Papa...
Motherhood looks good
on you, Mambo.
You'd make a beautiful mother.
But...
children ain't
in the cards for you.
N-No. No.
Not my baby.
Take it back, Papa.
Take it back.
Take the spell back.
I can be mortal again.
Take it back.
Now, you know
that ain't how it works, sugar.
Give the child to me.
I want my innocent soul.
Does he still come to you?
Mm-hmm. Once a year.
What does he want?
You asking for him
to come and see you?
'Cause the thing about him is,
if you want him bad
enough, he'll hear you.
Try and get some sleep now.
Just close your eyes
and forget about that for now.
Damn.
This kabob's
some kind of tasty.
Thanks for treating.
Get used to it.
If you really are
the next Supreme,
pretty soon,
you'll be drowning in merch.
Merch?
Merchandise. Swag.
The cookies.
You know.
No, I'm not sure I do.
Stevie gave you the shawl.
Fiona gave you Stevie.
Making you feel like
Supremely hot shit
when the fact is,
now you owe them both.
You are cynical.
And I don't think
the White Witch or
the Supreme need
my kind of help.
Maybe not today.
But a year from now,
you're on the throne,
they're in deep shit,
the phone rings, and,
"Hey, girlfriend,
it's Auntie Stevie.
Need some mojo. You still
looking like my album cover?"
Everything's transactional.
Guy buys you dinner,
he expects a blow job.
Welcome to earth.
Hey, are you trying to say
that Stevie was working me?
Players only love you
when they're playing.
No.
No, I know what
you're trying to do.
Mess me up,
make me doubt myself.
You think I'm stupid
because of where I came from.
Well, I'm not so easily bought,
and I ain't that easily fooled.
Thanks for the lunch.
You're right.
I do think you're stupid.
You want to change my opinion?
Let me show you something.
Enchant these guys, would you?
We just need a minute.
So, what did you
want to show me?
That I'm just
as powerful as you.
Prove it.
See?
You're powerful.
I'm powerful.
I don't need you.
I just want to be your friend.
Now lose that ugly shawl.
Are you insane?
This came direct from Stevie.
She probably has a bargain bin
in her basement
with 20 more just like it
to hand out when she needs
to make someone feel special.
Stevie would never do that.
Lose the shawl.
Drop it in the casket.
Let the part of you
that's just an imitation
of some other witch die.
Give life to you.
The one...
true...
Misty Day.
Stupid bitch.
Coffee break's over, boys.
We're just going
to pay our respects.
You can't mention Luke's dad,
or anything like that, right?
- I'm not stupid. - We need to know the
name of the mortuary.
Once we find out, we can get
Misty to help us bring him back.
And I can be with Luke forever.
I think the fondest memory
I have of Luke was
when he was nine.
He had made the most
adorable little cross
out of driftwood.
Where's his body?
I think she meant to ask, where
do you plan to have the funeral?
Well, there will be a
service in our church, but
Luke is here... now.
I had him cremated.
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust.
You... bitch!
I think it's time for us to go.
You killed him
with that pillow.
What are you talking about? What
are you talking about?!
Nan, what are you doing?
Let her go!
Stop!
She has to pay!
Nan!
You have to be... cleansed.
Could you please
stop playing for a minute?
I need to focus.
No, no, no. Sit.
Listen to the celestial tones.
What is that thing?
It's hideous and weird.
Don't be a hater, dear.
It's a theremin.
I cannot tell you
how playing this instrument
soothes my soul
in tempestuous times.
Nothing could soothe my soul.
I have nothing
to offer this coven anymore.
Who am I?
What do I do?
You buck up, is what you do!
Face reality headlong
and carry on.
But how?
I have no one,
and my powers are gone.
Your salad dressing
is absolutely magical.
Maybe you could bottle it.
Cordelia's Conjured
Coriander Condiment.
Or if you'd like
a little getaway,
maybe a job as a hostess
on a cruise ship.
You've got a lovely personality,
and you're always well-groomed.
Myrtle,
are you trying
to push me over the edge?
I'm trying to give you une demi
tasse de realite, darling.
Let's be honest.
Living in Fiona's shadow
is a challenge.
What are your options when
your mother's Hillary Clinton?
Between us chickens, no matter
how hard I worked at it,
I never felt special, either.
But with my reemergence
from the flames--
look at me, I'm fabulous!
Reinvigorated!
One never knows what the
universe has in store for us!
Oh, stop!
Stop talking!
You are insane! My God!
I am an absolute failure.
Everything that Fiona says
is true!
I don't belong here anymore.
I don't belong anywhere!
Oh!
They've just suspended
trading on our stock.
We lost 50%
of our value in ten minutes.
We've been in business
over 180 years.
Now... I give us a week.
Vultures are waiting to strip
the flesh from our bones.
SEC has nothing on us.
Nothing!
You get our people on the phone.
Call... call the senator.
Call... what's his name?
Bernanke.
I've been trying all day.
Nobody is coming near us.
It's like a tornado
ripped through this company.
There's nothing natural
about this.
It's time we finally
deal with those witches.
Papa Legba,
ouvirier barrier
pour moi.
Papa Legba,
ouvirier barrier...
...pour moi.
Papa Legba,
ouvirier barrier pour moi
agoe.
Papa Legba, ouvirier barrier
pour moi agoe.
Oh... Papa Legba,
ouvirier barrier...
...pour moi agoe.
Papa Legba,
ouvirier barrier
pour moi agoe.
Papa Legba,
ouvirier barrier...
You broke out the good stuff.
I don't want to die.
Same as everyone.
I am not the same as everyone.
This could be a big-ticket night
for you, Papa.
I'm queen of the witches.
I don't give a wet donkey's shit
about your title.
I shine to only one thing:
your soul.
Then let's talk business.
I give you my soul,
and what do you give me
in return?
Freedom from death.
I want terms defined.
Life everlasting.
No aging,
no decrepitude
forever.
Just like that.
Just like that?
In exchange, you
provide services.
One night a year, on the
date of my choosing.
No refusal ever.
What kind of services?
For instance,
would you cripple
your daughter?
Today?
Absolutely.
Murder an innocent?
Someone you love.
Whatever it takes.
Then...
we have a deal.
Seal it.
The deal is off.
Why?
You have nothing to sell.
You have no soul.
Bum luck, baby.
No sale.
I'll get my immortality.
All we got to do is find
the young girl
that's taking you down.
Haven't you heard?
I have no soul.
I'll just kill 'em all.
Maybe you are the Supreme.
I mean, the way you
got inside her head,
only ever seen Fiona do that.
Fiona's a bitch.
I'm gonna be a nice Supreme.
I hear something.
Yeah. You always
hear something.
What you doing?
I heard it crying.
That's impossible.
That closet was...
Oh.
You the clairvoyant.
You stole this baby to kill it.
You don't know what you talking about.
Now give it here.
Eat my shit.
I'm the next Supreme.
I just killed the woman next
door with my powers just now,
and I will kill you.
What is going on here?
Oh.
She say she the next Supreme.
Say she done killed
the neighbor lady.
Oh, great.
Now we'll have more
cops on our trail.
Whose baby is that?
Mine.
Check the skin tone.
She stole it.
She's gonna kill it.
This girl is out of line.
Nan, hand the baby
back to her,
or I'll make you do it.
Now leave.
You have blood on your hands.
The both of you.
Now, that girl is dangerous.
Yes, she is.
So whose is it really?
It's for Papa.
Every year,
his requests get worse,
but you gonna come to find out.
No.
We couldn't come to terms.
I barely remember
my baby's face.
So when I look at this child,
I feel like she mine.
But Papa's coming.
He needs
the soul of an innocent.
Well,
perhaps we can...
kill two birds with one stone.
Oh, Christ.
I didn't think
she was this strong.
Never!
Stop making such a fuss.
You're not the first witch
to be drowned.
I was very clear.
No substitutions.
Papa,
you asked for a soul.
I give you one.
You must provide an innocent.
She's innocent.
Mostly.
She killed the neighbor,
but the bitch had it coming.
Oh, come on, Papa, huh?
Be a sport.
You two together?
Big trouble.
Come, child.
Do I have to wear this outfit
for all eternity?
Not at all.
You will find the other side
is filled with treats for a girl
like you.
Anywhere is better than here.
That's so beautiful.
I've always loved that song,
Stevie.
The perfect ending
to a long day.
♪ Has anyone ever written
anything for you ♪
♪ In all your darkest hours
♪ Did you ever hear me sing?
♪ Listen to me now
♪ You know I'd rather be alone
♪ Than be without you
♪ Don't you know
♪ Has anyone ever given
♪ Anything to you
♪ In all your darkest sorrow
♪ Did you ever
just give it back? ♪
♪ Well, I have
♪ I have given that to you
♪ And if that's all
♪ All I ever do
♪ I want you to remember me
♪ Mm.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player