She has no identification,
no wallet, keys,
and she wouldn't talk to the cops.
So they dropped her on our doorstep?
When I was on the force,
we used to do that all the time.
Involuntary psychiatric hold.
(patients screaming)
You know, we cut out
a lot of paperwork.
Wait here.
You got it.
What's your name?
I hear you caused
quite a disturbance tonight.
Some anti-Semitic remark
set you off.
They made a joke.
The businessmen at the bar.
They said,
"Don't let them Jew you down."
That's how it always starts, you know?
With jokes.
There's blood on your coat there.
Is it yours? It's theirs.
I broke a beer bottle.
I stabbed them.
They will live, but...
they will never forget.
I'm not immune
to the atrocities
your people suffered.
Did you lose someone in the war?
(whistling)
We'll start treatment
first thing in the morning.
Lock her up.
(whistling continues)
Am I going to die?
Not exactly.
As a matter of fact,
after this, you'll
probably live forever.
(screaming)
I could sure use
a cigarette about now.
Arden?
Where is it?
That son of a bitch.
ARDEN: No fresh incisions
to indicate surgical implantation.
What'd it do, crawl back inside you?
Through which orifice?
What are you talking about?
Yeah, he smacked me around,
shot me with X-rays...
That thing he found on my neck.
(machine whirring)
The tracer from
the creatures in the sky?
You still believe me, don't you?
Yeah, of course.
But it doesn't matter what I believe.
It does.
Especially in this place.
Your story is who you are.
I wish I could forget my story.
No, you have to say it
out loud all the time
just to keep it straight in your head.
Tell me.
Tell me your story.
I won't judge you.
I can still hear the sound
if I let myself.
(rattling, distant thumping)
You hear something?
What's going on?
What time is it?
Stay here.
(floorboard creaking)
(clattering)
(floorboards creaking)
(clattering continues)
(screaming)
Grace...
(grunting)
Get back here!
(door slams)
(screams, whimpers)
I lost my father
and my stepmother that night.
I lost my stepsister the next day
when she accused me of murdering them.
Red and Patsy were secretly lovers.
They wanted the farm for themselves.
They planned every detail
to convince the police,
and no matter how many times
I told my story,
no one would believe me.
I believe you.
I loved the farm.
I miss the horses the most.
The freedom I felt riding them.
Like I was flying.
You'll fly again.
Where did you go during
the movie, Lana?
I... I told you,
I excused myself.
I'm not going to say a word
to Sister Jude.
I would have done that already
if I thought that's what was needed.
You reappeared.
You, Kit and Grace.
SISTER JUDE: The Mexican,
a sex-crazed deviant,
and a pinhead
won't get far in this storm.
I hope they all drown out there.
Lights out in ten minutes.
(thunder crashing)
All right, let's go.
Shelley made it out.
She got past whatever's out there.
What the hell were they?
We can never talk about that.
If they know we got out,
it's the end of us.
(thunder booming)
THREDSON:
Here's the thing, Lana.
You don't belong here.
You're not a danger to society.
You were right to try to escape.
(chuckles)
You headshrinkers are such hypocrites.
According to your bible,
the Diagnostic and Statistical
Manual of Mental Disorders,
I'm sick.
I have an illness.
I believe I can help you.
I'd like to try, if you'll let me.
But I'm not even your patient.
I see myself in you.
You're thoughtful and intelligent.
You have something to offer the world.
And they can't keep you here
if they don't have
a current diagnosis.
If I can convince them
that I've cured you,
they'll be forced to release you.
Doctor, I have been this way since...
...since I can remember.
There is no cure.
Your choice.
I'm not like Sister Jude.
I won't force you to do anything.
But I also won't be here
very much longer... another week
if we're lucky...
so if you want help
getting out of this shithole...
...we'd better jump in.
You're a fish out of water, Lana,
gasping for life.
It won't end well.
Trust me.
(upbeat French song
"Dominique" playing)
WOMAN: 15th of November 1964.
Dear Kitty:
This relentlessly cheerful tune
never stops playing.
The walls are closing in.
I can hardly breathe.
It's Amsterdam all over again.
But there are eyes everywhere.
These eyes of madness and disease.
These people,
they are resigned to die here.
We were never resigned.
We always held on to a shred of hope.
Give me your pen.
If they catch you writing,
they'll throw you in solitary.
In spite of the
religious icons everywhere,
this is a godless place.
You might want a friend.
Okay.
I hope you like pain.
Ah.
You must be the new girl.
You were there.
What? In Auschwitz.
Nazi murderer!
You Nazi swine!
Take this one.
Murderer! Nazi swine!
(grunts) Don't you
remember me, Doctor?
I am Anne.
Anne Frank!
SISTER JUDE:
So, Anne Frank, is it?
What a relief it will be
to millions of schoolchildren
to know you survived.
You think I'm crazy.
Anne Frank died,
Bergen-Belsen, 1945.
Just weeks before the camp
was liberated.
There were so many bodies
when the Allies arrived...
thousands...
buried in mass graves...
but I wasn't one of them.
I was too sick
to tell anyone my name,
even if they had asked.
The Brits nursed us back
to some semblance of health.
Afterwards, I kept to
the streets in Germany.
A pickpocket, a thief.
And then I met a soldier.
Private William Snow
of Rutherford, New Jersey.
He saved me.
He brought me to America.
So you're a married lady.
A widow.
William was called back to service
during the Korean Conflict.
He was killed there in '52.
That same year,
my diary was published
here in America.
Only then did I realize
that Pim had survived the war.
And you made
no attempt to contact your father?
I wanted to,
at first.
But he had a new family, a new life.
But more than that, it was the diary.
People finally
started to pay attention
to what they'd done to us.
All because of
a martyred 15-year-old girl.
She had to stay 15.
And a martyr.
I could do
more good dead than alive.
Your story
is indecent.
No, you are indecent.
You have a Nazi war
criminal working here.
THREDSON: I find myself in
a bit of an ethical dilemma, Kit.
If I deem you as sane,
you'll almost certainly
go to the electric chair, but if I...
judge you unfit to stand trial,
you'll be allowed to live out
the rest of your days here.
So... what's the problem?
The problem is I don't
think you're crazy.
But I don't think you're evil.
You think I'm innocent?
In some ways, yes.
The innocent victim
of a brutish society
which drove you
to commit acts so terrible,
so... antithetical
to who you are
as a person that your psyche
concocted this elaborate fantasy
about alien abduction to
absolve you of your guilt.
No.
That's not true.
I believe it is.
But I also believe that your death
at the hands of the state
serves no moral purpose.
Listen to me very carefully, Kit.
I'm willing to lie to the courts
in order to save your life,
but only under one condition:
That for the rest of
our time together,
you face the truth
of what you've done.
If you can do that,
then I'll be able to leave here
feeling I've done some good.
I already told you what happened.
Yes.
Now let me tell you.
ANNE:
He wasn't called Arden then.
He was Gruper.
Hans Gruper.
He was SS.
And he was not like the others.
I saw him the night we
arrived in Auschwitz.
That's where they sent us first.
(train chugging)
(Arden speaking German)
He seemed kind... gentle.
I remember that there were
two boys, twins,
and when the guards
herded the other children away,
Gruper saved those twins.
I can recall thinking
that they were lucky.
But nobody was lucky in Auschwitz.
I didn't know it then,
but Dr. Gruper never
saved a single soul.
He would visit us regularly
in the women's barracks,
bring us sweets,
chocolates.
The guards would never
strike us when he was present.
He wanted to help, he said.
But he couldn't treat
all the girls, he would say.
So he left it to chance.
And when they came back,
if they came back...
...something had changed.
He had made them sick.
Whatever he'd done to them.
They'd be afraid to speak out.
(girl sobbing)
They'd be sworn to secrecy.
THREDSON:
You married Alma in secret.
You didn't feel you could tell anyone.
And as time passed, what
should've been your greatest joy
became your greatest shame.
And the pressure in you built
and needed a release.
And it found one.
On... January 16,
Donna Burton, a librarian,
was abducted from
the Wausaukee County Library...
a short drive from the
gas station where you worked.
Her remains were found two days later.
Her skin had been removed.
So had her head.
Why the skin, Kit?
Why the head?
I don't know.
Her race?
Her identity?
The very things about Alma
society was punishing you for?
No.
It happened again in March.
Allison Rydell,
a secretary, was taken
outside of her home.
Then it happened to Alma.
The night it happened,
you said you had been
visited at work by friends.
You said that they were suspicious,
that they followed you home.
But it wasn't them.
Of course it was, Kit.
(knocking on door)
MAN: Kit? Kit?
THREDSON: And maybe Alma
had had enough of the hiding,
of the shame.
And when she confronted
you about it, you snapped.
(yells)
Your rage at Alma's shame had
finally found its real target.
You killed the thing
you loved the most.
It wasn't me.
It wasn't him.
I know what I saw.
You didn't see anything,
because you weren't there.
I know where I came from, Sister.
Can you say the same
about your Dr. Arden?
("Dominique" playing)
MAN:
From the Commonwealth Gazette
in Western Massachusetts,
for her searing,
six-part exposé
of the horrific mental health
abuses at Briarcliff Manor,
home for the criminally insane,
where she was held against her will
and subjected to unspeakable torture,
the brave Miss Lana Winters.
(applause)
Thank you.
I want to thank my real heroes:
The other inmates at Briarcliff,
whose stories broke my heart
and inspired me to survive.
Like Martha.
They say when she first arrived,
she was young and beautiful.
She had suffered a nervous breakdown
after her husband committed suicide.
When I met her,
she banged her head against the wall
pretty much every single day.
And Rudy.
Diagnosed as a chronic masturbator,
Sister Jude's cane did
little to help his habit.
In fact, he got worse.
They tried hard to crush my spirit.
(screaming, electricity crackling)
"Something there is
that doesn't love a wall"
(words echo quietly)
"That sends the
frozen-ground-swell under it,
And..."
To destroy my mind
so I'd forget what I saw.
"...the upper boulders
in the sun..."
(words echo quietly)
I did everything
I could think of to survive.
And then I did what I had to do
to get out.
(swallows hard)
How soon can we begin your therapy?
Are you seeing Sister Jude's
face in the dough?
I want to punch her, too, for
making us work double shifts.
What if I am crazy?
Huh? What if I imagined
the whole thing?
The spaceship,
the creatures, Alma abducted.
What if... what if
I made it all up
because I couldn't face
up to what I'd done?
Why are you saying this now?
Dr. Thredson, he...
he said some things that
are starting to make sense.
Well, if you were crazy,
they wouldn't make sense to you.
Self-doubt is
a sure sign of sanity.
Wait, you're confusing me.
If... you're saying
that if I'm crazy,
then I wouldn't believe
Dr. Thredson, but if I'm sane,
then my crazy stories would be true?
I have no idea what you just said.
What am I?
Crazy or sane?
Am I a killer?
I don't care.
Whatever you are,
I'll be with you.
(moaning, panting)
(grunting)
(both panting)
(door opens)
I've taken the liberty
of choosing one, Sister Jude.
A cane befitting
their... transgression.
I don't know what's gotten
into you lately, Sister,
but it's a decided improvement.
You two...
are far too familiar.
You're drawn to each other
like the serpent and the apple.
Are you purposely trying
to make a murder baby?
Grace didn't kill anyone.
She told me her story;
She was framed.
Just give us our beating
and get it over with.
I think a more reliable step
needs to be taken:
Sterilization, for the both of you.
You can't do that.
What is it?
Two detectives are here
questioning Dr. Arden.
I don't know about what.
Sister...
see to it that these two are secured
till the paperwork for
the procedure is approved.
FRANK:
I'll take 'em to solitary.
Frank... why don't you take
Grace, and I'll take Kit.
Would that be all right, Sister Jude?
Just make sure they're kept apart.
Come on. Let's go, get up.
Let's go.
It's good advice, Kit.
She's not the innocent girl
she claims to be.
Dr. Arden, I'd like
to go over with... oh.
Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
I wasn't aware you had visitors.
I'm Sister Jude.
I run this facility.
Detective Byers.
This is Detective Connors.
Detectives. My gracious.
This really doesn't
concern you, Sister.
Two police detectives questioning
one of my most valued staff members
concerns me greatly.
Maybe the sister can help.
A nun would make one
hell of a character witness.
If it's a question of the doctor's
character, I've got lots to say.
Well, your colleague here
has been accused of roughing up
a certain lady of the evening.
A prostitute?!
No need to retire to your
fainting couch, Sister.
Because all of this
is an egregious lie.
I've never even met the woman.
It must have been frightening,
meeting strange men,
what with a killer on the loose.
She says she saw some things
which alarmed her.
Obscene material,
pornography...
...Nazi memorabilia.
When she tried to leave his home,
he got physical with her.
No!
This is utter hogwash.
I was here.
Can you verify that for us, Sister?
Did you say Nazi memorabilia?
This is outrageous.
I have no idea what
I'm even being accused of.
One would think that
the Wausaukee County Police Department
would have something
better to do with its time.
I know I have.
Good day to you.
Aren't you going to arrest him?
For what?
Well, you're the Vice detectives.
Actually, Sister, we're Homicide.
Homicide?
Certain details of the victim's
statement caught our eye.
Maybe we can ask you a question.
It's about one of your patients here,
Kit Walker. What about him?
He seemed like the kind of guy
that would have the surgical
skill to remove a woman's skin?
And her head?
(stifled retch)
What is this stuff?
Apomorphine.
The standard drug
for this kind of cutting-edge
aversion therapy.
They use it at Harvard,
Brigham Young, Cornell.
The theory is that we're
training your body
to be physically repelled
by certain...
triggers.
How did you get that?
From your house, when I was there.
I thought you might want it.
Say when.
(shuddering)
I need a few more minutes...
I need a few minutes
before the next one.
I'm very impressed with
your determination, Lana.
Let's take a break from that.
Let's move on to the conversion part
of your therapy.
I think you might
actually enjoy this part.
You know Daniel.
I've asked him to help out
with your treatment.
He told me that he thinks
you're a very good person,
and he would be honored
to participate
in anything that might liberate you.
Whatever you say, Doctor.
I want to do whatever works.
Good.
Let's get started, then.
Daniel...
We'll begin with
very simple visual stimulation.
Daniel will take off his robe,
and you will regard his physique.
(panting)
I'm sorry, but...
I don't feel anything.
That's okay.
You're not gonna make
him touch me, are you?
Actually, I'm going to ask you...
to touch yourself.
Can you do that?
I don't know...
Try to focus on his genitals.
THREDSON: Good.
Good, Lana.
Now, take your other hand
and place it on Daniel's member.
(gasping)
(exhaling sharply)
Good.
Good. Now keep
touching yourself
and try to relate the
pleasure that you're feeling
to his tumescence.
(sobs)
(panting)
You're doing good work, Lana.
(gasps, sobs)
We're all rooting for you.
Oh!
(vomits)
Give me a few minutes!
Please just
give me a few more seconds!
I know I can do it!
In a perfect world,
I would love to dive
into talk therapy,
discover the root of your fixation,
but my expertise is telling me
that aversion/conversion therapy
won't work with you.
(whimpers)
Sister Jude, we need to talk.
Yes, I agree.
The police came
to Briarcliff last night.
It seems
Dr. Arden solicited a...
a woman of the night.
The young woman found
Nazi souvenirs in his bedroom.
Are the police pursuing
a case against him?
No, I don't believe so, but...
Sister, this obsession with
Dr. Arden has to stop.
But there's mounting evidence
that this man is a war criminal.
Just a moment.
Where are you getting
this information?
There is a patient who
survived the death camps.
She remembers him.
Which patient is this?
Her name is Anne.
Anne who?
Anne Frank.
I know it... I know how
it sounds, but you...
No, I really don't think you do.
(whispers):
I saw a prison tattoo.
She was in Auschwitz.
Where's she now, hiding in the attic?
You're so eager
to believe any calumny,
any vile thing said
about this man you despise
that you're taking the word of
an inmate in a mental ward.
Father, this isn't about me.
I am trying to protect you,
this institution, our dream!
You imperil the dream, Sister,
by refusing to face your own failures.
You'd rather see Nazi war
criminals in our midst
than look in the mirror.
Or maybe this job is too much for you.
No, this job means everything to me.
You know that.
All I know is that you've
been drinking again.
Several of our employees witnessed
you were a drunken fool
on the night of the escape,
slurring your words, almost slobbering
during the introduction of the
film from your movie night.
Do you think alcohol has compromised
your judgment in these matters?
You don't need to answer now.
Reflect.
Pray on it.
(phone ringing)
Hello.
They're on to you, Arthur.
If you have any housekeeping
to take care of,
I suggest you do it now.
(wheezing)
Mother Superior, I have slipped.
Oh, dear.
Pressures had mounted all around me,
and then this
God-forsaken storm.
And somehow there was a carafe
of communion wine left in my office.
That's how God is.
He loves to test us.
Well, I failed.
And now he's giving
you another opportunity.
God loves to see us triumph.
It gives Him pleasure.
Was your alcoholic
transgression the only reason
you sought my counsel today, my child?
(wry laugh)
No, Mother.
There's an employee of Briarcliff
who I believe is a sadist
and possibly a war criminal.
Have you brought this to the
attention of your monsignor?
He has declined to pursue
justice or action.
The men of our church...
your Monsignor Timothy,
even the Holy Father himself,
by their very nature
they react out of fear
when confronted with tough questions.
It's their instinct
to protect themselves,
cover their mistakes.
Now, I'm familiar with
somebody who may help you.
Oh, no, Mother, I cannot,
I will not go behind the back
of the man who gave me
my mission in life;
Who believed in me;
With whom I share a dream.
He is not who made you
who you are, Jude.
You came to me a tortured woman,
ravaged by alcohol and guilt,
but you had a compass.
That was your gift.
And God gave you that
gift for a purpose.
Now he's put obstacles in your path,
and like all this debris
after the storm,
it's up to you to make
clear that path again.
(outer door opens, rattles)
(outer door shuts)
(door shuts)
(gasping anxiously)
Kit?
Kit, are you all right?
Did they... Cut my balls off?
Not yet.
(laughs quietly)
I was so worried.
You are the only person I ever
had a second thought about
in this hellhole.
Why'd you lie to me, Grace?
There was no man named Red.
You killed your stepmother
and then your father.
What do you want?
You want to hear me
say I'm sorry for what I've done?
I'm not sorry.
(bangs on wall)
Tell me the truth!
(sighs deeply)
I was so young when it started.
My father would come
into my room at night...
and do things.
(door creaking)
Sometimes I felt like
I was in a dream,
watching him do it to a stranger,
or a corpse.
I finally got the courage
to tell my stepmother.
(scrubbing)
She gave me candy to keep quiet.
(scrubbing continues)
(screams)
There was truth to the story
I told before, Kit.
I loved my horses.
They were my escape.
(sighs)
I found out he sold them all.
(panting heavily)
Patsy...
(shrieking)
That's when I woke up
and saw my life for what it was.
And once I opened my eyes,
there was no turning back.
Have I opened your eyes, Kit?
Are you repulsed by what I am?
No.
I admire you.
("Dominique" playing)
(woman wailing in distance)
I want to talk to you.
I haven't been able to sleep
since you left my office.
(sighs)
I'm so sorry, Lana.
I wish I had been a real help.
I'm not an aversion therapy advocate,
but I thought it made
sense in the moment.
Now I wish I'd spared you.
You tried.
I brought you this.
Thought you'd want it.
(whispering):
They'll never let me keep this.
You only have to hide it
until the end of the week.
I'm leaving here on Friday
and I am taking you with me.
I don't know how yet, but...
I will not leave you
in this place, Lana.
That's a promise.
SISTER JUDE: I understand
you want to confess.
I can only regard this as a ploy,
considering the circumstances.
You were, after all,
caught in the act.
No, uh, Sister, this is, uh,
this is not about Grace and me.
This is about my crimes.
Your crimes.
Yeah.
And I know I'm not
a very religious man,
but I did go to Sunday School,
and I was taught
that God sees everything.
Is that true?
It is. And He does.
Even if I might not remember
some terrible act
that I might have committed?
He knows, right?
(tires screeching, crashing)
God knows all.
Well, then He knows...
if I murdered those women.
He knows if I... if I did
those horrible things.
And He knows if I killed Alma.
Did you?
I must have.
I mean...
(cries quietly)
...everyone's saying that I did.
(sobbing quietly)
And those creatures, the creatures,
they can't really exist.
I remember when
I first showed up here,
you said to me that,
in order to find forgiveness,
that I had to... (sobs)
that I had to... that I had
to admit to what I'd done.
Sister...
I need to be forgiven.
God forgives all who seek Him.
Then help me.
Please.
Help me find God.
I'll admit to everything that I've done.
My child...
...we're all sinners,
every one of us.
But the things I've done, Sister...
That you can't recall.
(crying)
(grunting)
Now, what have you been
saying about me?
The truth. I know who you are!
(scoffs)
You don't even know who you are.
Anne Frank?! She died!
Or didn't you bother to read the book?
Your lies have caused me
a great deal of embarrassment.
What are you going to do to me?
The same things you did to
those girls in Auschwitz? Huh?
I was never in Auschwitz.
I'm from Scottsdale!
Liar! I bet it looked
a lot like this place!
You want to know what goes on in here?
You're about to find out.
Where'd you get that?
I'm not the only one who's on to you.
Oh... oh, sorry. (Laughs)
Come on...
now's the time.
Confess, Hans Gruper.
Nazi piece of shit.
(clattering, thudding)
What's that?
(gunshot, Arden yells in pain)
Bitch! What is in that room?
Go to hell. I've been there.
Give me the key. (Spits)
(yells in pain) Give me the key!
Want to lose another leg?
(lock clicks, door creaks)
Kill me.