(engine shuts off)
(muffled talking,
phone ringing)
Mr. Goodman?
Mr. Goodman was my father,
alev hashalom.
Please call me Sam.
I am sorry we have
to meet like this,
but confidentiality is the
heart and soul of my work.
Yes, uh, Mother Claudia
explained all that to me.
She's the only one
who knows I'm here.
I'd like to keep it that way.
The monsignor,
he thinks I've lost my mind,
but I haven't.
I, um... I trust my instincts.
Instincts are everything.
We ignore them at our peril.
Do I... pay you for this?
No, no, no, no.
I don't do this for money.
It's more of a calling.
Did you lose someone?
(sighs)
Everyone.
Is that for me?
Um...
Please sit.
Thank you.
He goes by the name Arden,
but I believe his real name
may be Grouper.
He may have been an SS doctor.
I mean, there's hardly
anything at all in there.
Um, just a home address,
and even that my be a lie.
(chuckles)
Probably is a lie, all of it.
What do you mean?
Have you heard
of Operation Paperclip?
After the war, the Joint
Intelligence Objectives Agency
actively recruited
the best Nazi scientists.
To get around Truman's
express orders
to exclude Nazi supporters,
they created false biographies
for these men.
Forgive the question,
but have you ever seen him
without a shirt on?
Me?
Oh, no, no, never.
SS have a tattoo
of their blood type here.
It's how they were
easily identified
by the Allied Forces
after the liberation.
Do I need to look for it?
(quietly): No, no, no.
In fact, don't do anything
until I've completed my work.
If he is who you suspect,
the last thing you want to do
is corner him.
Dr. Arden?
Stop. You leave him there.
Where's Sister Jude?
I have to speak
to her right away.
This man is a monster.
You should see what
he's got in his office.
Go, Sister.
I've waited
so many years for this.
I can wait a few more minutes.
FRANK: Drop the gun, or I'll blow
your goddamn head off.
SISTER JUDE: You put up a
bit of a fight, I hear.
You had to be sedated.
Where did you
get the gun, Anne?
I took it off
one of those detectives.
And it's a good thing I did.
He would've killed me.
Dr. Arden?
Grouper.
Hans Grouper, I told you.
He's a Nazi.
The thing in his lab,
- did you see it?
- What thing?
Tell me, what do you
think you saw?
Oh, God. He got rid of it
before anyone could see.
Dr. Arden was in no condition
to do any such thing.
When I arrived, he was being
rushed to the hospital.
Good. I hope he dies.
Now, come on, wake up.
He's not going to die.
He'll be back here and soon.
Maybe with the police,
maybe with the monsignor.
You could end up
on his operating table,
and I out on the street,
so before that happens,
I want you to tell me
what you think you saw.
Go and look.
SISTER JUDE: We did look.
Now, Frank says you claimed
to have seen
some sort of creature
that was alive.
(hinges creak)
Maybe it escaped on its own.
I doubt that, Sister.
It had no legs.
Sister Jude?
Can't you see I'm busy?
There's a man in your office.
What man?
Did he say what he wanted?
His wife.
MAN: Her name is Charlotte.
Charlotte Brown
is her married name.
She was born Charlotte Cohen.
That's our son, David.
He's a sweet little boy,
but he has the colic.
He cries five,
six times a night.
Nothing we can do
to comfort him.
It's enough to make anyone
a little cuckoo,
especially a woman
as high-strung as Charlotte.
(chuckles) Cuckoo.
High-strung.
How about world-class actress?
She was very convincing,
playing Anne Frank.
That's how it all started.
She read the diary,
and when she was
eight months pregnant,
we drove down to Boston to see
a production of Anne Frank.
Just sort of hit her
in some personal way
when she saw the play.
I would say
that people sometimes
remark that she resembled
Anne Frank.
They were the same age.
So, the tattoo
on her arm...
Charlotte?
What the hell are you doing?
And all of this happened
after a night in the theater?
No. It all started
after we had the baby.
She couldn't sleep
because of the crying.
She said it made her
feel powerless.
She began to turn a deaf ear,
and then she began
leaving the house
and going to a library
to read about Auschwitz.
It's almost like
she wanted to relive it.
That she somehow could
change the outcome.
She'd go on about these babies
who were gassed
and tortured, and I'd ask her,
"What about your own baby,
Charlotte?"
(baby crying)
He doesn't want me.
He wants you.
- He wants his mother.
- I keep telling you,
I can't help it!
He's not the one
who needs me.
She'd come home with bags
full of old newspapers,
art supplies.
She'd disappear into the den
to work on her project.
THREDSON: Sounds to me
like a classic case
of postpartum psychosis.
How long have you
been standing there,
Dr. Butt-in-ski?
Long enough to make a
pretty good diagnosis.
The obsession, the manic
behavior, the disconnection
from her baby.
My wife isn't a psychotic.
She's a very emotional person.
She needs to come home.
I think that's dangerous.
Did you hear what he said?
The man wants his wife at home.
They made me change my clothes,
Sister Jude.
Why do I have to wear
this uncomfortable dress?
I don't care for it anymore.
It'll help make the
transition easier.
You're letting me go?
Charlotte?
My God, Charlotte.
I've been looking for you.
My name is Anne.
Charlotte,
it's time to come home.
Stay away from me.
My name is Anne Frank.
I'm a death camp survivor.
You're my wife and the
mother of our baby.
Now, please stop this
and come home with me.
No! You don't know me.
Sister Jude,
you have to help me.
I'm helping you, Charlotte.
I'm trying to reunite you
with your family.
What about Grouper?
His crimes against humanity?
No, no, go home.
Go home.
It can't be.
David needs you.
My baby?
I need you.
Everything's going
to be all right.
Okay? You'll see.
(door closes)
You're making a mistake.
Forget about it, Doctor.
It's none of
our concern anymore.
Kit Walker is my concern.
What's this barbaric rumor
I hear about sterilization?
- It's not a rumor.
- You're not a doctor.
You have no right
to authorize medical procedures
without their consent.
Are you afraid?
No.
I don't believe you.
Alma and I always wanted kids.
We always talked
about having two or three.
Always tomorrow.
And now there will be
no tomorrow.
For either of us.
I'm so sorry.
I got us into this mess.
No. I don't regret what we did.
There's no one to blame
except Sister Jude.
I think she's the devil.
(distant screaming,
footsteps approaching)
(keys jangling)
(lock clicking)
Now?
Yes.
If you hurry, you might
be able to have supper.
Supper?
I thought you were taking me
for the operation.
No, Kit.
Sister Jude changed her mind.
She said you showed signs
of true redemption.
You're being released
from solitary.
Yay.
What about Grace?
Oh, I haven't forgotten
about her.
GRACE: I can't believe
you'll hear me say this,
but I actually miss
the food from the kitchen.
Oh, you won't be eating tonight.
No food for
12 hours before the procedure.
You said Sister Jude
changed her mind.
For Kit. Rest up, dear.
You're going under the knife
in the morning.
You'll need your strength.
No. No, you can't do that!
Let me out!
Come back! Let me out!
Let me out! Someone!
(screams)
(rumbling)
We're leaving
right after dinner.
Meet me by the
front staircase at 6:00.
Is this real?
Don't be late.
Kit.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Doc, you got to help Grace.
Jude's going to sterilize her.
- It's not right.
- Grace isn't my patient, Kit.
You are.
So, why don't we
just concentrate on you...
...and then I'll see
what I can do for Grace.
Deal?
Have you given thought
to what we discussed last time?
You want me to say I killed Alma
and those other ladies.
Only if you believe it's true.
You need to give yourself
permission to remember.
I think one way to do that
is to hear it in your own words.
I want you to describe
what you think happened.
Then I'll play it back for you
so you can hear it
in your own voice,
- with your own ears.
- And if I do that,
you're going to tell the courts
that I should...
that I should stay here,
and I-I won't go to the chair?
Yes. That is the bargain.
But I need to feel
you're sincere.
My name is Kit Walker.
And I murdered my wife.
Don't fight it.
It'll only make it worse.
Who is it?
What are you? My name is Alma.
(screaming)
SISTER JUDE: Can you take down
a message for Mr. Goodman?
Goodman. Tell him...
it was all a mistake and that
he should just go back home.
I gave him
the wrong information.
No, the wrong information.
Thanks.
What information was that?
It's not important.
It sounded to me
as if there was some
juicy little tidbit
stuck in your craw.
Oh, come on, Sister,
spit it up.
- You'll feel better.
- How's your leg?
Please.
Let's dispense
with the small talk, shall we?
You and I both know that,
during my absence,
you finally got a chance
to stick your nose in my lab.
A patient made a complaint.
I was obliged to follow up.
And?
It wasn't all that interesting.
I see.
Do you mind?
You should probably know
that I plan
on pressing charges.
To what end?
She's a confused young woman.
No, not her.
You. On your watch,
that crazy bitch got
a hold of a loaded gun,
and you sent her home without
so much as a slap on the wrist.
Your ineptitude is staggering.
Dr. Arden...
I know, in the past,
you and I have had
our differences,
and you're certainly
entitled to a...
a sense of safety here.
I hope, perhaps you and
I can start afresh.
Is that your idea
of an apology?
(chuckles)
Is that what you're
looking for... an apology?
No.
I'd prefer you grovel.
I think I'm entitled to it.
Perhaps if you prostrated
yourself on the floor
and begged my forgiveness.
No?
Barring that,
I have no other option
but to call the monsignor
and demand your dismissal.
You're through here, Sister.
And you know it.
(door closes)
SISTER EUNICE: Let me do that.
Sister!
- I didn't hear you.
- Now, now.
It's all right, Arthur.
You've nothing
to be ashamed of.
All the nuns here have had
some training as nurses. Sit.
I've been meaning
to speak to you.
I wanted to apologize
for my behavior
the night of the storm.
It was... untoward.
What do you say we chalk it up
to the barometric pressure
and never speak of it again?
I know what you did, Sister.
Thank you for protecting me.
Protecting us.
Even though I don't
fully understand your work,
I feel I've been
an important part of it.
ARDEN:
And so you have, my cherub.
(wheezing)
You'll be free
to continue that work
once Sister Jude
has been turned out.
The monsignor
will put you in charge,
and you'll need
a strong right hand.
Someone you can trust.
I trust you...
completely.
And I'm very impressed
that you managed to get her out
and into the woods
all on your own.
You'd be surprised.
She weighed very little.
(school bell ringing)
(children squealing playfully)
(blows whistle)
Mikey Curtis,
no monkey business!
(screams)
Peggy Cartwright,
what on earth is the matter?
There's a monster!
(all scream)
(shrieking)
(shrieking continues)
(Charlotte whimpering)
ARDEN: Well, well, well.
Look what the cat dragged in.
That didn't take very
long now, did it?
Stay away from me.
Not so tough without your gun.
(door slams)
You didn't give it
much of a chance.
I have to go to work.
I'm afraid to leave her alone.
It's a period of adjustment.
I mean, you said yourself,
a baby needs its mother.
A normal mother, yes!
Charlotte's not normal!
She's worse.
At least before,
she could tune out the crying.
(baby crying) Charlotte?
Do you want to hold your baby?
(crying continues)
Yes, darling,
why don't I do that?!
Hey, stop it!
Are you insane?!
I thought if I brought her home,
she spent time with us,
she'd remember who she was,
see how much we need her.
Please, Sister.
You have to take her.
I can't handle her.
Isn't there some family
that could stay with her?
She needs professional help,
the care of a good doctor.
Like the doctor that came
in here and diagnosed her.
He seemed to understand
what she needed.
Dr. Thredson?
You're welcome to consult with
him if that's what you want.
Frank?
Find Dr. Thredson,
send him here.
Are you ready?
What's the plan?
How do we do this?
We'll walk out the door,
we'll walk straight to my car.
Do you understand?
What do you mean?
How do we get past the guard?
Like I said, walk.
Night, Jimmy.
Dr. Thredson!
Excuse me. What were you...?
Dr. Arden?
That's right.
Oh, my God. You're the...
you're the man my wife shot.
Thank you for not
pressing charges.
She doesn't know
what she was doing.
She's out of her mind.
Yes, I'm aware
of that, Mr. Brown.
But you needn't worry.
I see no reason
for punitive action.
Not when there's a far more
humane remedy at hand.
As a matter of fact,
we could do it tonight.
Then she'll be home
by tomorrow, a new woman.
Dr. Thredson!
Dr. Thredson, Sister
Jude is asking for you.
Anne Frank, or whoever she is,
her husband brought her back.
(trunk slams)
I don't work here
anymore, Frank.
As a matter of fact,
I never did.
You can tell her I said that.
(engine starts)
(sniffling, whimpering)
Are you sure that this is safe?
ARDEN: Not only safe,
but highly effective.
In my hands,
the transorbital lobotomy
has become as routine as...
filling a cavity.
Holy apostle, Saint Jude,
faithful servant
and friend of Jesus,
the patron of hopeless cases
and things almost despaired of,
pray for me,
who am so miserable.
Make use, I implore thee,
of the particular privilege
that is accorded to thee,
to bring visible and speedy help
where help was almost
despaired of.
(knocking)
Um, bad news.
We searched everywhere.
Lana Winters
is nowhere to be found.
I'm certain she's off grounds,
Sister.
(sighs)
You know, when I was a child,
I'd come home after school
to an empty house.
My father had flown the coop,
and my mother worked
as a maid in a hotel.
It was lonely,
so I brought in
a baby squirrel I'd found,
and kept him in a shoebox.
And then, one day,
when I came home,
he looked sickly.
He was dead already,
but I didn't know that.
I'd forgotten to...
feed him for a couple days.
So I took him out of the box
and I laid him on the table
and I prayed my heart out
for several hours.
And when my mother came home
and found us,
she screamed bloody murder.
She picked him up
and threw him in the garbage.
She worked hard, my mother.
She was exhausted,
and she couldn't have known
how cruel that was.
But I cried and cried, saying,
"God didn't answer my prayers!"
(chuckles ruefully)
I remember...
my mother was pouring herself
a whiskey;
The Martin family cure
for everything.
She looked at me and laughed.
"God always answers
our prayers, Judy."
It's just rarely...
"the answer we're looking for."
It's over for me, Frank.
My goose is cooked.
I certainly hope
you're not blaming yourself.
Men are never gonna accept
a woman taking charge,
especially not a woman
as strong as you are.
In my opinion,
you never really had a chance.
(gasps)
(watch ticking)
♪ ♪
What's your poison, sweetheart?
(Thredson exhales)
Make yourself at home.
- Dr. Thredson?
- Oliver.
I really appreciate
everything you've done, but...
I think I want
to go to my house.
Lana, once they discover
you missing,
the first place
they'll look is there.
You're much safer here...
at least for the night.
First thing in the morning,
we go to the police.
I already have an appointment
set up with Detective Spears.
I trust him implicitly.
We present the evidence,
together we shut down
Briarcliff.
(quiet laugh)
Relax. That place
is behind you.
Please, come in. Have a seat.
You've had an incredibly
stressful day.
I'm going to prescribe a little
something to take the edge off.
I-I don't want any medicine.
A big, delicious glass of wine.
Well, that doesn't sound
half bad.
White or red?
Red.
(cork pops)
(wine pours)
(line ringing)
No calls.
I was trying to get a hold
of my friend Lois...
she might have heard
something about Wendy.
Lana, you have to realize
that I am at risk as well here.
I broke you out
of a mental institution.
I can't afford to let
anyone know where you are.
Not until we go
public tomorrow.
You're gonna write about this.
You're gonna win
a Pulitzer Prize.
I just know it, Lana.
You are the person
to tell my story.
Your story?
Here's to taking down
Briarcliff.
Hear, hear.
Mint?
Boy... (quiet laugh)
That wine, um,
went straight to my head.
Would you mind
if I used your restroom?
Sure.
It's right down the hall.
Thank you.
(deep exhale)
(door opens)
I think I made a wrong turn.
I see you found my little...
hobby.
(breathing heavy)
You make furniture?
Lamps mainly.
I make the shades myself.
Really?
What kind of material
do you use?
(inhales) Skin.
(screams)
Grace?
When'd you get...
Oh, God.
Hey, we need a doctor!
Those bastards... I can't believe
they actually did it.
Dr. Thredson, he promised me
this wasn't going to happen.
MAN: Kit Walker, you're under arrest
for the murder of Donna Burton,
Alison Riedel and Alma Walker.
- Wait.
- Where's Thredson?
You guys need
to talk to Dr. Thredson.
- No, we don't.
- It's a mistake.
We got his evaluation
and your taped confession.
- Come on, Kit. Let's go.
- No, he didn't do it.
She's alive.
- What?
- Everything you said is true.
For Christ sakes,
let me talk to her!
I saw her!
Alma's alive.
(yells)
I saw her!
(groaning)
Hello?
Hello?!
Wendy.
Oh, my God.
Wendy...
Wendy.
(crying): Wendy!
(screams)
(yells)
THREDSON: She's been
on ice for a while.
I was hoping she'd be
a little more pliable
by the time you came to.
What's happening?
What did you do to her?!
Kept her fresh.
(exhales)
Normally, by now, I would've...
removed the skin.
And head.
No, we need to keep her around
a little longer
for our purposes.
We're going to continue
our therapy now, Lana.
You can begin...
by kissing her cold lips.
Don't worry.
She won't bite.
I took her teeth.
(screams)
Shh.
♪ If we could consider
each other ♪
♪ A neighbor, a friend
or a brother ♪
♪ It could be a wonderful,
wonderful world ♪
♪ It could be
a wonderful world ♪
♪ If each little kid could
have fresh milk each day ♪
♪ If each working man
had enough time to play ♪
♪ If each homeless soul
had a good place to stay ♪
♪ It could be
a wonderful world ♪
JIM: Honey, I'm home!
♪ If we could consider
each other... ♪
What are you kids up to?
We're just cleaning
up down here.
♪ It could be a wonderful,
wonderful world ♪
♪ It could be
a wonderful world ♪
I smelled something
yummy in the kitchen.
Pot roast.
With carrots,
potatoes and onions.
(exhales) Well,
I'm gonna make a martini.
Don't be silly...
I can make that for you.
I can clean up down here
tomorrow.
Is that trash?
- I can take this.
- That would be swell.
You seem happy, sweetheart.
Are you as happy as you look?
I've never been happier.
♪ It could be
a wonderful world ♪
♪ If we could consider
each other ♪
♪ A neighbor, a friend
or a brother ♪
♪ It could be a wonderful,
wonderful world ♪
♪ It could be
a wonderful world ♪
♪ It could be a wonderful,
wonderful world ♪
♪ It could be ♪ ♪ It could be ♪
♪ It could be
a wonderful world ♪