Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Fiona.
Fiona!
I thought you had gone
with the other girls
down to Jackson Square
to burn your bra.
Why?
So I can gag
on the toxic fumes coming off
all that burning Playtex?
No, thanks.
Fiona, you're wicked.
When did you first know
you were destined
to become the next Supreme?
I was just 29 years old
when the reigning
Supreme at the time,
MiMi DeLongpre,
called a Council and I
performed the Seven Wonders
and was unanimously proclaimed
to be the true born heir
of the Supremacy.
I wasn't talking
about the Council.
When did you know?
In your bones?
Well, I will tell you.
By the time I was your age,
I had already been
manifesting multiple powers.
It's not unusual
for a talented witch
to manifest four,
even five innate gifts
once she starts to flower.
But that does not
make you the Supreme.
Only the mastery of the Seven
Wonders could prove that.
So let me prove it.
Don't be a fool.
You're still a child.
Even if you are next in line.
I am ready.
And I say you're not.
Because you don't want
to be replaced...
by me.
Careful, girl.
Don't test my wrath.
They say when a new Supreme
starts to flower,
the old Supreme begins to fade.
You've been fading Anna Leigh.
Shall I show you my power?
You're weak, Anna Leigh.
We both know why.
Diabetes, heart trouble,
liver failure.
God knows what else.
As I get stronger,
you get weaker.
You vicious little gash.
I've seen the ruin
you will bring this coven
if you are allowed
to take power now.
You're a selfish,
craven little child, Fiona.
And I will make it my mission
to ensure that you will
never take the throne.
I'll see you burn
in hell first.
Fine, save me a spot.
What's the matter?
Cat got your tongue?
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
It's a dance, a dance
no one ever had to teach me.
A dance I've known
since I first saw
my reflection
in my father's eyes.
My partners have been princes
and starving artists,
Greek gods and clowns.
And everyone of them
certain they lead.
But it's always my dance.
I make the first move,
which is no move at all.
I've always just understood
that they will eventually
find themselves
in front of me.
Primitive, beautiful animals.
Their bodies responding
to the inevitability of it all.
It's my dance
and I have performed it
with finesse and abandon
with countless partners.
Only the faces change.
And all this time,
I never suspected
the night would come
when the dance would end.
I always respect
a good hard slap.
Just don't make me look
like a goddamn trout
when I walk out of here.
Is that the video?
Yes, as we discussed.
But please let me underline
that this is
an instructional video
shot for surgeons.
If I am going to commit
to butchery,
I want to see exactly
how the sausage is made.
As you can see,
the human face isn't attached
to the skull at all.
After I make the initial
incision... here,
then I'll have the freedom
to stretch and
tighten the skin.
Then fat cells harvested
through liposuction
are packed in the cheekbones
to create fullness.
So, what made you
come to see me?
No one else has bothered.
I've been feeling so haunted.
It all seemed
so unfair, so random.
You know, a truly
decent person like him.
I can't even imagine
what it must be like for you.
Losing your son.
He had a stash in his room.
I've been sleeping in there.
I'm driving.
They didn't tell
me he had a girl.
It wasn't romantic,
Mrs. Spencer.
I see.
Well, you're a good friend.
That's what matters.
God bless him.
When his father left,
he became the man of this house.
He worked part-time
as an SAT tutor.
He did repairs.
People said that's a lot
of pressure to put on a boy.
He was just a...
he was a natural gentleman
in his bones.
Yeah.
He was like that.
Can I share something with you?
I don't want to burden you.
Of course.
That's why I came.
I almost didn't answer.
But something told me I should.
You were a saint to make
that call, you sweet girl.
I wish I was as sweet
as you think.
I wish I
could hold him again.
And kiss him.
If only to say good-bye.
You'll see him again.
I envy you believers.
I don't know
how it works either.
But I'm telling you,
Mrs. Spencer.
Kyle has not left us.
♪ La-la-la-da-la-da
♪ La-la-
la-da-la-da ♪
♪ La-la-la-da-la-da
♪ La-da-la-la-da
♪ La-la-da-la-la-la-da...
He's cute.
Like butter on a stick.
What are you two yapping about?
Our new neighbors
moving in next door.
♪ La-da-la-da...
Where's your modesty?
Put your shirt on.
It's totally wet, Mom.
"Hell is naked before him and
destruction hath no covering."
♪ La-la-la-da
♪ La-da...
Get in the house,
put on a clean shirt.
♪ La-da.
I believe we can build
on the progress we've made.
Oh, no...
And continue to fight
for new jobs, new opportunity,
a new security
for the middle class...
Why, oh, Lord,
my God have you forsaken
this once proud country?
Oh, God.
Are you blubbering again?
Eternal life...
and all you can do with it
is stuff your face and cry.
That magic box lies.
Somebody...
somebody in there...
they just said that...
that-that Negro...
is the President
of the United States.
I voted for him.
Twice.
We've also had black
secretaries of states,
Supreme Court justices,
and even the poet laureate.
Lies.
You know, you've got
a lot to learn.
And you're gonna learn it
right here
inside the walls of this school.
Oh, God...
help me.
Congratulations, kiddo.
You... are the new maid.
Maid.
Have you any idea
with whom you are speaking?
Yes.
The maid unless you want
to go back in the box.
Can't stop thinking about
our new neighbor.
He's nice.
He's waiting for someone.
Maybe he likes
a little chocolate.
It's hilarious to listen
to you virgins get
all hot and bothered.
I'm not a virgin.
I'm not.
I get it on all the time.
And guys find me hot.
Look at you.
Who'd have thought we'd
have so much in common?
So what's your story, Queenie?
Who popped
your chocolate-covered cherry?
No one yet.
She's a virgin.
Shut up, Nan.
I'm saving myself.
You the bitch that blindsided
me with that candlestick.
How dare you open
your foul mouth to me, Negress.
Excuse me?
I may be a maid,
but there are limits
to my servitude.
You best put that food
down in front of me
before I Frisbee this
plate at your head.
Cracker bitch!
Hey!
What the hell is going on here?
Miss Aryan Sisterhood came
between Queenie and her food.
I will not stoop
to serve her kind.
You know, Delphine,
from now on you are gonna
be Queenie's personal slave.
And, Queenie, you ask her
to do whatever you need done:
make your bed,
scrub your toilet.
I don't give a shit.
Sweet.
There's nothing I hate
more than a racist.
♪ Wait a minute, baby
♪ Stay with me awhile
♪ Said you'd give me light
♪ But you never told me
about the fire ♪
Stevie didn't really
find her voice
until she and Lindsey
joined Fleetwood Mac.
That's the thing.
Can't be your best self
until you find your tribe.
I'm still looking for mine.
♪ Drownin'
♪ In the sea of love
Misty?
Zoe.
Come see.
♪ But now it's gone
♪ It doesn't matter what for
♪ When you build your house...
How did you do that?
It's the humic acid in the mud.
Burns, scrapes, bug bites.
I put Louisiana mud on anything.
This one's really deep.
I tried. That's the best
I could do.
♪ And it was just like
♪ A great dark wind
Kyle...
it's Zoe.
Do you remember me?
♪ I think I had met my match
♪ He was singing
♪ And undoing
Misty, I have to take him home.
His mother's a wreck.
Maybe seeing her will help
heal him in some way.
I healed him.
Me. I...
I bathed him and...
and fed him
and nursed him to health.
You did.
And I owe you big time.
Well, then s-stay...
stay for dinner.
Another time.
I promise.
♪ Ooh, ooh
♪ Said, "Sara...
♪ You're the poet
in my heart" ♪
No. No. No,
he's not ready yet.
He needs me.
We're connected.
Kyle, when she abandoned you,
I was there.
You can't just replace me.
Let him go.
Let him... let
him go. He wants
to go home.
Okay.
I'll come back for you.
I promise.
No, you won't.
♪ Hold on
♪ The night is comin'
♪ And the starling flew
for days... ♪
What do you expect
to get with that
stupid cake?
Just being neighborly.
What do you expect to get with
that dress?
Laid.
He's gonna be my fall fling.
Welcome to the neighborhood.
We're from next door.
My name is Nan.
Madison.
Thanks.
I'm Luke. Come in.
This looks amazing.
Homemade?
I bake.
The cake's just an excuse.
I saw you moving in.
You looked pretty good
without a shirt.
Made me interested in the rest
of the package.
Is this lemon?
It's yellow cake
with butter frosting. I
knew it'd be your favorite.
It's the one thing
I can't resist.
W... Are you seriously
ignoring me for dessert?
I get the feeling
you're used to being
the center of attention.
This is Madison Montgomery.
She's famous.
Well, we don't have TV.
Or Internet.
Sweet.
Well, is this
the welcoming committee?
And you brought baked goods.
Aren't you darling?
Well, we'd love to visit,
but we're running late
for church.
We'll take the cake to share.
Church?
It's not even
Sunday.
Bible study.
It's how we maintain
our personal relationship
with our Lord Jesus Christ.
You know that's all a crock
of shit, right?
I mean, why wait for some
phony
happily-ever-after
when you can have
your piece now, I say.
What about you, Luke?
I forbid you to talk to my son
or to set foot
in this house again.
I didn't say anything.
Both of you!
Get out of my house!
We'll pray for you.
I didn't know
you could do that.
Neither did I until now.
Hank doesn't know I'm here.
He's out of town bidding
on a construction project.
We tried alternative methods,
but...
they didn't take.
So here I am.
I'm glad you came.
I was actually gonna call you.
Oh?
Your, uh, blood work came back.
Ms. Foxx, we have a problem.
What kind of problem?
The kind that rules out
you having any sort
of elective surgery.
Now or for
the foreseeable future.
I'll find another doctor.
I can assure you no reputable
surgeon's gonna take you on.
Your blood work is alarming,
and your immune system seems
to be in some kind of...
free fall.
You simply can't have a baby.
There's got to be something
you can do.
I know how disappointing
this must be.
Times like these I wish I had
a magic wand I could wave.
But I don't.
That's right.
You don't.
♪ La-la-la-da-la-da
♪ La-da, la-da...
I know this is
the right thing, Kyle.
She's the one person in
the world that you'll remember.
Everything will make
sense when you see her.
Oh! Oh!
Well, who do we have here?
Joan Ramsey.
My... son Luke and I
moved into the old colonial
next door.
I'd like you to have this.
Hmm.
I always bring a copy
of the Good Book
whenever I come into someone's
house for the first time.
How devout of you.
May I offer you a drink?
No, I don't imbibe.
I don't know
if this is a school or...
a rehab facility or what it is,
but two of your girls
invaded my property.
One of them was dressed
so scandalously
I'm-I'm worried
about the long-term effect
it might have on Luke.
You know, I've never
understood you Bible-thumpers
and your hypocrisy towards sex.
I know, behind closed doors,
you are the biggest perverts
of all.
Your student threw a knife
at me.
It missed my head
by three inches.
Yeah. She has to
work on her aim.
I didn't come here to listen
to your drunken mocking.
Those girls had better not come
around my placain.
I will call the police
and I will
press charges.
Assault
with a deadly weapon, arson.
Arson?
The trashy one
lit my curtains on fire.
I don't know how she did it,
but she did it.
I conjured the Devil.
That's her.
You stay away from my boy.
Hmm, good luck
keeping him away from me.
He's so backed up all
I'd have to say is "panties"
and he'd jizz his jeans.
Stay away from my family.
In Jesus' name.
Madison.
Have you got a light?
Well done.
Right?
Who knew
I could do that?
Come here.
Sit down.
Let's talk.
Are you asleep?
I can't believe
you're really here.
I nearly died from
missing you, baby.
I was just thinking something.
It's keeping me awake.
Before, when you went
to go take a shower...
You're a different person.
Your body.
You look like someone else.
I don't understand
what's happening.
But that-that doesn't matter.
Doesn't it?
You're still my beautiful boy.
We're together again.
Let it all go.
I'm here now.
I said if you want breakfast,
you better carry your ass
downstairs and make it yourself.
Ain't nobody frying no eggs.
I'm looking for Marie.
I'm here to consult with her?
About a fertility problem?
Chinwe, Mambo here?
You want a Coca-Cola?
No, thank you.
Thank you for seeing me
right away.
I've heard about you
since I was a child.
Full disclosure...
I'm from...
Darling.
I know who you are.
Okay.
So tell me
about your fertility spell.
Oh, don't know nothing
about that.
Marie?
If you know who I am,
then you know I am well-aware
of the Pochaut Medecine.
Hmm.
Then you know
that spell ain't no picnic
for anyone involved.
On the day of,
you bring us two ounces
of your husband's baby gravy
in a mason jar.
We use a Guinea pepper...
hotter than Hades.
When the gods see this
willingness to suffer...
to sacrifice,
they pay attention.
When it's over,
I sleep for four days
and four nights.
How soon can we do it?
Got to be a new moon.
And $50,000 in cash up front.
Jesus.
We have a 100% success rate.
I'll find it somehow.
Borrow it, rob a bank.
When's the new moon?
Ain't gonna do
no Pochaut Medecine on you.
Not for $50,000.
Not for $100,000.
You were born
into the wrong tribe.
You the daughter
of my sworn enemy.
Fiona has got nothing
to do with me.
She has no idea I came to see you.
Ooh.
Hmm.
You are my one real shot
at this point.
Too late for tears.
Damage is done.
Waltzing in here
like she the Queen of England.
Talking about hammer and nails,
looking to start a war.
Fiona was here?
She done messed
with the wrong witch.
And she knows it.
And now you know it.
You like him.
Excuse me?
You're thinking about a boy.
I can tell.
You know it's rude to get
in people's heads like that.
You think I like having to hear
other people's thoughts
all the time?
I don't.
So stop.
Wish I could.
These help.
Hello?
Zoe, it happened.
Oh, hey, Alicia.
Kyle's come back to me.
Except...
it's not Kyle.
I'll be right over.
I'm not gonna apologize.
Whatever for?
For whatever it is
you want me to.
That's why we're here,
isn't it?
People in our position have
no need to apologize.
Our actions speak
for themselves.
I'm curious.
Have you always known
you were special?
Child actor,
poised beyond your years?
My mother put me to work
ever since I could talk.
I hated it.
It's hard to stop
when you're the only one
in your family making money,
you know.
You didn't have a good
relationship with her?
The last time I saw her,
she snorted half my coke,
and then let
the cops bust me for it.
She's a selfish bitch.
Hmm.
So was I.
Ask Cordelia.
I was a horrible mother.
And I regret it.
She's not dead.
You can change.
I've tried.
But I think it's too late.
I have so much to give.
So much to teach.
Teach me.
Self-preservation,
it's the most
primal instinct
of the human psyche.
So, what would it take...
to make a person disregard
their will to survive?
I don't get it.
Use your imagination.
Make what you want him to do
so much more attractive
than what he's actually doing.
Make him believe
he's safer
in the middle of the street.
Did I do that or did you?
I sure do love chicken potpie.
For dessert you can make me
a peach cobbler.
You never gonna catch
a man that way.
Let alone find one to love you.
You were my daughter,
I'd padlock that icebox
and throw away the key.
Peach cobbler won't keep
you warm at night.
My problem ain't food,
you dumb bitch.
It's love.
Dr. Phil says that kids
from broken homes
use food to replace love.
It's comforting.
Well, I think you best look
for a new physician.
What was that?
What was what?
Something is out there.
Ain't nothing out there.
Get back to work
before I smack you, slave.
No, it can't be.
God help me.
What the hell are you doing?
He's out there!
We have to hide.
What are you talking about? Who's out there?
My houseboy.
Your what?
No, don't unlock that!
He'll ravage both of us.
Bitch, you don't make
a bit of sense.
What the hell is that thing?
It's Bastien.
My houseboy.
He was a beast in life.
Now evermore so.
Enchanted no doubt
by the same dark magic
which has kept me alive.
Who are you?
I am Madame Delphine LaLaurie.
Mistress of the house
LaLaurie.
The Code Noir was replaced
by the Madame's
own code of terror.
Who brought you back-- Fiona?
The witch freed me only
to make me a slave.
You deserve worse if half of
what they say about you is true.
You unhand me.
Did you do that to him?
He violated my daughter.
Please, we have to hide.
I beg you... have mercy.
Please, don't...
don't let him take me.
Get up.
Get up!
Oh, wait...
Get out of here.
You go hide,
I'll take care of this.
Slave, wait.
Get out of here.
Oh, God, God...
Come on.
I won't hurt you.
Over here.
She told me what you did
to her daughter.
You just wanted love.
And that makes you a beast?
They call me that, too.
But that's not who we are.
We both deserve love
like everybody else.
Don't you want to love me?
Kyle, honey?
I have a little
surprise for you.
I invited your friend Zoe
to come join us
for dinner tonight.
What do you think
of that? Hmm?
She's a sweet girl.
I don't know why you didn't
tell me about her before.
Did you think I'd not approve?
I certainly hope
you don't feel like you have
to keep secrets from me.
I've been possessive.
I do know that.
I never meant
for it to go so far,
or go on for so long.
But I think maybe you
needed it as much as I did.
But now it's time
for you to move on
with your life, and I understand
that, and I want that.
Jesus, Kyle!
Why won't you talk to me?!
What's happened to you?
They were so sure you
were dead. They said
they identified your body.
Your body.
I know your body,
Kyle. I know it.
And this...
it's different!
You're different!
Who are you, if
you're not my son?!
My son. My son.
My sweet baby boy.
No one knows you like I do.
Not even that girl.
She doesn't know
how to please you.
Not like I can.
Mama knows how
to please you, baby.
It's okay.
No!
Kyle!
No! No!
No! No! No!
No! No...!
♪ Come on over, baby,
whole lot of shakin' goin' on ♪
♪ Yeah, come on over, baby
♪ Baby, you can't wrong
♪ Honey, I ain't fakin'
♪ I got a whole lot
of shakin' goin' on ♪
♪ Well, I said shake it
♪ I said, shake it, baby,
shake it ♪
♪ I said shake,
don't you let it break now ♪
♪ Shake it, shake it, shake
♪ Come on over
♪ Whole lot of shakin'
goin' on ♪
♪ Let's go, it's time now ♪
♪ Well, come on over, baby
♪ We got chicken in the barn
Ooh!
♪ Whose barn? What barn?
My barn ♪
♪ Come on, baby
♪ You know, I got the bull
by the horn, oh, yeah ♪
♪ I ain't fakin',
whole lot of shakin' goin' on ♪
♪ Easy now, say shake
♪ Ooh...
♪ Now let's go one time
♪ Shake it, baby, shake it
♪ Shake it, baby,
shake, come on now ♪
♪ Shake,
don't you let it break ♪
♪ But you got to shake,
oh, baby, shake ♪
♪ Come on over,
whole lot of shakin' going on. ♪
Hello?
Alicia?
Oh. Ooh.
Ladies.
Oh, you're looking well tonight.
Let me give you some advice.
Get your portrait painted
when you're young.
Just look at these old bats.
Mine is gonna go over here.
And yours'll go...
over there.
Doubt I'm even graduating
this shit show.
No way they're gonna
commemorate me.
Well, they'll have to...
...because you're
the next Supreme.
Wait.
Are you serious?
How do you know
I'm the next Supreme?
Because I am the old one.
And I'm dying.
My time is up,
and you're...
killing me.
Your powers--
you've been feeling
them growing?
Yeah, l-like crazy.
Have you ever wondered why?
Uh, apart from
my being awesome?
I'm the source.
My life force is literally
pouring out of my body
and into yours.
This is no mystical
mumbo-jumbo.
This is real.
I have cancer.
I won't last the year.
I have connections.
My agent can get
the best oncologist
in the country here in a flash.
Chemo?
Oh.
Oh, no, no.
No, no, no, I'm not going out
bald and shriveled and...
...begging for morphine.
No. I've lived a disreputable
life, but I've done it in style,
and I'll die likewise.
I don't belong on these walls.
I took my inheritance
too soon and
squandered it.
All that... power,
all those gifts.
I just took it
and poured it back into myself
and dressed it up in Chanel.
I was a shitty Supreme.
But, now, my mentor,
Anna Leigh Leighton--
now there was a Supreme.
She was majestic
and powerful.
She taught me everything I know.
You know how I thanked her?
By cutting her throat.
Right where I'm standing.
With this.
I've kept it all these years.
And now, I give it to you.
Why? I don't want that.
Yeah.
Come on, here.
No.
Don't be afraid.
Use it.
Kill me
for the sake of the coven.
No. No.
Yes. Come on.
Don't be afraid. Do it!
Come on, now, do it!
I can't!
No!
Yes, you can, you stupid girl!
Do it!
And feel my power flow into you!
I know, because I was standing
where you're standing!
Stop yelling at me!
Do it! Do it!
No!
Do it!
Bury her deep.
God knows what all that shit
in her body will do to the lawn
when it comes up in the spring.
This coven doesn't need
a new Supreme.
It needs a new rug.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player