Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
_
FIONA: Your highest honor
comes at the greatest price.
Death is not uncommon.
And danger...
...inescapable.
Attempting the Seven Wonders
can get you killed.
But perform them...
and you are the next Supreme.
(laughs)
I don't even need
to read your mind
to know what you're doing.
You want us to perform
the Seven Wonders
so that you can find
the next Supreme
and then kill her.
(laughs)
Poor, sweet, dumb,
paranoid girl.
The awful truth is
I am tired.
Mm-hmm.
Where's Marie Laveau?
That's not our business.
It's mine.
The only other black witch
in this place goes missing,
I want to know what happened.
She's probably off
in some unholy
nether realm.
Cavorting with that half-baked
Beetlejuice.
(laughs)
Papa Legaboo-boo,
whatever the hell his name is.
Legba!
He's a deity.
Show some respect.
(gasping for air)
Respect is something
that is definitely lacking
around here.
I will grant you that.
You will show me respect!
Your Supreme
until the moment
I am replaced.
(gasping)
So rest up,
little girl.
Take your vitamin B-12s.
(laughs)
Your trials begin
Saturday morning.
You will perform
the Seven Wonders.
Or...
you will die trying.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Madison?
I need your help.
Jesus, Cordelia.
You look like shit.
I can't believe
you did that to yourself.
I've been in Misty's room
trying to see something.
I've held her boots,
hair from her brush.
Nothing.
I hate to be the Debbie Downer,
but maybe she's gone.
Or maybe my gift of the
sight hasn't come back.
Whoa! That was cool!
I did transmutation.
I didn't even have
to think about it.
It just happened.
I wouldn't read
too much into it, Madison.
You can manifest multiple powers
without being the Supreme.
Our powers always spike
(cane tapping on ground)
in times of crisis.
This is one of those times.
Madison, I need to touch you.
Tell the truth, Cordelia.
You into girls now?
The last time I touched you,
I saw things.
What are you afraid
I might see?
Nothing stays a secret
for very long
in this house, Madison.
It will come to light
whether you want it to or not.
I don't have any secrets.
Then walk over here.
Knock yourself out.
Boom, boom.
Aw.
LAVEAU:
That damn
buttermilk biscuit!
Thinks she can take me down.
Hell no!
I'm the queen--
I will rise again!
Mark my words.
My people gonna come for you.
Rip you apart.
Marie?!
Spiritu duce, in me est.
Deduc me in tenebris vita.
Ad extremum ut
salutaret 'nferi.
(gasps)
Descensum.
What you doing, girl?
Give me the box of chicken.
Today, please.
Listen, watch
the counter for me.
I'm going on break, okay?
(distantly):
What am I doing here?
Been asking myself
the same thing
for 20 years.
Just watch the counter.
What the hell?
You're Papa Legba.
You live in a chicken shack?
No, darling.
It's not the hell.
It's your hell.
This was the worst time
of your life.
Waiting on people
who treated you
like the piece of trash
you thought you were.
No power.
No respect.
And no future
that you could see.
Just grease in your hair
and the smell of lard
in your nose.
Look...
I came to talk to you
about Marie Laveau.
I was told
you hang out together.
She ain't here. There's this
thing about being immortal.
Your hell's on Earth.
Hey, dude!
Just order and get out of line!
I've been waiting forever
for my chicken!
And you can wait some more!
Don't make me
put you in the fryer.
Now, go to the back of the line!
See?
Everybody got to pay in the end.
He gets to smell
the delicious chicken
and never get a bite.
Took some skills to come
down here before your time.
Most people be afraid
they couldn't get back.
Wait! I'm not done with you!
It's almost sun up.
Unless you want to
stay here forever,
you better hurry and get back.
What are you talking about?
I've been here five minutes.
Time...
moves differently in here.
(deep laughter)
WOMAN: I want the jumbo
box with butter corn.
No wings, no thighs.
Give me only breasts and legs.
Yo! You listening to me?
I'm talking to you, bitch!
(sniffs)
Ah!
You made it back.
I'm impressed.
Now that I've proven my power,
you're gonna give me
some answers.
(screaming)
You remember how you told me
you were gonna
cut me up in little pieces
and plant me all
over the place?
(yells)
I thought that was
a honey of an idea.
(screams)
There's got to be
a way to kill her.
So long as the
voodoo queen live,
so do Madame LaLaurie.
More marshmallows.
Then you need
to take Marie Laveau
out of the equation for me.
Can't do that.
Me and Marie Laveau--
we got a deal.
I thought your deal was
that every year
she needs to perform
a service for you.
So it is.
Well, she's not gonna
be doing anything
while she's chopped
into 50 pieces
and those pieces are scattered
all over the city.
Technically,
you can say she's
already in breach, right?
You are one crafty witch.
The elegant
and universally admired
Madame Delphine LaLaurie
was not only a brilliant hostess
for high society soirées.
But she was also renown
for her remarkable
equestrian abilities
and her tireless
charitable works.
Says here she was
a serial killer.
That's a misprint.
When do we get to see
the attic torture chamber?
That part of the house is
closed off for renovations.
(clicks tongue) Oh, great.
And there is no torture chamber.
The attic was used for storage.
And occasionally for the firm,
but humane correction
of Madame LaLaurie's domestics.
These wild tales of barbarity
you've heard
are nothing more than lies
invented by her many enemies.
Madame Delphine LaLaurie
was a woman ahead of her time.
A visionary.
Misunderstood.
And hated for it.
This way, please.
What a total rip-off.
Thank you for coming.
(traffic sounds, siren wailing)
(sighs)
Psst!
Queenie.
How did you find me?
Wasn't hard.
You're a cliché, Delphine.
A dog returns to its vomit.
I see you finally got
that makeover.
Guess you figured you could
makeover a little history, too.
On the contrary.
I'm here to set
the record straight.
(laughs)
This historical site was nothing
but a house of lies
before I came back.
This very house, the center
of New Orleans high society,
was also a place
of abject horror.
Madame Delphine LaLaurie
earned her place in history
alongside such monsters
as Jack the Ripper,
Ed Gein and Jeffrey Dahmer.
She even looks like a monster.
The inhuman LaLaurie
is said to have murdered as many
as 150 slaves right here.
Many times while there were
extravagant parties
going on just below,
the sounds of music
and revelry drowning out
the cries of torment.
Horseshit.
You don't believe it?
Nobody's gonna waste their
time with some uppity Negro
and miss a fabulous party.
It beggars all belief.
(door opens)
GUIDE:
Thank you for coming.
LaLAURIE:
Excuse me?
(door closes)
Yes?
I seem to have mislaid
my pocketbook.
I think I set it down upstairs.
I don't see anything.
Are you certain?
By the way,
it wasn't any 150 slaves
that died up here.
I can tell you that.
I'm sorry?
It was 62.
I kept a ledger.
I-I don't understand.
The information you've been
feeding these people?
(clicks tongue)
It's inaccurate.
I want my money back.
Do not touch the display items!
Ma'am, I am gonna have
to ask you to leave now.
My own house?
(body thuds)
(woman moans quietly)
You have to let this woman go.
What you gonna do?
Offer you a second chance.
You don't mean it.
You will never be able
to pay for your crimes.
But I'm willing to walk you
into the local office
of the Urban League.
You can offer your
services as a volunteer.
You can help the descendants
of the people you brutalized.
(laughs)
Are you out of your simple mind?
It's your only chance
for redemption.
Redemption?
(laughs)
I know how redemption works
in this century.
I seen it all on the magic box.
REPORTER: ...Paula Deen was
asked, "Have you ever used
the 'N' word yourself?"
"Yes, of course," she stated.
"But it's been
a really long time."
Agree to be publically
humiliated-- all is forgiven.
Last Friday night I tweeted
a photograph of myself
to a woman in Seattle,
and I'm deeply sorry.
People have gotten soft,
weak, lily-livered.
All anybody has to do nowadays
is shed some tears,
say some words...
It's called repentance.
Oh, repentance my ass.
You think a man jack among them
was well and truly sorry?
Not a one.
Sorry they got caught is all.
Y'all nothing but a pack
of sniveling hypocrites,
as far as I can see.
Not me.
I won't profess to be sorry,
'cause I'm not.
I don't believe that.
I was getting to you before.
I know it.
You made me weep.
But not as you would have it
for my supposed sins.
I wept for the state
of this world.
A world of lies.
A world that makes promises
it cannot keep.
To tell a colored man
that he can be equal
to a white man?
There's the real cruelty.
I'm not going anywhere.
Actually you are.
Ow!
Straight to hell.
It's impossible!
I'm immortal.
Wrong.
I don't want to die.
Tough shit.
Who does?
(grunting)
I want my portrait hung
just there.
Yes, I knew you'd occupy
a prominent place on the wall.
And I didn't want some garish
paint-by-numbers by a local.
That's why I flew
Claude in from London.
He's done everyone.
Margaret Thatcher.
Sting.
What are you doing back there?
You have to balance the frame.
The negative space makes
you like more drawn.
Claude trusts my taste.
Well, I don't.
I'm sorry.
Do you need a break?
No.
No, I'll be fine.
Just a minute.
Oh, God.
This is the face
they'll be stuck with.
I probably have two weeks
left on Earth.
So what the hell
am I doing here?
(door opens)
CORDELIA:
Goddamn it, Mother.
What's this I hear
about Queenie performing
the Seven Wonders on Saturday?
Cordelia, please.
Maybe we could
be kind to one another
for a change, huh?
My God, look at you.
My beautiful little girl.
Oh. (laughs)
Did you really think
self-mutilation would
restore your power?
Right up until I tried it.
You cannot lose your power.
You never will.
It's inside of you.
And it is not something
I gave to you.
As much as I'd like to,
I cannot take credit for that.
It's all you.
You are just full of surprises,
Fiona Goode, you know that?
Well, I have one more.
It's from the vault.
(cane taps on ground)
What is it?
It was my mother's.
Her most precious heirloom.
(laughs)
Grandmother's necklace?
Do you remember?
Yes. Of course I do.
When I was a little girl,
I used to gaze up at her
wearing this necklace.
Thinking to myself I
will never grow to be
so transcendent.
Oh, I know the feeling well.
Here, take it.
You're saying good-bye?
Yes, I am.
Hmm.
And I mean it this time.
We both knew it was coming.
Here.
Lift your hair.
I want to put it on you.
(distant screams)
(slow footfalls)
(echoing screams)
(liquid dripping)
(footfalls)
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I'm fine.
I just...
Wasn't there a ring...
that Grandmother used
to wear with this?
I feel so selfish asking.
(chuckles)
Well...
if not now, when, huh?
Right.
(door creaks)
AXEMAN: Just because you
witches can open the locks
with your hocus-pocus...
...it doesn't make it polite.
A man shouldn't be disturbed
when he's playing
with his instrument.
You don't have your
mother's features.
Oh, you know who I am?
Oh, yes, of course.
We spent quite an evening
together.
It's not safe to love
my mother, you know.
I speak from experience.
She can't love anyone
but herself.
I'm sure the transcendence
of my relationship
with your mother is hard for you
to understand.
But I'm happy that
she told you about us.
She didn't tell me anything.
I saw everything.
(whispers):
Everything.
And she's gonna kill all of us
and leave you behind, too.
Unzip me.
AXEMAN:
Sitting on a porch
drinking gin rickeys.
CORDELIA: She's not going
to run away with you.
Whatever fantasy you have
about who she is
and what you are to her,
it's all bullshit.
She used you.
All she does is use people.
It's nothing.
It's just a piece of paper.
It's as... as light as air.
That flight leaves in two days.
You think she might have
let you know
that you were leaving town
that soon.
I don't suspect you have
a passport ready.
She's going
to regain her power,
and when she does, she's not
going to waste her time
on some halfway decent musician
in a $12 suit.
You feel that?
That empty...
heartbroken feeling?
That's what it feels like
to get close to Fiona.
CORDELIA:
Come on, Misty, give me a hint.
MISTY (softly):
♪ And I saw my reflection
(inhales deeply)
♪ In the snow covered hills
♪ Till the landslide
brought me down ♪
I see you. I see you.
Where are you?
MISTY (softly):
♪ Take my love, take it down
(echoes) ♪ Climbed a mountain
and turned around... ♪
(panting)
(crickets chirping)
QUEENIE: How the hell are we
gonna get her out of there?
With a jackhammer,
if we have to.
I'm gonna go
find a maintenance man.
No, no, just us.
You mean, just me,
and I don't have a jackhammer.
Stop being so literal
and remember who you are.
When the rest of the world
sees a wall,
we see a window.
That's it.
Keep going.
(bricks cracking)
(exhales sharply)
Is she alive?
It's hard to tell.
Misty!
She's not breathing.
Oh, God.
Okay, okay.
(blows air) Vitalum vitalis.
(gasping inhale)
(coughs)
That's deadly nightshade
you're about to ingest
through your nostrils.
I wouldn't sniff around
unless you're looking
for a bout of delirium.
Sounds like every Saturday night
since I was 15.
Where is everybody?
Our beloved Cordelia
has regained her second sight.
She's off with Queenie
to try and rescue Misty Day.
Apparently, the poor girl
has been entombed.
Who would have been
cruel enough
to commit such an atrocity?
I have no idea.
I just hope
they get to her in time.
I heard people die
after three days without water.
Please tell me
this is a hallucination
driven by my bouquet
of Atropa belladonna.
Zoe, you can't possibly be
back at the Robichaux Academy.
I won't allow it.
You were supposed to spend
your days in romantic splendor
with your true love.
You're just like Halston
when he sold his brand
to J.C. Penney.
You've forsaken your destiny.
No, Myrtle, I've embraced it.
We made it to Florida.
What better than
the Sunshine State
to cast the darkness
out of our lives?
(both chuckle)
You bit it off.
(both laugh)
Hey, you're in my spot!
Get out of here!
I want to sleep!
We're leaving.
You, don't talk to me!
Don't talk to me!
Kyle, no!
(neck cracks)
MADISON:
What a surprise.
Your pit bull mauled somebody.
Is that why you came back,
because you can't handle him?
No.
I came back because
there's no escaping what I am.
Vitalum vitalis.
(man coughs)
I came back
because I'm clearly
the next Supreme.
(Madison scoffs)
You bitch.
Oh!
You thought I was some dumb swamp rat
you could leave behind to die?
Um, yes.
(laughs)
Oh!
Girls, stop these
vulgar fisticuffs at once.
It's beneath us.
MYRTLE: Cordelia?
I'm good.
I don't want to waste
my magic on you.
I can do you with my hands.
(Madison screams)
You hit like a girl!
(grunting, yelling)
(groans)
This is awesome!
No, it's not. Stop!
Come on. Get up, Hollywood.
(grunts)
(yells)
(grunting)
(shrieks)
(gasps)
Ow!
(both scream) Enough!
You! You must pay
for what you've done!
Wow, did you walk
into the wrong house.
(yells)
(yelling)
Who the hell is this guy?
CORDELIA:
I know that voice.
It's the Axeman.
I thought you banished his soul
to the appropriate
nether realms?
CORDELIA: No, he's
on the mortal coil.
I'll kill all of you!
Is that blood?
Not his.
Then whose?
How could you do this to me?
This blood is my mother's.
(door closes in distance,
footfalls)
(door creaks open)
(chuckles) It's quiet.
I don't remember the last time
I was here when there wasn't
music playing.
You pack your wader boots?
What?
'Cause I want
to take you fishing.
(chuckles) Fishing.
Yeah. Yeah, fishing.
For catfish.
Catfish.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
When you fry them,
the batter, it has to be
crunchy, never greasy.
I don't like catfish.
I loathe all
bottom-feeders.
Well, then I'll take
you boar hunting.
While you're sitting on a porch
drinking gin rickeys, huh?
Gin rickeys.
(giggles)
Unzip me.
Your daughter...
she paid me a visit.
Oh...
Please tell me
she's in the bathtub.
(short laugh)
She's pretty, but she doesn't
have your cheekbones.
She came, I guess, to...
to rile me up.
I imagine she wanted me
to do her dirty work for her.
What is the world
coming to, huh,
when the Supreme's
daughter... (laughs)
...has to outsource
her own killings?
(exhales)
We had a deal.
It wasn't on paper...
it wasn't stamped by a notary,
but we had a deal!
(slams glass down on counter)
And what, Cordelia has
convinced you otherwise?
Why do they insist on always
putting me in seat 1A?
Well, I guess the cat
is out of the bag, huh?
I mean, I was gonna tell you.
You have been the most
delightful distraction.
A life preserver.
But I'm gonna be
on dry land soon.
Can't you at least pretend?
Just... just humor
me for a while?
I guess I loved you.
Huh.
Although I really don't know
anything about love,
if I'm gonna be honest.
But you were the
sweetest of lovers.
(chuckles)
The best I ever had.
And I'll miss that.
Let's be realistic.
When the new Supreme is dead,
I'll have 30 years of vitality
until another one comes along.
And the doors of every palace
are going to open for me.
I mean, hell,
I know you've got
all this to offer,
but come on,
you and I both knew
that this
would never... Ah!
(grunting) Son of a...
Let go of me!
I love you!
Oh, Jesus...
I know you love me!
I don't!
Christ, I was sick!
I just needed
to feel something.
That was all!
Ah. Shit.
Ah...
(breathing hard)
I made you die
those little deaths
for the first time
in your sorry life.
I made you sing
when you had no tunes
left in you.
Get off of me!
Get off of me, get off of me,
you son of a bitch!
No!
Christ.
No tears, old boy.
Huh?
What you're doing is a
crime against humanity.
A betrayal...
of the true heart of love.
Well, I've never been
one for love,
true or otherwise.
(panting)
I live in a floating world,
you know?
Always...
(panting)
...two steps ahead
of heartbreak.
(laughs)
When I was eight years old...
my mother brought me
a little calico cat.
(gasps)
(grunting)
(Axeman's grunts echo)
MADISON:
Holy shit.
So she's really gone.
Does anyone feel any different?
Where's the body?
In the swamps.
He fed her to the alligators.
Jesus.
MISTY: Well, that's it, then.
Even I can't bring somebody back
once they're gator shit.
Okay.
So who wants to do this?
Somebody's got
to kill this creep.
MYRTLE: Oh, bloody-blood-blood
all day in this place.
Is that really necessary?
Yeah.
He's a psycho mass murderer.
Is there anyone here of whom
that could not be said?
This poor troubled soul
has saved this coven
by doing away with Fiona.
And as Cervantes once said,
"Where there is music,
there can be no evil."
Cervantes never
meant this asshole.
Come on.
(grunting)
(Axeman grunting)
I'm coven guard dog.
I'll kill him.
No.
I'll do it.
(Axeman grunting)
(grunts)
We really don't need a man
to protect us.
(grunting, screams)
Nobody messes with our coven!
LaLAURIE:
Please, no!
(screams)
Let me go!
No!
(sobbing):
Wait, please...
No...
(LaLaurie screams)
God, why this?
BORQUITA:
Mother?
Borquita, my sweet child.
I know I mistreated you
in the past...
...but there's
no greater pain...
(man screams in distance)
...than being this close
and not...
not being
able to reach you.
And to comfort you.
Oh, I'm... consumed with regret.
BORQUITA: Why are they
doing this to us?
Because we can.
Behold the kingdom
of the family LaLaurie!
BORQUITA:
Please...
I'm so thirsty.
Please have mercy.
LaLAURIE: Give her
something to drink,
you animal!
(groans)
(sobbing)
Mm...
No, no...
(Borquita chokes)
LAVEAU: Are you hungry, too?
I'll slice off one of
your mama's fingers
and feed it to you!
(gasps)
LaLAURIE:
You monster.
Yes, I have sinned.
I gave no quarter.
But torturing a mama's babies
in front of her?
Even when I killed
that little
high yellah bastard,
I spared his mammy
from seein' it.
Oh, please, no.
Have mercy on my soul!
This ain't for you!
But I will let you choose
whether I slide
it down her throat
or up her backside.
No, please!
Mother!
No! (screams)
LaLAURIE: Oh, no!
(Borquita and LaLaurie
screaming)
LaLAURIE: Oh, God,
please, not my baby.
How did I get here?
No, no, no, no.
I don't want to do that.
That girl ain't never done
nothing to me.
I don't want to do this!
You will do as you are tasked.
It is your soul's purpose,
because I own it.
Who is this man?
What is this place?
Congratulations,
Madame Delphine LaLaurie.
You have been granted
your sweet release
from the world of the mortal.
And as punishment
for your crimes
of murder, torture,
passion, fashion
and being an
all-around no-good
miserable bitch, you...
will spend all
of eternity here...
in my home.
It is my home.
No... it's mine.
Welcome to hell.
LAVEAU:
No, that can't be true.
I can't die!
We have a contract!
One you can no longer fulfill.
LAVEAU: But I was
good to people.
I protected so many.
PAPA LEGBA:
How many little babies
did you bring to me every year?
No one gets away with sin.
(chuckles)
Eventually...
everybody pays.
(man screams distantly)
Everybody suffers.
Now get back to work.
(laughing)
BORQUITA: No! Please!
Mother! No!
(screams)
(Papa Legba laughing)
(Borquita screaming)
(screams)
(fire crackling)
CORDELIA:
How does she look?
MYRTLE:
Magnificent.
I wish you could see it.
I can.
I can see it through you.
She was so beautiful.
ZOE: She was a great Supreme.
QUEENIE:
A lot to live up to.
(sighs) One of the best.
She was a force
to be reckoned with,
but she was a horrible Supreme.
She shirked all of
her responsibility,
including the most important:
identifying her successor.
So it will be up to us
to find our new leader.
And the only way is through
the test of Seven Wonders.
And since it could
be any one of you,
you will all be tested.
The Seven Wonders.
Sunday at dawn it begins.
Everyone participates.
And by next week,
we will have a new Supreme.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player