Can you hear me?
What happened?
You nearly died.
Your brain was almost out of oxygen.
You'll be seeing black spots
for the next few days.
The rest of your senses
will recover naturally.
Did it work?
Did they come?
No, Mr. Walker.
There was no visitation.
I waited as long as I could,
but finally, I had to revive you.
They seem to have repaired
the damage done by the bullet.
How did you get in here?
I go where Grace goes.
I've been charged to protect her.
Have you?
You can't even protect yourself.
They may have given you speech, Pepper;
Even a parrot can be taught to mimic.
But did they give you
the capacity to think?
I sincerely doubt it.
Tell me, Polly,
what did they put inside her?
I won't tell you anything.
If you're not going to tell me,
then I'll just have to find out
for myself, won't I?
X rays will harm the life
growing inside of her.
That's a chance I'm willing to take.
Stupid man.
You think they'd allow you
to continue your barbaric practice?
She's protected.
Your X rays won't penetrate her body.
You'll see nothing,
but they've been watching you.
You think you're like them,
with your clumsy experiments.
But they laugh at you,
Dr. Arden.
They make jokes.
Here's a good one.
Knock, knock. Who's there?
Arden. Arden who?
Arden you the quack
who'd make a better duck?
Huh.
Well, if taking X rays won't work,
perhaps more invasive observation will.
I think her condition calls
for an emergency C-section,
don't you?
You can't do that.
Watch me.
Dr. Arden, you still see me
as microcephalic.
No one takes a pinhead seriously.
When my sister's husband
drowned her baby
and sliced his ears off,
he told everyone I did it.
They tied me up and paraded me
in front of a judge.
He took one look
at the shape of my head,
and I was locked up for good.
That's how it works for us freaks.
We get blamed for everything.
But if something happens
to Grace in here
and she's harmed in any way,
there won't be anyone else to blame.
They'll take you,
open up your head,
and stir your brain with a fork.
And when you're returned,
you'll experience firsthand
how people treat us freaks.
I'll take care of Grace.
Why don't you go to your whore nun
and have her soothe your deflated ego?
I'm haunted by the idea that
Leigh Emerson is still at large.
Believe me, Monsignor,
finding Leigh Emerson
is a top priority.
They're searching for him
in five different states.
It's a huge manhunt.
I'm filled with remorse
at my blindness about him.
You are not to blame.
I'll be sleeping right there,
if you need something during the night.
Have you come for me?
Why are you here?
You have more work to do.
The Devil lives at Briarcliff
in your favorite young nun.
You must cast her out.
I'm too weak.
God will help you.
She'll know.
Guard your thoughts.
Use your rosary,
each bead is His Name.
This is your moment, Timothy.
Thank you for everything, Sister.
I'll be back later.
I have to oversee a delivery.
Exciting new things
are happening around here.
She's doing this to taunt me.
People!
I have an announcement to make.
As most of you know,
recently our beloved recording
of "Dominique" was smashed
to pieces by someone
who shall remain nameless.
In fact, I'll just call her
patient number G2573.
But rather than allow one
bitter woman's actions
ruin things for everyone,
I've decided to take
this opportunity to bring Briarcliff
into the 20th century.
I dug into our rainy day fund and bought
this beautiful used jukebox.
I'm sure there's something
in there that can
appeal to everyone's taste.
Camels?
Pack of Camels?
No, Gerard.
It's not a cigarette machine.
It's a great big music box!
And for our maiden number,
I would like to dedicate this one
to our newest resident,
patient number G2573,
Miss Judy Martin.
Enjoy.
♪ Ooh... spell ♪
That's your name?
Judy Martin?
Not anymore.
We're all just numbers here.
♪ I put a spell on you ♪
♪ Ooh... spell ♪
♪ 'Cause you're mine ♪
Come on.
♪ Stop the things you do ♪
We have to talk.
Something's happened.
Thredson's loose.
How do you know that?
♪ Watch out! ♪
♪ I ain't lying ♪
How'd he get out?
Son of a bitch.
♪ You're running around ♪
♪ Ooh... spell ♪
Well, well, well, well, well.
Isn't this pleasant,
the three of us sitting
around like civilized people?
That's a wise move.
I was about to bash your face in.
Hmm.
I know you were.
I admire your pluck.
It's a quality I hope
you'll pass on to our child.
Oh, she not tell you either?
Her attempts to self-abort
proved fruitless.
Our baby's strong, Lana.
A survivor.
And he's the only thing
that's keeping you alive right now.
As long as he's growing inside
of your womb, you're safe.
Then what happens?
You murder me?
Oh, no. I'll have
to keep you around
to breast-feed that baby
for at least the first year.
The health benefits are myriad.
You are one sick twist.
And you're a wanted man.
I wonder if they're offering a reward.
Find out. Turn me in.
Hmm. You'd like
that, wouldn't you?
Go to the police,
and your illegally obtained
taped confession goes with you.
We can discuss that
and other issues tomorrow,
when we resume your treatment.
That's right.
Sister Mary Eunice has offered me
a full-time position
here at Briarcliff.
She's a remarkably forward-
thinking administrator
for a nun, and surprisingly adept
at untying slipknots.
♪ You're mine ♪
♪ Spell... ♪
Everybody up and out now!
Step out.
Open those doors.
Get out here.
Open your door.
Room search, ladies.
We find it keeps our charges honest.
Are you mocking me?
I don't have time to mock you,
Judy; I have work to do.
A lot of work,
given your epic failure here.
You gave him a job?
Are you insane? Guards!
Dr. Thredson is on the cutting
edge of psychiatric medicine.
We need a guy like him around here
to whip this place into shape.
Yeah, well, he's here for me,
and you know it.
And when he murders me, which he will,
you will be responsible.
Oh.
Quite the contrary,
Miss Winters.
Dr. Thredson is
concerned for you
and for your unborn child.
Take her to hydrotherapy.
Strip her down and boil
her for 20 minutes.
No!
Anyone else have
a bone to pick with me?
I do.
I bet you do, Judy.
Let's have a look in your room.
Fine, there's nothing in there.
Judy, Judy, Judy...
Did you steal this from the kitchen?
I bet you got the idea from Shelley.
Very funny.
Do you think about the monsignor?
Vile thing.
This is awkward for me.
Given our prior relationship.
But I can't have you diddling
yourself all night long.
So punish me.
No, goddamn you... let me go.
This is sadism.
Quite the contrary...
you've exhibited clear-cut signs
of manic depression,
for which
electroshock therapy
is the prescribed treatment.
No!
Just look at Miss Winters.
It completely cured her gynephilia.
Sister,
Sister, I know somewhere in there
you can hear me.
This is wrong, it's wrong, it's wrong.
You know it's wrong!
Aw, Jude...
we're gonna burn those
bad memories right out of you.
That runaway groom,
those drunken blackouts,
all of it gone in a wisp of smoke.
She's right, you know.
Most patients experience a sense
of euphoria after the treatment.
May I, Doctor?
Yes, you may...
no higher than 50%.
She's one tough cookie.
She may need a little extra.
On?
Ow.
Oh, it's healing quite well.
Too well if you ask me.
What could you mean by that?
After showing such kindness to a
guttersnipe like Leigh Emerson,
you deserved to be canonized.
But these marks will fit
a future saint like you.
I command you, unclean spirit
now attacking this servant
of God, to obey me
to the letter... I, who
am a minister of God...
Good one, Father.
You want to hear mine?
There was a priest, the dirty
beast whose name was Alexander.
His mighty dick was inches thick.
He called it Salamander.
In Jesus' name
I command...
Is yours inches thick?
Father.
Stop it, please.
Your body disagrees with you.
I...
I took a vow.
You don't say that with much conviction.
Please...
don't do this to me.
The Church means...
everything to me.
It's okay...
we're like Adam and Eve.
Two innocent children
discovering each other's bodies
for the first time.
This is your first time, isn't it?
Yes.
I...
gave my body to...
Christ!
What has he given to you?
Oh, come on.
Don't you want to feel what it's like?
At least once...
before you die?
Does it feel like a warm,
wet... hug?
God...
you... have to...
stop.
Are you sure?
Yes...
No!
No, no.
No, don't do it...
don't do it yet.
♪ Ooh-woo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-woo-ooh ♪
♪ Do you want me, baby? ♪
Holy shit.
♪ Do you need me, baby? ♪
Looks like they turned
the juice up extra high.
Why doesn't it make me feel any better?
♪ Baby, you ♪
♪ You and I, baby, we're in love ♪
♪ Yeah, way deep in love ♪
♪ Ooh-woo-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-woo-ooh ♪
♪ Ooh-woo-ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey... ♪
Sister Jude.
It's me.
Lana.
Lana Banana?
Do you know your name?
♪ The name game ♪
♪ Judy ♪
♪ Judy, Judy, bo Budy ♪
♪ Banana fanna fo Fudy ♪
♪ Fee fi mo Mudy ♪
♪ Judy ♪
♪ Lana... Lana, Lana, bo Bana ♪
♪ Banana fanna fo Fana ♪
♪ Fee fi mo Mana ♪
♪ Lana ♪
♪ Come on, everybody ♪
♪ I say, now let's play a game ♪
♪ I bet you I can make a rhyme ♪
♪ Out of anybody's name ♪
♪ The first letter of the name ♪
♪ I treat it like it wasn't there ♪
♪ But a "B" or "F"
or an "M" will appear ♪
♪ And then I say bo, add a "B" ♪
♪ Then I say the name
and banana fanna and a fo ♪
♪ And then I say the name again
with an "F," very plain ♪
♪ And a fee fi and a mo ♪
♪ And then I say the name again
with an "M" this time ♪
♪ And there isn't any name
that I can't rhyme ♪
♪ Pepper...
Pepper, Pepper, bo Bepper ♪
♪ Banana fanna fo Fepper ♪
♪ Fee fi mo Mepper ♪
♪ Pepper ♪
♪ But if your first two letters
are ever the same ♪
♪ I drop them both and say the name ♪
♪ Like Bob, Bob,
drop the Bs... bo Ob ♪
♪ For Fred, Fred,
drop the Fs... fo Red ♪
♪ For Mary, Mary,
drop the Ms... mo Ary ♪
♪ That's the only rule
that is contrary ♪
♪ Okay? ♪
♪ Now say bo ♪ ♪ Bo ♪
♪ Now Tony with a "B" ♪
♪ Bony ♪
♪ Then banana fanna fo ♪
♪ Banana fanna fo ♪
♪ Then you say the name again with
an "F," very plain ♪ ♪ Fony ♪
♪ Then a fee fi and a mo ♪
♪ Fee fi mo ♪
♪ Then say the name again with
an "M" this time ♪ ♪ Mony ♪
♪ And there isn't any name
that you can't rhyme ♪
♪ Kit, Kit, bo Bit,
banana fanna fo Fit ♪
♪ Fee fi mo Mit, Kit ♪
♪ The name game. ♪
Do you know your name?
Your name is Judy Martin.
Dr. Arden!
Dr. Arden, what are you doing?
An afternoon feeding, Hans?
That's unusual, isn't it?
I asked you not to call me that.
Oh, Hans, it's just us here after all.
There is no "us."
Ooh, don't tell me you're jealous?
He didn't mean anything to me.
That I believe.
You know what I was thinking?
Wouldn't it be fun
and, uh, therapeutically beneficial
if we gave her a transorbital lobotomy?
Crack that thick skull
open like a walnut?
No.
Why not?
Because you wish it.
The experiment is over.
My...
Quite a tantrum, Arthur.
It's a farce.
Finita la commedia.
You...
have no idea what
it means to have lost you.
Jesus Christ.
You're being pitiful, Arthur.
Then...
have pity on me.
Everyone, I'd like you all
to stop what you're doing
and go to the common room.
Hang up your aprons
and line up over here.
We'll all go together.
Jude,
will you remain here,
please?
The medication
they give you is strong, I know.
It affects your motor skills.
Here.
Take your loaf
and push it with the heel of your hand.
Like that.
I'm all right.
Yes, my hands
are all right.
I came
to talk to you.
It seems I don't know who else
I can unburden myself to.
You've always been a
loyal and honest friend.
You've always had the
gift of moral clarity.
I owe you an apology, Jude.
More than an apology.
There are no words for my regret.
The Devil...
lives inside Sister Mary Eunice.
You were right.
I tried to cast it out, but I failed.
In truth, it was an epic failure.
She'll destroy everything.
Why didn't I listen to you?
Why was I so stubborn?
She's destroyed you.
And now she's destroyed me.
My virtue is gone, Jude.
She took it from me,
violated me.
I tried to resist, but...
I don't know where else to turn.
I'm struggling with whether
I should renounce my vows.
I need your counsel.
Should I confess
and walk away from my beloved Church
and my dream?
What should I do?
Kill her.
And have Kit Walker brought
to my office at 3:00 today.
Yes, Doctor.
Oh, and I think for this session,
we'll want to secure him
in a straitjacket.
Will do. That's Dr. Arden's
office around the corner.
Thank you, Carl.
I can take it from here.
Dr. Arden?
It's Oliver Thredson.
Are you in?
Dr. Arden?
Are you here?
Now, where would you keep
your sodium pentothal?
Dr. Arden?
She's crowning.
"Be strong in the Lord
"and in the power of his might.
"Put on the whole armor of God
"that ye may be able to stand
against the wiles
of the Devil..."
"For we wrestle not
against flesh and blood..."
"But against principalities,
"against powers,
"against rulers of the darkness
of this world,
"against spiritual wickedness
in high places."
Are we having regrets, Father?
Did our little tryst
turn your stomach into knots?
Or are we ready for round two?
I have to admit,
I found your innocence...
quite intoxicating.
Don't touch me.
We will never repeat
our indiscretion again.
No.
It's not what you want.
You don't want
to lay me on the ground.
You want to bury me beneath it.
That's why you're praying for strength.
How will you kill me?
A letter opener?
No, I don't think so.
Unless you hit pay dirt
on the first strike,
it'll be messy.
What else?
You could bludgeon me
with the statue of St. Francis.
That would be ironic,
considering that he renounced
his debauchery before becoming a saint,
and you, Father, living your life
in complete reversal.
Could you wrap your fingers
around my throat
and squeeze?
Hmm?
Or will you use your rosary
like you did with Shelley?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, you have
no secrets from me.
Especially not
after what we shared.
I know it all.
Don't worry, Father.
Your little fantasy
about killing me...
it hasn't put me off.
Quite the opposite.
I'm gonna make all
of your dreams come true.
We will rise in the hierarchy
of the Church together.
Bishop,
cardinal,
dare we even say...
pope?
I know it's what you want,
isn't it, Monsignor?
The desires of the
flesh, they're nothing
compared to the rewards of power
and ambition.
You don't know me.
I know you're weak.
But I'm strong enough for both of us.
You're mine now.
Body and soul.
I'm not yours.
I never will be.
I'd rather die than allow you
to defile the Church.
Are you talking?
You've suddenly grown quite tiresome.
You'll not win.
You couldn't even defeat
Sister Mary Eunice.
Her purity remains alive
inside, I know it.
Don't make me reconsider
my largess, Timothy.
I will cast you out
and return Mary Eunice
to her state of grace.
I gave you a chance, Timothy,
but you've just
pissed it away!
I'm done with you.
And with your sweet nun,
I'm about to devour
the last morsel of her soul.
I'm sorry, Monsignor.
I'm tired of fighting.
I want to let go.
Then let go of me, Sister.
Take me.
I'll take both of you.
We beseech thee,
oh, Lord, in thy mercy,
to have pity on the
soul of thy handmaid.
Restore to her that portion
of everlasting salvation
through Jesus Christ, our Lord.
She's been released
from Satan's grip.
Satan's or yours?
I was told
she fell from the third floor.
Evidently it was your grip
that failed her.
Her everlasting soul has been set free.
Now we must help it find rest.
It's time to prepare her for burial.
No.
She needs to be cremated.
Cremation is
a pagan practice
and a denial
of the Doctrine of Resurrection.
Monsignor,
the very cells of her body
were corrupted by the Devil.
No.
She has to be cremated.
The crematorium here at Briarcliff?
Is still fully functional.
Very well.
I will assist.
That won't be necessary.
I want to do it myself.
As a sign of sanctity,
sometimes God permits the dead body
to admit an odor of sweet perfume.
It was said
than when Santa Theresa de Avila died,
the smell of roses lingered
in the convent for days.
What do you smell now, Monsignor?
Nothing but decay.
3:00, right on time.
Want me to stick around?
He's got some attitude today.
We'll be just fine, Carl.
Thank you.
There's nothing you can do
to me to make me tell you
where that tape's at.
Oh, I'm well aware of that.
I diagnosed you long ago, Kit.
I know you'd rather die
than give me what I want.
But there's an impulse in you
that runs even deeper
than your martyr complex,
and that's your savior complex.
Particularly when it comes to women.
And, one would assume...
children.
Kit.
Grace?
No.
That's close enough.
It's not possible.
You were... Dead?
At least according to.
Dr. Arden's postmortem report.
Now, given Grace's condition,
one would either have to, A)
judge Arden as guilty of
one of the most egregious misdiagnoses
in the history of modern medicine,
or conclude that he's
been up to something
quite extraordinary in
that laboratory of his.
Grace...
says that's your son.
Now, what are we to make of that?
Is it true?
It's true.
You believe her, don't you, Kit?
What are you gonna do?
That's entirely up to you.
I don't want to ruin it
for you, but...
Spot jumps.
Where is the tape, you bitch?
Oliver, is that any way to speak to
the mother of your unborn child?
I'm the only one
who knows where it is now.
Kit's not going to find out.
And if you do anything to him,
anything at all,
or anyone else for that matter,
I'll find a way to get it to the police.
You know I can do it, Oliver.
I'm goddamn plucky, remember?
Margaret.
Kevin.
And, uh...
Milton.
Doris... Dor...
Dor...
No, Dolly. Dolly.
Clyde.
Uh...
Mother?
Hello, Jude.
Mother... Superior.
Claudia. Mother Claudia.
The monsignor said
you were speaking my name.
Wanted to say good-bye.
Good-bye?
I'm going to Rome.
The monsignor...
taking me to Rome.
We're going to be Pope.
We're getting married.
He likes my cooking.
I'm a rare bird.
Is it warm in Rome now?
She tried to steal... him away.
She rubbed her
naked body on him.
Ravish Me Red. Ravish Me Red.
Jude.
He killed her.
He had to.
We're getting married in the Vatican.
The Devil was jealous.
Try and rest your mind.
You're a little confused.
Do you see that woman
over there, smoking a cigarette?
Yes.
Her name is Lana Winters.
She doesn't belong here.
I put her here.
Help her...
get out.