WOMAN:
Please, have a seat, Mr. Morgan.
Do you mind if I call you John?
Johnny.
And how did you come
to find me, Johnny?
I saw your ad in one
of those m-magazines
they have in the mail,
the Penny Saver.
You probably saw
my smoking cessation ad.
"Guaranteed results
or your money back"?
I don't smoke.
(chuckles):
Well, you certainly don't look
like you need
to lose any weight.
Your ad said something about...
curbing compulsions.
Absolutely.
I've found posthypnotic
suggestion to be
one of the most powerful weapons
in a therapist's arsenal.
I want to stop. I really do.
If I have to go on medication,
whatever, I'm willing to try.
Tell me about the behavior
you want to curtail.
- Start from the beginning.
- I always, uh,
had these impulses,
you know, even as a kid.
The first time I tried it,
it was scary.
But it felt amazing.
My whole body came alive.
When my foster family
saw the evidence...
they kicked me out.
I bounced from house to house
until I learned how to hide it.
It's a shame so many people
have such a negative reaction
to something so natural.
Was that the first time
you touched yourself?
No.
I skinned a cat.
- It was already dead.
- So...
you went around
finding dead animals?
Yeah. First couple of times.
Then I learned that killing them
was just as good.
Even better.
And this compulsion followed you
into your adult life?
No. I don't harm
animals anymore.
I haven't since
I was a teenager.
Did you know that
killing animals
is a predictor for psychopaths?
I learned that in prison.
Armed robbery.
But it got me thinking.
What made me... the way I am?
Who were my real parents?
Well, they had a computer at the
joint, and I didn't have nothing
- but time, so...
- Mr. Morgan, you know,
I-I may not be qualified
to help you.
No, you have to help, Doctor.
I don't know what to do,
because those thoughts...
haven't stopped.
If anything,
they've gotten harder to ignore
since I found out who I am.
And what do those thoughts
tell you to do?
They told me to
retrace my roots,
so I'm renting the house
where my father lived.
They also told me to hurt women.
But not just hurt them.
Skin them.
Like the cats.
(distorted screaming)
Stop moving!
(screaming continues)
Shut up!
This is delicate work.
I didn't have the same skills
as my father.
I didn't get the
medical training.
I made a mess.
You think it's too late?
It's never too late
to turn yourself in.
No, to go to medical school.
I'll never live up to him.
That's why I wanted to stop.
You see,
my name isn't Morgan.
It's Thredson.
I'm the son of Bloody Face.
You wanted a word
with Miss Winters?
What did I tell you
about knocking?
Oh, it won't happen
again, Sister.
Have a seat.
Your Jude imitation is spot-on.
For a moment there,
- I thought you might cane her.
- Mm-hmm.
Awfully sassy for a
girl in your condition.
What condition is that?
Well... the good news is,
you seem to have conquered
your sexual perversion.
The bad news is...
the rabbit died.
If I were
my Aunt Celeste,
I would offer you
a Drano margarita.
- A what?
- You add half a cup of Drano
for every two weeks
you've been pregnant
to a margarita.
That's what she gave
my slutty cousin Molly
when she got preggers
by Billy Porter.
(quietly): - I'm pregnant?
- So are we still sticking
to the whole rapist story?
Interesting you haven't
mentioned Dr. Thredson once
since you came in here.
We starting to get
sweet on him now that
we're carrying his child?
(laughs softly)
Actually,
the whole... rape thing
must have been
some kind of hallucination
from the car crash
when I... I hit my head.
Well...
whoever the daddy is...
there's a little life growing
inside of you.
I can't keep this baby.
I can't have this baby
inside me.
You can have this baby,
and you will have this baby.
This is an insane asylum.
People hump like bunnies here.
You're hardly our first...
unwed mother.
Most of the babies, they
are born a little...
(singsongy): cuckoo.
So... our staff is
very experienced
at calming them and...
preparing them for
relocation to St. Ursula's.
Home for Lost Children.
You're worse than Jude.
You're a sadist.
Calm down, Mommy,
or it's going to be a
very long nine months.
We don't want to have
to restrain you... do we?
May I go?
Of course.
(distorted, echoing):
You're awake.
I'm so relieved.
(whispers): Oh, Monsignor.
(gasps)
MONSIGNOR:
No, no, no, you mustn't move.
You've been injured, I'm afraid.
(gasping breaths) Shh...
What happened?
(whispers): You don't remember?
MONSIGNOR: You killed a man.
- God rest his soul.
- I had no choice.
I was defending myself.
He tried to murder me,
and worse.
You've become unhinged;
That's clear.
I blame myself.
I should have seen it sooner.
- What?
- The pressures of running
- this place were too much for you.
- No!
You've grown paranoid,
seeking conspiracy.
And now Frank McCann is dead.
(whispers): What did you say?
MAN: Kindly speak up.
LEIGH:
I saw the nun, Sister Jude,
attack Frank McCann.
It was horrible.
And then what happened?
I made sure the other
inmates were secure,
and then alerted Dr. Arden
to the situation.
- Why didn't you call the police?
- There wasn't time.
It was...
if you'll pardon
the expression, bedlam.
Sister Jude was on a rampage.
She'd already killed
Frank McCann,
taken Leigh Emerson hostage,
and locked herself
in her old office.
I can't say any of this
came as a surprise to me.
MONSIGNOR: She'd been showing
signs of instability
for some time.
She seemed to be
taking on the delusions
of some of the patients here.
She accused Dr. Arden
of being a Nazi.
She came to me... convinced
that her young protégé,
Sister Mary Eunice,
was possessed by the Devil.
When I informed her
I would be removing her
from her position here,
she became inconsolable.
SISTER EUNICE: She
threatened me with the same
straight-edge razor that
she used to murder Frank McCann.
She smelled of liquor
and... cigarettes.
We had her escorted
off the property.
I-I-I should have called
the police then... I just...
I never for a moment thought
something like this could happen.
LEIGH: I saw her do it.
I saw Sister Jude...
murder Frank McCann
in cold blood and then try
- to do the same to me.
- Isn't it true
that you yourself
are responsible
for the deaths of 18 people?
Well, sir, the state...
found me not responsible,
which is why they
put me in here, but...
yes...
oh, yes, I am responsible,
I know that now. I've...
I've had time to reflect
upon my crimes...
Your Honor.
Christmas '62 was
a very bad time for me,
and the only solace I have
is knowing that...
because of what I did...
there are 18 more people
in Heaven.
That's a unique perspective,
- Mr. Emerson.
- W-Well, I do know, sir,
that no matter what,
I-I can't... hate Sister Jude
for what she did to me...
but I can...
try to forgive her,
and I can carry on
on my own personal road
to true redemption,
so that one day,
when I enter
the gates of Heaven...
I can apologize,
personally, to each of those
18 people that
I sent there before me.
The court magistrate is
determined that you will live out
the remainder of your days
here at Briarcliff.
You will, of course, be stripped
of your clerical standing.
No longer will you be a sister
of the Holy Catholic Church.
You are once again
Miss Judy Martin.
Patient.
No, you can't do this to me!
- You did it to yourself.
- Come back here,
you son of a bitch!
Come back here! (Shouts)
It's a set-up!
God, help me! (Screams)
Apparently she had
quite the secret inner life.
Oh, (chuckles) Sister,
you... startled me.
I'm just packing up her things
so they can be donated
to the poor.
I was as shocked as you are
when I first saw this.
I wonder who she was
fancying when she wore it.
Of course, none of this
is of our concern.
(chuckles)
We had a dream together,
you know.
She told me.
She said you
wanted to be Pope.
Those
things were said in confidence.
You know what I said to her
when she told me your dream?
I said, "Rome is
where that man belongs."
She was so happy when you said
you wanted her on
that journey with you.
Like a girl who'd just received
a marriage proposal.
I can't help but wonder,
if I'd been paying closer
attention,
could this tragedy
have been averted?
Oh, Monsignor,
as she herself would say,
"No time"
for navel-gazing.
"Too much to be done."
But you've had to focus
on your own goals.
There is no other goal
than to save souls.
She also said that.
Of course.
I know I, uh...
I can't begin to fill
the shoes of the...
Sister Jude we all knew
and loved, but...
let me say...
I'm here to serve you.
I want to help you save souls,
all the way to Rome.
(lock clicks)
(thunder rumbles)
Get away from me!
Get away from me! No!
I demand to speak to someone!
Now, now, Sister Jude.
You mustn't behave so.
(groans)
She's no Sister no more.
She's no queen of
the castle neither.
She's just a naughty patient.
Now do as you're told
and take these pills.
- No!
- Or I'll
- happily force 'em down your gullet.
- No!
(groaning)
You clip me again
and I'll call Frank in here.
Oh, but I can't,
because you already
clipped Frank but good.
No!
That's a lie! Get off of me!
Get off of me!
(screams) MONSIGNOR:
What's all this fuss then?
Hmm? Hmm? That's quite enough.
(sobs) Timothy. Please.
Why don't you go and
find some other tasks
- for the moment?
- Yes, Monsignor.
NURSE: Of course, Father.
(whispers): Timothy.
Well, I was hoping you might be
up for a visitor, but I
see that our adjustment period
continues.
(sobbing): No. No.
Monsignor, please.
Don't go.
Are you sure?
(sniffles) I'm better now.
What's he doing here?
Leigh...
has something he would
like to say to you.
And...
I think you'll find
it more medicinal
than any pill.
Leigh?
I forgive you.
You forgive me?
I do.
SISTER JUDE:
Make it tight, Frank.
LEIGH:
Make it tight. I like it tight.
Just ask Sister Chastity.
I'll deal with Sister Chastity.
You might start by picking
a new name for her.
(chuckles)
You know,
I thought by allowing you time
in the general population
that it would have had
a civilizing effect on you,
but clearly
I was wrong, Mr. Emerson.
So you'll spend the next
couple days here,
reflecting on your behavior.
How can I reflect
when my hand's tied down?
You're disgusting.
We all got our crosses to bear.
Come on. Where's your spirit
of forgiveness?
I reserve it for those
who are truly repentant.
All God's chillun got to have
forgiveness...
isn't that what
your church teaches you?
I'm under no obligation
to forgive you.
I'm no priest,
and you are no penitent.
I don't need your forgiveness.
MONSIGNOR: And therein lies
the journey to true redemption.
I hope for both of you.
(door shuts)
(door opens)
(footsteps approaching)
- It's me.
- What are you doing here?
Shit. Did they find him?
Not yet.
Are you okay?
You look terrible.
Kit...
- we have to kill him.
- What?
We should've done it
when we had the chance.
They're gonna find him,
and then he'll be free again,
and we cannot wait
for that to happen.
We're not going to. Lana,
he's the only thing standing
between me and the death house.
We have to get him to confess.
You know what
sodium pentothal is?
It's truth serum.
Even if we could
get our hands on some,
those confessions are deemed
inadmissible in court.
It'll never fly.
I'm desperate.
Look, I don't know
why they haven't
turned me in to the
state police yet.
Maybe 'cause I've seen too
much here but either way,
I need Thredson to talk.
I think I might know how.
(wheels squeak)
(door creaks)
(grunting)
You know how this goes.
You make a sound,
I bash your face in.
(panting)
You'd like to kill me right now,
Oliver, wouldn't you?
(panting)
(paper rustling)
This might change your mind.
What is this?
It's the ultimate cosmic joke.
You got me pregnant.
I'm gonna be a father?
No, Oliver, you're not
gonna be a father.
Not this time.
What do you mean? Oh, no.
No, no. Lana, please,
please, please don't
give him away.
I know what it's like to be
raised in the system...
- it ruins...
- Oliver, stop!
This monster
you planted inside me,
I'm getting rid of it.
And since I'm stuck here,
I'm gonna have to get creative.
No.
Lana, no, please.
This is a mercy killing, Oliver.
No baby
should have to grow up
knowing Daddy is Bloody Face.
No. He'll never have to know.
Kit Walker is gonna
take the fall for those crimes.
I promise you,
it'll all work out.
Is that how you see it?
Lana...
you know me, I can change.
I have great determination
- and now I have reason...
- Really?
You gonna be
a real stand-up guy now?
Yes. You owe me this.
It's my child, too. Please.
You're a sociopath.
You can't be honest
with anybody.
I can. I can be... honest.
I can. Please help me.
(grunts)
(gasps)
Okay.
(panting)
Donna Burton.
Why did you choose her?
I saw her...
at the library
a couple of nights.
What did you like about her?
(panting)
Her skin.
It was fuzzy like a peach.
And I wanted to feel it.
So you skinned her alive.
Yes.
And Alison Reidel?
(panting)
She was a secretary
at my dentist's office.
I always liked her.
I put her to sleep first,
but she kept talking to me.
I was so confused.
And what about Wendy?
She never loved you.
She locked you away.
DR. THREDSON: Her skin was fuzzy like
a peach, and I wanted to feel it.
LANA: - So you skinned her alive.
- What?
Hey.
LANA: And Alison Reidel?
- I think we got it.
LANA: - Hide that tape.
I'm not finished here.
Hey... bitch.
So it was all an act, huh?
- No.
- You were never pregnant?
No, that part was true.
Was. Sadly,
your beloved baby died
last night.
(crackling thunder)
(gasping, thunder rumbling)
It started as a trickle.
Within an hour,
it was a bloody mess.
(crashing thunder)
It really wasn't
that bad, actually.
God, you're a monster.
You are worse than I am.
You killed an innocent child.
(gasping)
I have bakery duty later.
And after knife count,
I'm gonna pocket one,
and I'm gonna come back and
slit your throat nice and easy.
I always wanted
to know what it was like
inside the mind of a killer.
Now I know. (Gasps)
(door closes)
Ah, Mr. Walker.
I thought it might
be you. You really
shouldn't be wandering around
these halls, you know.
You're not even officially
part of this institution.
However, I'm very glad
you're here. We have so much
to talk about.
Après vous, monsieur.
I always keep a bottle of
18-year-old single malt
in my desk...
for special
occasions like this.
I think you'll find this
exceptionally smooth.
What are you doing?
I'm just trying
to being friendly.
Why?
(sighs)
Because I've seen
what you've seen.
They were here.
The creatures you
told me about.
The little green men,
except of course,
they're not green,
are they, Mr. Walker?
No. They're obviously
a great deal more powerful
and technologically advanced
than we are.
They're terrifying.
Mm-hmm. They took Grace.
They took her body while I
was trying to dispose of it.
What would they...
what would they want with her?
That's what
I've been asking myself.
Tell me, Mr. Walker.
Did you have sex with your wife
just before she was taken?
I've almost forgotten her.
I'll take that
as a yes. You also
had relations with our Grace,
which is why Sister Jude wanted
me to sterilize the two of you.
Oh, you're saying
it's 'cause of me
that those creatures took them?
They're experimenting,
probably refining
some form of eugenics.
I want you to help me
to bring them back.
They're studying
you, Mr. Walker.
You're obviously valuable
to them,
and a good scientist always
protects his subject.
For example,
if your life were threatened,
they would have to act
to preserve their specimen.
What are you saying?
If you were to be brought
to the brink of death,
they would return
to reverse the process.
You want to kill me?
No, Mr. Walker.
I want to almost kill you.
Of course, it would be ideal
if you were to cooperate,
but then, I'm not asking
for your permission.
You're a crazy bastard.
But you got my permission.
If there's a chance
I could see Alma again.
I'll do what I have to do.
Well, then, Mr. Walker,
prepare to die.
You are nothin' but
trouble, lady. Give me that.
You ain't got the
guts to kill no one.
Give me the knife,
and we'll call it a night.
(sighs)
Haven't prayed in years, Father.
How does it feel?
Strange, but good.
Nobody ever gave me this shot...
to rehabilitate myself.
As the figurehead
of this institution,
I want all of our patients
to find forgiveness
and a new purpose.
Even you,
in spite of your crimes.
Oh, I want to be saved, Father.
I'm already living in hell.
I don't want to spend eternity
- there, too.
- You could be my miracle, Leigh.
Do you repent of your sins?
I do.
If I can turn a man
like you towards Christ,
imagine the reforms
I could make
on a national scale.
Not just mental health.
Believe me, if
I ascend to the highest ranks
of the church,
I won't back down
from the fight.
LEIGH: You're quite an
ambitious man, Father.
MONSIGNOR: I just want to serve
and make a real
difference in the world.
Do you renounce Satan
and all things evil?
I do.
Turns your eyes
to Christ, Leigh.
Whatever shackles you,
your freedom lives
- in him.
- Praise Jesus.
Do you intend to
lead a new life,
putting God first
in all things?
I do.
Then I baptize you in
the name of the Father,
Son and the Holy Spirit.
Oh, thank you, Father.
I feel like a new man.
Thank you, Sister. I just
needed to lie down for a bit.
(door creaks shut)
(door closes)
Hello, Oliver,
I'm here to keep my word.
(gasps) Missing something,
Miss Winters?
It was you.
You let him out,
you let Bloody Face out,
I know you did.
What have you got here?
(gasps, clicks tongue)
Miss Winters, I thought
we talked about this.
It's too late,
it's already done.
Really?
(heart beating)
(sighs)
Praise God.
Your attempt to murder
this precious child
was unsuccessful.
You couldn't
possibly know that.
Oh, but I do,
and I know something else.
It's a boy.
(knocking)
I think I need
another posthypnotic suggestion,
Dr. Gardner.
I ate an entire bucket
of chicken by myself last night.
Dr. Gardner?
(gasping)
(screams)
("Dominique" by The Singing Nun
playing)
♪ ♪
My God,
what did they do to you?
Nothing I didn't do to you.
Give me a cigarette.
Come on, goddamn it,
give me a cigarette;
I've earned it.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Lana.
Can I call you Lana?
Sure.
I'm truly sorry for
what I did to you.
What I did...
was more than just
wrong, it was immoral.
It was criminal.
Yes.
I don't expect you
to forgive me.
But I'm gonna make it
up to you, I swear it.
How?
- I'm going to get you out of here.
- Oh, yeah?
Last time someone said that
to me, it didn't go so well.
Yeah.
- You don't trust me.
- No.
I don't trust anyone
or anything.
Yeah, well, I'm gonna
earn your trust.
- You think so?
- I do.
Yeah, things are going
to change around here.
(shouting and applause)
(gasping)
(indistinct chatter)
Well, hot damn.
That pink stuff...
that's gonna kill me?
Potassium chloride.
I'll inject this directly
into your heart muscle,
which will cause the
heart to stop beating.
From my experience, it'll take
approximately two
to four minutes
for all the oxygen in
your brain to be depleted,
and then you'll die.
But you can reverse it,
you can, you can
bring me back to life.
This syringe contains atropine,
extracted from
deadly nightshade.
When I need to revive you,
I'll inject this
along with adrenaline
into your system.
These two drugs,
administered within two
minutes after your death,
along with a sharp blow to
your chest with my fist,
will restart the heart.
(sighs)
I don't mind telling you...
I'm scared.
(chuckles) I'll admit
I'm feeling slightly
apprehensive myself.
(sighing)
(whispering): Our Father,
who art in Heaven,
hallowed be thy name,
thy kingdom come,
thy will be done on Earth,
as it is in Heaven.
What are you mumbling about?
It's the only prayer
I can remember.
Just in case.
(clears throat)
(exhales)
This is going to hurt.
(grunting)
(heart beating)
(gasping)
(heartbeat stops)
The baby's full-term.
It won't be long.
Grace.
Who brought you here?
- I thought you were...
- She'll need a room.
I'll look after her.
Oh, God.
(footfalls approaching)
- Help me.
- I'm here.