Ben...
Harmon!
I am not leaving here
till I have my $1,000!
Screw you!
You owe me!
Oh, here.
Here, take one.
And go!
You little brats!
You little rotten-- go!
Come on, come on.
Hey, honey.
Dad, there's some freaky dude
at the door
screaming about money.
I think he might be
one of your patients.
I don't know,
should I call the cops?
No. No.
Just-Just keep the door closed.
Is it locked?
Yeah.
Okay, we're on our way home
right now.
Violet, just-just keep
the door locked.
Ah.
I know you're in there.
Is that your daughter?
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Tate?
Hey.
It's been insane here.
First the cops were outside,
then some freak
started banging on the door,
screaming about money.
Hey, hey.
Shit like tend
to go down on Halloween.
It's probably just
asshole kids.
It's fine now.
I'm here.
I painted it black.
I know how you don't
like normal things.
You're the first boy
to ever give me a flower.
Thank you. I love it.
You ready to go on our date?
Yeah.
Violet?
Violet?!
Violet!
Violet?
Viol...
Ben!
She's not here.
Call her cell phone.
Violet, where are you?
I'm just hanging with friends.
We told you not to leave.
I'm sorry.
I should've called you earlier.
Is this the part where
you make me come home?
Are you safe?
I swear.
Are you having fun?
Yeah.
What happened with the guy
who was banging on the door?
It was just some kids.
I think they were
playing a prank.
They went away.
I want you home in an hour.
Okay. All right, bye.
Who was that?
My mom.
Aw...
I spoke to Violet.
She was out with friends.
What are you doing
with a knife?
I'm sick of those kids
wrecking our house.
They destroyed the pumpkins
on the front porch.
So your plan is to kill them?
I'll go clean up
the mess out front.
Okay.
Clearly, we've both
had a long day.
I'm gonna go take a bath.
Then tomorrow,
I'd like to talk about
you moving out.
I'm not leaving this house.
And I'm not giving up
on this family.
You hear me?
I'm not
giving up on this family!
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
I want my money.
You stupid...
Son of a bitch.
Where is she?!
Who?!
Hayden! I know she's
out here somewhere.
Get your hands
off of me! Help!
Where is she?!
She's under the gazebo!
There's nothing under this
gazebo and you know it.
This was all
staged. Why?
What are you talking about?!
She was at my door
ten minutes ago!
What?
Oh, shit!
Was she pissed?
I'm pissed!
All this for $1,000?
I don't think so.
What are you two playing at?
I won't be the victim
of your sick extortion.
You're in this together!
Oh, wow.
You really don't
get it, do you?
Your narrow, clinical
worldview doesn't let you.
Buddy, you are so screwed.
You know what the thing
about the dead is?
They got nothing left to lose!
Enough of this bullshit!
I want some goddamn answers!
Baby...
you don't even know
what the goddamn question is.
Where is she?!
Beats me.
Tell me!
She could be anywhere.
Probably here.
You better watch your back.
As well as your front.
Because, you thought
she was dangerous before...
Let me tell you who's dangerous.
That would be me!
You really want to keep going
with this story, Larry?!
'Cause I'm right at the edge!
And if I go over,
I'm taking you with me!
Do it.
Oh, do it now.
Oh, I'm begging you.
Please, kill me, Ben.
Kill me.
That way,
I can come back
and haunt you, too.
You see that crazy bitch,
you tell her we're done.
I'm not playing your games.
You come back on this property,
and I will kill you.
You hear me?
I will kill you.
Promises, promises.
Hi.
Um, sorry to bother you,
but your alarm was triggered.
Is everything okay here?
Yeah.
You know, our daughter
went out a little while ago.
I bet she set it off.
Oh, okay, okay.
Who, uh, who did this
to your pumpkin patch?
I don't know.
It looks like
asshole kids to me.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, you catch them doing
any more mischief,
send them my way.
Will do.
And thank you so much
for responding so quickly.
I must say, since we hired you,
I feel...
Safer?
Yeah, yeah.
Good.
Okay. Have a good night.
Thank you.
I want to.
Oh, no.
Sorry.
I thought...
I just...
Violet, I swear...
I want to be with you so badly.
And that's never
happened to me.
With a girl.
Are you gay?
No.
I just...
Maybe it's those meds
your dad gave me.
...do that, you know.
I'm gonna go.
No, no. No, Vi.
I'm not ready to go.
Not yet.
I used to come here...
when the world closed in
and got so small
I couldn't breathe.
I'd look out at the ocean,
and I'd think...
"Yo, douche bag,
high school counts
for jack shit."
Kurt Cobain,
Quentin Tarantino,
Brando, De Niro,
Pacino...
all high school dropouts.
I...
hated high school.
So I'd come here
and I'd look out at this
vast, limitless expanse.
Then it's like,
that's your life, man.
You can do anything,
be anything.
Screw high school. That's...
It's just a blip
in your timeline.
Don't get stuck there.
There's someone here.
Nice costumes.
What are you, the Dead
Breakfast Club?
You know, there's a whole lot
of beach, guys.
Good job, Tate.
You finally came out of hiding.
We've been waiting for years
for you to show your face.
- But you like Mommy's little safe house,
don't you? - I don't know you.
You know, I'm actually surprised you have
the balls to show your face around here.
Yeah. Maybe you should have worn a mask.
I'm not really into Halloween.
But this year's different,
right? You have a date.
How cute is that?
Leave her alone.
We don't want her.
We want you.
How about we drown him?
No, we should shoot him
right between the eyes.
Ha, ha, Halloween pranks.
Somebody please waste this bitch.
Yeah, why does he get a girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Kyle, you?
No. I haven't had sex in a long time.
Come on, let's go.
This beach sucks.
Someone should
pick up the trash.
Hello.
You called me?
Yeah, I did.
I think it's time for us
to have a conversation.
Has he told you about Boston?
Here's the thing, Hayden,
I know that you might find
this hard to believe,
but I was your age once too,
and not really that long ago.
And I wasn't such
a saint either.
I fell in love
with a married man,
and I lived and breathed
the fantasy
that we were going
to be together forever.
Soul mates and lovers, and
everyone was going to be happy,
and everybody lived forever.
And that didn't happen, Hayden.
'Cause it never happens
that way, it never does.
'Cause what he's looking for
has nothing to do with you.
It's got nothing
to do with anybody.
There's something
missing in him.
He found something in me he'll
never find in you again.
He said my face was soft
like a baby,
and between my thighs
I tasted like
raspberries and cream.
You know what I really regret
when I walked in on you
screwing my husband?
Was that I didn't just rip your
smug little face off!
Way too late for any
of that now, Mrs. Harmon.
Ask him about Boston.
Hayden is in the house!
Where?
I didn't see her, but I know she's here.
Where is she?
I'll look around. I can talk to her.
Do not talk to her.
I want to call the police
and have her arrested...
You're overreacting.
...and thrown in jail. I am not overreacting!
Hayden is just
a confused little girl.
She's not going to hurt you, Vivien...
Stop protecting her!
I'm not protecting her!
I'm protecting you!
You seriously want ten cop cars
out in front of Murder House
on Halloween night?!
You think that's going
to help us sell this place?
Just wait here.
Hayden!
Hayden?
You down here?
I love it when you say my name.
Say it again.
Hayden, you have to leave.
Such a mean thing to do.
Close the door in my face?
How could you do that to the
mother of your child, Ben?
Come on, you
remember, don't you?
Hayden, I know what this is.
You can't extort me.
You and that psychopath.
Kiss me.
I miss your mouth.
I miss the way it tastes.
I'm aching for you.
My tongue is swollen,
my lips are raw.
I'm rotting from the inside out.
What's happening to me?
Oh, right, a gazebo, Ben?
Not even a decent
headstone? A gazebo?!
You thought I was gone, so you
just thought you could throw me
away like I didn't matter?!
Like I never even existed?!
Is that what you think
of women, Ben?
Like they're just some
disposable nothings
that you can sit on top of
as you casually drink ice tea?
Stop screwing with me!
What is this? What do you want?
I want your wife to know
the truth about you.
You're sick, Hayden.
You need help.
Professional help.
A therapist, Ben?
Is that what I need?
I really owe you an apology.
Here goes.
I'm so sorry about
what I did to you.
It was nothing personal...
I'll deal with you later.
Right now I need
to take care of Vivien.
Oh, please.
Let me help.
I haven't used this in ages.
What are you doing?
I'm redecorating.
I'm sorry, Vivien, I really am.
But you ruined my Halloween,
and now you have to pay.
Stop it!
All I wanted was one night
with my guy, some Halloween fun,
some crafting in a house that
I love and have bled for,
and you ruined it, and he left.
And now he's out at the bars.
He's probably on his fourth
unprotected blowjob.
You are a psychopath. I am
calling my security company.
You don't get it, do you?
No one can protect you now.
Get out of my house!
Get out!
Ben?!
Get out of my house!
It's mine!
Get out!
Ben!
Ben?
What is it, hon?
What is it, baby?
What is it, sweet girl?
Are you seriously going to act
like nothing happened
at the beach?
They totally knew you, Tate.
But I don't know them.
Then why do they hate you?
They-They're just
high school assholes.
I mean, the world's
full of them.
It's popular kids who get off
on being mean and cruel.
I thought you understood that.
Tate, I can tell you're totally freaked out.
It's them.
They followed us here?
This is bullshit.
Hayden?
Ben!
Hayden, where are you?
I wanted to apologize.
Oh, you wanted to apologize,
really?
I just thought
it would be a shame
to let all those lovely bubbles
go to waste.
I'm sure your maid
can deal with the ring.
Where are you?
Come over here, girl.
I would be happy to.
Just tell me where you are.
I wasn't talking to you.
I love what you've done
with this kitchen.
Hallie, girl?
Hallie!
Oh, great, he sends
his little girlfriend out.
With a pair of scissors. You
gonna make us some paper dolls?
This is private property.
I have every right
to call the cops.
Go ahead, call them.
You'll probably need them.
Screw that.
She deserves whatever
happens to her.
Yeah, she's like those
lonely, fat chicks that
marry guys on Death Row.
You're deeply,
deeply disturbed.
You guys need
to take your disgusting
made-up faces and go home.
Made-up?
Now.
Home?
Where is that?
I'm an only child.
After what happened,
my parents split up, sold
the house, moved away.
No forwarding address.
So I don't have a home.
Parents suck,
but I can't fix it for you.
Can you fix this?
Can you give
me back my scholarship
to Georgia Tech?
I'm supposed to be starting
quarterback freshman year.
- She doesn't care.
- She's in love, and she'll do anything
for him, including giving him
her virginity.
Tonight was the night,
wasn't it?
None of your business.
KYLE Stupid slut.
She's worse than he is.
She thinks it's okay
what he did to us.
What did he do to you?!
She doesn't know.
About what?
It's okay.
How have you not heard about Westfield High?
We just moved here.
Pick up a yearbook, bitch.
Or read a newspaper.
We're kind of famous.
So you're popular
and you're pissed off.
I don't know who you are.
Let's put her down,
out of her misery.
Leave her alone!
Finally, the Prodigal Son
returns.
Come on down, man.
We've got some questions.
Go inside.
I can handle this.
I seriously doubt that.
Go inside!
No. They want to hurt you.
Karma's a bitch, Tate.
You want to talk to me?
Let's see how fast you can run.
Hello. Hey,
my boyfriend's in trouble.
There's a bunch of kids
chasing him.
I think they're gonna kill him.
Come with me to my house now.
Leave me alone, you crazy bitch!
Addy is dead because of you!
Hallie! Hallie.
Hallie, come here.
Hallie, come here!
What do you want, Hayden?!
For the truth to be known,
finally,
and for once.
I'm not interested in anything
you have to say.
How well do you know
your husband?
Too well. Get out.
What do you think
he's capable of?
Adultery, clearly.
What about murder?
If you're trying to shock me,
or show me how enlightened
you are
about my perfect life,
you're a little late.
Leave.
Not until you know.
Not until you understand,
really understand who
it is you're married to.
That's all I want, Vivien...
for you to know the truth.
That's why we have
to talk about Boston,
about the pregnancy,
about everything.
He told you I'm pregnant?
What?
You're pregnant?
Oh, God, that's why.
That's why.
"It's your choice," he said.
"Yours."
But there was never any
other choice!
He didn't want me
to keep my baby,
because he already had yours.
What do you think you're doing
to my house?
You're a disgrace.
Is that all the fight you have
left in you?
How can you allow that ghoul
to take the only thing
that gives your pathetic life
any meaning at all?
Hold still.
I will not permit
another failure in this house.
Save the baby.
Hayden, I don't know what he did
to you or what you think...
That's the trouble!
You don't know!
I'm not some silly schoolgirl!
I'm a woman!
And I matter!
You're hurt.
Yes, I'm hurt!
He hurt me.
And he'll hurt you
and that baby.
That's why it's better
for you and for it
if we just end this now.
I'm going to cut it out
of you now.
No!
Hayden, no!
As him about Boston! Ask him!
Tell me about Boston, Ben!
Tell her!
I lied to you, Vivien.
I didn't go to Boston
to be with a patient.
I went there to be with Hayden.
She needed me.
She needed you because
she was pregnant, Ben?
But that's not true, is it?
Because you hadn't
seen her in over a year.
Isn't that right?
I went back.
Months later, I went back.
I lied about that, too.
There, she knows everything,
Hayden. Now put it down.
Please.
- Mrs. Harmon?
- Yeah!
You activated the panic button?
Yes.
She's the intruder?
CONSTANCE
She wanted to be a pretty girl.
Of course, she didn't look
so pretty...
lying on that table
under those harsh,
energy-efficient lights.
May I have a moment, please?
One of the many comforts of
having children is knowing
one's youth has not fled,
but merely been passed down
to a new generation.
They say when a parent dies,
a child feels
his own mortality.
But when a child dies,
it's immortality
that a parent loses.
Look at you, my pretty girl.
My beautiful, beautiful baby.
Constance, I'm so sorry.
Well, you did encourage her,
that's true.
But you were just trying
to be kind, weren't you?
I was the one who sent her out
into the world tonight.
And it did what it will do.
Go ahead, drink your,
drink your tea, honey.
Can I have one of those?
Oh, a cigarette?
Certainly.
Just don't let your mama know
that I am encouraging
your vices.
You know, Adelaide was
a willful child.
I suppose if she inherited
anything from me, it was that.
In truth, I think
my little monster was more
like me
than any of my other children.
I didn't know
you had other children.
Tate is my son.
What?
He cannot know about this,
Violet.
He cannot know
that his sister has passed.
Not now.
He doesn't...
react well to certain things.
So you...
you have to promise me.
I don't understand.
Well, he's a sensitive boy.
You've seen that.
He's a young man with...
too deep feelings,
the soul of a poet.
But none of the grit or steel
that acts as a bulwark
against this...
these horrors of this world.
The steel that...
has protected me.
That Adelaide possessed.
And that...
that you have, too.
I, uh...
I think...
that's why he's taken so
with you.
He craves your strength.
Look.
Maybe he misses his sister.
But we must
protect him, Violet.
I used to run track.
We know.
Is somebody going to explain this to me?
Do you believe in God?
Is that what this is about?
You guys are with
Campus Crusade.
You asked me
if I believed in God,
and you put a gun to my head.
I said yes.
It wasn't even true,
and I said yes.
And then...
you pulled the trigger.
What is this?
Is this part
of a Halloween act?
Because, I mean, the
makeup, it's chilling,
but the performance...
No more bullshit, Tate!
You owe us an explanation!
Why are you doing this to me?
What do you...
Why did you target the jocks?
I never did anything to you!
It wasn't
just the jocks, man.
I mean, look at me.
Look at Amir.
Did you ever once go
to a football game?
This guy was honor roll.
He could have been
valedictorian.
Asshole! No, I'm not going
to change
the world, okay,
but he could have.
He could have been something,
and you ruined
all that potential.
We want to know why.
You owe us that.
Way more than that.
You got the wrong guy, okay?
No. Don't you re.
We have been looking
for you for years.
He's screwing with us.
Maybe he's in denial.
Maybe he's psychotic.
Get out!
Get out of my head!
We aren't in your head.
We are right here.
Chloe, sun's coming up.
Please just say it.
Just say what you did.
I should be 34 years old.
And married, with babies.
I don't know you.
I'm sorry.
Come on. We got to go.
How was your night?
My mother's dead.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't go with her.
No.
I am not speaking to you.
I'm sorry, baby.
I can't help myself.
I feel like I'm doomed
for all of eternity
to be trapped in an unhappy,
adulterous relationship
wrecking on this goddamn house...
...which will never be
just the way I want it.
You are.
So what is it with you girls?
Young, everything to live for,
but you throw it all away
on some guy you
can't even have.
I did have him.
We were in love.
He was just too guilty
to leave her.
A lovely woman
like Mrs. Harmon--
pretending
that you nuked her dog.
That's just evil--
just plain evil.
You don't do things like that
out of love.
What'd you put in there anyway?
Tomatoes.
It was a joke.
Stupid Halloween prank.
I see.
Oh, you don't see anything.
He was the love of my life.
What's going to happen now?
You're going to jail.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player