("Seven Wonders" intro plays)
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ So long ago
♪ Certain place, certain time
♪ You touched my hand
♪ On the way
♪ On the way down to Emmiline
♪ But if our paths
♪ Never cross
♪ Well, you know I'm sorry but
♪ If I live to see
the seven wonders ♪
♪ I'll make a path
to the rainbow's end ♪
♪ I'll never live to match
the beauty again ♪
♪ The rainbow's end
♪ So it's hard to find
♪ Someone with that kind
♪ That kind of intensity
♪ You touched my hand
♪ I played it cool
♪ And you reached out
♪ Your hand to me
♪ But if our paths never cross
♪ Well, you know I'm sorry but
♪ If I live to see
the seven wonders ♪
♪ I'll make a path
to the rainbow's end ♪
♪ I'll never live to match
♪ The beauty again
♪ The rainbow's end
♪ So long ago
♪ It's a certain time
♪ It's a certain place
♪ You touched my hand
♪ And you smile
♪ All the way back
♪ You held out your hand
♪ If I hope and if I pray
♪ Ooh, well, it might
work out someday ♪
♪ If I live to see
♪ The seven wonders
♪ I'll make a path
to the rainbow's end ♪
♪ I'll never to live
to match the beauty ♪
♪ Again
Good luck, girls.
♪ If I live to see ♪
♪ The seven wonders ♪
♪ If I live to see the seven wonders ♪
♪ I'll make a path
to the rainbow's end ♪
♪ I'll make a path back
♪ I'll never live
to match the beauty ♪
to see that beauty ♪
♪ That beauty
♪ That same, same beauty again
♪ If I live to see
the seven wonders ♪
♪ Oh, if I live to see...
(door slams shut)
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
MYRTLE:
The great Leonardo da Vinci,
who I'm certain was a warlock,
although it's never been proven,
in his masterpiece
The Last Supper,
depicted grilled eels,
bread and wine on the table.
I've chosen caviar
from the Caspian Sea.
Served on billinis.
Along with champagne.
As fitting stand-ins
as we partake
of our own last supper.
For one of you,
a last moment of freedom
and anonymity
before assuming the Supremacy.
For any one of you others,
possibly a last meal.
CORDELIA:
Since the beginning
of this coven, it has been
every outgoing Supreme's duty
to identify her successor.
Which Fiona
not only neglected to do,
she actually tried to kill
her successor.
So we are doing something
never done in our history.
We are going to give
all four of you
the chance to prove yourselves.
Only one of you will succeed.
To quote the Bible...
loosely...
"When I was a child,
"I spoke like a child,
I understood
"like a child,
I thought like a child.
"But when I became a woman,
I put aside childish things."
Childhood is over, my girls.
Put aside fears,
reservations and petty things.
Kick ass tomorrow.
MYRTLE:
The Seven Wonders.
Usually we move
from easiest to hardest.
But since we're breaking
with tradition this year,
let's begin with my
personal favorite.
Telekinesis.
MISTY:
What if I can't do it?
Then you're not the Supreme.
And you can go back
to your swamp.
Misty,
you're first.
Intention.
I did it.
Almost sounds like you want it.
It's not about want.
You either are
or you aren't a Supreme.
Maybe I am.
Queenie?
Yup.
Madison, obviously
this is your bailiwick.
Whatever that means.
Last but not least, Zoe.
MYRTLE:
Concilium.
Commonly only known
to the public
as "mind control."
It's a tricky little craft.
When properly exercised,
can bend the strongest
of wills to your desire.
Now, let's see
which of you fillies
has really got the stuff.
QUEENIE: Stare all you want,
flower child.
Nobody controls my mind but me.
Oh, shit.
Knock it off!
This is fun.
(yells)
Next.
No hard feelings about...
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow,
ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Next.
He's not part of this!
He is now.
Well done.
I'm not done.
Now, lick it.
That's enough.
Let's move on.
Having fun yet?
Yeah, it's a real party.
The descent into the nether
world will be your next test.
Getting to hell will be simple
for girls of your talents.
It's the getting back, darlings,
that is the challenge.
If your soul hasn't returned
to your body by sunup,
you'll die.
What do you think
it'll be like?
I was hoping to never find out.
Girls, you may begin.
(all take a long, deep breath)
ALL:
Spiritu duce, in me est.
Deduc me in tenebris vita
ad extremum,
ut salutaret 'nferi.
Descensum!
(sizzling)
(gasps)
You're the first to return.
Damn.
I saw the same people
in the same line
for the same chicken.
(gasps)
It was horrible.
I was stuck on a
network musical.
It was a live version
of The Sound of Music.
I wasn't even the lead.
I was Liesl.
(gasps)
What happened to you?
Kyle and I kept breaking up.
On a loop.
He said he didn't love me.
Over and over,
over and over.
It's okay, it's okay, I'm right here.
(crying)
KYLE (whispers): I'm right here, it's okay.
Are we all back?
Everyone but Misty.
(frog croaking)
BOY:
Freak.
You're a freak.
Mr. Kringley, she did it again.
Where's the dissection frog?
It's right there, she brought it back to life.
Shut up, Bobby.
She snuck a live one in
to trick you,
but the trick's on her.
Pick up the scalpel.
No, please don't make me.
If you won't dissect
a dead frog,
then you will dissect a live one.
No, I don't want to kill
a living thing, please,
you can't make me.
You kill it, or I'll have
a talk with your parents.
(croaks)
No!
(croaking)
BOY:
Mr. Kringley, she did it again.
If you won't dissect
a dead frog,
you'll dissect a live one.
No, you can't make me kill a living thing.
Please, you can't make me!
(screams)
Mr. Kringley...
If you won't dissect a dead frog,
then you'll dissect a live one.
No, no, no...
(screams)
If you won't dissect a dead frog...
No, no...
(screams)
(croaking)
If you won't dissect
a dead frog, then you'll...
(screaming)
If you won't dissect a dead frog...
If you won't dissect
a dead frog...
She's stuck.
We have to help her.
There's nothing we can do.
She has to get back on her own.
CORDELIA:
Misty...
Follow my voice.
We are all here
waiting for you.
Sequere...
lucem.
Venite ad me.
Her time is up.
(sobs)
No...
(sobbing):
No, no!
No...
No!
(gasping sobs)
No, no...
Before we recommence,
I would like to take a moment
to remember our fallen
sister witch, Misty Day.
MADISON:
Can we get on with it?
I didn't really
know her that well.
You're a stone cold bitch.
MADISON:
When you play
with fire, you get burned.
She's right.
Misty's gone.
There's nothing
we can do about it.
QUEENIE:
All right, then.
Let's get on with
finding the new Supreme.
The next task before
our candidates
is transmutation.
Tag, you're it.
Now you're it.
Gotcha.
(gasps)
QUEENIE:
No tag-backs.
Tag.
Tag, you're it. (giggles)
(yelps)
CORDELIA:
Careful, girls!
It's not a game!
It's the best game,
and we need a goddamned break!
(screams)
(laughs)
CORDELIA:
Careful, girls...
Can't we just have a little fun?
(Queenie and Madison laugh)
MADISON:
You bitch.
(Queenie laughing)
QUEENIE:
Suck it!
(Madison laughing)
(Zoe gagging)
KYLE:
e!
Oh! Oh!
Dear God.
KYLE: Oh, God!
What is it?
Oh, God, Zoe! Zoe!
Our dear Zoe!
Help!
Somebody help us!
Somebody help us, please!
Help! Help!
(gagging)
Zoe!
CORDELIA:
Vitalum
Vitalis.
Vitalum Vitalis.
(exhales)
Nothing's happening.
Please.
(exhales)
Guess who isn't Supreme
after all?
(sniffles)
I'm sorry.
CORDELIA: Queenie, take
Kyle into the house.
Madison, the Vitalum
Vitalis.
You want me to bring her back?
Do you think you can?
Oh, I know I can.
Then do it.
Would that make me Supreme?
It would mean we could continue
with the Seven Wonders.
Because she'd be back in the game.
Just like you
were back in the game
after you were brought back.
Unless you're afraid
you might not really be
the Supreme.
(fly buzzing)
(buzzing)
(chuckles)
She lost, fair and square.
It's not my fault.
Madison, if you refuse this,
then you don't deserve
to be Supreme.
What's deserve got to do
with any of this?
You can't disqualify me.
Either I'm Supreme or I'm not.
And, obviously, I am.
You know, I'm starting to think
Fiona had the right idea,
leaving this shit show behind.
I'm thinking very seriously
about doing the same thing.
So either crown me
or kiss my ass.
CORDELIA:
I can feel all their eyes on me.
I failed.
I let this coven fall
into ruin.
MYRTLE: Don't be so hard on yourself,
Delia. You did all you could.
Not enough.
If Madison Montgomery really
is all that's left to us,
maybe it is better this way.
Maybe we deserve to die out.
I'll confess, I've had
similar dark thoughts.
I was so certain
about Misty Day.
Or even our dear Zoe.
She had the makings
of a fine leader.
(sniffling)
(exhales, sniffles)
(panting)
(cries)
Why'd you leave me?
(sniffles)
You said you'd never leave me.
(sniffling)
CORDELIA: Oh, I can't
believe she was right.
It was Madison all this time.
My mother was always right.
That's not true.
She was never right about you.
Well, I guess it's different
when it's your own family.
How true is it that a prophet
is never recognized
in his own country?
Madison was not born
to the Supremacy.
But you, Cordelia,
you have royal blood
in your veins.
What are you saying?
I was a fool not
to have realized it earlier,
seeking all this time
in the dust
for that which may have been
right before us all along.
I-I don't understand.
First, you were suppressed
by your mother,
then by your own theories.
You have great power,
my girl, power that
has been seeking expression
in these young vessels.
But it's in you.
You must let it out.
You must
perform the Seven Wonders.
You think I could be
the next Supreme?
I'd stake your life on it.
(sighs)
I know what you guys are doing.
You want me to finish
the Seven Wonders,
so you're trumping up
some competition.
I'm not stupid.
Yes, you are.
Are you ready?
(scoffs)
(piano thumps)
CORDELIA:
Descensum.
(gasping)
What did you see?
(panting)
Me,
trying to get Fiona's approval
and getting bitch-slapped
for it.
Not exactly new.
Transmutation.
That's five Wonders
accomplished.
Let us move to the sixth,
divination. Cordelia...
Fine. Okay,
I'm back in.
(chuckles)
What? It's only fair.
This thing started
as a competition.
I say we end it like one.
Divination.
Let's rock.
Hidden in this house are items
belonging to former Supremes.
Cordelia, divine
in the pebbles the location
of the item
which belonged
to MiMi DeLongpre.
Who knew the test
came in Braille?
Shh.
Southwest corner.
Up the stairs.
Second door
down the hall,
beneath the dresser.
The antique broach presented
to Supreme MiMi DeLongpre
on the night
of the Great Ascension.
Correct.
Your turn, hotshot.
MYRTLE:
Divine for us
the location of the object
belonging to Supreme Anna
Leigh Leighton, Madison.
This is stupid.
I'm not doing it.
Because you can't?
Let me show you some real power.
Let's go into the greenhouse
right now, and I'll bring
Zoe back to life.
Divination first.
We're doing this by the book.
I'm sick of your book.
I have so many powers,
I could tear this room apart
until there's nothing left
but your little trinkets
but, no, I have to do
this bullshit!
Fail.
(exhales)
Wait.
The vase above the fireplace.
Wrong.
The piano. I meant...
I meant the piano. There's
something in the thing.
Girl, no.
This is bullshit.
Cordelia did it.
Because the game is rigged,
Queenie.
Wake up!
You would accuse us
of chicanery?
You bet your bony ass.
I never had a shot
at running this shit hole coven.
(grunts)
I didn't even want to come here
in the first place.
It's all just some jacked-up
version of Celebrity Rehab.
I'm out of here.
Thus endeth your Seven Wonders.
Oh, no shit, lady!
I'm going back to Hollywood
where people are normal.
And I suggest
you change the locks
because when I tell
TMZ everything,
it won't be long
before torches, pitchforks
and Molotov cocktails become
a real big part of your day.
Peace out!
(whimpers)
(whimpers, sighs)
What do you want, dumb-ass?
(whimpering)
You let her die.
(gasps)
Why...
did you let her die?
I...
(shrieks)
(exhales loudly)
(wooden creaking)
You know that dark place! We've both
been there! (loud, raspy breath)
We both came back.
(whimpering)
Why?!
I did it for us.
I love you.
I love you. Please. Please.
(sobbing)
You're not that good an actress.
(gasping)
(yelling):
Stop! No!
(gasping)
(screams)
(guttural gasping)
(grunts)
(airy gasp, grunts)
(Kyle grunts, Madison gasps)
(loud, high-pitched gasp)
(Zoe coughs)
(gasps)
She'd already started packing.
That's helpful.
No one will wonder where
the body went once we bury her.
Who the hell are you?
The help.
CORDELIA: The hallmark
of any rising Supreme
is glowing, radiant health.
(echoing):
...glowing, radiant health.
Behold. The one, true Supreme.
MAN: Since your extraordinary
public statement last month,
there has been quite
a bit of fanfare.
This frank revelation
about your cult--
that's sparked quite a brouhaha
in the media, and...
Let me clarify that, Bill.
We are not a cult.
We-we don't proselytize.
We have no agenda,
we're not recruiting.
Women who identify
as witches are born as such,
and their abilities--
which we call powers--
are part of who they are, part
of their DNA, if you will.
BILL: Oh, I see. So,
in fact, you're saying
that it's not a choice,
being a witch.
CORDELIA:
That's exactly what I'm saying.
There are so many young witches
who have resisted their calling
because they're afraid...
of how they may be perceived,
or what's expected of them.
But there are
still hate crimes.
That is true, but, you know,
when you hide in the shadows,
you are less visible,
you have less protection.
We'll always be targets
for the ignorant.
It is what it is.
But we are strong women, Bill.
So, what would you like
to say to all those girls
watching and wondering
if they might be witches?
Hmm?
Call us, e-mail us
or just come to New Orleans.
There is a home and a family
waiting for you.
MYRTLE:
I'm so proud of you.
We need to discuss the Council.
We've never had
young witches on the Council,
and Queenie and Zoe deserve an
elevated role here at the school
to set them apart.
What do you think?
I would start by telling them
that being an authority figure
requires you
to make hard, unpopular
decisions for the greater good.
They've matured so much,
I think they can handle it.
I was talking about you.
Me?
You have every chance
to be the greatest Supreme
this coven has ever seen.
Stop.
Delia, I have something to say,
and your tasteful modesty is
out of fashion, so knock it off.
Thanks to you,
we're entering a new era.
You've planted the seeds,
but in order to
reap their harvest,
you have to clear the rot
of the past.
Myrtle, you know
I love your metaphors,
but I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Me. I'm talking about me.
We all know
what happens to a witch
who grievously harms
another witch.
I hope you're not suggesting...
I'm not suggesting.
I'm insisting.
You want to be burned
at the stake?
Again?
Want has nothing to do with it.
At the start
of your glorious reign,
the last thing you need
is an ABSCAM or Watergate.
I killed, and I
must pay for it.
Now, before word leaks,
and you are tainted by my hubris
and actions, however deserved.
Myrtle,
stop talking.
I didn't hear this.
I didn't.
Listen to me, child.
Now that you're in charge,
my life's work is fulfilled.
I've made many painful
mistakes in my life.
I want my death
to have some meaning.
No!
No way!
You were my mother,
my true mother,
just as you promised
you would be,
and I can't do this without you.
Stiff upper lip, my dear.
Everything you do or say ripples
through the entire coven.
You cannot be a hypocrite.
I won't stand for it.
("Silver Spring" begins playing)
♪ You could be
my silver spring ♪
♪ Blue-green,
colors flashin' ♪
♪ I would be your only dream
♪ Your shinin' autumn
ocean crashin' ♪
♪ Don't say that she's pretty ♪
♪ And did you say
that she loves you? ♪
♪ Baby, I don't wanna know...
In the absence of the Council,
as reigning Supreme
of this coven,
I hereby decree...
(bird screeching)
...for the murders of our
sister witch Cecily Pembroke
and our colleague
Quentin Fleming,
you...
Myrtle Snow...
...are hereby sentenced
to death by fire.
Delia...
my sweet daughter...
I have never been more proud.
Any last words?
Only one.
Balenciaga!
(echoing)
(screaming)
♪ La, la, la-da, la-da
(indistinct crowd chatter)
♪ La, la,
la-da, la-da ♪
♪ La-da...
QUEENIE: You got to
check this shit out.
Line's around the block.
Where are we gonna
put all these girls?
We'll buy more houses
if we have to.
Look at you.
You two are powerful witches
with more skills and confidence
at your young age
than I had for much of my life.
I need both of you to
help me fulfill the promise
of all this coven can be.
A place to protect, develop
and celebrate witches.
You will not only be
my right hands,
you will be my Council.
What do you say?
I got your back.
Good. And you?
I'd be honored.
Should we open the doors now?
(Fiona laughs distantly)
Not yet.
Stay here.
(echoing footstep)
There's just one more thing
I need to deal with.
(echoing footsteps)
I saw you die.
Look again...
now that you have real vision.
We had a deal.
It wasn't notarized,
it wasn't on paper,
but we had a deal!
(Fiona laughs)
You men, with
your fragile egos.
We still have a deal, babe.
I'm going to Paris
for just a couple days.
Just until Cordelia
gets her little dwarves
to perform the Seven Wonders
and I find out
who the next Supreme is.
Why? Why would she
decide to do that?
Because the old Supreme
will be dead.
Or at least that's
what she'll think.
Well...
But I'm gonna need your help.
I mean, it won't
be pleasant for you.
But if you do it right...
I promise you the world.
Hmm.
(soft laugh)
I'm gonna put something
inside you.
Well, a...
A young gypsy girl
tried that on me once,
I almost hit the ceiling, I jumped so high.
(laughs)
No. In your brain, sweet boy.
Oh.
A vision.
A memory.
What happens when I wake
up from this vision?
You'll figure it out.
Now drink.
No.
If you're gonna
offer me your spit,
I'll take it straight
from the spigot.
(chuckles)
(glass clatters)
(door slams shut)
FIONA: I ruined a perfectly
good pair of Jimmy Choos.
But I knew you'd
get rid of him for me,
once he served his purpose.
Whose blood was it?
A goat's.
I never killed anybody.
Not yet.
But that is what
you came here to do.
(short laugh)
That was the plan.
Let you do the dirty work.
Identify the Supreme and then
I come in and take her out.
Makes it a little harder
when it turns out
to be your own daughter.
Not really.
(quick laugh)
You didn't come
here to kill me.
You were hoping
I'd put you out of your misery,
but I don't need to.
You're close.
I doubt you'll make it
through the night.
Might make you
feel good, though.
(chuckles)
Is that why you were
always so awful to me?
Because you knew I was going to
take your power some day?
You took my power...
the minute I gave birth to you.
A woman becomes a mother,
she can't help but
see her mortality
in that cherubic little face.
Every time I looked at you
I saw my own death.
You were a constant reminder...
of my worst fears.
Oh, and all this time,
I thought you just
didn't like me.
It was nothing
personal, darling.
I loved you plenty, though.
Just my own way.
Which, I'll admit,
had its limitations.
Your fault was
you were always looking for
another version of motherhood.
(exhales)
I can feel the power
vibrating off of you.
It feels good,
doesn't it? Hmm?
It's mine, you know?
When it came into you,
it left me.
The law of conservation
of energy.
I have to die
for you to truly live.
Crying over me.
Isn't that the ultimate twist.
I'm not crying over you.
I'm crying for me.
You were the monster
in every one of my closets.
A lifetime spent either
trying to prove myself to you,
get close to you
or get away from you.
I'm crying for the girl in me
who dies when you die.
Then kill them both right now.
Huh?
They both hurt too much.
And when we're finally gone
you will fulfill your destiny
and lead this coven.
God knows you'll do a better job
of it than I ever did,
though you won't look
half as good doing it.
Come on.
For God's sake...
have mercy on me.
Put me out of my misery.
I hurt everywhere.
You're scared,
maybe for the first
time in your life.
No powers, no magic.
Just a woman facing
the inevitable.
A divine being
finally having
a human experience.
(sniffles)
No one can help you, Mother.
You have to do this alone.
And the only way out...
is through.
So, feel the fear
and the pain.
Let it all in...
...and then let it all go.
(short sob)
I don't think we ever hugged.
(short, sniffling breath)
(sniffles)
(coughing)
(rooster crows)
(birds chirping)
(dog barking outside)
(rooster continues crowing)
(mutters)
(man whistling a tune)
AXEMAN:
Oh. Sweetness.
You're up.
I hope you're hungry.
I brought you some, uh,
some catfish, I'll fry it up.
Granddaddy's favorite.
Oh, get those goddamn things
out of my face.
Why you always got to be like this?
Huh?
Always got to be like what?
"Be like"--
what do you mean?
Every morning you wake up,
and you act like you
don't know where you are.
And then we fight.
I'm... I'm tired
of fighting.
Every morning?
How long have we been here?
Well, now,
you can't put a clock...
on eternity.
Oh, no.
Jesus Christ.
(rooster crowing)
If want a stiff one,
come over here.
Don't be vulgar.
Oh!
Maybe you ought to...
(groans)
...lay off the sauce
for a while.
(breathing heavily)
Drink in the... the fresh air.
(groans)
(spits)
Delia did this.
No, nobody sent you here...
but you, baby.
We had a deal.
Oh, God.
I can't spend eternity here.
This place--
it reeks of fish
and cat piss.
(whimpers)
What is this?
Knotty pine?!
I want Delia.
I want...
It's too late for that.
I want my daughter.
No, come on, you're here.
(whimpering)
You're here.
With me.
Nobody is going anywhere.
I'm in heaven.
So just, uh...
Oh, no.
relax. You're here.
(Axeman laughing)
(Papa Legba cackling)
(laughter distorts and echoes)
(footsteps echo)
All right... (exhales)
...let's open the doors.
(girls chattering,
screaming playfully outside)
♪ La, la, la-da, la-da...
CORDELIA: Miss Robichaux's Academy
for Exceptional Young Ladies
was established as a premiere
girls' finishing
school in 1790.
Afterwards, it came
under new management.
Our management.
We survive.
Up until now,
that's all we've done.
But as I look at your faces--
all of them beautiful,
all of them perfect--
I know together...
we can do more than survive.
It's our time to thrive.
What's a Supreme?
You're looking at her.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player