(doorbell ringing, knocking on door)
Does Tate Langdon live here?
He's my son.
Why? What has he done?
All right, make entry.
(sirens wailing in distance)
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Stop it.
Ah, okay.
(two gunshots)
(people screaming in distance)
(three gunshots)
(footsteps running)
What the hell, dude?
Somebody's shooting up the school.
He's shooting people.
Wait, are you hit?
Where are you hit?
Shit, I don't, I don't know, man.
That's not my blood.
I was right next to Mark Finstein,
and the guy shot him
in the freaking skull.
Who's doing this?
I-I don't know.
We need to get the hell out of here!
(two gunshots)
Go! Go!
(footsteps walking slowly)
(door handle rattling)
(muffled whimpering)
(sniffles)
(footsteps slowly walking away)
(whispers):
Block the door!
Get the door!
(rapid gunshots)
(boy whistling tune)
(panting)
(screams)
(gunshot, body thuds)
(footsteps walking)
(whispers):
Hey.
No, no.
Please, no!
(gunshot)
(whimpers softly)
(footsteps walking)
(gunshot, thud)
Screw this.
It's going to be okay.
Ev-Everything is
going to be okay.
It's going to be okay.
(shell clatters on floor)
Hey!
It's enough.
Get out of here.
(gunshot)
(sobs)
(pumps shotgun)
Oh, God!
(sirens approaching)
(sobbing)
Oh, God.
Please!
(screams)
Why?!
(sobs):
Why?
(pumps shotgun)
(sirens getting closer)
Please.
(gunshot)
(sirens wailing)
CONSTANCE:
Let me just talk to him!
Please, just let me talk to him!
Tate!
(sobbing):
Tate. No, please.
He'll go peacefully.
He's just a child!
Tate! Tate!
Oh, God, please don't do this!
He's just a child!
Let me talk to him!
(whispers gunshot sound)
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
(panting)
Mom?
Mommy.
She's not here.
Where is she?
Did you hurt her?
(chuckles)
Of course not.
She's probably at the grocery store,
buying some frozen fare to
reheat for your supper tonight.
You found out about Tate,
didn't you?
I knew you would.
Get out of my house!
This is not happening.
I questioned my sanity
when I first found out..
But this house...
this house will make you a believer.
You see, Violet,
we were living here
when Tate lost his way.
And I believe that the house
drove him to it.
What? No.
That can't be real.
You're a smart girl.
How can you be
so arrogant to think
that there's only one reality
that you're able to see?
I want you to meet someone.
Violet Harmon,
meet Billie Dean Howard.
The child has no manners.
Billie is a gifted medium.
She can help.
You're confused.
Overwhelmed.
Why wouldn't you be?
I never asked for any of this.
None of us did.
But nothing can be done
once one's been chosen.
Billie has been helping me for years.
I first found her on Craigslist.
I've been through all the phonies,
but she is 100% authentic.
I've just come from a
meeting at Lifetime;
they're interested in
making a pilot with me.
A Craigslist psychic
with a Hollywood agent.
Who'd have thought?
A medium, dear.
I can't read your future.
That's a different gift.
Have some chamomile tea.
It'll calm the nerves.
I'm in a dream.
I used to be like you.
Until I was 25.
When out of the blue, my cleaning lady
shows up as I'm brushing my teeth.
Except she's got no toilet brush
and rubber gloves,
she's naked and bloody.
Her husband murdered
her with an ice pick.
It's hard to keep good help.
BILLIE:
Do you think I wanted
a bloody Mexican ghost in my bathroom?
All I wanted
was to improve my tennis game
and unseat Charlotte Whitney
as president of my book club.
But I was chosen.
And when you're chosen,
you either get with the program
or you go crazy.
Understanding the truth
is your only choice.
What's your version of the truth?
There are some who have
an understandably violent
and vengeful reaction
to being horribly murdered.
They refuse to move on, until
they exact their pound of flesh.
Then there are a very few souls,
like Tate,
who don't even know they're dead,
who walk among the living
in child-like
confusion.
That's why I wanted him
to see your father.
I was hoping your father
might help him achieve some
clarity about himself
so that he could
see the truth on his own.
We must help him cross over, Violet.
This is bullshit.
I was set up.
My computer was--
someone messed with my...
Who is Mary?
VIVIEN: Violet, she wants
to talk to you.
(monitor beeping steadily)
I don't understand you.
Never will understand you.
Does that mean anything to you?
"They don't
understand you?"
(sobs)
(door opens, closes)
Can I trust her?
I'm not sure.
(Bach's "Cello Suite No. 5
in C Minor" playing)
(screams)
(ring clinks on table)
(beeps)
Okay, so I've checked the perimeter
of the property, the
upstairs, the basement.
Everything's secure.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm just hearing things.
I'm sorry I wasted your time.
Oh, no, it's not a waste
of time. Not at all.
That's what I'm here for.
Even if it's only for
your peace of mind.
Thank you. My husband just moved
out recently, so...
He had an affair,
and don't know why I'm telling
you this.
Oh, no. It's okay.
Actually, we get sensitivity training.
We deal with people's worst
fears, real or imaginary.
That makes sense.
But, actually, with the, uh,
with the infidelity,
I have firsthand experience with that.
Hmm.
Not me. No, my wife.
With another man?
It was a woman.
Yeah, I know. A lot
of guys would be into that,
right? Me, not so much.
(door opens)
What happened now?
I thought I heard somebody.
Where? Outside or inside?
Outside.
I looked around,
checked the alarm system.
Everything seems to be working fine.
Thanks for filling in.
Oh, by the way, the woman
that I took out of here?
She never made it to
the police station.
What? I don't understand.
She must have hopped out of my vehicle
at a stop sign or something.
Please keep you alarm on
even when you're home.
Thank you.
(door opens, closes)
What are you doing here?
I've got to work, Vivien.
Rent an office.
We don't the have the money, Viv!
I promise I'll leave right after
my last patient.
I don't want you here.
You brought this on yourself.
(sighs)
You're right.
And you're angry.
If you violated our marriage
right in front of me, I'd be furious.
But I need a place to work, Vivien.
We need the money.
I'm finding it really hard
to look at your face.
'Cause I really, really, really
want to bash it in.
I find you disgusting...
and disappointing
as a man.
And we're gonna end this marriage
and we're gonna sell this house
and I'll let you be a father
to our kids
because I happen
to think that you're a good one.
But I'm not gonna be your friend.
I will merely tolerate you.
And you can see
your patients in the house,
but I want you to leave after
your last session of the day.
♪ ♪
Are you scared now?
BEN:
Urban legends?
Urban legends, they, they terrify me.
Lately, it's gotten so bad
I can't even function.
When you say "urban legends..."
All of 'em:
Bloody Mary, Candy Man,
Lady in White.
Children's ghost stories.
When I was younger, my brothers
would tell them to me.
Hold me down,
force me to listen to 'em.
Older brothers can be mean.
They were younger.
I see.
Nothing else scares me:
terrorism, disease, violent crime,
crashing economy.
Just these stories
that I know are utter bullshit.
I'm paralyzed, Doctor.
I can't maintain a relationship.
What girl wants to screw a grown man
who has to sleep with his lights on?
Speaking of sleep, I can't.
I don't. I binge eat.
I smoke like a fish.
Lately, it's gotten a lot worse.
I must look terrible.
I haven't had the courage
to look in a mirror
in the last week.
Why's that?
Piggy Man.
Piggy Man?
I don't think I heard that one before.
Oh, God.
It's, uh, it's terrifying.
Okay, story goes, um... he was
a hog butcher in Chicago
during the World's Fair of 1893.
And before he would go
into the slaughter pen,
he would put on this mask,
this pig mask
that he'd made from one of his
other kills,
and he would snort--
(snorts)
you know, like a pig--
make 'em think he was one of them.
Then one day, he slipped
and he fell.
The pigs, hogs tore him apart.
And they didn't find
one piece of him anywhere.
So everyone assumed.
'Cause not too long after,
his former customers,
they started turning up dead;
gutted, skinned and hung upside down
in the bathtub to drain,
like a hog in his shop.
And they say if you stand in
front of a mirror and say...
Here, piggy pig-pig.
"Here, piggy pig-pig,"
that he'll return for the slaughter.
And have you tried that?
Here, piggy pig...
(squealing)
No. But there's
something inside of me
that's afraid that I might.
And that scares the hell out of me.
We're gonna get to the root
of what that is, I promise you.
Okay.
I want to see you again Wednesday,
3:00, all right?
Sure.
In the meantime, I want you to shave.
In a mirror?
Can you try, Derek?
Yeah.
Good.
Call me if you need me.
Okay. Thank you
very much.
Dad?
Hey, honey.
I'm sorry, Daddy.
It's all my fault.
What?
No. No, baby.
No, no, no.
Your mom and I both love you
very much.
It's never gonna change.
It's the darkness.
It has me.
I have you.
Baby, I have you.
She's a nurse in your department.
I think her name is Angie something?
She fainted during an ultrasound.
Right. She's
an ultrasound technician.
So she quit?
Would you ask her to call me, then?
Vivien Harmon.
Okay, thank, thank you.
Hi, Constance.
I'm so sorry
about Adelaide.
I've been meaning
to make a condolence call,
and I've just been...
Moira tells me that you've
been suffering terribly.
That every time you leave
the house, you're racked
with violent morning sickness?
Yeah.
Well, you know, my mother
always recommended
a big platter of offal
during the first trimester
of pregnancy.
She preferred pork.
Oh, well, how nice of you
to think of me during this...
I believe life is for the
living, don't you?
Sweetbreads.
Now these two are thymus
glands, one from the heart,
one from the throat.
And this is the pancreas.
It's so good for mother and child.
Full of protein, vitamin C,
all the B vitamins and iron.
And speaking of which...
how is your other baby?
She was such a dear sweet child,
and such a comfort to me
when Addie passed.
Well, she's been very upset.
Spending a lot of time in her room.
Sometimes, children going
through transition
just need alone time.
Well, I, um, can't thank you
enough for the offal.
Offal.
Moira, why don't you sauté
these for Mrs. Harmon's lunch?
Do 'em the way that you used
to do them for me, remember?
With sweet butter.
I'd be happy to do that
for Mrs. Harmon.
(chuckles) We need that baby.
We need another...
sweet child around here.
May I say something that could
be considered out of turn,
but that is sincerely heartfelt?
I guess so.
Cheating on one's pregnant wife
qualifies as an unspeakable
criminal act.
It's on a par with murder.
And I'll tell you one thing I know,
if I know anything at all--
Dr. Harmon will cheat again,
if given half the chance.
I hope I haven't upset you,
speaking my mind so directly.
Just a pinch of the sea salt,
a tiny squeeze of the
lemon, if you like.
Although I prefer without.
And ma'am,
I've left the pancreas uncooked.
They say it's the
tenderest organ of them all,
especially when eaten raw.
Oh... Uh, no,
I don't think so, Moira.
Think of the baby.
Mmm.
DEREK: I don't think
I can do this.
Have you been doing the exercises
we talked about--
looking in the bathroom
mirror at home?
Yeah, but I cheated.
I used my toaster-- it has
a very reflective surface.
(chuckles) Okay, well, that's a start.
You're in my house now.
And you're safe.
You're safe.
I'm going to stand
right outside this door.
I can't do it.
Here.
Use this.
But only if you have to.
Breathe...
I'm going to turn off the light.
I'm going to close the door,
and I'll be right outside.
Breathe, just breathe.
That's it.
Turning off the light.
(whimpering)
And I'm going to shut the door.
(gasping, hyperventilating)
Think I'm having a heart attack!
I'm right here, Derek.
Five feet away.
Just say the words.
Nothing's going to happen.
Here, piggy, pig-pig.
(gasping):
Here... piggy... pig.
(screaming)
Derek! Derek, it's okay.
It's okay.
There's-there's
something in there!
It's okay.
(gasps)
There's no one in there.
You see?
(sobbing)
It's never going to stop.
I'm broken!
No, no, no, no...
I didn't get to the last pig.
Over 5,000 amnios, and not
a single miscarriage,
but who's counting?
And so this would--
with the Down syndrome...?
Down syndrome, cystic fibrosis,
spina bifida.
The amnio results should
put your mind at ease.
Sorry I'm late.
Traffic was insane.
You didn't have to leave work
to come here.
Of course he should.
He's the daddy.
That's right, I'm the daddy.
We have to be nice to Mommy today.
And keep her off her feet.
Will do.
Regina is going to find
the perfect spot
so we don't hurt the baby.
Right there.
You're going to feel a tiny pinch.
I owe you an apology.
It attacked you too, didn't it?
No.
But I don't know what's real anymore.
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
The Devil is real.
And he's not a little red man
with horns and a tail.
He can be beautiful.
Because he's a fallen angel,
and he used to be God's favorite.
Have you read the Book of Revelation?
No.
In Heaven, there's this woman in labor
howling in pain.
And there's a red dragon
with seven heads waiting
so he can eat her baby.
But the Archangel Michael,
he hurls the dragon down to earth.
From that moment on,
the red dragon hates the woman,
and declares war on her
and all of her children.
That's us.
Oh, yeah, things have
gotten pretty weird for me.
Me, too.
I can't eat, I can't sleep.
The nights are the worst.
I get four hours, if I'm lucky.
That's only with pills.
What kind of pills?
Can I have one?
They were over by the sofa.
Used to be a row of tables.
I get four or five
of you sickos a year.
Usually freshmen.
What, are you a transfer?
You're that teacher.
You're like a hero.
Now you know what heroes look like.
Wait, I'm sorry.
I'm not like those other kids.
I know Tate.
I mean, I know his mom.
We moved next door to her.
Did you know him?
Before he did this?
I knew his face.
Didn't seem like a bad kid, actually.
He was in here a lot.
Kind of thoughtful, liked to read.
Byron, books on birds, random stuff.
Was he bullied or something?
Did he even know the kids he shot?
I just want to know why he did it.
Me, too.
Why are you bullshitting me?!
If the bullet had been
an inch to the right,
it would've missed my spine
and I would have walked out of here.
Might have even been able to stop him.
An inch higher,
it would have killed me.
Sometimes shit just happens.
Good people don't just have a bad day
and start shooting people.
Maybe he wasn't a good person.
Moira.
I'm afraid I've got some bad news.
You've lost the baby.
No, no, no, no.
Oh.
Stop. Stop cleaning
and come sit down.
Have a seat.
I'm afraid we're going
to have to let you go.
I don't understand.
The house is spotless.
It has nothing to do with you,
believe me.
Mrs. Harmon,
this is not a job.
For me, coming here is a reprieve.
I understand.
We just can't afford it.
Then I'll work for free,
till you sell.
I'll make the house gleam and
glitter for the new owners.
Then, perhaps, they'll hire me.
Mrs. Harmon,
I've had my share of regrets.
But leaving an expectant mother
in the time of her need
will not be one of them.
I'm staying.
(laughing)
You're being so dramatic.
I'm not helpless, Moira.
Well, I'm not one to belabor a point,
but where has the time gone?
You must be famished.
I mean, I am hungry.
Constance dropped by earlier
with another delicious delicacy.
No.
I don't want you cooking for me.
Please, don't go to the trouble.
Come on.
No trouble at all.
It's served raw.
So you and the baby get
the full measure of vitamins.
It's the most nutritious
organ of them all.
It came from an organic farm.
I hear the raw food movement
is really taking off.
For the baby.
♪ ♪
(touchpad beeping)
Tate?
I'm not playing
hide-and-seek, Tate.
You have to leave now!
(ghostly laughter)
Get out of my house!
Look at what he did to me.
(screaming)
Excuse me, ma'am,
I don't want to bother you,
but I'm hurt and needing some help.
Has my wife medicated you?
Are you here for the procedure?
(rock music blaring)
(music stops)
(sobbing)
(gasping, shuddering)
Don't you die on me, Violet!
No. Don't you die!
Don't you die on me.
Violet!
Stay with me.
(gagging)
(sobbing)
It's okay.
Have you been doing
the cognitive exercises
we talked about?
Yes. Nothing helps.
I can't take this anxiety.
The other night, I meet a girl.
Allyson--
works in accounting.
There's a real chemistry there.
Derek, that's great.
Ask her out.
Get out of your own head.
I... I would love to.
But what happens if she wants
to come home with me some night?
How... how do I explain why
all the mirrors are covered up?
Derek, you're doing this to yourself.
Think of it as the
psychological law of physics.
The more you fear something,
the more power you give it.
You need to conquer this thing, Derek.
You're going to go home,
you're going to look in the mirror,
and you're going to say those words.
They're not magic words.
There is no Piggy Man.
Once you face that,
you can finally start to deal
with the real issues in your life.
I mean, you're absolutely right.
I want to do it.
I can do it.
The moment you do...
you'll be free.
(bell tolling)
Angela?
Vivien.
Thank you so much
for agreeing to meet with me.
Of course.
That's, uh, probably close enough.
When you gave me the address,
I didn't realize it was a church.
It's where I feel safe.
The hospital said you quit your job,
but they didn't say why.
I've been concerned
because of the ultrasound
and...
They said that the machine
malfunctioned, but...
it seemed to me that you
saw something that scared you.
Yes, and I've been praying
about it ever since.
I saw the unclean thing,
what you carry in your womb.
The plague of nations, the Beast.
Okay, so you didn't see anything.
So... the machine malfunctioned.
It did not.
I saw the little hooves.
You need some help.
"And the woman was full of the
filthiness of her fornication!
"The mother of harlots
and abominations of the Earth!"
(sighs)
Here, piggy, piggy, pig.
Pig.
(laughs quietly)
Here, piggy, piggy, pig.
Who you calling a pig?
(gun fires)
What the hell did you do?
This was supposed to be a robbery.
Now it's murder, you asshole.
Called me a pig.
We got to get out of here.
(both chuckling)
I am beginning to think
you're a fraud.
And that nail polish is vulgar.
Don't take it out on me just because
your dead daughter is mad at you.
Now, why the hell
would you say that to me?
Because you're capable
of handling the truth.
I see it all the time.
The dead can hold a grudge
better than most Scorpios.
I want to talk to her, Billie.
I have one last thing...
that I have to say to her.
I just miss her so terribly.
She was my reason for living.
She says you should have told
her that when she was alive.
She's a feisty one.
Talk to her.
She's here.
Come on.
(sighs, chuckles)
Baby...
I am so sorry.
I'm sorry because...
most of the time that I was with you,
especially when you were younger,
I was just so overwhelmed.
It wasn't easy being a single parent,
and you were such a handful.
So I guess I forgot to say
the things that I was supposed to say,
but that I honestly
always felt in my heart.
I am so proud of you, Addie.
I admire you so...
(sighs)
for what you were able to overcome.
And I think you're beautiful.
Addie, I think you are
the most beautiful girl...
I ever met.
She says thank you.
And that she knows.
And that where she is now,
on the other side...
she's a pretty girl at last.
(laughs)
She also wants you to know
that she's grateful.
For not getting her
to the lawn at the old house.
She doesn't want to be with Tate.
She's afraid of him
now that she knows the truth.
CONSTANCE:
Please don't hurt him!
Tate! Tate!
Wait! Let me just talk to him!
Will you please
just let me talk to him?
Tate!
Tate! No, please.
He'll go peacefully.
CONSTANCE:
He's just a child!
Please don't hurt my son.
(sirens wailing)
(whispers gunshot sound)
(heavy gunfire)
Why did you do it?
(sirens wailing, horns blasting)
TATE:
I like birds, too.
Why do you like them?
'Cause they can fly away
when things get too crazy, I guess.
Are you going to tell your parents?
About the pills?
No.
I've been sleeping a lot.
They think I'm depressed.
Are you?
I'm sad.
Me, too.
Violet.
Something has changed in you.
Toward me.
You're distant, cold.
I don't know what I've done,
but I'll leave you alone from now on
if that's what you want.
Is that what you want?
You know why I'd leave you alone?
Because I care about
your feelings more than mine.
I love you.
There, I said it--
not just on some chalkboard.
I would never let anybody
or anything hurt you.
I've never felt that way about anyone.
Come here.
I'm tired.
Me too.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player