(big band song playing)
♪ Because I love him so ♪
♪ I'd be good
for nothing too, I know ♪
♪ Without good for nothing Joe ♪
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
(door opens)
(door closes)
♪ I'd be good
for nothing too, I know... ♪
(doorbell rings)
Dr. Curan, I presume?
You work out of your home.
I think that's wonderful.
Well, I cater mostly to the
families in the neighborhood.
Makes it convenient
for them and for me.
And for your wife.
Oh, I'm not married, not currently.
Where did you say you heard of me?
My girlfriend Nabby Pierce?
You filled her cavity.
She said you were very good.
Nabby, yes, nice gal.
Nabby also said
you sometimes made
special arrangements
with girls who were a little short.
You don't have any money?
Not very much.
I'm still trying to establish myself.
I'm an actress.
I'm going to make it big.
Everyone says so.
You can expect to see me up
on the silver screen one day.
Don't you think
we could come to some kind
of mutually beneficial arrangement,
Dr. Curan?
Well, I-I don't know.
It hurts, Doctor.
I really need you to fill it.
I'm just going to put this on you.
(gas hissing)
I don't want to crush your carnation.
It's not a carnation, silly.
It's a dahlia.
Just breathe.
(gas hissing)
WOMAN:
Isn't it a beautiful day, Ava?
Mommy, what's that?
That's nothing, honey, it's just
a department store manne...
(gasps)
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Violet's camping out in her room.
I was wondering if you could
make her a sandwich.
Of course, Dr. Harmon.
Thank you.
Could you help me a minute?
It must be hard on you
with your wife indisposed.
I miss Vivien.
We became quite close.
Don't worry.
Our secret is safe.
What secret?
The way you look at me, the
way you fantasize about me.
You have a diseased
mind, Dr. Harmon.
That must be why you
became a therapist.
I'm glad you and my wife are friends,
but I'm not interested
in your pet theories about me.
So maybe I'm way off base
or maybe I'm crazy like Vivien.
Is that what you think, Doctor?
I think you must have
pretty low self-esteem
to keep throwing yourself
at a married man
who doesn't want you.
So you don't want me?
You don't find me attractive?
Just make Violet a sandwich, please.
I don't believe you, Ben.
I know you want me.
No, I don't want this.
I love my wife.
I want her to get better
and come home
so I can take care of her.
I just want a normal...
boring family.
That's a beautiful speech, Ben.
It's Dr. Harmon.
No more games.
No more bullshit.
Do you understand?
I'd better make Violet a sandwich.
You know, it's just
a matter of time, Ben.
"The spirit is willing,
but the flesh is weak."
(dogs barking in distance)
(door opens)
Hey.
Did they all...?
Poo? Uh, yeah.
Oh, all except for that one.
Well, if he shits in the house
you're cleaning it up.
Damn, look at the mud you tracked in.
Nice.
You smoked the last one.
My daughter just died,
and you're on my back
about a goddamn cigarette?
Here, smoke that one, asshole.
I'm not another one
of your dogs. I got a job.
I work hard. I don't want
to come over here;
I don't want to have to work more.
You got a job.
Reading a script down at a call
center for two hours a day.
Oh, my.
Let me rub your feet.
And how did those headshots
that I paid for
work out for you?
I'm sorry about Addie.
She was a cool chick.
Ugh!
Yeah. Maybe that's why you used
to come over here early, huh?
Before I got home?
So you could spend
a little time diddling her, huh?
Whispering sweet nothings in her ear?
I hate when you drink.
Hey!
What?
Why don't you run on down
to the Koreans and get us
another carton of ciggies?
That's where I'm going.
And take that goddamn dog with you.
And don't come back until he does
his business.
(sighs)
(door opens, shuts)
Come on, buddy.
(wolf whistles)
That for me?
For the dog, actually.
Where you headed?
The store.
You want me to get you
some candy, little girl?
You're with that lady next door.
She a little old for you?
She seems like a royal bitch.
(sighs)
Maybe you and I should run away
together, then.
(Travis grunting)
♪ In the cool of the evening ♪
♪ When everybody's getting
kind of groovy ♪
(Travis gasping loudly)
♪ You call me up and ask me
would I like to go... ♪
I came inside.
It's cool.
I can't get pregnant.
Really? (chuckles)
Sweet!
Your mom isn't gonna get pissed?
Freaking hope she does.
Then I'm some sweet revenge.
I'm not gonna tell her.
Then what is the point?
Sex is the only weapon
you have against her.
She's treating you like shit
because she's afraid of losing you.
Prove to her that she's right,
and she'll be blowing rainbows
up your ass again.
I think that I love her.
Hey!
What's your story? I mean,
how come you get to live here?
You know, I heard they took
that lady to the loony bin.
I don't live here yet.
I'm moving in soon, though.
Dr. Harmon and I are in love.
Okay...
then how come you rocked out with me?
To see if I could do it
with a guy who's still alive.
♪ Ah-ha-ha, spooky. ♪
(doorbell rings)
Dr. Harmon, Detective
Jack Colquitt.
Missing Persons, right?
Mm-hmm. This young lady
believes you might be
involved in a case we just opened.
You don't remember me, Ben?
Marla McClaine.
Hayden's sister?
BEN: I honestly have no idea
what happened to her.
In fact, I have a few questions
for her myself.
You're a liar.
Hayden is pregnant with your baby.
And she comes here with the crazy idea
that somehow, you're gonna leave
your wife, support her
and raise your child together.
So what'd you do, Ben?
Where is she?
In a hole somewhere?
Dr. Harmon, the last time
I was here, I saw Ms. McClaine's
sister coming out of the house.
Yes. We made plans to
go to lunch... at Norm's.
You were also working in
the backyard digging
weren't you, around the time
she disappeared?
Detective, you have no idea
what happened here.
That's what we're here to find out.
What's with all the drama?
MARLA: What the hell, Hayden?
How come you haven't
answered your phone
or called or anything?
Uh, to be honest with you,
Marla, I didn't think
you gave a rat's ass about me.
I thought you were calling
to borrow money again.
So you're okay, then?
Obviously you're not missing.
Nope.
You don't have to worry about me, sis.
You were wrong about Ben.
I've decided to stay
here in La-La Land.
This is my home now.
(door closes)
BEN: You got about ten
seconds to give me
some answers before
I call that detective back
and have you arrested
for assaulting my family.
I'm-I'm sorry, Ben.
I was pregnant, scared and hormonal.
I was a crazy bitch
when I came here on Halloween.
I deserve whatever punishment
you think is right.
Ben, this whole thing
has been so ugly.
It's not me.
It's not how I want you
to think of me.
I don't know if we have
a future together,
but I've always been there for you.
From the beginning.
I just want you to remember that.
By the way...
I had the abortion.
You don't have to worry
about it anymore.
Dr. Harmon?
Excuse me, do we have an appointment?
I was told there was a doctor
here who might help me.
You need to call
and make an appointment.
Doctor, I think something
terrible might happen to me.
What do you mean,
"something terrible"?
I'm not quite certain.
It's a strange feeling.
An endless foreboding.
Like a dream I can't wake
myself out of.
Sounds like acute anxiety.
But you really--
It's worse than that.
I do things with men.
Things I shouldn't.
But I'm a great actress,
and it's frustrating.
I just need that break.
All you need is that one
person who believes in you--
and every time I go into an audition,
I think maybe he's the one and...
I get carried away.
Do you know what I mean?
I do.
I have an opening tomorrow at noon.
What's your name?
Elizabeth Short.
I assume you're
covered by SAG insurance?
I see.
Well, you're a beautiful young girl.
I just assumed that
you were working steadily.
In the meantime, we need to discuss
how you plan to pay for treatment.
Do you really think I'm beautiful?
Really?
You're, um...
an attractive young woman.
No, no, no, no, Beth,
we, we, we just discussed that.
You don't need to do that.
But I don't know how else to pay you.
I know you're the one who can help me.
I can tell you understand.
Well, we can...
figure something out.
You never need to do that with me.
I'm the one you should feel safe with.
(cell phone buzzing)
Excuse me.
Uh, I need to, I need to get this.
You won't regret this.
Hello?
Uh, just-just slow down, Doctor.
I can't...
I can't understand you.
I spoke with Vivien's psychiatrist,
and he doesn't feel she's
mentally strong enough
to hear this news right now.
Normally, I would be
very uncomfortable
giving a husband this information,
but you are her designated
health care proxy.
Would you just tell me
what's going on, Doctor?
Heteropaternal superfecundation.
Hetero-what?
Your wife's twins
have different fathers.
I'm sorry.
What did you say?
It's extremely rare.
Maybe one in a million.
Your wife must have had
intercourse with two different men
during the same ovulation cycle,
within a 48-hour period.
Where is she?
Little slut.
Who?
Violet.
She's been catting around
with my dog walker.
Nonsense.
The girl's taste in men
is hardly refined,
but I doubt it runs to rough trade.
Well, when Travis came back
from dog walking--
a 15-minute affair that somehow
stretched into 45--
he smelled... of something
other than canine.
You're delusional.
That girl wouldn't give
your greasy boy toy
a second glance.
She thinks she's in love
with your little angel.
But once the truth comes out,
I suspect that'll change.
What the hell are you babbling about?
The two babies her
mother is carrying--
only one of them was
fathered by Dr. Harmon.
Tate?
Tate, honey, it's Mama.
I have to talk to you.
Tate?
Tate...?
So talk.
(gasps) Oh!
Oh, God.
Tell me it isn't true,
what I've been hearing about you.
About what?
Your behavior.
God, after all the missteps,
we finally have somebody in this house
that maybe can help you.
Tell me you did not crawl
on top of that man's wife.
Oh...
Mama... Mama, you can't
tell Violet, okay?
Please don't...
What is wrong with you, for God sakes?
What's wrong with you?
Mama!
Don't you realize what you've done?
(sobbing):
Mama...!
Come play, Ben.
Come, Ben...
(echoing):
Please...?
(moaning, kissing)
Oh, Ben...
(moaning, gasping)
Get out.
Elizabeth, put your
clothes on and leave.
I'm sorry, but I can't
treat you anymore.
You're not really gonna
turn this down, are you?
And you're fired.
Sue me if you need to.
Make your last chore to show her out.
You said this would work.
You said this is what he wanted.
She's using you, honey.
(sobs)
My dreams will never come true.
Your dreams?
I know it sounds terribly selfish,
but I must become famous.
It's the only thing I've ever wanted.
Honey, don't you know who you are?
I'm Elizabeth Short.
You really don't know, do you?
(grunting)
(gas hissing)
(quietly):
God, you're beautiful.
Now, let's look at those teeth.
(drill whirring)
Beth?
Beth...
Oh, God!
(sobs)
Who are you?
My name is Charles Montgomery.
I am quite a renowned surgeon.
I'm here to help you.
(inhales deeply)
(inhales)
(humming a tune)
(singing quietly)
What have you done?
I've bisected her body,
removed the intestines
and drained her blood.
Why?
A writer writes, a surgeon cuts.
I think you will find
these pieces more portable.
What are you doing now?
She seemed so sad.
I've decided to give her a smile
that will last forever.
That's how they found me--
naked, on display for
the whole world to see.
You were the front-page news of
every paper for two months.
I really did become somebody.
She's been extremely agitated,
and the paranoia hasn't abated.
I'm sure the doctor will change
up the meds when he gets here,
but, in the meantime, we've
had to keep her restrained.
Restrained?
She attacked one of the orderlies.
He suggested that this
rapist in a rubber suit
was some kind of sexual fantasy.
Vivien...
you have a visitor.
(sighs deeply)
I know you can't carry on
a conversation right now.
That's okay.
I know what you're thinking.
You're thinking, "Thank God he's here."
"Thank God he can see
what they're doing to me,
"and how wrong it is.
And thank God he's a shrink,
so he can get me out of here."
You're right.
You're in hell here.
This is no place for my wife.
And I'd move heaven and earth
for the Vivien I thought
I was married to.
But you aren't her.
You're a stranger to me.
You actually pretended,
maybe even believed, like a sociopath,
that you were some kind of
holy saint without sin
while you shit all over me...
our life...
and our family
with betrayal and lies.
The way I feel right now,
I wouldn't lift a finger
to help you get out of here.
God, I miss college.
Enjoy it before real life
knocks you on your ass.
Do you want to talk about it?
Nope. I don't.
I miss beer.
Vivien hates it when I drink.
Especially beer.
I like beer.
("Spooky" playing)
Mm! There you go!
Can I confess something to you?
Hmm! I think the smart answer
would have to be no.
I'm not really confused about
interpersonal aggression.
You're not?
Uh-uh.
That's a shame, because
I could tell you a lot
about interpersonal aggression.
My marriage, for one thing.
Not in a happy place right now.
See? You do want
to talk about it.
I don't. I just want to--
I just want to drink
and get drunk and stumble
home on the T.
The thing is, Dr. Harmon--
I have a crush on you.
That's a bad move.
Seriously. I mean...
You're going to have
so many men in your life.
What does that mean?
It means you're a knockout.
You're smart as hell.
Is hell smart?
(chuckles)
Oh, oh, listen to this guitar solo.
I mean, it's-it's incredible.
(electric guitar solo)
(chuckles)
It was written in the stars.
And I was meant to take your class
right at the moment
your marriage imploded.
You needed me, Ben.
I did.
I did need you.
But I shouldn't have crossed the line.
Ben...
I abused my authority.
I was a consenting adult.
I still am.
Hayden, please, listen to me.
My marriage was a mess when we met.
And now? It's even worse, Ben.
You're right, it's bad.
It's really bad.
But here's the thing, Hayden--
and I hope you understand this--
we weren't written in the stars.
We're not meant to be together.
Not then, not now,
not six months from now.
Ben...
I was lonely, I was
heartbroken and I used you.
It was unforgivable.
I'm sorry.
But no matter what
happens with my wife,
I can't be with you.
I don't love you, Hayden.
I'm sorry.
I never did.
You don't love me?
You don't love me.
Okay.
Could I have a hug?
Of course.
Hayden, come on.
It's over.
You can't just hang around here.
I'm not just hanging around here.
I came for a reason.
When it concerns your family,
you have a right to know.
What are you talking about?
Vivien and that black guy--
you know, in the uniform.
I came around here the other
morning and he was leaving.
Who knows how long it's been going on?
Just thought you should know.
CONSTANCE:
Travis.
I need to talk to you, honey.
You mean yell at me some more?
On the contrary.
I want to apologize
for my earlier manners.
It was unnecessarily cruel.
Well, you've been going through
a lot of stuff lately, so...
It's true, I have.
But so have you. Here by my side.
Oh, and don't think it hasn't
gone unnoticed or unappreciated.
(chuckling)
You know, in many ways,
you are a fine man, Travis.
Sit down, baby.
I want to ask you something.
Okay.
What do you want to ask me?
Will you marry me?
(laughing)
Marry you?!
Listen to me, there's
going to be a child
and I want to bring that
child into this home
and raise it as my own.
What child?
Our child-- or it could be.
We could be a family.
I won't make the same mistakes
that I made the last time.
And you would be a wonderful father.
Father, whoa. Um...
I'm not ready to be a father.
Oh, but you are.
I've seen how you were with Addie,
and with the dogs.
With Addie and the dogs, it's...
Okay...
What about my career?
Your what?
My career, you know.
Maybe-- I don't know,
maybe we should wait
and let me get myself established
and then we could do whatever, you know?
What career?
What? This dream you have
of-- of appearing half naked
in your skivvies 60 feet
high above Times Square?
I don't know why
that's so funny to you.
I know that dream.
I had that dream!
I was going to be a big star,
and, baby, if it didn't happen for me,
it is not going to happen for you.
Why are you being so mean?
I am being honest.
No, you're being mean.
A lean torso in this town
is a dime a dozen, baby,
and that's all you've got.
I'm offering reality,
community property,
a chance to be somebody.
A father.
I mean, look at you. What are you now?
You're nothing.
No, I am something, and just
because you say that I'm not
going to make it, doesn't mean it's true!
Oh!
Doesn't mean it's true.
Jesus Christ! Jesus Christ!
God, how could I have ever
thought you could be a father?
You are not even a man.
Oh, come on...
Don't you dare!
You'd better be careful.
You know why?
Because the last man who thought
that he could strike me...
...came to a very unpleasant
end, and he was a man.
(groans)
She said that I wasn't a man.
She said I'd never be famous.
Bitch! Bitch! Bitch!
(panting)
Feel better?
Yeah.
I don't.
He said we weren't
meant to be together.
We were meant to be.
Let's go again.
What are you doing?
I totally thought you came.
No.
Really?
Look, uh, would you mind
finishing yourself?
I really got to go.
- I mean, I can't leave it like this
with Constance. - You're kidding me.
I thought you said you hated her.
I guess I love her.
And we got a baby coming.
A baby what, fossil?
I don't know.
I guess we're going to adopt.
After all that shit she said to you?
I'm going to come back, I promise.
Can I at least get a hug?
Yeah.
I had a really good time.
(squishing thud)
Shit! (groans)
(yelling)
(groans)
(panting)
I had a really great time, too.
Oh, shit, now what am I going
to do with you?
Whoa, Constance was right.
Now I'm never going to be famous.
That's not necessarily true.
In fact, now you might
even have a better chance.
The only one who's going to be
famous out of this is Ben
when they find the body down here.
They'll send him to prison.
Or he'll move out.
Goddamn it.
Who's to say the body
has to be found here?
What, are you going to drag
him out of here, Casper?
Well, if you know someone who might,
I could certainly make it easier.
There is someone who owes me a favor.
Shit.
Holy shit.
Yo, yo! Yo, come over here!
What?
Holy shit.
Holy shit. Yo!
(sighs)
(knocking)
Knock, knock.
My dear--
look at you.
Even this hideous place
can't dim
your charming girlish spirit.
Hello, Constance.
What a surprise.
Well, I hope it is a good one.
You know, I've been
thinking about you so much
and about this ordeal
that you've been through.
And being pregnant on top
of everything else.
My goodness, that poor baby.
Babies, it's twins.
Oh, of course.
Babies.
And is everything all right
with the babies?
They're growing very fast.
You can't believe how much food
I've been consuming.
Even in here, I'm just ravenous.
That's a good thing.
Oh, Vivien, Vivien,
I want you to know that I
intend to be there for you.
Whatever help you need.
I mean, babies are my thing.
I have a special gift.
And I've been a
single mother, I mean...
I know how we tell ourselves
that we don't need a man.
We can do it alone.
But the secret, Vivien?
The secret is community.
Sisterhood.
Constance, I don't want to
be rude or seem ungrateful,
I'm just so tired, and I just...
Probably from the meds.
I need to nap.
Of course, honey.
Oh, I'll just disappear...
Vivien, you know,
I know the pain of being doubted
by everyone around you.
It ravages the soul.
Well, those are for you.
Thank you.
I-I think I might stop by
at Sweet Lady Jane's,
and pick up some pastry for
that sweet little Violet.
Constance.
I was raped.
I didn't hallucinate any of it.
Well, of course not.
Oh, honey, I never
doubted it for a minute.
Please don't tell
anybody that I told you,
because I need for them to think
that I'm coming to my senses
so that I can get out of here.
Of course.
You poor thing.
What you've been through...
(alarm ringing)
(alarm shuts off)
You didn't have to
trigger the alarm system
to get me over here.
I've been wracking my brains,
trying to figure it out.
I gotta hand it to you both.
It was a terrific cover.
I'm lost here.
Where'd you meet her?
At Whole Foods? At the gym?
I installed your
security system, remember?
We moved here in early fall.
You met Vivien...
whenever.
Started having an affair.
Got her pregnant.
What?
She's having twins.
And only one of them is mine.
(chuckles)
Ah, okay.
So I guess the other one must be mine.
Look...
I'm not asking you for child support.
In fact, you're not even
gonna see this baby.
I just want to hear it
from you, man to man...
All right.
Man to man.
Hear this, Ben.
If that was my baby,
you couldn't keep me away.
But the sad fact is, is
that I'm shooting blanks.
You can ask my ex-wife.
We tried for five years.
All it takes is one good swimmer.
Look... I don't know
Vivien that well.
But clearly she has
been a very busy girl.
Hey, don't talk about
my wife like that.
You don't know her.
And you do?
You called her a whore and a liar.
That was just in
the last five minutes.
Your own wife...
You locked her away, Ben.
You know what?
Maybe it's good.
Maybe she's safer there.
MOIRA:
Kinky.
You want me to try that on?
Looks like you went to
a lot of trouble to find it.
What do you know about this?
I know I get wet just thinking about
sliding that rubber on my body.
Stop it. Stop your bullshit
and listen to me.
You're in this house all
the time. You see everything.
What happened with Vivien?
Why do you care?
You're a man.
Isn't this what all men want?
The freedom to satiate
their needs, guilt-free?
Just tell me the truth.
I think I made a horrible mistake
by putting Vivien in the hospital.
She was attacked by someone.
Congratulations, Dr. Harmon.
You're finally beginning
to see things as they are.
I think we're gonna get
a pickup on my Lifetime pilot.
And as soon as we do, I want
to bring you on as my guest.
I can't focus on your...
career right now.
I may be looking at a rather
earth-shattering situation.
Could we be talking menopause baby...?
Why am I seeing baby pictures?
Tell me...
What happens when a human...
copulates with someone
from the spirit world?
Spirits aren't known
for their potency.
Yes, but...
what if there is,
in fact, a conception?
You do know about the box.
The Pope's box?
What the hell are you talking about?
When a new Pope has been chosen...
and the bells of
St. Peter's chime...
...he is shown into
a small chamber
next to the Sistine Chapel.
They call it the Room of Tears,
named for the sublime mixture
of joy and sorrow
that he must contemplate
at this moment.
He is brought a key to this box.
It has been said that this box
contains the ultimate secret.
It holds the secret
of the end of the world.
Well, for Christ's sakes, Billie Dean,
the cameras aren't rolling in here.
Will you just cut to the chase?
This piece of paper
reveals the precise nature
of the Anti-Christ.
"A child born of human and spirit
will usher in the end of times."
It is the essence of evil.
A perversion of
the Immaculate Conception.
What are you talking about?
Oh, come on, honey.
The Holy Ghost merely whispered
in the Virgin Mary's ear
and she begat the son of God.
If the devil's going to use
a human womb for his spawn,
he's going to want a little
more bang for his buck.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player