Honey, you got to come see this.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
I'm going to go.
I'm taking Violet
and going to Jo's.
Florida?
I want to get there
before the school year starts.
I don't understand.
What about Los Angeles?
I thought we agreed
about the fresh start.
I just can't.
We really tried.
We haven't tried.
I can't do it anymore.
Therapy isn't trying.
It's just figuring stuff out
so you can really do something.
I've tried.
And as much as I keep trying
to let you in again,
this wall comes up,
and I... I can't...
I can't get past it.
Just look at this house.
Look at this house I found...
it's right near
Hancock Park, where all those
big mansions from the '20s are.
You always talked about how much
you wanted a house like this...
one with personality.
Well, here it is.
You don't listen.
The house isn't going
to fix it, Ben.
It's just a house, Viv.
Come on.
Take a look.
It's nice, right?
Tiffany lamps and everything.
I don't know, maybe it's
haunted or something.
I mean, it's still a stretch
at that price,
but it's been on the market
for a while,
so maybe they'll go lower.
There's even an office,
so I can see patients at home.
I mean, it's perfect.
No.
Honey... honey, the reason
you can't hold on
to this idea of leaving
is because it's
not what you want.
I-I've been looking
at houses for a month,
and when I found
this one, I swear to God,
it was like a...
it was like a laser beam
shot right into my brain.
I could see it all so clearly.
It was like a movie in my mind.
We were together...
you, me and Violet...
all around the fire.
Violet was reading
some depressing Russian novel,
and I was stoking the fire,
and you were on the couch
rocking a baby.
Honey... we have made
so many life choices
based on our gut,
and right now...
my gut is telling me
that this place...
this house is going to...
it's going to break down
that wall inside you.
I'm sure it's a
beautiful house.
I love you so much.
I'm begging you...
just come see the house.
The three of us will fly out.
Just come see it.
When I look at this place,
for the first time, I feel...
like there's hope.
Vivien?
Vivien!
Violet!
Where are you, Vivien?
Vivien!
Where are you?
Sync & corrected by APOLLO
www.addic7ed.com
We weren't expecting
you until tomorrow.
After the service.
I know.
But I can't impose on you
like this, Constance.
Don't be silly.
Looking after this little angel
is no imposition whatsoever.
And I wouldn't think
of burdening you
with the care of a newborn
during this time of your...
unspeakable tragedy.
Thank you, but...
Vivien's sister
is here now, so...
Oh, I see.
What a blessing
distant relations are
in times of trouble.
If I could just get
his things...
Certainly, uh...
though it is nearly
his lunchtime.
I know...
why don't I feed him?
He'll fall right asleep,
and then you can come back
in several hours.
I can feed him.
It's really no trouble at all.
I'm here to get my son,
Constance.
Your son... of course.
Let me just
gather up his things.
This formula
has to be warmed up.
All you have to do is run it
under the hot water tap.
I'll be fine.
No, I don't believe you will.
Nor will that child
if you take him back
into that house.
Just give me his things.
Dr. Harmon, hear me.
There are forces in that house
that mean to do this child
grave harm.
We both know that it's true.
The same forces
that killed your sweet wife.
Oh, and what
about your daughter?
Tell me, Dr. Harmon,
did you buy a casket
for Violet, too?
If that house
can claim her spirit,
what's going to happen
to this sweet little baby?
The baby's going to be fine.
Oh, you are a fool!
After everything
that you've seen...
after everything
that has happened,
how can you still be so blind?
- Hello?
- Hey, it's Ben Harmon, Tate's therapist.
Yeah, I'm calling because
I can't treat your son anymore.
I'd like... I'd like
to give you the number
of another psychiatrist
who I think could help him.
Oh, no, but why, Doctor?
Because your son has crossed
a line with my daughter.
Oh, but...
I'm so sorry.
Where is he?
In his grave.
Where he's been
longer than he lived
on this Earth.
You destroyed my family.
You!
You are paying for
your own sins, Dr. Harmon.
Let me give you some advice.
When I leave here,
lock your door
and pray I don't come back.
I wonder, how is your
adjustment going?
I have to say
one of the hardest things
is watching Ben.
He's so devastated.
Yes, well, it's always
the living that make it hard.
Hmm.
You don't need
to run off, dear.
He can't see you unless
you want him to.
Right. Keep forgetting.
I want to nurse him so badly.
No, Ben.
Not the microwave.
You're hovering, dear.
It's a bad idea.
See, he remembered.
He was a good dad.
Moira, I know you
don't approve,
but despite all his flaws...
he's a good father.
I'll never understand why you
always need to come
to his defense.
Here you go.
Do you want him to see you?
Is that what's going on?
Are you fighting the
desire to appear?
No, I do not want him to see me.
I absolutely do not want him
to see me or Violet.
I have made her promise me,
because if he see us,
then he is going to want
to stay here.
- It's okay, kiddo.
- And he has to leave this house.
And raise our baby.
Then sit down
and keep your distance.
Remember the endgame.
It's all going to work out.
There's something about
Ben that's different.
He's so sanguine.
Perhaps he's dreaming
of all the women
he can have relations with.
Forgive me.
I suppose that was unkind.
Moira, would you make me
a cup of tea, please?
No.
Your denial is impressive.
You're a ghost,
Mrs. Harmon.
I don't take orders from ghosts.
I'm your equal now
in this world.
So you are.
I owe you an apology.
And I think you
should call me Vivien.
I'd like that.
Vivien, if I may...
Leave him be.
Don't torture yourself.
It's not your fault.
None of this is.
Your Aunt Jo's
going to be here soon.
Okay.
Okay. Okay.
It's okay.
You can't do this.
Vivien.
I knew you were here.
Why didn't you come to me?
It would just make it worse.
I want you
to take the baby and go.
No, just let me do it,
then we can be together.
No, no, no! No.
That baby needs a father, Ben.
I'm not his father.
You know it, and I know it.
He's my baby,
and you shouldn't be smoking.
I don't really care
where it came from.
I would give anything
if I could take care of him.
Vivien, I am...
so sorry for everything
I put you through.
I want you to hear me.
I forgive you.
So enough
with the drama and the tragedy.
We've had enough in this family.
We've had enough.
And the one spot of light
that there is,
is that baby asleep upstairs.
That's your opportunity
to do something different.
I want you to take the baby,
and I want you
to leave this house,
and I want you to never
come back.
Your sister said she
would take care of him.
She's a good mother.
No, I don't want that.
What do you want?
I want to...
envision you with that boy
on your shoulders
walking down Newbury Street.
What about Violet?
I'm a teenage girl.
Not exactly a cakewalk.
Violet.
What kind of father
have I been?
You weren't eating.
You weren't going to school.
You were already gone,
and... I didn't get it.
I shut you out.
I was afraid it would break you.
I miss you so much.
I was never getting
into Harvard.
Oh...
But I saved you
a shitload of money.
Yeah, you did.
You have to leave, Dad.
Every minute you're
in this house,
you're in danger,
and so is that baby.
Please.
Do it for us.
Where are you going, Ben?
You didn't think
I'd just let you leave?
Get out of my way, Hayden.
I don't have time
for your bullshit.
Ah!
Now we have all
the time in the world.
Welcome!
You must be the Ramos.
Yes. I'm Stacy.
Mm-hmm.
This is my husband Miguel.
Hi.
Miguel.
What an exotic name.
I must confess to a fascination
for all thgs
south of the border.
Actually, my family's from Spain.
Yeah.
All the better.
I find European Hispanics
vastly superior.
This is a classic
L.A. Victorian, built in the
1920s by a doctor to the stars.
As you can see,
it's just fabulous.
These are real Tiffany fixtures.
Yeah?
Everything else in the house
has been updated.
Uh, Gabriel.
Hold on.
Uh, I apologize for my son.
Apparently he's got
the skateboard
surgically attached
to his body.
He doesn't go anywhere
without it.
It's quite all right, Mr. Ramos.
As long as we don't
leave any marks on the floor.
Are we waiting
for another sibling?
No, we just have the one.
Thank you.
The furnishing
is from the previous owner,
but if you see anything
that you like,
I'm sure the estate
is open to selling
at the right price.
- This is amazing, babe.
- Look at this house.
Um, speaking of money, Marcy,
I know the, uh, economy is down,
but why is the asking price
so far below market?
There isn't a problem
with mold or radon, is there?
No. Nothing so simple.
In the interest of
full disclosure,
I must inform you that the
previous owners passed away
in the house.
Oh.
How?
The wife died
during childbirth,
and the husband, in his grief,
committed suicide.
He hung himself
from the second-story balcony.
It's a tragically
romantic love story.
This is their dog, Hallie.
She's the only remaining member
of the Harmon family.
I've adopted her.
Well, at least
they weren't murdered.
Mrs. Ramos.
Yes? I'd be happy to
show you another house.
But no matter where you go,
you'll be moving into
somebody's history.
Only this one can be had for
$200,000 less than
the last time I sold it.
What do you think, Gabe?
I don't believe in ghosts.
Ah.
Of course he would say that.
Should we continue the tour?
Yes. Sure.
I know you're going
to love the kitchen.
It's got
marble countertops,
a breakfast nook,
and have you ever
seen a pasta arm?
No.
Personally, I
haven't... I live alone...
but Mrs. Harmon fancied
herself a bit of a gourmet.
Notice the gazebo
in the backyard.
Ow.
You okay?
Yeah.
I-I slipped.
Where-where's Mom?
Oh, the second she stepped
foot in the kitchen,
it was game over.
I think we just bought
ourselves a house.
Come on, you gotta check out
the rest of this place.
There's definitely room
for a pool table.
Imagine sipping a nice
mojito on a hot summer day.
I guess you folks tolerate
the heat better than us gringos.
Am I right?
I see you've got a new family
moving in next door.
Yes, I noted that.
Oh, I do hope they're
a... nice family.
I'd go over there
and welcome them personally,
but as you may imagine,
returning to that house
is difficult for me.
After what I saw.
You stupid son of a bitch.
Please tell me that you're not
here with any more bad news.
No real news, actually.
So you still haven't found
that precious baby?
No trace.
That's very... worrying.
We'd like to go over
your statement again.
Just to make sure we
didn't miss anything.
Of course. You said you'd gone over
to the Harmons' at approximately
7:30 p.m.
To check on Dr. Harmon
and his daughter.
After ringing the bell and
getting no response, you decided
to enter the premises.
Being no stranger to tragedy,
I was understandably concerned.
Prescient, as it turned out.
You stupid son of a bitch.
I can't believe she killed me.
Serves you right.
My first instinct was to flee.
To run screaming
and never return.
But then I tenhought of the bab.
Shit.
Dad?
Well, that's all very touching.
But where the hell's the baby?
So I went searching for
the Harmons' daughter.
And when I discovered
that she was gone, too...
I understood
what must have happened.
Have you come to see my baby?
I've come to fch my grandson.
Oh, you think so?
Mrs. Harmon agrees with me.
House of the dead is no
place to raise a child.
It is for this baby.
He's special.
He's mine.
Over my dead body.
We're well past that.
Aw, shit.
Violet took that child,
and fled.
God knows where.
But I keep them both
in my prayers, every night.
Well...
If you, uh, think of anything
Violet said to you
that could, uh, indicate
where she might have gone,
you will let us know?
Oh, without hesitation.
Thank you for your time.
Aw...
Who's my good little angel, huh?
Who's my good little angel?
Oh..Oh
Oh, there's my good
little angel.
Huh?
Who are you?
You have awful taste in music.
Butthole Surfers?
Hello? Breaking
and entering.
Who are you?
A ghost of my former self.
Violet. I live
in the neighborhood.
Your hand's cold.
You know what they say.
Cold hands, warm heart.
Hmm.
Yo!
Don't you have any Ramones?
Like Animal Boy,
or Too Tough To Die?
Hey. Get out of my room.
Are you sure
you want to be alone?
They say this house is haunted.
You're kind of
twisted, aren't you?
You don't know the half of it.
Whoa.
You okay?
Yeah. This floor is warped.
You know who's warped?
That realtor, Marcy.
You think?
I think she's hot.
Red hot.
Smokin' hot.
Really?
Mm.
I may have to waste
that bitch, then.
Hey. There's enough
of me to go around.
Well, I'm not into
sharing.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
Are we gonna christen
the house tonight?
Hmm.
Does this answer your question?
Mmm.
This does.
Babe...
Gabe's upstairs.
Shh.
I remember when
we were like that.
In the beginning.
Mmm.
To be continued.
Uh-huh.
On that note.
Yes?
Gabe's graduating this year.
This house is so big.
Do you think we'll be lonely?
A baby?
Don't you think I'm too old?
Almost. Almost.
Aw.
So we should get going.
I lost two babies in this house.
One of them
never even took a breath,
and Constance stole
the other one.
At least he's out of this house.
They seem like
such a nice couple.
They can't have a baby
in this house.
You're right.
We have to do something.
You're going to need help.
Some spirits in the house
are angry and vengeful,
and eager to inflict
their fate on others.
But many of us are innocent,
kind, blameless victims
at the hands of another.
And we don't want to see
more suffering in this house.
What were you
dreaming about?
Shit!
Bet I know.
I'd dream about her, too,
if I could dream.
I don't think I do anymore.
The hell?
Who are you?
What are you doing in my room?
This used to be my room.
And then it was hers.
What are you talking about?
Violet.
She was my girlfriend.
The freaky chick from before?
What do you mean by freaky?
She seemed really cool.
Nothing happened.
She didn't say
she had a boyfriend.
We kind of broke up.
Right.
Well, I mean,
it's totally hands off,
dude. I get it.
No...
I don't think you do.
Shit!
Mom?!
Oh, my God!
Miguel! Miguel!
Miguel!
Stay away from me.
Get away from me!
Get away!
No! You stay here!
What do you want?!
Gabe!
Gabe! Gabe?!
Why?!
I want her to be happy.
She liked you, I could tell.
You're a good guy, right?
What?
I mean,
you got all these friends
and you played some sports.
You make good grades, right?
Average.
Average is good.
Normal is good.
She deserves normal.
Get out of my way!
I don't want to hurt you!
Though I do have to kill you.
Miguel...
it's time for you
to open your eyes
and see what this place
is, what it can do.
I need someone to feel my pain.
Let me lead you.
Look what he did to me.
Why are you doing this?
Please, I told you, man,
nothing happened!
Could you maybe not look at me?
- What?
- I mean, could you...
could you, like, stand up or...
I don't know, turn around
or something?!
Please...
don't kill me.
Oh, it's nothing personal.
It's just that she's all alone.
And that's not right!
Stand up!
Padre.
Stop that, stop
that. Come on.
Turn around.
Naughty boy.
What would Stacy think?
Oh, God, I'm dreaming.
You're wide awake.
Oh, God!
God!
Miguel!
Stacy!
Stacy?
Miguel!
Stacy!
Leave her alone!
Hey, stop!
You sick, perverted bastard.
They're barely moved in,
you're already preying
on the new meat?
Who the hell are you people?
He used to be my husband.
You have no idea how long
I've been wanting to do that.
You have no idea how
long I've wanted to do that.
This is what it does to you.
This house.
Run.
Tate, no.
Put down the knife, Tate.
I can't.
I'm doing this for you.
I couldn't save you.
It's my fault you're alone.
But I'm not alone.
My family's here now.
It's not enough.
You need someone.
Not him.
Then what do you want?!
What I wanted was you.
You told me to go away.
Yeah...
but I never said good-bye.
Come let me say good-bye.
Good-bye, Tate.
Gabe! Gabe, come on!
Come on, come on, come on.
Some other poor family's
just gonna move in here.
Suckers who will have no
idea what they're in for.
And we know exactly what to do.
Our tour concludes
with one of the most famous
houses of horror
in the City of Angels.
And the recent and bloody
tragedy of the Harmon family...
No, there's nothing to see here.
Only adds to the infamy of
the Murder House!
I have to sell this house.
Get out of here!
It's enough already!
Now I have to sell this house!
Have you got a minute?
I know. I'm the last person
you want to see right now.
You're not a person.
You're a monster.
I really miss our talks, Ben.
They were really helping me.
Bullshit.
You're a psychopath, Tate.
It's a mental disorder,
and therapy can't cure it.
So that's your diagnosis?
I'm a psychopath?
Yep, and the worst kind.
You're charismatic
and compelling
and a pathological liar.
But don't listen to me.
I'm a total fraud.
And by the way,
therapy doesn't work.
It doesn't work?
Then why do people do it?
Because they don't want
to take any responsibility
for their crappy lives!
So they pay a therapist
to listen to their bullshit
and make it all feel... special.
So they can blame
their crazy mothers
for everything that went wrong.
Sound familiar?
It's a great racket, too.
Week after week,
month after month,
year after year
we collect checks, but deep down
we know it doesn't work.
You son of a bitch.
We're not so different, Tate.
I'm a bad person, too.
I hurt the people I was
supposed to... love the most.
But they forgave you, right?
Maybe Violet
will forgive me, too.
She can't.
You can only forgive someone
for what they've done
to you directly.
Those people you murdered?
They're the only ones
who can forgive you,
and you took away their chance.
So this is it?
There's no...
there's nothing I can do?
There's no chance of mercy?
Terrific performance, Tate.
The whole misunderstood kid
act? Oh...
I fell for it, Violet did, too.
But a psychopath, by definition,
is incapable
of remorse.
So, come on, let's
try this again
for real this time.
You...
destroyed everything
that mattered most to me.
What could you possibly
want from me now?
I don't know about definitions,
but I really am sorry, Ben.
To you more than anyone.
Sorrys are easy.
What about taking responsibility
for the things you've done?
Christ, you can't even
say the words.
In 1994...
I set my mom's boyfriend
on fire...
and then I shot and killed
15 kids at Westfield High.
I murdered the gay couple
who lived here before you...
and I raped your wife.
There were other things, too.
Other people I hurt.
I'll tell you everything.
I'm not your priest, Tate.
I can't absolve you
for any of this.
Right, I get that.
But can you just...
hang out with me sometimes?
Hello?
Oh, thank God you're here.
I'm so exhausted.
You're the new nanny?
Hello?
Nora?
Mrs. Montgomery, please.
Mother taught me that's
a rule to live by:
Never allow the help to call you
by your first name, so...
Is that my ba...
Uh, forgive me,
Mrs. Montgomery.
I would have come sooner,
but I...
I didn't think he made it;
I thought he was stillborn.
Nearly.
He made one tiny little cry
and then passed on.
Apparently, I'm the only one who
witnessed it; Charles didn't.
Genius.
He's an unhappy child,
I'll tell you that.
Oh, it's you...
the birth mother.
Perhaps it was
your poor nutrition or just your
genetic inferiority.
In any case,
I'm quite dissatisfied.
He's a weakling.
Well, his lungs are strong;
I could hear him upstairs.
May I?
No, hands off!
You people... you think you
can just show up and claim
some sort of birthright,
but arrangements were made.
This baby is mine.
I understand.
But I do know some...
some tricks that might
be helpful to quiet him down.
What do you call him?
Little Noisy Monster.
Shh, shh, shh, shh...
Oh, thank God.
I was actually afraid
I might harm him
if he didn't quiet down.
He has been inconsolable
for days and days.
I am so exhausted.
Oh, dear, I think
I might need to...
take a rest.
Perhaps you could keep him
for the night.
You take a rest, Mrs. Montgomery.
You need a nice rest.
We'll be fine.
I'm not entirely sure I have
the patience to be a mother.
Probably all of
those hideous nannies.
Mother wasn't very good at
it either, truth be told.
Are you gonna be a Nicholas?
Or a Jonah?
Or a Jeffrey?
Are you gonna be
a little Jeffrey?
Who are you gonna be,
little guy?
Moira, what are you doing?
Scouring the cinets
with vinegar, Mrs. Harmon.
I... I just noticed how sticky they
were when the new family moved out.
I don't know what else
to do with myself.
Cleaning is what I'm good at,
so I'll just carry on.
Sorry, Moira.
Look who I found.
He was in the basement.
He was down there with Nora,
wouldn't stop crying.
I knew she couldn't handle him.
She doesn't really want a baby.
She just got
stuck on that idea.
Not a motherly bone
in her body, that one.
Do you want to hold him?
Here you go.
He's such a frail little thing.
His skin is like peaches.
I would have made
a good mother,
if I hadn't been
such a little tramp.
Forgive me.
There's nothing worse than
a self-pitying old maid.
You know, I'm gonna need
so much help with him.
I can't accept such a position.
I'm not trained as a nanny.
I wasn't thinking that you
would come work for us.
I was gonna ask you if you
wanted to be his godmother.
If that'd make
you feel safer...
I think you'd be a great
addition to the family.
I found these in the attic.
Wow.
These ornaments are ancient.
I suppose they are.
You'll come to understand,
Violet,
that the word "ancient"
will lose all its meaning
when your entire existence
is one long today.
Okay, everybody ready?
Look at that.
I chopped it down myself,
I'm proud to say.
Have you ever seen
anything so beautiful?
I have!
Look at him.
He's so amazing.
Oh!
Best temperament.
Hardly ever cries.
Looks like his daddy.
Want to hold him?
Mm-hmm.
Here you go.
I didn't think it was
possible for me, Vivien...
but I'm happy.
Grow a pair, Rimbaud.
She's not into you.
You're not getting
back into her.
She'll never talk to you again.
I'll wait.
Forever, if I have to.
Ding-dong!
How would you feel
about working
a miracle today, Helen?
Constance, you get your ass
in my chair!
Oh, where you been, girl?
I was starting to think you
found yourself another salon.
Oh, heavens no, no, no, no!
No, I've just been a bit
housebound of late.
Now, don't shriek when
this scarf comes off.
Lady Clairol and I have become
entirely too familiar.
Housebound?
You have an accident?
No.
I had a baby.
A... a baby?
A boy.
A son!
Oh, I... No, I-I didn't give
birth to him, of course.
No, he was the, um...
child of distant cousins
on my mother's side.
The DeLongprees of Virginia.
Evaline and Steve.
They died tragically
in a highway accident
outside Richmond,
leaving that poor
little angel an orphan.
Terrible.
Yes, but little Michael and I
were meant to be together.
He was meant to be my son.
And I, his mother.
And I am sick
of looking like his grandmother.
Oh!
So... here.
You work your magic.
Oh!
Oh, Helen!
Oh, you truly are an artist.
Well, even an artist needs
the right materials.
Oh!
You know, Constance, in all
the years I've known you,
I don't think you have ever
looked younger or more radiant.
It's true, isn't it?
May I confide something?
Yeah.
Ever since I was a little girl,
I knew I was destined
for great things.
I was gonna be somebody...
a person of...
significance.
A star of the silver screen,
I once thought.
But...
my dreams became nightmares.
Instead of laurels...
funeral wreathes.
Instead of glory...
bitter disappointment,
cruel afflictions.
Well, now I understand
tragedy was preparing me...
for something greater.
Every loss that came before
was a lesson.
I was being prepared.
And now I know for what.
This child.
A remarkable boy.
Destined for greatness!
In need of a remarkable mother.
Someone forged in the fires
of adversity...
who can guide him...
with wisdom,
with firmness.
With love.
I apologize for being
so late, Flora.
But Helen had to go
into minute detail
every tiresome moment
of her niece's Bat Mitzvah.
The amount of money those people
throw away
on a 13-year-old is...
Flora?
Hey...
Now what am I gonna do with you?
Sync & corrected by APOLLO
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player