Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Let me guess.
You work the late shift,
some shit-hole diner.
Now you're taking
the shortcut home.
You don't go home till I say.
Make me fight for it,
I'll carve you up
in big thick slices,
then plug every hole you got.
What you did?
What I do.
This works, too.
Queenie.
What the hell are you doing?
Nothing you'd understand.
This is voodoo.
You're a witch.
We need you back in the coven.
Marie Laveau set me straight.
You were never my friends.
Oh, boo-friggin'-hoo.
You switched
because girls were mean to you?
Fiona slit my throat.
You don't see me bitching out.
We know our coven's
a shit show right now.
But things are changing.
A new Supreme is rising.
And who's that? You?
Fiona filled my head
with that bullshit, too.
That bitch will say anything
if it gets her what she wants.
This isn't for you. Yet.
Holy shit.
You just killed an innocent man!
Innocent? Shows what you know.
This bastard raped three
schoolgirls that we know of,
probably more.
Marie Laveau needs a dark heart,
and I'm gonna give it to her.
Voodoo Queen is making
a special potion
to give me more powers.
Fiona ever do that?
Huh?
Voodoo, witchcraft.
This town ain't big enough
for the two of us.
War is coming.
And you're gonna lose.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com.
Meningeal carcinomatosis.
That's what the doctor
called it.
Tiny seedlings
that the cancer planted
in the lining of my spine.
The little bastards
are Satan's diet pill.
I used to think
I understood pain.
A burn, a cut, a broken bone.
Heartbreak.
But this is as if I've been
dipped in the River Styx
and all the suffering
of all the souls that ever were
or will be has soaked my body.
My body doesn't belong to me--
not that I'd want it
in this state.
I'm starting
to look less Samantha
and more Endora every day.
And what could be more painful
than having to tell your child
that you're going to die?
The doctors say it's terminal.
Do me a favor.
Die before Thanksgiving,
so none of us have to suffer
through that mess of raisins
and Styrofoam you call stuffing.
They say love
is the best medicine.
You are so beautiful.
You're just a fool in love.
You like the way I look,
take a picture.
A month from now, I'll be a...
a balding and
toothless skeleton.
So run away with me.
Paris.
Rome. Marrakesh.
We can spend
that month together.
I don't want you
watching me decay.
Are you scared?
I'm not scared of dying.
I'm scared of living like this.
The constant pain
and the ugliness.
You ever consider
making it stop?
No.
I wouldn't give anyone
the satisfaction
of me killing myself.
Mm.
I'll stay alive
just to spite them.
You know,
the only reason...
...my cancer is
moving so fast
and my hair's falling
out like dead weight...
...is because one of those
girls is coming into her own.
Flexing her muscle.
I just have to figure out
which one of those
little pecker-heads it is.
Bitch.
Her name is Nan.
Dark-sided.
The whole lot of them.
They worship the devil.
That's not true, Mother.
Where else could they get
their dark power from?
Look what they did to you.
You don't get it!
They saved me!
Only Jesus can save you.
But only if you repent.
Only if you cleanse yourself
of all the impurities.
"Let the wicked forsake
their ways and the unrighteous
their thoughts."
Nothing happened in that house.
You brought this on yourself.
You had no business going
to that house.
You don't have
to do this, Mother.
Oh, but I do.
You're unclean.
From the inside out.
But we're going to fix that.
Take off your pants.
Don't! No, no! No! No!
She's hurting him.
Sit down, Nan.
Let go of everything
outside this room right now.
Losing Queenie
is a terrible failure.
My failure.
But as of now,
she's dead to me.
And no one else will slip
through the cracks.
Let's get back
to the battle plan.
It begins with killing Fiona.
- We can't afford to wait.
- I should be the one.
I want to slit her throat.
No.
You have to stay hidden
until it's time.
She cannot know you're back.
We have one shot.
That's it.
Our plan has to be flawless.
So does the execution.
Failure turns this into
a suicide mission.
Where the hell is Spalding?
Delphine?
I'll get it.
Misty?
You have to save me.
I knew the world could be
a dark and evil place.
It drove me to my haven
in the swamp.
I had my Stevie. My garden.
I tried to
disappear into nature.
But I have been found.
Aw.
Aw, you probably have no idea
where you are.
Hmm.
You've been through
a terrifying ordeal,
but you came back.
You're safe now.
Not likely, my dear.
There's a man in the woods
with a gun circling the shack.
I saw the assassin when
he nearly stepped on my face.
Do you hear that?
No.
The cicadas
have stopped singing.
We hid in the swamp
through the night.
Made our way here
when I was sure he was gone.
Who's there?
A witch.
Seeking safety.
Somebody is looking to kill me.
You're Misty Day.
You were set on fire
and left for dead.
Whatever troubles you had,
they are ours now.
You're under
the protection of this coven.
This is your house.
Could my friend stay, also?
I left her out back
in the greenhouse.
Hello?
Don't worry.
You're amongst friends.
Of course I am, Cordelia.
So long as Fiona isn't with you.
Myrtle? Oh, my God.
I thought I'd never
see you again.
Poor choice of words, girl.
But given
my wretched appearance,
maybe it's a good thing
you're blind as a butter knife.
How did your hair
grow back so quick?
Oh, little bird,
I've been buying in bulk
from North Korea for years.
What have they done to you?
I've lost my eyes.
You were burned at the stake,
and our own Supreme murdered
one of her witches.
I'm afraid
this coven has fallen
on hard times.
Or maybe it's the best of times.
Resurrection
is a feat more difficult
than all the tests
of the Seven Wonders.
Those of us who
have recently died
have been brought back to life
by the hand of one person here.
Misty Day.
Behold, our next Supreme.
Our journey starts today.
Sort some sounds
and read the books,
and we'll be on our way.
I can't.
Not now.
We're doing a thing downstairs,
so you have to stay here, okay?
And get real smart.
So you can finally tell me
what's going on in your head.
Relax.
We're sharing him, remember?
What's this?
We're gonna be busy all night.
Now he has something to do.
Why can't he watch porn and
jerk off like any other guy?
And why can't he learn something
so he can rejoin society
and have a life?
Be good, baby.
We'll have fun later.
See if you can guess...
Mothballs and history.
It's a cocktail I swoon for.
- I feel like a queen.
- How does
putting on this smelly old stuff
help us get rid of Fiona?
It's part of a ceremony
called the "Sacred Taking,"
which allows for the ascension
of the new Supreme.
And we're sure Misty's
the next Supreme?
I'm certain of her credentials.
She's brought back
more people from the dead
than Jesus Christ.
Disappointed?
You thought it was you,
didn't you?
Well, I knew it wasn't you,
because when Fiona cut
your throat, you died.
It could be any one of us.
Not really.
It's pretty obvious.
And what does that mean?
Being the Supreme
isn't something to wish for.
It's not a gift. It's a burden.
How many of these
women had happy lives?
They had the power,
but with it came the crushing
responsibility of the coven.
They all bowed
under the weight,
except my mother"
who ran from it.
Can I say something?
I don't want to be the Supreme.
Nobody gets to choose.
When Fiona dies,
whoever it is... will be.
Now, give me your hands.
We're ready to begin.
The Sacred Taking is a ritual
used in times of crisis
to ensure the survival
of the coven.
It has been invoked three times
in our history.
The first, during
the Salem Witch Trials in 1692.
The coven had decided
to flee south,
away from Salem
and the persecution
of the Court of Oyer
and Terminer.
The reigning Supreme
at that time, Prudence Mather,
suffered from consumption,
and knew she would be too weak
to make the journey.
She gathered her witches
and invoked the Sacred Taking.
It's the most hallowed
sacrifice a Supreme can make.
Prudence took her own life,
which allowed a new Supreme
to rise
and lead them to safety.
Can you imagine
those poor Salem witches,
traveling all the way down here
in covered wagons
without a proper charcuterie
platter or a bidet?
Absolutely savage!
Does nobody see the flaw
in this plan?
You really expect
that narcissistic bitch
to kill herself for this coven?
Not without a push.
♪ When I look out my window
♪ Many sights to see
♪ And when I look
in my window... ♪
I just love this room,
especially the walk-in closet.
I need that.
And my Warhol Mao
would look great
on this wall.
Madison?
Surprise, bitch.
I bet you thought
you'd seen the last of me.
Hmm. How soon can you have
all of your stuff out of here?
I really need my own room.
Oh, and a bed.
I can't wait to break it in.
God knows
it's not getting any action
from you, Grandma.
What are you?
♪ Must be the season
of the witch, yeah... ♪
Who brought you back?
Are you deaf?
I'm the next Supreme.
I brought myself back.
Looks like you've got
some 'splainin' to do.
Maybe we should call
the Council.
Oh, wait.
You killed Myrtle, too.
Well, that won't matter.
We all know the playbook
on this.
You killed me,
so we burn you at the stake.
I'm gonna bring marshmallows
and graham crackers
to make s'mores.
Does Cordelia know?
That you killed me?
Everyone knows.
You'll be hash browns
by this time tomorrow.
Coseur, you're half-dead
already.
♪ Sure is strange...
Get out!
Poor Fifi.
As my powers grow...
yours fade away.
Let me break this down
for you--
and stop me if I talk too fast.
I'm in, you're out.
And you can
leave this world
one of two ways.
You can burn at the stake
tomorrow,
which would be messy
and painful,
although very entertaining.
Or...
...you can swallow these pills
and go to sleep.
Stop suffering.
And stop our suffering.
The choice is yours.
♪ You got to pick up
every stitch ♪
♪ Two rabbits
running in the ditch... ♪
Going somewhere?
Oh.
Is everyone back from the dead,
or have I already died
and gone to heaven?
Well, I suppose
it would be hell, you know.
I've been resurrected by
our new Supreme, young Madison.
She rather reminds me
of you in your youth,
thin as a pin with a dreadful
case of the "me, me, mes."
Yes.
Well, I wish her the best.
I will be... on the island...
of Patmos.
That's not one of
the choices, darling.
Take your own life
or be burned, I believe it was.
No, I'm not ready.
I have finally
found someone belong to.
Someone I truly love.
No details, darling.
I couldn't bear it.
I am very ill, Myrtle.
I won't st long.
And he wants
to take care of me.
You haven't thought
through this, Fiona.
Maybe it's your weakened state.
You're still
my beautiful angel.
This dream of a perfect
love you're clinging to
is just a nasty trick
life is playing on you.
You will die the same way
you lived your life--
alone and disappointed
by everyone.
What's the matter?
Huh?
He won't stay till the end.
They promise,
but... they don't.
You are nothing...
but an envious old bitch.
Where are you going?
This is taking too long
for you to die.
Don't... don't leave.
The smells--
they make me sick.
Your breath, your piss,
your shit-- this whole room
smells of death!
I know. I' die soon.
I promise.
How'd it go?
Boffo.
She thinks
I'm the next Supreme.
Why can't it be me?
Because you have
no style and your pits
smell like fish sticks.
Do you think I could
be the Supreme?
You guys suck balls.
Nan...
Luke?
Oh, God.
You're preparing the corpse.
Be a dear, will you?
Come hold this mirror for me.
My hand shakes so
from those meds.
Life is a carnival, Myrtle.
Oh, my God.
Do you remember Levon?
The drummer with The Band.
Great God, he was something.
I was so crazy about him.
We had such a...
wild six months
together in Woodstock.
Anyway, the point is...
...some play it safe
on the merry-go-round,
others go for the thrills
on the roller coaster.
I mean, I could sit here
and boo-hoo my choices,
torment myself...
over the selfish detours
I have taken.
But what good
would it do now? Hmm?
Do me a favor, get me
my fur from the closet.
They were all over me
at season.
But Levon, mm...
Oh, my.
It was preemptive, I suppose,
my leaving.
Get out of town before
they run you out on a rail.
I've always been rigorous
about not staying too long
at the party.
Bad form.
Know when it's over.
Look after my beautiful Delia,
will you?
My most...
terrible failure.
One that'll torment me
into eternity, I imagine.
And you've chosen the
perfect color for your lips.
I could never
pull off the corals.
Make sure they hang my portrait
in the place I chose.
Don't let them store me
in the basement
with that disgraced...
Russian witch.
Half of it's paste,
but goddamn half of it's good.
Madame.
Wake up.
Spalding?
You need to take this. We must
purge you of this poison.
You can speak.
Yes.
I was murdered.
Those idiot girls thought
they could silence me,
but they've only given me voice
here in the spirit world.
300 years,
my family has been
a clan of watchers.
And now...
I see everything.
Take this.
No, Spalding...
you don't understand.
I am finally...
trying to do...
something decent...
something noble for e coven.
Horseshit.
You're making a martyr
of yourself by giving up.
You've been tricked.
You've allowed a pack
of lesser witches to buffalo you
into this ignominious end.
I won't permit it.
I don't understand.
They've been running
a number on you.
Huh?
Madison Montgomery
is not the next Supreme.
She didn't conquer death.
She was brought back
by some dirty little...
swamp witch.
They've been leading
you to your doom
with lies.
Lies...
you swallowed more easily
than those pills.
Huh?
Oh, Spalding...
you've always been
my silent sentinel.
And I will avenge your murder.
Right after
I've avenged my own.
Delphine?
Is that a Jumpin' Jack
with cheese I smell?
Mmm.
Oh!
Heaven.
Ain't they feeding you?
All they ever do is bleed me
for her poultice.
Come tomorrow, I'm
gonna be dry as a bone.
Whatever did I do
to deserve this betrayal?
Didn't you like my pot pie
and my peach crumble
I learned how to make
just for you?
You put me in here.
You can get me out.
Only for a minute,
just so I can stretch my legs.
This cage is just
un-unfit for a human.
Which is why
it's so perfect for you.
What I told you
about feeding the animals?
Queenie?
I'm sorry, reine.
Mm.
You know,
when I had the idea
to have you brought back to me,
I thought of all the many ways
I could dispose of you.
But I've found
it give me great pleasure
just to know you in a cage.
Shut your mouth, Negress.
Bring me something to
drink in a clean glass,
so I can enjoy my
food in silence.
I'm not your damn maid!
And if I were you,
I wouldn't be so eager
to show my arrogance
from that side of the cage.
What you gonna do? Kill me?
I can't die.
Eh, throw me back in the box.
I seen enough of this world.
I'll take no part
in a country that has a darkie
in the White House.
Hundred years from now,
when they dig me up again,
the natural order
will be restored.
You think I only have
those two choices?
The mistake you make is
from a lack of imagination.
I'm not afraid of you.
I wouldn't give you
that satisfaction.
Dear God!
Oh, my God!
You know, you're right,
Delphine.
This gave me no satisfaction.
But we've only just begun.
We can't go next door.
It's the first place
she'll look.
Then where?
I don't care.
Anywhere.
Just us.
You mean
boyfriend-girlfriend?
Yes, there's an intruder
in my house right now.
I'm staring at her.
She's armed and dangerous.
That's a lie!
How dare you come into my house
after what you've done.
Stay away from her!
We're leaving, Mother.
You can't stop us.
The hell I can't.
I'm your mother.
I made you and I can unmake you.
No!
Luke.
Don't leave me!
I'm your Supreme.
How about something
less doleful, Myrtle?
It's Schubert's last sonata.
It's all about acceptance
of death.
This is
so incredibly
stressful and weird.
You don't feel anything?
My stomach feels like
a storm's about to hit,
but it's probably
just my nerves.
I'm not exactly what you call
a natural born leader.
Neither was
King George,
but one rises to the occasion.
Your feet should be
getting warmer.
I'm told it starts
as a tingle in the cooch.
For me, it started
as a classic migraine.
Auras, nausea,
pain behind the eyes.
You know, Myrtle,
Schubert was emotional,
not mawkish.
So where...
is this gifted little
swamp witch
that everyone's been
talking about?
I'm going with him.
Well, well, well.
So you're the swamp witch
I've heard so much about.
It's not every day
we see a witch with
the power of resurgence.
According to my daughter,
a power fit for a Supreme.
Hey, ladies,
you can't be in here.
Yes, we can.
You're gonna tell us
what happened here, Officer.
There was a shooting.
Maybe a robbery gone wrong.
Son has a grievous head wound.
Mother is dead.
We're waiting on the coroner.
That's perfect.
Here's one
you can... use your talent on.
They think maybe
it was a robbery.
And my mother? Misty?
I saw Fiona go inside.
Lead me.
Wait.
There's something here.
This was no robbery.
He was after us.
This road goes two ways.
See if you can guess
which road
the friends will take.
- Click...
- This...
This road goes two ways.
Click on the microphone button
and say the word.
It's not you.
We're under attack.
None of us are safe.
I have to get you out of here.
No!
This... road...
goes...
two... ways.
What does it mean, Kyle?
I...
love...
...you.
I love you, too.
Where are all the servants?
I might have slept until noon.
You didn't really
make this coffee
all on your own, did you?
I'm not entirely helpless,
Mother.
Oh, no, of course not.
Though I do think we might
move your bed downstairs.
I mean, we wouldn't
want you to have a...
accident coming
down those steps.
Wouldn't we?
I'd much rather be found
at the bottom of those stairs
than be burned at the stake.
According to Auntie Myrtle,
that just hurts like hell.
Oh, Cordelia.
You don't really think I'd do
something like that
to my own daughter?
Cut the shit, Fiona.
We both know I tried
to orchestrate
your death last night.
Yes.
And very nearly succeeded.
If you're waiting for me
to get down on my knees
and beg for your forgiveness,
you can forget it.
It's not gonna happen.
Beg?
I might throw you a parade.
What you and your girls
demonstrated last night
was real grit.
I finally have hope for
the future of this coven.
And you,
my dear...
...I'm so proud of.
You really are my daughter.
Now you're proud?
Hell...
if I knew how easy it was
to win your approval,
I would have made
an attempt on your life
way before now.
What's this?
A silver bullet.
I found it last night
in the street.
It's blessed.
Mm-hmm.
Witch hunters.
I'll admit, when I found it,
I was glad you were
still with us.
We need you now, Fiona.
More than ever.
Where are the servants?
Who was it?
I don't know.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Help.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player