Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Mom?
Dad?
Mom!
Mom?
Mom, open the door!
Mom!
What is it, Norman?
It's dad.
He's--hurry!
Dad? Dad? Dad?
Dad...
Norman...
Norman?
Norman.
Oh, honey.
I'm so sorry.
Dad.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
This is the part where you say,
"Mother, this is beautiful.
"I am so happy
we're moving here.
You are so smart
to have thought of this."
Mother, this is so beautiful.
I'm so happy
you're making me move here.
You're so smart
to force me to do things
I have no say in.
You're an ass.
Okay, no peeking!
Keep 'em closed.
Okay.
Okay, not yet.
Open your eyes.
What do you think?
This is crazy, mom.
It's not crazy.
It's not.
We're gonna run this place.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
We own a motel, Norman Bates.
Come on.
I wanna show you the house.
I bought the whole thing,
the house and the motel,
on a foreclosure.
And everything came with it.
Awesome.
You can't buy furniture
like this anymore.
You have to imagine this room
without all this crap in it.
Just simple,
elegant furnishings,
open space, light.
Linen drapes, fresh peonies.
This space is beautiful.
Come on.
I want to show you upstairs.
What's up here?
My room?
No, I put you down here,
closer to me.
This...is your room.
And this...
is my room.
Norman,
we've been through a lot.
This is our chance
to start over.
Maybe some people
don't get to start over.
Maybe they just bring themselves
to a new place.
They do get to start over,
but they have to try.
Yeah?
Norman, please, for me.
It's all gonna be good.
You'll see.
You're new.
What's your name?
Norman Bates.
When did you move here,
Norman Bates?
Last night.
Where?
What house?
Oh, here.
The house at the motel.
Oh, so you bought the motel?
Are you actually
gonna live here,
or are you just flipping
the property?
- We're not flipping.
- Do you have any brothers?
An older brother.
But he doesn't live here.
- Just me and my mom.
- You have a girlfriend?
No.
Want a ride?
♪ Oh oh-oh-oh oh-oh
oh-oh-oh ♪
Oh, my God!
- You got it! It's amazing!
- Come on.
Come with us. Come on.
Am I too heavy?
No.
You're fine.
♪ I got my black suit
on my office pumps again ♪
♪ work is such a bitch
she wants it yesterday ♪
♪ nobody hears a word I say ♪
Bradley Martin.
You have any questions
at school, you call me.
- Okay?
- Thanks.
Hello, Dylan.
Thanks for letting me know
you moved, mom.
Well, I'm pretty sure
the last time we spoke,
you told me
to "drop dead, bitch."
Sorry I took it personally.
What, so you thought
that it was okay
not to tell your own son
that you moved?
What if I was hurt?
What if I was in the hospital?
What if I needed you?
Are you hurt?
Are you in a hospital?
I need some money.
My job fell apart.
Hello? Norma?
Hello?
So I want you to just think
about poetry tonight.
I mean, what does it mean?
Why is it timeless?
Why is there power in words
arranged in cadences
and structures?
Be ready to talk tomorrow.
Norman, can I talk to you
for a minute?
Sure.
I'm gonna be your advisor here,
and I was just reviewing
your school records and, um...
Your test scores are...
really impressive.
But your grades
just don't match up with them.
That's a shame.
Why do you think that is,
Norman?
- We move a lot.
- Mm-hmm, yeah, I see that.
You've been
to five different schools.
Is everything okay at home?
Yeah, yeah.
My mom's just a little...
impulsive.
She gets these ideas
about things,
and--and then we move
and start over...
- which is good.
- Mm.
You know, I think
it might be a good idea,
now that you're here,
to try to put down some roots.
You know, get involved,
maybe join a sports team?
I don't really play any sports.
My mom never really liked them.
Hmm.
What about track?
You look like a runner.
- You ever do any running?
- Not as a sport, no.
Well, track team tryouts
are today.
Why don't you go talk
to coach carpenter after school?
I'll--I'll tell him
that you're coming down.
Okay.
Norman, I...
I see that you
lost your dad recently.
I know how hard that must be.
So please know
that you can come to me
if you have any issues
or questions about anything,
because I'm here for you.
Okay?
I have to go now.
Wow.
Dinner smells great, mom.
I've been--
I've been waiting for you.
I stayed after school
to try out for the track team.
Oh, the track team?
Yeah, well, it was
Miss Watson's idea, I...
Who's Miss Watson?
My language arts teacher.
But yeah, she thought
it'd be a good idea
for me to get involved
at school.
That it'd be good for me.
I need you to sign this parent's
permission slip, though.
Honey, this is, like,
every day after school,
and track meets on Saturdays?
We just bought a motel.
I mean, how do you
expect me to get it
up and running
without your help?
I mean, you're putting me
in a tough spot here.
Mom, it's okay.
I don't have to do it.
No, I'm not gonna be
the mother who tells her kid
he can't be on the track team.
It's fine.
It's okay.
I'll just do everything myself,
the way I always do.
Mom, come on, sit down.
Let's eat dinner.
You know, Norman,
I just spent all day...
doing all of this.
You know, I just--
Never mind, I'm not hungry.
It's fine.
You know, it doesn't matter.
I have to get some groceries.
Just eat your dinner.
Mother!
- Norman Bates?
- Yes.
Just moved in
a couple of nights ago.
How do you like it?
Yeah, it's fine so far.
You live here with your mom?
Yeah.
Yeah, do you know her?
I know--
I know about her.
- Do you want me to get her?
- You're 17.
You're from Arizona,
and your father died.
- Yeah, let me get my mom.
- It's just the two of you.
What do you know about
running a motel, anything?
'Cause you look like
a little kid to me.
I don't think you could run
much of nothing.
Can I help you with something?
I think it's you
that needs help.
Really?
How might that be?
I'm Keith Summers.
Summers!
This is my family's property.
My great-great-grandfather
built this house in 1912,
and my grandfather
built that motel in the '50s.
And that's
my grandmother's rug!
This property has been in
my family for over a century.
I'm sure it was very hard
for you to lose it to the bank,
and I'm very sorry, but, uh...
well, it is ours now.
I know everything
about this place.
Every nook and cranny.
Every dirty secret.
You don't know
how this place works.
This town?
You know nothing
about this town.
What makes you think you
can run this place by yourself?
Because I can.
Now get the hell off
my property.
And if I ever see you here again
I will call the police,
or I will shoot you myself.
You're gonna call the police?
- Get in, get in!
- Go ahead, call the police.
I go fishing with half of 'em.
I grew up here.
This is my house!
So you're gonna
call the cops on me?
Well go ahead!
Go ahead, call 'em!
Do you think you should've
said all that stuff to him?
He's just some pathetic,
drunk loser slob, honey.
He's--he's not gonna
bother us anymore.
♪ Your beast of burden ♪
♪ my back is broad ♪
The last time the roofing
was redone on this place
was the '50s.
Look, I don't want to wait
until the next century
to get this estimate,
so if you reschedule me again,
I'll just go someplace else,
okay?
♪ I'll never be
your beast of burden ♪
♪ I've walked for miles ♪
♪ My feet are hurting ♪
♪ all I want is for you
to make love to me ♪
Hi, are you Mrs. Bates?
- I am.
- I'm Bradley Martin.
Oh, we're friends
with Norman from school
and we're going to the library,
and we were wondering if he
wanted to come study with us.
- Hey.
- Hey, Norman.
I'm sure he would love to go,
but we're in the middle
of a lot of stuff.
We still have unpacking to do.
I totally understand.
I like your house.
It's so cool.
Thank you.
There's--
We got a lot of work to do,
but it's--it's got potential.
- Well, maybe I could--
- No, Norman, not tonight.
No, it's not a good idea, no.
Another time.
No worries.
It was really nice meeting you,
Mrs. Bates.
Nice to meet you too.
Thanks for stopping by.
- Nice to meet you.
- Good night, Norman.
- See you, Norman.
- See ya.
How could you do that?
You didn't even let me answer.
Well, there was no point
in answering
because I knew
you would say "Yes,"
and I knew that
I would have to say "No."
I could have gone, mom.
You can go another time,
when we're settled in.
This is what it's always
gonna be like with you.
"Later."
"Another time."
When, mom?
You said you wanted me
to have a life here--
this is how you have one!
You meet friends, you let
other people in your life!
- Friends?
- Yeah, she's pretty.
Maybe she kind of likes me.
I'm 17!
Norman,
you don't even know them!
You have to be
a little careful.
Why do I have to be careful?
Norman, don't lose
your temper with me!
I'm just looking out for you.
Well, maybe you better
just stay there
the rest of the night then!
I suck.
Oh, my God, you're so cute.
You actually thought
we were gonna go study.
Yeah.
♪ I got self-preservation,
my eyes on survival ♪
♪ I'm living with the lost ♪
♪ and we're living in denial ♪
♪ it begs to question
who's gonna carry on ♪
♪ if no one's awake ♪
♪ then there's no one
who can play along ♪
♪ I need a rival,
I need a rival ♪
♪ I'm tired of the fools
who are killing for survival ♪
♪ I need a rival,
I need a rival ♪
♪ I found my soul,
let's set it on fire ♪
♪ It barks ♪
♪ at no one else ♪
♪ but me ♪
♪ like it's ♪
♪ seen ♪
♪ a ghost ♪
Those dumb bitches
leave you here by yourself?
No, it's fine.
There's a lot to look at.
Is that a line?
You don't seem like
a guy who would have lines.
No, I've--
I mean, really.
There's a lot to look at.
It wasn't a line.
You're different, aren't you?
I don't know, maybe.
I think people who are different
don't know they're different
'cause they have nothing
to compare it to.
Yeah.
You're different.
- What's so different about me?
- I don't know, it's just...
a feeling I get.
You're like...
a beautiful, deep, still lake
in the middle
of a concrete world.
I am?
That's...kind of weird.
You're kind of weird.
Weird good.
Hey, Brad, you know who's
doing the recycling around here?
Oh, hey, Richard.
You get your diorama finished?
Richard had to do a diorama
for the globe theater
for his drama lit class.
I mean, seriously,
what grade are we in?
Yeah, I got it done,
and it actually kills.
Richard, this is Norman.
- He's new at our school.
- Hey.
Hey.
Babe, Jones just got here.
Let's go say hi, all right?
Okay.
You wanna come?
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm--I'm good.
You sure?
♪ See sparks ♪
- Yeah.
- Okay.
No!
Norman!
Aah!
Ow! Ow!
Norman!
This house...
This house is mine.
And everything
in this house is mine.
Norman!
Norman! No!
Mom?
Norman, the handcuffs.
See if he has a key.
Hurry, hurry!
Give it to me.
Give it to me, give it to me!
- Ow!
- Mom, your hand.
Get the emergency kit.
It's in the bathroom cabinet.
Yeah.
You liked it.
Mother!
We have to call 911.
No!
No.
We're not calling 911.
Not doing it.
Mom, he attacked you.
It was self-defense.
It was self-defense,
wasn't it?
Norman, no matter what,
this will become public.
And it'll be in all the papers.
Everyone in town
will know about it.
Who is gonna book a room
in the rape/murder motel?
It will ruin us!
It's gonna make me
a laughingstock.
You know, we came here
to start over.
We came here to start over.
I am starting over!
And where the hell
were you, Norman?
I-I was upstairs.
No, you were not!
You were not upstairs.
If you were upstairs,
you would have come down,
and you would have helped me.
So where were you?
I snuck out of my room
and went to a party.
Mom, I thought
I was gonna study with them,
but they took me to a party.
I didn't know.
It hardly matters right now.
There's a--
there's a dead man on the floor,
there's a lake of blood!
What are we supposed to do,
clean this up with paper towels
and spray cleaner?
I don't think so.
Holy hell, mother,
we're totally screwed!
What are we doing?
We don't know what we're doing!
- Norman? Norman.
- We just don't know
- what we're doing!
- Okay.
Calm down.
It's gonna be okay.
It's okay.
Look, it's gonna be fine.
It's gonna be okay.
Here's what we're gonna do...
Okay, we're gonna take
all the bed linens
from every motel room,
and we're gonna use it
to soak this all up.
We're gonna wrap the body
in one of the comforters,
and we'll put it in a--
in one of the tubs
in one
of the motel rooms just--
just until I can figure out
what to do with it tomorrow.
Okay.
Yeah?
Norman, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that this dirtbag
raped me, okay?
But here you are,
and here I am,
and he's not gonna win
this one.
Go wash up a little.
Put your bloody clothes
in the trash bag.
Mother, are you sure
we shouldn't call for help?
No one's ever
gonna help us, Norman.
No one's ever helped us.
Don't go so fast.
I can't walk that fast
backwards.
It's heavy!
Shh.
Norman!
How can there still
be more blood?
Just get him in the tub first,
then we'll figure
everything else out.
Unh.
Get him off me!
Get him off me.
Okay.
One...two...three.
Mom, what are gonna do?
We're gonna deal with the rug.
We're gonna have to pull up
the whole carpet.
Tonight?
It's already midnight.
And not only this one,
we're gonna have to pull up
four through seven.
They all have the same carpet.
So that way,
this creep goes missing,
anyone comes,
starts asking us questions,
you know, nothing will be
out of the ordinary here.
We're just--just doing
some renovations, you know?
We're just--
just recarpeting.
How the hell
do we pull up carpeting?
Good evening, gentlemen.
I was about to tell you
we're not open
for business yet, but...
it doesn't look like
you're looking for a room.
I'm Norma Bates.
We moved in a few days ago.
No, ma'am.
No, not looking for a room.
Deputy Zack Shelby.
- This is Sheriff Alex Romero.
- We just wanted to make sure
everything was all right here.
We didn't know anybody
had moved in yet.
Oh, that's kind of you.
Yeah, we're all fine.
Yeah, my son and I are just
pulling up some carpeting
we're replacing.
We're just updating.
God knows it could use--
You have a son?
Yeah, my son, Norman.
He's 17.
- Norma and Norman.
- Yeah.
That's...unusual.
Well, boys take their father's
names all the time.
You know, it's almost
2:00 in the morning.
Your son's got school tomorrow.
You really think
this is a good idea to--
I had no idea it was that late.
But thanks for letting me know.
I'm gonna go close up shop.
What happened to your hand?
Um...
I just--
I scratched it with, um...
I was cutting carpet,
and it just--
It's nothing.
It's a nick.
It was nice to meet you.
Thank you.
- Mrs. Bates, you...
- Yes, sheriff?
Wouldn't mind if we take
a look inside, would you?
No, no, not at all.
Come.
Yeah.
Evening.
Norman...
This is Sheriff Romero
and Deputy Shelby.
They--they saw the lights on
and were kind enough
to check on us.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
That's extremely good of you.
Oh, everything's good here.
- Except for this carpeting.
- Sheriff Romero wanted to...
Well, you wanted
to see what we're doing.
I guess you're
a little interested in design?
Wouldn't put it that way.
It's a rare man that is.
Let me tell you, nothing bored
my late husband more,
may he rest in peace.
Oh, you're a widow.
Sorry about that.
Yeah.
Six months ago.
We're trying to get used to it.
Can I use your bathroom?
- This bathroom?
- Yeah.
- This bathroom is broken.
- What's wrong with it?
- It's not flushing.
- All these toilets do that.
I told Summers he needed
to replace them ten years ago.
You gotta jiggle the chain.
It--I'll take a look at it.
- Nice night, huh?
- Yeah.
Where you guys from?
We're from--
we're from Arizona.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah, right--like,
right outside of Scottsdale.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, I know Arizona.
I was there once.
Yeah, the air there,
it was--
it was unlike anything else
I'd ever experienced.
The air here at night
is nice too.
Yep, yeah.
Yeah, it is, it's--
It is.
You just gotta jiggle it.
Unit one,
we have a vehicle collision,
multiple injuries,
at Ocean and Sea Bluff.
Ma'am...
Get the boy to bed, ma'am.
Ms. Bates.
He's new, all right?
He's not used to the food yet.
Make sure you're done.
Don't try to cut it short
just because it's embarrassing.
I think I'm done.
Mint.
It'll calm your stomach.
Thanks.
I'm kind of an expert
on vomiting.
I have C.F., so I've been
on meds my whole life.
Some of them give you any number
of hideous side effects,
puking being one
of the more pleasant ones.
Do you have some sort
of chronic illness?
- No.
- Oh.
I'm Emma...Decody.
Nor--Norman Bates.
Yeah, I think we have
Language Arts together.
Well, I just wanted to make sure
you were okay.
Are you...okay?
I'm okay.
God, I hope he fits
in the trunk.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Let's do this.
I suck.
Mom, he attacked you.
I'm not even talking about him.
I found out today
that the city is building
a new bypass
on the far side of town.
It's gonna be
the new main road.
I bought a motel that no one
is ever gonna know
is even there.
Why didn't the real estate guy
tell you that?
Because, Norman, people suck.
I'll tell you, everyone
I have ever known has sucked.
Except you.
God, you're too good for me.
I'm the worst mother
in the world.
- Mother--
- Look at what we're doing, Norman.
You deserve so much better.
You know, when you were born,
it was like
God gave me a second chance.
And all I ever wanted
was for life to be beautiful
for you, and look at it.
Look at what your life
has been.
I mean,
what good am I doing you?
Mom, you're everything...
everything to me.
And I don't ever want to live
in a world without you.
You're my family.
My whole family, my whole life,
my whole self.
You always have been.
It's like there's
a cord between our hearts.
Honey, that's--
that's from Jane Eyre.
Yeah.
Orson Welles says it to...
- Joan Fontaine.
- Right.
But you know what I mean.
It's you and me.
It's always been you and me.
We belong to each other.
I love you, Norman.
You're the best thing
that has ever happened to me.
I love you too, mom.
I guess this is deep enough.
Come here!
I have a surprise for you.
Okay, look, look, look,
look, look!
I turned it on.
I made it blue.
It's your favorite color.
- It's cool, mom.
- Yeah.
It's ours, Norman.
It's our very own.
And you know what?
You know that new bypass?
- They're not gonna build it.
- When did that happen?
It didn't, yet.
I'll think of something.
I'm sure you will.
What's important
is that we're together.
And as long as we're together,
then nothing bad
can really happen.
- Right, Norman?
- Right, mother.
Yeah.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player