Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Coming!
Hey, mom.
Has he told you
how long he's staying?
No, and I didn't ask him.
I didn't want him
to think it was an option.
As far as I'm concerned,
I'll find him some money,
and then he can get on his way.
Your toast is done.
Yeah.
I know.
I don't suppose
you want some breakfast?
Thanks, no.
The bread's gonna get stale.
Why are you here?
Because that's what
normal people do, Norma,
when they've lost their job,
and they've got no money
and no place to stay.
They go home.
Although most normal mothers
don't move their home
out of state
and try and hide it
from their own son.
We're out of cream.
He looked like a lost puppy
at the party.
Shh, he's coming.
- Hey.
So the other night,
why'd you leave the party
so early?
Where did you go?
You hook up with someone?
I'd like to lie to you
and say yes,
but I actually
got my history book
out of your car
and went home and--
And probably studied.
Good for you.
I hate studying.
- A necessary evil.
- Yeah.
You wanna actually
study together
for the history test?
I mean, not go to a party
this time.
I could really use the help.
Oh, my God, that guy
must be completely wasted.
That's my dad's car.
Dad! Dad!
Oh, my God!
Let me--let me--
let me get it.
Hurry up!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
His name's Jerry Martin.
Owns a warehouse up the road.
It looks like somebody
set a fire there.
He was trapped inside of it.
Wait, you're saying someone
intentionally
set fire to his warehouse?
That's horrible.
Yes, you're right.
It's horrible.
Sheriff!
There's something here
you need to see.
Interesting morning
in White Pine Bay.
Burnt up dude
drives into a ditch
in front of your new hotel?
How rude.
You know,
it's a really nice town
you picked here, Norma,
to start a new life and all,
you know?
Stop calling me Norma.
And if you're gonna stay here,
you're gonna pitch in.
I ordered
all-new bed linens.
They're ready to be picked up.
I'm gonna get you the car keys.
Mrs. Bates.
Could you come here, please?
Yep, that's it.
This is, uh--
this is Keith Summers's truck,
used to own this place.
He hasn't been home
in a couple of nights.
Have you seen him?
No.
No, I haven't.
Why would he
leave his truck here?
Well,
that's what we're wondering.
All right, let's get everybody
down here by the truck.
We're gonna search the woods
up here behind the house.
Fine. Let's go!
Well, good luck
with everything.
So I want you to select a poem
from one of these classic poets
and prepare a presentation
on why this poem
is still relevant
in today's world.
Now this
is a partner assignment,
so I want you to figure out
who you wanna work with.
Hey.
Wanna do this with me?
Yeah, okay.
Good.
We can meet tomorrow.
Cool.
You live at the motel, right?
I'll come to your place.
Oh, well,
maybe we should--
11:00. I'll be there.
Dr. Klonkin.
- I'll talk to him.
- Okay.
So why are you here?
I just felt bad about
what happened to Bradley's dad.
- And I was there.
- Yeah, I know.
Well, I just wanted
to give her this.
I'll give it to her.
Great.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, thank you.
♪ I'm just a bachelor ♪
♪ I'm looking for a partner ♪
What the hell
are you looking at?
♪ Someone
who knows how to ride ♪
♪ without even falling off ♪
♪ gotta be compatible ♪
I'm sorry, man.
My boss got
in a bad accident today.
He got burned real bad.
He's in a coma.
Probably not gonna make it.
I just moved here, but...
that's not right, man.
No, it's not.
He was a good man.
Here, I got them.
♪ My saddle's waiting ♪
♪ come and jump on it ♪
♪ sitting here flossing ♪
Dude, in a town like this,
where the hell do you get
that kind of money?
♪ Just once
if I have the chance ♪
♪ the things I-- ♪
- Evening, Norma.
- Listen, dumb-ass.
This is not gonna stand.
It's not.
You're not gonna be coming home
in the middle of the night
like this.
Okay? I am trying to build
a life here for me and Norman.
You are not going
to be screwing this up.
I got it, okay?
I grew up in a house
with you, remember?
It was always what you
were trying to do for Norman.
Norman is a good boy.
He's a good son.
Dylan, would you please
put that on a plate?
Well, golly, you know,
I'm sorry if I was
a little annoyed with you
after you drove my dad away
by skanking around
with Norman's father.
I wasn't skanking around.
It wasn't my fault.
I was 17 years old
when I met your father.
I had no idea what I was doing.
I met Sam, and I fell in love.
Oh, yeah?
How'd that work out for you?
I hate you.
You have never had
an ounce of kindness for me.
Well, I'm sorry
it was a little bit hard
to get on the tea party
with you and Norbit.
What are you talking about?
What tea party?
He likes me. He just likes me,
so we are close.
That is the normal arrangement
between mothers and sons,
not this crap.
How'd you get
all this money, Norma?
How'd you buy a motel
and a new car?
We haven't had a dime
in our life, okay?
I've been worried about money
since I was conscious.
What's up with that, huh?
Sam's insurance policy.
He sold insurance,
and he was well covered.
Yeah, I guess so.
Good night, Norma.
Stop calling me Norma.
I am your mother!
Get all the corners and the edges.
I think we're good.
Just 'cause they found his car
doesn't mean
they're necessarily gonna--
Don't you two
ever get tired of each other?
These are good.
I got it, gang, it's cool.
Don't stop your swiffering.
Hi. I'm here
to study with Norman.
Hey, Norman,
there's a girl here for you.
Come in.
Hi, Norman.
Oh, hey, Emma.
This is my mom.
Emma.
We're doing a language arts
project together at school.
I guess I forgot to tell you.
- I'm Dylan.
- Well, that's okay then.
Come on in.
It's nice to meet you.
- You too.
- Where do you live, Emma?
My dad has a shop
in the village.
We live in the space above it.
Did we land on a poem yet?
What's your last name?
Decody.
No, but I brought some books.
"Decody."
Is that Italian?
No, no, it isn't.
We're from the U.K.,
actually.
Hey, mom, uh,
didn't you--
didn't you need me
to go to the grocery store?
- Come sit down.
- Do you have that list?
Have a seat.
No, I haven't made it yet.
Oh.
So how long
have you lived here?
About five years.
My dad was a professor
in Manchester.
- He was a professor?
- Yeah.
But he wanted to spend time
just focusing
on taking care of me,
so he retired
and opened the shop.
And are you okay?
Oh, this?
Yeah.
It's my pet.
I take it everywhere.
I have C.F.
Mom.
Mm.
I have--
I have heard of it,
but I don't know
what it is, exactly.
I don't know.
Well, cystic fibrosis
is when your lungs
create a lot
of this thick mucous,
and it makes it
really hard to breathe--
some would say impossible.
I'm on a list
for a lung transplant,
but that comes
with its own demons.
And God knows
if I'll ever get one in time.
Well, I hope you do.
What is
your life expectancy, Emma?
Maybe 27.
Hmm.
Well, why don't you two
go upstairs,
do your homework?
And you let me know
if you get hungry.
Do you think
that she has to take that thing
out of her nose
when they make out?
How about this?
The Tiger.
It's a classic.
"Tiger, tiger, burning bright
"in the forest of the night.
"What immortal hand or eye
could frame
thy fearful symmetry?"
And what does it mean?
It's about how could a God,
who made all this beautiful
stuff in the world,
also make things
that are scary and evil?
It could work.
We could talk about it in terms
of famous contemporary murders,
like O.J. or--
or Charles Manson.
"What the hammer,
what the chain,
"in what furnace was thy brain?
"What the anvil,
what dread grasp,
dare its deadly terrors
clasp?"
What's this?
Oh, it's nothing.
I don't care.
Wow, these pictures
are amazing.
Did you draw these?
No. No, I found it
in one of the motel rooms.
I didn't know
what to do with it, so--
Oh, please.
I've read a lot of manga--
a lot steamier than this.
Can I borrow it?
Sure.
Thanks.
Good evening, gentlemen.
Sorry to be in a robe.
You caught me
getting ready for bed.
Yeah, we need to ask you
some questions.
Sure, sure, ask away.
The other morning
when we were out here,
you said you hadn't seen
Keith Summers.
Yes, that's correct.
But we have an eyewitness
who was driving by here
who said he saw him
standing right here
on your front lawn
and that you and your son
were talking to him...
And it looked a little heated.
Well, yes,
I mean, I'm--
I didn't know that you had meant
had I ever seen him.
I thought you meant recently.
Well, some people might think
in the last week
as being recently.
Yeah, some people might.
So you're admitting
you did see him?
No, I never said
I hadn't ever seen him,
so I'm not admitting anything.
Did he make any--
any threats to you or--
Threats? No. Why if he had,
I would've called the police.
Because he wasn't too happy
about you waltzing in
and buying his property
at a foreclosure.
Well, you know, the fact
that I bought this property
at a good price
hardly incriminates me
in his disappearance.
He disappeared?
I-I don't remember
bringing up a disappearance.
No, but you're implying it.
No, I believe
you're inferring it.
That's all the information
I have, so...
- is that it?
- Actually, no.
I'd like to take a look around,
if you don't mind.
Actually, I do mind.
I think you need
a search warrant
for something like that, right?
I mean, based on something
more than just
some meaningless conversation
out on my motel front lawn,
right?
You better work with me, okay?
I'm the last guy
you want on your bad side.
Okay.
♪ Baby girl, don't be shy ♪
♪ I don't wanna be the ♪
♪ bad guy ♪
♪ I don't wanna be
your sleepwalk dance anymore ♪
♪ I just wanna see some ♪
Deputy Shelby?
Hey, you guys
be safe today, yeah?
- Hello, Mrs. Bates.
- Hello, go ahead.
Slap the handcuffs on.
Well, that is Romero.
That's just his style,
you know?
He's a dog with a bone,
so I wouldn't take it
too personally.
Yeah, I tell you,
it's a little hard not to.
I know.
Well, I'm sorry.
Um...
Hey, would you let me
buy you a cup of coffee,
maybe, as a gesture
of goodwill?
Sure.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
It was horrible for Norman
to lose his father.
And I came here
because I wanted
to clean the slate for him.
You know, I wanted him--
I wanted to give him
a new life.
- I wanted to give him hope.
- Sure, yeah.
And let's just say
that gets
a little bit compromised
when Sheriff Bulldog
is standing on my porch
and he's making all kinds
of accusations.
First of all, to be fair,
I really don't think
he was making accusations.
I do--no, I do think
that you were inferring that.
Oh, no.
Now we're back to that again?
Okay, Romero.
He grew up with Keith Summers.
They were boyhood pals,
you know?
So they spent
a lot of time together
doin' a whole lot of nothing,
and you get close
to people that way, so--
so Keith's disappearance,
you know, this is--
it's very personal to him.
I can understand that.
Hey, deputy.
We gonna see you
at the Woodchuck tonight?
Absolutely, yeah,
wouldn't miss it.
- Right on, man.
- All right.
Woodchuck? What on earth
is the Woodchuck?
Yeah, the Woodchuck
is this stupid,
but very fun,
local sort of festival.
It's left over from when
this used to be a logging town.
- Sounds charming.
- Yeah, no, it is, actually.
It is.
You should come.
Yeah, okay.
I would love to.
Great.
Um...
I just--
I really can't--
I mean, I couldn't take you,
you know, 'cause of the whole
Keith Summers, the whole--
But, I mean,
we could meet there, right?
Because, I mean...
I'm going.
You're going, so...
Just a thought.
How does this look?
For what?
I'm meeting
Deputy Shelby in town.
Does this top look like
I'm trying too hard?
That depends
on what you're trying.
Ah, I didn't want
to have to tell you this.
I didn't want you to worry.
The police came by last night.
Apparently someone saw us
talking to Keith Summers outside
after I specifically
told the police
that we hadn't seen him.
Mom, that's-
I know, it's not good.
I think I dodged it
for the moment,
but I don't think it's over.
Deputy seems to like us,
so I'm gonna go
on a goodwill mission.
I'm meeting him
at a community event in town.
Hmm.
Norman, please.
I'm just doing
what I need to do.
This one's better, right?
Lord, Norman, I'm your mother.
It's not like it's weird
or anything.
You don't have to do this, mom.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm not "doing" anything.
I ran into him in town,
and I'm just gonna go
hang out for a bit.
No, I don't want you to go.
- Honey, you're overreacting.
- Fine.
- It's a community thing?
- Yes.
- I'll go with you.
- No.
- Yeah.
No, you're not going with me,
and you know it.
It's fine, Norman.
It doesn't mean anything.
It's not like I'm actually
interested in him.
I don't want you to worry
about this.
about anything.
That's why I'm doing this.
- Okay, mom.
- Okay?
It's all gonna be good.
Hey, Gil.
This is Dylan Massett.
He's the guy
I was telling you about.
So, Dylan...
you know how to use a gun?
Yeah.
- What's for dinner, honey?
- Screw off.
And I didn't make it.
Mom made it.
Crap.
We're out of beer.
Apparently "the whore"
is calling you.
Hi, Norma.
Yeah, I met with the plumber,
and I got the quotes
for the new toilets.
Yeah, it's in the kitchen.
Okay, fine, fine.
Yes.
Don't you ever
call our mother a whore!
Get the hell off of me!
What do you think you're doing?
You're a damn joke, Norman.
You let that bitch
run you like a puppet.
She doesn't run me.
She cares about me.
And she's not a bad person,
she's just not perfect!
At least she tries,
you son of a bitch!
You don't get it,
do you, Norman?
She's ruined you.
If you hate her so much,
why the hell
do you wanna stay here?
Because I've got
nowhere else to go!
But don't you come at me again,
or I will hurt you bad.
Do you understand?
I told you not to do that.
She's not a whore.
- Great job.
- That's awesome.
♪ I can see why you think ♪
Great job, man, just awesome.
- Look at you.
- Oh!
See, I told you, this is--
it's stupid.
You know, there are
a million reasons
why Keith Summers
could have disappeared.
He probably landed
in a ditch somewhere
as a result of some bad crap
that he got into.
You mean, illegal stuff?
Let's just say that
he was a train wreck in general.
♪ Amie ♪
You know, I had such high hopes
when I came here to make a home
for me and Norman.
And things just keep happening,
weird things,
you know?
It's like this,
but...it's not like this.
Look, nowhere is like this.
I mean,
not all the way through.
Have you noticed what
these people do for a living?
Artisanal cheese,
organic pig farms.
And yet, most of these people,
somehow,
they're all living
in million-dollar homes.
They're driving European cars.
The town, it was built
on the logging industry,
but all that collapsed
with the tree huggers.
I'm just saying
that there are...
there's different ways
to produce an economy,
and it's not always
what it seems.
But surely you can't allow
illegal things,
bad things to happen here.
The people in this town,
they deal with things
in a different way,
but it gets dealt with.
And what about the guy
who was burned?
It'll be dealt with.
An eye for an eye.
It'll get handled.
The boat sails
for New York in 20 minutes.
- Let it sail.
- Look, Mastermind,
the tour is over.
We've been posse-baitin'
every town from coast to coast,
and we just ran out of towns.
Norman?
What on earth happened to you?
Oh, Dylan and I just
got into a fight.
It's not a big deal.
It absolutely is a big deal.
Look at your sweet face.
This is awful.
What happened?
I don't even know, mom.
We just don't get along.
He's gonna have to leave.
He can't come into our lives
and disrupt them like this.
He can't talk to us
the way he does.
And he can't hurt you.
I will not stand for it.
I won't.
Maybe it would be
the best thing.
Get some sleep, sweetheart.
Oh, hey.
Cool. You came.
You said it was important.
Holy crap.
What happened to your face?
Oh, I fell down the stairs,
you know,
those long stairs
in front of our house.
It's okay.
You don't have to tell me.
Thanks.
So what's with
all the stuffed animals?
Are they real?
They were once.
My dad does it.
He's one of the best taxidermy
artists on the west coast.
But enough
about stuffing dead animals.
Sit down.
I'm gonna tell you
a little story
about real, living things.
Four girls from Shunyi, China,
get told that, if they come
to America illegally
and work as housemaids,
they will get citizenship
in seven years.
But they aren't gonna be maids.
They are forced to have sex
with different men every day.
One of them
dies from an overdose.
They force the other girls
to carry her body
into the hills, dig a grave,
and then bury her
by a shed in the trees.
This is a pretty wild story.
Wild, yes, and not over.
So eventually,
after they have been sampled,
they are sold one by one
into sex slavery.
Look at this.
That's Ladyface.
It's a mountain
just outside of White Pine Bay.
My dad's shown it to me before.
It really exists.
And?
Someone did this
to these girls, Norman,
and we can prove it.
We can find the spot
and find the grave.
Then we'll know
if it's real or not.
This is all a little peculiar.
No.
You know what's peculiar?
A 17-year-old boy
using the word "peculiar."
So you in?
♪ You see this guy ♪
♪ this guy's in love with you ♪
♪ Yes, I'm in love ♪
♪ who looks at you
the way I do ♪
♪ when you smile ♪
♪ I can tell ♪
♪ we know each other
very well ♪
♪ how can I show you ♪
♪ I'm glad ♪
What are you doing?
It's the middle of the night.
Just having a cocktail
and listening
to some of the previous owner's
old music.
You?
Hey, I saw
what you did to Norman.
You can't stay here.
You're toxic.
You're leaving in the morning.
How did Sam die, Norma?
You know, it's funny.
Because I had to do
a lot of research to find out
where you guys had moved to.
And I wound up talking
to one of the insurance people,
and they talked
about how sad it was
that Sam had died
and what a wonderful husband
and father he was.
And then, I thought,
you know, "Hmm.
"Wouldn't it be interesting
if I told them what life
with Sam was really like?"
You know, how you guys
got along and all.
♪ Tell me now ♪
♪ is it so ♪
♪ don't let me be
the last to know ♪
Just keep the music down.
♪ Don't let ♪
♪ my heart keep breakin' ♪
♪ 'cause I need your love ♪
You're right.
That's it.
See? It's real.
Let's go.
Crap.
This is a big mountain.
Where's that shed?
We should take a break
for a second.
It's okay for you
to be doing this, right?
Totally.
Fine.
I'm okay.
It's cool up here.
My dad, he taught me
this meditation
where first you imagine
your spirit
rising up out of your body,
then out of your house,
out of your town,
out of the sky,
like a golden light
zooming and growing,
out into, and even past,
the universe.
And from that point,
you look back
and you realize how small
you are in the world.
Don't you feel like that
up here, Norman?
That you're connected
to something
so much larger than ourselves?
What the hell is that?
Holy crap.
It's one of the pot fields.
I've heard about them,
but I've never
actually seen one.
What pot fields?
What are you talking about?
Hey! Hey!
What the hell
are you doing there?
Emma, we need to run.
- Hey! Hey!
- We need to run.
Come on.
Come on, Emma!
Shh, get down.
Don't even breathe.
Sorry.
Aah!
Norman, it's the shed.
From the pictures.
We can't stop now.
Come on, Emma!
Come on, Emma.
Come on.
Let's go, let's go.
Go, go, go!
Come on!
Go, go!
Keep moving, let's go.
Let's go, let's go, come on.
Let's go.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player