Previously on Bates Motel...
[Dog barking]
I mean, we can't take
on a dog right now.
I always wanted a dog.
I mean, all families have a dog.
Could you tell me what
happened to the Seafarer Motel?
It's the Bates Motel now.
You know where I can find
Keith Summers?
He's actually dead.
There's nothing more
to tell you.
That's the entire truth.
Everything that happened
with Keith Summers,
with Deputy Shelby...
you know it all.
Someone in the motel?
This man, he had a standing
reservation at the Seafarer
every two months for a week.
I'd love to have the same
business arrangement
that I had with Keith,
if that's possible.
There's not anything illegal,
right?
- No.
- Come here, girl.
[Dog whimpering]
[Car approaching]
Stay! Stay!
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
The art of it is to recreate
the beauty of motion
in something still.
To create life, if you will.
Here is where
we'll make incisions.
Then what do you do?
Well, then you have
to take everything out.
I'm sorry.
There's no pretty way to put it.
Oh, no, that's okay.
I figured as much.
Now...
[Clears throat]
here are some of the various
stages of how it works.
I'm sorry you lost
your friend here.
It just seems sad
to let her go.
You know, dishonorable, sort of,
just to put her in the ground.
[Chuckles]
I think she was lonely.
I understand.
Well, I think what you do
to these animals is...
- amazing.
- Come and help me.
I can teach you how it works.
You might enjoy it.
Once you get past the blood
and the guts of it all,
it's really
quite beautiful work,
if you're at all artistic,
which I have a feeling
you might be.
Thank you, Mr. Decody.
[Coughing]
[Sprays inhaler, gasps]
[Coughs]
[Door opens]
[Girls giggling]
I feel so bad for him.
He's always just staring at her
like a lost puppy.
Yeah, it's a little pathetic.
He's a little pathetic.
Yeah, Norman's nice,
but he's really weird.
The way he just stares
into space like that.
He's the definition
of socially challenged.
I mean, he can't actually think
he has a shot with her, right?
He's not that out of reality.
Bradley's so nice.
She just felt sorry for him.
I think she thinks of him
as more of pet than a guy.
Like, really,
like she would ever have sex
with someone like that.
No way.
He can't be that stupid.
Well, maybe you better
talk to her...
because she did.
I don't think you know
what we're talking about.
Actually, I don't think you
know what you're talking about.
Bradley had sex with Norman.
Sex, as in
carnal-back-and-forth.
Maybe she has sex
with all her pets.
I don't know.
But you should really
get your facts straight
before you shoot your mouth off
with your demeaning opinions.
And you've got toilet paper
on your shoe.
Hmm.
- Sheriff Romero's office.
- Hello.
Can I speak
with Sheriff Romero, please?
- Who may I say is calling?
- Norma Bates.
Hold, please.
[Hold music playing]
♪ ♪
I'm sorry.
I don't have him right now.
Well, can you please leave
a message that I called?
- He knows me.
- Of course.
Can you spell your last name
for me, please?
Bates.
B-a-t-e-s.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
[Cell phone buzzing]
Hey, it's Dylan.
Yeah, we just brought
in the harvest
from the Red Creek field.
I need you and Remo
to go down to California
and pick up the trimmers.
- Yeah, okay.
- It's all set up.
They'll be waiting
for you tomorrow.
3:00 P.M., Twin Eagles Motel
in Fortuna.
Yeah, um, what exactly
are trimmers?
[Chuckles] Yeah, get Remo
to explain it to you.
He's made the run
about 20 times.
It was Gil.
He wants us
to go down to Fortuna
and pick up the trimmers.
What exactly are trimmers?
Really?
You don't know
what a trimmer is?
Why don't you explain it to me?
[Sighs] How about I don't?
Here comes Ronny and Don.
I'll get the van.
You can pack up.
Wait, wait.
Pack what?
It's an overnight trip, Nimrod.
Pack a change of clothes,
or not.
You want me to come over
and tell you what to wear?
Okay, let's--
let's just go.
Hey, yo!
Let's go!
[Students chattering]
Why did you tell everyone?
Tell everyone what?
About you and I--
what happened that night.
I didn't tell anyone.
You told Emma Decody,
because she told everyone
in the girls' bathroom.
I'm sorry.
I-I don't know why
she would do that.
Listen,
it's just not cool, Norman.
Okay, but why isn't it?
I mean, it happened, right?
Yeah, but it shouldn't have.
We need to forget about it.
I have a boyfriend, okay?
I don't want people to know.
Just forget it happened.
Norman?
Excuse me, Norman.
What is going on?
- I have to leave.
- Why?
- I just have to.
- Well, do you have a note?
You have to have a note.
Norman, you cannot just walk
away from school and leave.
You'll get cited.
You'll get suspended.
I don't care!
Norman.
Just come back inside,
and we can--
[whistling]
[Sighs] Housekeeping.
Morning. I wasn't sure
what time you wanted me
to come and clean the room.
Will you be leaving soon?
You can come in
and clean it now--that's fine.
Oh, no, that's okay.
I'll come back later
when you're gone.
Actually...
I'd like my room made up now.
I was in town last night.
I...
heard there was an unpleasant
incident here recently.
- A dog got hit out front.
- No.
I heard Zack Shelby
got shot here.
Right up there on those steps.
Yeah, he did.
It's funny.
You never know someone.
I knew Keith Summers
all these years.
Not well, but I knew him.
And here he was--
he's in the motel for this...
sex trade.
You just never know, do you?
Yeah, I guess you don't.
[Gasps] Oh!
[Shattering sound]
Sorry about that.
I'll grab a bulb
from another room.
It's no worries.
Did you know Zack Shelby?
Did I know him?
A little.
I guess like how you knew
Keith Summers.
So not so much?
No, not so much.
I'm sorry.
I have to, um--
I just remembered.
I have to give my son
a ride somewhere.
He's not here.
Yeah.
Yeah, I saw him leave.
School, wasn't it?
I got to go.
I'm gonna come back,
and I'll finish up later, okay?
[Muttering]
I just--just...
We're good for now.
If I need anything else,
I'll come by the office.
Sure.
Mm-hmm.
Sheriff Romero can see you now.
So what can I help you with,
Mrs. Bates?
Oh, please, call me Norma,
after everything
we've been through...
You know that I called
your office this morning.
You know,
I was coming in town anyway.
I thought, oh, I'll just pop in
and see him.
So anyway, um...
you know, I bought the motel
a few months ago,
and no one told me at the time
that the city's planning on
building a new bypass
that would basically
take my motel off the map.
Mm-hmm.
So I'm just trying
to figure out a way
that, um, I can fight this
from the inside.
Well, I, um, I see that
there's a seat open
on the city planning committee,
and I wanted you
to put me forward for it.
Maybe I can influence
their decision.
Why would I do that?
Be...cause
I thought you would.
Why?
Because...
because of what
we've been through.
Because...
we know things
about each other.
We don't owe each other
anything.
We're not friends.
You don't know me
in any social sense,
other than as your sheriff.
Don't assume differently
just 'cause I was kind enough
to save your ass once.
Excuse me, but weren't you
saving your own ass at the time?
I mean, the fact is that your
deputy was doing all of this
right under your nose,
and you knew nothing about it.
I mean, that's not
how you rewrote the story.
Are you trying to say
that you have something on me?
Is that it?
'Cause if you did,
that really
wouldn't be good for you, okay?
I mean, I might have to...
burn you down
to the ground, you know?
Don't ever try
to intimidate me.
Don't walk into my office
and ask me for political favors
based on nothing.
You and I have no connection.
We're not
on the same playing field.
Don't ever assume that we are.
You don't know
what you're doing.
Go home, Mrs. Bates.
[Cell phone buzzing]
Hello?
- Mrs. Bates?
- Yes.
This is Tom Hudgins.
I'm the principal of
White Pine Bay High School.
I'd like you to come in
this afternoon.
We need to discuss
your son's behavior at school.
Can you go on the Internet,
find out what a trimmer is?
Yeah.
Trimmers are the guys who cut
and process the weed,
and they turn the raw plants
into final product.
The man's a scholar.
No rust on you, Bubba.
Come on, get in.
Hey.
I didn't see you
at school today.
Oh, I wasn't feeling good.
I went home early.
Are you okay?
Why did you tell all the girls
I slept with Bradley?
It just came up.
Sort of.
Just like it came up
with my mom?
Did your mom tell you that?
No, she didn't have to.
I just don't understand.
Wh-what're you trying to do?
I'm sorry.
Bradley was really upset.
Don't ever tell anyone
something I tell you
in confidence again, okay?
Okay.
Leaving school without
permission is a serious offense.
He's gonna be suspended
for three days.
Well, he came home.
He just wasn't feeling
that well.
He didn't seem sick
when I saw him.
- He seemed upset.
- No, he wasn't upset.
Well, I tried to tell him
that he couldn't leave campus,
and he was practically shaking.
I took his arm
to lead him back in,
and he pulled it away
pretty violently.
Are you supposed to be putting
your hands on the students?
Um, I think we should stick
with the issue here.
Ms. Bates, what we've observed
and what we're concerned about
is your son's
emotional instability.
Instability?
He is emotionally unusual
for a boy his age.
He doesn't interact much
with others.
He keeps to himself a lot.
And based on the behavior
that I have seen,
Principal Hudgins and I
would like him to speak with
one of the school psychologists.
I don't know if I want him
to be doing that.
And why is that?
Because I would rather
that he...
you know, I think that he should
see a private psychologist.
You know, I would like
to choose the therapist.
Okay.
Well, I think that therapy would
be very beneficial for him.
Mm.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, okay.
And, um, perhaps I could get
the name of that therapist
so that I could maybe explain
to him what I've seen in school?
Okay, of course, absolutely.
I will keep in touch.
Okay.
[George Thorogood's
Who Do You Love]
♪ I walked 47 miles
of barbed wire ♪
♪ I got a cobra snake ♪
Ah, there's no liqueur
in this drink.
I'm gonna get some sleep.
Two more shots
for me and my boss.
Boss.
What's your problem?
You've been on my ass
since we met.
♪ Who do you love? ♪
You know,
I got 23 years, all right?
23 years experience,
and now here I am
working for you.
You ever wonder
why that might be?
Hmm? Hmm?
Because I think
it's pretty obvious.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
In fact, I don't think
there's enough liquor
in this entire bar
to make you forget
what a pathetic,
self-destructive loser you are.
♪ Yeah, who do you love? ♪
Want me to kick your ass
right now?
Oh, you're gonna kick my ass?
Really? That's the funniest joke
you've ever had.
Uhh!
[Glass shatters]
You better watch out for me,
golden boy.
I'll try to destroy you.
I used to be like you.
The boss loved me.
Gave me a chance to step up.
Yeah.
What happened?
I don't have
leadership potential.
What'd you do?
I'm not what you would call
consistently reliable.
Now nobody respects me.
Nobody.
You say you've been working
for Gil for 23 years?
Yep.
No, not Gil.
The big boss.
Who's that?
You'll know
when you need to know.
- Why do you stay?
- What?
I mean, if you don't like it,
then why do you stay?
If no one respects you,
why don't you quit?
[Chuckles] Quit?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
There's no quitting in this job.
No, you can't quit.
No.
You could get fired, though.
You don't want that
to happen to you, believe me.
Anyway, good night.
Mother...
I'm sorry...you know,
about what happened at school.
[Inhales] What did happen?
- Well, I-I got upset.
- About what?
I don't want to talk about it.
You know, I promise
it won't happen again.
It can't happen
because now they want you
to go see a therapist.
I mean, this is all gonna
go on your record,
and you have
to be more careful.
You have to try to fit in,
Norman.
You can't go around being
so emotional all the time.
I know, mother, and I'm sorry.
But I do think I fit in,
for the most part.
Oh, can you give me a ride
to Emma's shop?
- Yeah, why?
- I'm working with her dad.
He's teaching me
how to do taxidermy.
Will, this is my mom.
- I'm Norma Bates.
- You can call me will.
Will, I'm wondering if we can
have a word in private.
Yeah, of course.
Norman, would you give us
a minute, please?
Mm.
- Please.
- Thank you.
I don't know
if this is such a good thing
for Norman to be doing.
- No?
- Uh-uh.
He's already sort of...
um, sort of an unusual boy.
You know, he has a hard time
fitting in.
He gets upset very easily.
- Really?
- Yeah.
He's always very calm
when he's here working.
But hobbies
can be good that way.
Oh, of course, and...
I just don't want him getting
labeled as a freak or anything.
I don't think
that learning taxidermy
necessarily makes one a freak.
No!
No, no.
I'm not saying
that you're a freak.
No, that's not
what I'm saying at all.
- Not at all.
- No?
I'm... [laughs]
I'm not saying that.
- Oh, no.
- Um...
I'm--I'm just saying that not
a lot of people do it.
Not many people write poetry,
but we still have to have poets,
right?
He's good at it,
and he's good company.
We're not hurting anyone.
The animals are already dead.
So what's the harm
in letting a young person
follow their passion?
What can go wrong with that?
[Strumming guitar]
Ugh.
There he is.
Let's go.
You guys heading out
to White Pine Bay?
What does it look like,
douchebag?
You're an hour late,
by the way.
Hey...
That guy right there,
I remember him from last year.
He's a complete pain
in the ass.
We should leave him behind.
Gil said we should bring
all of them.
I think we should do that.
Whatever.
[Laughs]
You're so good at this.
Have you done it
your whole life?
Pretty much, yeah.
I stopped for about ten years,
though, when I was married.
Yeah, Emma's mom
didn't like it much.
She didn't like me
very much either.
But I rediscovered myself
after she left.
I'm sorry, Will.
It's okay.
I left that life behind
in England.
And I got Emma.
And that's all that matters.
[Car engine starts]
[Engine starts]
[Door creaks open]
[Door closes]
[Tires screech]
[Shrieks]
[Panting]
What are you doing here, Norma?
I could ask you the same thing.
I think you're following me.
I think you want to know
what I'm up to.
And I think you know
what I'm looking for.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Really?
Nothing at all?
Where is it?
- Where is what?
- Where'd you hide it?
Hide what?
I don't have anything.
Really?
Then you weren't...
screwing Zack Shelby either?
Excuse me.
I have to go.
Do you think I'm just gonna
walk away from this?
I'm not some moron
like Keith Summers.
He was the bottom rung.
I'm on the top.
- You understand?
- No, I don't.
I don't understand.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Well, my guess is,
once you think about it,
you'll remember.
When you do,
come by my hotel room.
Mm.
We'll talk about it.
Okay?
Tell me a little bit about
losing your father, Norman.
He died in an accident
in our garage.
Six months ago.
It was devastating, of course.
But...we moved.
And we're doing our best
to start over
and reinvent our lives.
Yes.
Can you talk to me about
how it felt to move
from the home where you lived
with your dad
- to a whole new town?
- Yeah.
[Clears throat]
Yeah, I guess it, uh,
it felt...
I guess I felt a lot of things.
Like what, Norman?
It was sad.
He was sad.
We were both sad.
Mm, sad.
♪ In the dark night ♪
[Strumming guitar]
♪ When I found all your love ♪
[Chuckles]
♪ ♪
♪ You were an angel
sent from above ♪
- ♪ I thought-- ♪
- Could you just shut up?
Put that guitar away.
My head is about to explode.
I can't listen to any more
of his crap.
You all remember this pus ball
from last year, right?
I think I'm gonna tell Gil
we're not coming back next year.
And it's past lunch.
It's time for you to pull over
and buy us a meal.
We'll stop in a while.
Management here seems to think
he can tell us
when we're gonna eat.
We want to stop, man!
We want to stop.
Remo, pull over.
Get out.
Get out and what?
You want me to watch you piss?
No, I want you to get out
of the van right now.
You, your guitar,
and anyone else
who thinks this is a democracy,
you can get out too!
We can stop for lunch
whenever, man.
- It's all good.
- I said get out!
Let's go!
Walk over here.
Go on.
Thank you.
So same time next week, Norman?
Well, I'm gonna call
and schedule something,
but have a lot going on
with the motel opening.
May I talk to you privately
for a moment?
Mm, yeah.
Yeah, I'll be right out, Norman.
Um...
I think it might be helpful
if I saw Norman on his own
next time.
No offense, but I don't feel
comfortable with that.
I mean, I don't know you.
Have you ever been in therapy,
Mrs. Bates?
No.
Would you consider coming
for some sessions of your own?
Why?
Well, I've noticed you have
a strong influence on Norman,
maybe a need to control things.
- I'm his mother.
- Of course.
But as our children grow older,
we need to let go a little.
Hmm?
The thing is, um...
people who feel
the need to control everything
often, in actuality, feel
out of control on the inside.
Do you ever feel that way?
No, I don't.
[Stammers]
I feel completely in control
of everything in my life.
How dare you make these stupid
assumptions about me.
You don't know anything
about me.
I work hard.
I take care of my son.
I know what's right
and what's wrong for him.
No one pushes me around.
I control my own life.
I'm in total control
of my own life.
I have a lot going on.
I have a lot to deal with,
but I do not feel powerless.
Ever!
[Sighs] We're going, Norman.
What happened, mother?
- Did I say something wrong?
- No, you were perfect.
Let's go.
Norman, go up to the house.
I'll be right there.
Okay, mom.
Come on in.
I'd offer you a drink,
but I can't seem
to find a mini bar.
Here's your money back.
I want you out of my motel!
You didn't just do that,
did you?
Look, I don't know
who you are, and I don't care,
but I don't want to have
anything more to do with you.
Okay?
We are not having future
business together.
You are not booking rooms here
ever again.
You need to dial it down
right now, Norma,
before I get truly annoyed.
You want me to call the cops
and tell them what you've been
saying to me? Hmm?
How you wanted to rent rooms
and have "privacy"?
How you knew Keith Summers
and Zack Shelby?
I know all about you
and Zack Shelby.
What?
There's nothing to know.
I'm not afraid of you.
You have no power over me.
You were gonna try
and convince me
that you and Shelby
were casual acquaintances,
that you knew nothing
about what was going on?
If you are not out of
this room in five minutes,
I am calling the police.
Okay, you want to play?
We'll play.
Five minutes!
[Door closes]
[Car drives off]
[Tires screech]
Hey.
Can we talk?
Mm, yeah.
The reason I told those girls
about you and Bradley
is because I heard them
talking about you,
saying things like
it was embarrassing
how you just stared
at Bradley all the time
and how someone like her
would never have
anything to do
with someone like you.
Oh.
And it just made me so angry,
because I think
you are so special
and so much better
than any of them.
I just couldn't keep
my mouth shut.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
I just didn't want you to think
I had any other motive.
I know you think I like you.
And, okay, I guess I do, but...
it's not about that.
I don't care if you're not
gonna be my boyfriend.
I'm pretty used to things
not turning out the way I expect
and making the best of it.
It's just...
you are really special to me.
And I feel safe with you.
You are my friend,
and I don't want
to mess that up or lose you.
I don't have many real friends.
It's okay, Emma.
I'm sorry I was mad.
I'm sorry.
If there was a door,
I would have knocked.
It's fine, dad.
[Chuckles]
[Car approaching]
How many rooms
we got available?
All of them.
12 rooms, 12 vacancies.
What happened to number nine?
You were right about that guy.
So I got rid of him.
I handled it.
Cool.
Um...
look, I got seven people here
who need rooms.
They're gonna be doing some work
for my boss,
and we need somewhere to put 'em
for the next two weeks.
Really?
Yeah!
Yeah.
Well, I'll go open the office.
Thank you, Dylan.
Yeah, sure, Norma.
You know, Norman is staying
for dinner at Emma's tonight.
Do you want to go get a bite
in the village?
It would just be the two of us.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
I'm just gonna get out
of these clothes.
I'll run upstairs,
and then I'll come back down
to meet you
and settle everybody in.
- Okay?
- Okay.
[Chuckles] Okay.
Oh!
[Screams]
Oh, God! Norman!
Norman!
[Screams]
Norman! Norman!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player