Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
There is a place
not far from here
where you could be
feared and respected.
Eight men who support Hamund.
You said it yourself.
We kill him, they all become threats
to both of us.
They disappear
all at once tonight.
Between you and Flint, I'm not certain
who I should be more afraid of.
- Leave with me. - I've spent my life
trying to build something here.
What if I forgo payment
for the schedule
in exchange for my share
of the prize?
When the time comes for me
to reveal the last piece,
I will be right by your side.
It wasn't Singleton
that stole the page.
- It was him.
- You're lying to them.
If no one knows, everyone wins.
I believe in this place.
If there's anyone who can do
what's necessary to make it
something better, it's you.
Once we have the money,
Flint dies.
- No argument.
- Not from me.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Ca va?
Mr. Rackham,
a word.
I've been expecting you,
please Sit.
Won't you tell me what you
think of our little production?
The theme is
"Evenings in Paris."
I'll give you three
guesses whose idea it was.
Mr. Rackham,
I just saw the bursar.
He says I'm no longer
to receive my distribution
of the house's profits.
Your instruction?
Yes, I did some rough calculations
to figure the amount
you've been skimming from the take
since we first began this arrangement.
It only seems fair to garnish
your proceeds to account for it.
Mr. Rackham, I understand
your new friend
has helped to bring
the girls into line,
has them reporting their
income in a most honest fashion.
That must be very nice for you.
But let us get something
very straight.
I'm not one of the girls.
I will have my cut
or everyone in this street will know
what became of Mr. Noonan.
- You would do that?
- Don't you dare doubt it.
Well, Mrs. Mapleton, that sounds
like gross insubordination to me.
That, coupled with the graft
you've been responsible for,
leaves me with no choice but to terminate
your employment here.
- What?
- You're dismissed.
Thank you for your service.
Pardon me, but have you
lost your mind?
Not that I'm aware of, no.
I just told you
that I am fully willing
to inform every
merchant in Nassau
that you murdered your way
into ownership of this place.
They will band together
to see you hanged.
Which ones exactly?
Which merchants will see
Mr. Rackham hanged?
Mr. Connors
the wheelwright?
Or perhaps Mr. Peterson
the butcher.
Maybe Mr. Rusch
the lapidary?
They all have enjoyed
steep discounts here lately.
Affordable now that the books are
in good order.
I wonder, given their fondness
for the new management,
which one of them would much care
what you think happened to Mr. Noonan?
You forgot the only name
that matters, dear.
The lady across the street.
She finds out about this...
Oh, Madam Guthrie knows.
She's fine with it.
But by all means, go ahead, tell
her again. I can't see any harm in it.
You will regret this, sir.
I'm sure I won't.
Au revoir.
Please don't judge me,
but I really enjoyed that.
You do not believe she will
attempt to strike back at you?
I wouldn't put it past her.
But at the moment I'll live with
the potential for future trouble
over the certainty of actual
trouble she was causing.
To a profitable venture.
And a partner significantly
more pleasing to the eye.
What am I supposed
to do with this?
If he's to continue on the ship, the crutch
is too much of an impediment.
He shall have to wear this
whether he likes it or not.
Come on, Randall.
Dr. Howell made this
'specially for you.
Help you move around better.
Perhaps you'll even be able to visit the shitter
once in a while without needing my help.
Whoa, easy there.
You're responsible for him.
You figure it out.
"Oh, Mr. Silver.
How can I ever thank you?
First you save me from ending up as
a stain on the Walrus's underside.
Then you secured
my position on the crew
on the verge
of an historic haul.
And if that weren't enough,
you're still trying to find
something comfortable
to put at the end of my stump.
From the bottom
of my heart, thank you."
You're welcome.
Launch from the Ranger.
Captain Gates is coming over.
Crazy bastard.
What could be
so fucking important
that he has to row
through all that shit out there?
We make landfall in the morning.
The last part of the schedule
if you don't mind.
What's that?
My own reconnaissance.
There are a dozen bays and inlets
within a day's journey from here
that will make reasonable locations
for the Urca to take on water.
If the course you write down
leads to one of them,
odds are that your
information is accurate.
And if it doesn't?
Division Bay.
The course leads
to Division Bay.
Shoals on the eastern shore,
but if we approach
from the windward,
we should be able to take up
a strong opening position.
Take this
to Mr. De Groot.
Tell him to adjust
our course accordingly
and set up our final
approach for the morning.
Something else?
Well, now that I've fulfilled
my end of the bargain,
I'm just wondering
where you and I stand.
Keep wondering.
I best be getting back.
Let's not tempt fate.
Talbot Rhodes.
Private stock.
I've been waiting
for an occasion.
My reckoning is tomorrow
we'll either be able to afford
a lot more of it or...
We'll be too dead to care.
Captain asked me
to pass these to you.
A new course.
The captain accepted the last segment
of the Urca route as valid?
One thing you should not doubt.
Certainty is not a word
I throw around lightly.
Now this information,
I am quite certain I have it right.
That man has a strange
way of handling
the prospect of imminent
wealth beyond reason.
Ma'am.
What are you doing here?
Captain Hornigold
asked me to sit in
on Captain Lawrence's final
preparations before departure.
They're just finishing upstairs.
Mm.
I'm fine.
Believe it or not,
this place didn't collapse
the moment you walked
out the door.
You really believe my concern
is for this place?
It's a ship killer out there.
I can't even imagine
what it's like further north.
You'd been opposed to hunting
the Urca from the beginning.
Perhaps God's on your side
of this one.
I just think of all the trouble that
fucking schedule caused.
The trouble it caused Max and I.
Caused you and I.
The thought that it could all
end up being for nothing...
Perhaps the trouble
was going to happen anyway.
Schedule or no.
Perhaps.
Tomorrow a thing
that you conceived
out of thin air becomes real.
A thing that will
give this place
a chance to find some
small measure of peace.
That is not nothing.
Henderson?
It wasn't Henderson.
It was something like Henderson.
Harrison? Harvey?
I don't know who the fuck
you're talking about.
The man that nicked
that bottle was called Cregg.
Cregg! That's him.
Cregg.
Mr. Cregg.
Carpenter's mate.
Had a nose
for sniffing out booze
on a prize ship
like a fucking bloodhound.
Oh, Cregg. I remember walking in
on him once,
digging through a stash
on a prize.
He...
he found this bottle of booze
behind a baseboard.
Now he's convinced that the prize
captain's been hiding his best liquor.
So he pops the cork
and takes this big swig
in front of all of us.
- And it was piss.
- It was piss.
Aye, Cregg.
- Oh, God.
- Oh, Cregg.
I brought him over
with me, you know.
We served together under
Avery when we was kids.
Huh.
He was my first bunkmate.
For years he went on
how he'd got this
huge stash hidden away.
And I should live to survive him
because one day
I will be a rich man.
As you know, we lost
him on the Pembroke.
So I open his locker
and what do I find?
12 pesos, a busted pocket watch,
and a letter with instructions
to deliver it
to his sister in New York.
Lying sack of shit
was Mr. Cregg.
So I bought the boys
a round with the pesos,
traded the pocket watch
for a bit of tail,
and spent two weeks
that winter in New York
trying to deliver that fucking
letter to his sister.
Looked high and low.
Never found her.
So on the way home,
I waited till we were
in open water
and I could see no land
in any direction,
and I dropped it over the side.
Returned to the sea.
There are no legacies
in this life, are there?
No monuments.
No history.
Just the water.
It pays us
and then it claims us.
Swallows us whole.
As if we'd never
been here at all.
Well...
I better be getting back.
How the fuck can you cut Mapleton
loose without even telling me?
I'm sorry. I wasn't aware you were her
attorney in this matter.
She'll run her mouth all over
the fucking island about Noonan.
Who cares? The only people who
could conceivably make trouble for us
are currently elbow deep
in free prostitute downstairs.
What's worse, you keep counsel
with a whore about it.
Wait, what?
You think you can
trust her, you dumb shit?
That's what this
is about? Max?
You fucked her, didn't you?
Jesus H. Christ.
I can't win with you.
She's in the camp
with the men and it's, "Come on, Jack,
let's go kill everybody
and see if we can't get her out of there.
Hope you don't mind.
Made that decision on your behalf."
And now she's out, making us
a small fortune, by the way,
and you're pissed off
about that, too.
Might you consider making up your fucking
mind about it, please?
- Fuck you, Jack.
- "Fuck you, Jack."
Yes, I know.
Fuck me.
Listen here!
When we crest the point ahead
and spot the Urca in anchor,
we'll begin
our final run at her.
- Take it. - The Spanish banner may
earn us a few hundred yards
of confusion before the captain
identifies us and opens fire.
So we'll close fast on her,
hammer her well with our guns,
and then take the fight
to her decks.
That fight will be the fight
of our lives,
make no mistake.
But on the other side
lies paradise.
I'll see you there.
Mr. De Groot?
A full complement,
if you please.
Signal the Ranger.
- Aye, captain.
- Full sail, final approach.
Check our position.
- This is the course.
- Well, check it again.
Captain, this is
the location you requested.
Your true manifest.
Your false manifest.
And, most importantly,
your bribe money.
Godspeed, Captain.
Perhaps we should go over
the details one more time.
The harbormaster's
name is Singer.
The foreman's name is Smith.
The warehouse manager's Clay,
and the customs man is Kent.
Now if you don't let me
board my ship
and leave this place,
none of it will matter
as the goods in my hold will be rotten
by the time I arrive.
- Goodbye.
- Godspeed.
I have to hand it to you,
you said you'd rebuild things
here without your father,
and damned if you
didn't do just that.
Still one step
yet to accomplish.
Removing my father entirely.
Excuse me?
I know he's out
in the Underhill estate.
If you think he isn't scheming
to undo everything
we've done here,
you're kidding yourself.
You are truly amazing.
In a moment when stability
is at hand and the world is at your feet,
your first instinct is to go out in search
of someone new to fight.
Captain, a moment.
God.
Can't believe you left me
for that old lady.
Captain Hornigold is right.
What the fuck?
Where did that come from?
Jesus Christ, Ben, why are your men firing
on their own ship?
My men aren't the ones
doing the firing.
We need to get you
off the beach now.
Is someone shooting
the guns off out here?
What the hell is going on?
Someone has taken over the fort.
Captain, after an
inventory of our stores,
the men have assented
to your plan.
Provided we find a suitable
place to land the Walrus,
you'll have two days
to send out scouts
and hopefully locate the Urca.
Given their mood, I'd say we were
lucky to get that long.
Do it, then.
- What?
- It's Mr. De Groot.
He's put his foot down.
Once we make landfall,
he wants Flint tried immediately.
Oh, Jesus.
He's bitter about the fact that we
didn't listen to him regarding the cook.
He says there's no Urca out here
and that justice has been
delayed long enough.
That's not gonna happen,
so let's discuss reality.
He said that you'd say that.
And after all your talk,
you're just protecting Flint.
I'm protecting all of us.
These men are right on the edge
and he wants to rile
them up more
by talking about a lying,
thieving captain,
then stand on a deserted beach
and talk about an election.
Before you know it, half a dozen men
will have laid claim to the captaincy.
Camps will divide.
It won't be dark yet
before the fighting starts.
We're gonna see Flint
pay for his crimes.
But we'll do it at home
and we'll do it
like civilized men.
That's how we avoid the abyss.
We knew you spent the night
drinking together.
How can we take you
at your word?
You don't have to take my word.
Good enough for you?
Mr. Gates...
Sails!
To the south!
Is it the Urca?
Captain, is it her?
Captain, is it the Urca?
Man-of-war!
She's a man-of-war!
Spanish banners!
In less than half an hour,
she'll be right on top of us.
Get orders to the Ranger.
Tell her to raise the black
and fire two shots over our bow.
- Mr. De Groot.
- Captain?
Rig a spring to the forward anchor,
then drop her immediately.
Drop anchor?
You mean to fight her?
You all have your orders!
Captain, join me.
- We don't have time.
- Make time.
If he engages that ship
in battle, we're dead.
- I know.
- I know you know.
But does Mr. Gates?
I can't let you
go down this road.
As far that
man-of-war knows,
we're Spanish merchantmen
under attack by pirate raiders.
We order the Ranger to flee,
the Spaniard passes us
to give chase,
and before she realizes her
error, we've got her trapped.
She's got 100 guns.
We do this properly, she'll never
get a chance to use them.
We'll rake her stern to bow,
the Ranger will rake
her bow to stern.
With a little luck, we'll hammer her
into submission
before she can bring
her broadsides to bear.
To accomplish what, exactly?
The Urca. She's here.
Can't you see that?
All I can see is an empty bay,
a guardacosta warship,
and a captain that's lost
his fucking grip on reality.
Guardacosta?
You think that ship's here on patrol?
That she just happened
by this place at this time?
That ship is an escort.
It's the only explanation.
The Urca has no escort.
Was that not the justification
for this entire endeavor?
They altered their plans.
Found a ship they could spare.
I'm taking the Ranger
and I'm leaving.
What did you just say?
I'm gonna weigh anchor
and I'm gonna make a run for it.
If I can keep ahead
of it before dark,
there's just a chance
we can slip away.
Without the Ranger,
I have no chance against that ship.
I know.
So you're deliberately
challenging my authority here?
Deliberately
violating your duty?
My duty?
My duty is to them, not to you.
Although I have
violated it more times
than I can remember
in your defense.
Helped you deceive good men
who put their trust in me
because I was convinced
they would be better off for it.
Well, not here.
Not this.
This is fucking madness.
Mr. Gates, if you
walk through that door
with the intent
of subverting my plans,
I will have no alternative but to interpret
that as an incitement of mutiny.
You think I'm inciting mutiny?
- You are inciting mutiny.
- I'm managing one!
There are men
out there right now
that know about Singleton,
the book, the cook, all of it.
They know. And they mean to see
you hanged for it.
You told them?
After Billy, I just...
I didn't want to believe you could be
capable of doing something like that.
But I couldn't convince
myself that you weren't.
That's when I realized,
this has got to end.
So what, then?
You preside over a trial
that sees me hanged?
No.
We're going to go home
and I will see you
and Mrs. Barlow secreted away
before anybody
knows you're gone.
You're gonna go to Boston.
You're gonna take the pardon
that she's offered you.
And that is the last that you and I will
ever see of each other.
Please.
Please, don't do this.
I'm sorry.
Take a moment.
I'll deal with them.
This is not what I wanted.
I'm sorry.
I came to lend
credence to your case
that the Urca
is still to be won.
What the fuck
are you doing to him?
- Making sure there's nothing
incriminating... - Stop. Stop.
There's no way out of this.
Take it from me,
there's always a way.
Sir.
- What is it? - A small band of men were
seen approaching the fort
from the west this morning.
No one's been able to identify them.
Are all the home crews
accounted for?
Aye. Every one.
They had nothing to do with this.
Could this be a first move by England
to reclaim the island?
Without a single ship involved?
This does not have the air of
a state move. This is something else.
Captain, how easily
are the great guns
- on the fort repositioned?
- What difference does that make?
He's asking if the fort
can turn her guns around
and bring them to bear
on the street... on us.
Let's hope whomever's up there is
not mad enough to consider that.
That's less than
confidence-inspiring.
I have lieutenants
calling in favors
from the crews of the Colonial Dawn
and the Medusa.
I'll have 250 men assembled and ready
to storm the fort in a matter of hours.
By first light tomorrow,
I'll be back in my chair
and whoever did this
will be hanging by his goddamn...
- What is it?
- Quick, you all need to see this.
Go back inside.
Miss Guthrie.
I think it's time we talked.
Mr. Gates's heart
has given out.
He's dead?
Mr. Logan.
Signal Mr. Thompson
on the Ranger.
Inform him he's now in command.
His orders are to sail north.
When we fire on the target,
he's to tack hard to port and do the same.
Hoist the signals from the foremast
below the yard.
Get 'em up and down quickly before
the Spaniard sees them.
The question you need
to ask yourself
is "What good
can I do?"
You can call this murder.
A number of the men
might even believe you,
but will that be enough
to stop this fight
that is about to happen?
Because if it's not,
a fight we might win
becomes a battle
we are doomed to lose.
Because the men went into it
infected with your suspicions,
with your doubts.
So, Mr. Quartermaster,
is that truly what's
in their best interests?
St. Augustine.
Beg pardon?
When the warship draws close,
she'll ask our
last port of call.
St. Augustine's
the closest.
And as she's likely
a customs ship,
we must identify our cargo
as anything but tobacco.
Seville regulates
the trade heavily.
Thank you, Mr. Dufresne.
What the fuck did you do?
Spend enough time on an island,
begin to forget there's
a whole world out there.
A world where the rules
are different.
I went out there, found men
who don't know the rules here
and who don't much care
to learn them.
They helped me surprise
Captain Hornigold's men,
we took his fort, and not once were
any of them burdened
with the thought, "What if this were to
upset Eleanor Guthrie?"
Well, they're about
to learn the rules, Charles.
The hard way.
You think I'm gonna let this stand?
That Hornigold will?
We have men lining up
in droves to back us
in retaking it.
I'd expect nothing less.
Just out of curiosity,
how long do you think
that's gonna take?
Can you take back
that fort before...
I sink another ship in the bay?
Three more?
All of them?
Who knows?
If my men hold out long enough,
we may just decide
to sink the Walrus
when she returns with your
precious Spanish gold
just out of spite.
So that's what this is.
You're annoyed at me, so you're
gonna destroy everything I've built.
Never said I wanted
to destroy anything.
Then what do you want?
Hornigold controlled the fort.
The fort controls the bay.
The bay controls commerce.
That meant he was your partner.
Now, I control the fort.
So I will be your partner.
You are kidding me.
I was a tenant in this
place for a long time.
Didn't work out so well.
Now I'd like a stake.
You've absolutely
lost your mind.
I remember
the first time I saw you.
You were about 13.
You'd snuck down to the beach
despite Mr. Scott's
rules forbidding it.
A girl that age
looking like you did.
And you just walked up
and down between the camps
like you owned the place.
Fearless.
Then you saw me watching you
and you didn't look away.
Didn't cower.
You just gave me this look...
this little smile...
that said you refused
to be afraid of me.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
I know you.
Better than your father,
better than Scott.
Maybe better than anyone.
You don't give a shit
about money or respect.
Or the things you've built here.
I think you're just tired
of fathers
telling you what to do.
And so I'm offering you
a life free from them.
With me in that fort,
you do as you like.
As long as it doesn't cross me,
you'll hear no complaints.
You know I have no choice
but to say yes.
But before I do, know this,
you'll sit in that fort for a while.
You'll get comfortable.
And that's the day
I'm gonna push you and your men
right into the fucking sea.
God, I missed that look.
Ben.
What the hell did he say?
He wants your seat on the consortium.
To be a partner to us.
Well, I have 300 men out there
more than happy to deny him.
- You can't, Ben.
- Oh, watch me.
I told him about the tunnels.
The tunnels that you would use to
launch a surprise attack into the fort.
- I told him.
- Jesus!
You told me to keep emotion
from clouding judgment.
To act in everyone's
best interest.
I believe that's what I'm doing.
This is not the end of this.
Captain.
Welcome back.
I hear congratulations
are in order.
Steward of the fort.
Stroke of pure genius.
In some ways, Jack,
it had to come to this.
- Don't you think?
- Come to what?
Me deciding if you live or die.
Captain, I don't know
what you've heard...
Hamund pulls you out of bed...
marches you down to the wrecks
to look for a stash
of stolen pearls.
And somehow, only you and your dog
make it back alive.
Quite a moment.
Jack Rackham
with nothing to say.
Had I a shrewd
quartermaster right now,
he would tell me that
can't let what you did stand.
He would say an offense
like that
demanded an example
be made of both of you.
The bloodier the better.
But today,
I'm a little less worried
about perception
than I used to be.
As long as I hold that fort,
doesn't really matter.
So the street
will know what you did.
They will know you betrayed your
brothers for a woman.
That story will spread
far and wide
and you'll never sail
beneath the black again.
You'll sit in this place and rot
with the rest of the whores.
Something tells me that'll
sting worse than dying.
Loyalty, Jack.
It's supposed to mean something.
It does to me, anyway.
Oh.
Love what you've
done with the place.
Here she comes.
Cazadora.
Marco Fernandez, captain.
Marco Fernandez, capitán.
St, Augustine.
Tobacco trade.
If I'm not mistaken,
you told him to name us
anything but a tobacco
trader, did you not?
I did.
He means to prove that
that ship is not guardacosta.
That it's here for
the same reason we are.
The Urca.
That ship lets us pass,
he will have managed to both
renew the men's lust for gold
and their faith in his judgment.
Hello.
All hands to their stations.
Quietly, if you please.
At 300 yards, we open fire.
Time and again
he gambles with our lives.
That is, when he's not
taking them in cold blood.
And once more
his influence grows.
And we're at his mercy
with no way to challenge him.
No, sir.
It only looks that way.
Turn us around slowly, boys.
They need to think
we're just drifting.
Range?
Hundred yards, Captain.
- Open.
- Come right a few degrees.
- Aye, Captain.
We only get one shot at this.
We miss, we die.
- Clear, tack hull.
- Range?
Approaching 200 yards, Captain.
All crews, fire on my mark.
Steady.
Almost there.
Captain Flint.
As quartermaster,
I hereby accuse you
of tyrannical crimes
against your crew.
All crews, fire!
Belay that order!
Your duties as a member of this crew
have reached an end.
Take a seat.
Beginning with the murders
of Mr. Singleton,
Billy Bones,
and Mr. Gates.
What exactly do you hope
to accomplish by doing this?
In your case,
Mr. Silver, justice.
Once Dufresne exposes Flint's lies
in their totality,
the crew are gonna want
answers from you, too.
And as I explained
to Mr. Dufresne,
it's his word against Flint's.
Why would anyone believe him?
I hold in my hand a letter
written by Mr. Gates
confessing his knowledge
and complicity in
the captain's myriad crimes.
We're going to lose them.
We don't have time for this.
As well as his knowledge
of the captain's continued treachery
up to and including
his plan to steal
a portion of the treasure
fleet proceeds for himself.
I gave you all an order!
Fire!
Mr. Logan.
It's in Mr. Gates's hand.
Where are you going?
Justice, thief.
This time there's
no escaping it.
You're welcome.
Raise the sails.
We're going home.
Who's shooting?!
Sorry.
Had to be done.
There's no running now.
The Ranger's coming about.
The Spaniards have got
men in the rigging.
Fire, Mr. Dufresne.
Everything you've got.
Don't waste this moment.
All cannons, open fire!
Open fire!
Reload!
Ready with this cannon!
Fire!
The Ranger's opened fire!
Again!
...Fire!
She's coming about!
Fire!
Below!
To your stations!
Set sail!
Doctor! Doctor!
No-man's-land.
There was a time when
stopping halfway across this bridge
would have been
unthinkable to you.
How things change.
I can see that.
Max, I know we haven't spoken,
but I just want you
to know how sorry I am...
Don't.
You have nothing
to be sorry about.
I was standing between
you and your dreams for this place.
You did what you had to do.
I thought you said
this place was just sand.
Sand has its virtues.
On sand, nothing is fixed.
Nothing is permanent.
And fates change so quickly.
Yesterday Captain Hornigold
was immovable from that fort
and Captain Vane was a beggar.
Now look at them today.
Yesterday I was a whore
of little consequence,
easily dismissed,
easily forgotten.
Today I am a madam
with an income and allies
and a woman who has learned the most
important of lessons.
Never let anyone stand in between you
and your ambitions.
Thank you for teaching it to me.
Ma'am, they're ready.
Congratulations on the launch
of your endeavor, by the way.
Today you have everything
you have ever wanted.
I suppose we can only guess
what tomorrow will bring.
They think it'll be a while
before she sails again.
In the meantime,
you and I have been charged
with provoking this whole mess.
Why am I still alive?
Why didn't you kill me?
Get him up.
Told you I was certain about
my information regarding the Urca.
Unfortunately, you and I
failed to take into account the weather.
The Urca de Lima wrecked
at sea last night.
Dashed by the storm.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player