__
GATES: Singleton, he has the votes
to remove you as captain.
They think he has any idea how
to put money in their pockets?
Landfall. We're home.
- SILVER: Is this English soil?
- LOGAN: It was once.
- Whose is it?
- Ours. (Laughs)
You screwed me tonight.
Flint, his captaincy, I had an interest.
When the sea grows rough,
you come to Max.
L'Urca de Lima.
Total cargo of $5 million.
Take them into custody.
What happened with Richard?
Someone tore from this log
the very page necessary
to discover that prize
and then stoked your resentment
to make himself your captain.
It's the stolen page.
MAX: A whore for every
finger on your hand,
but your eyes keep drifting to this.
I think I have something
you might like to buy.
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
(Birds chirping)
(Chatter)
When my father still lived here,
this place was a fucking mess.
Men just fucked in tents,
threw their shit in the streets.
I wonder if he didn't notice
everyone living like animals
or if he just didn't care.
Why all this talk of your father?
A man-o'-war was spotted yesterday.
Royal Navy.
What if today's the day?
What if Scott
is downstairs right now
waiting to give me the news?
The British are back.
Decamp from Nassau.
And then what?
Then they blockade the island,
choke off trade.
A few crews will resist,
but how long can they survive
without my father's support?
One by one their numbers
will dwindle.
The fort will be abandoned.
Soldiers will storm the beach.
By the time the smoke clears,
my father will have arrived.
First time he's set foot
here in five years
waving the royal commission
that his bribes purchased
and lording over the place.
Round of applause,
the new governor.
Somewhere in London, some foul
fuck will get news of all of this,
light his pipe and say,
"Finally, all is right again
in Nassau."
You say this as if it is certain.
Perhaps you can buy this place.
Nassau will need an inn.
Max could be your partner.
There is no finer host in the world.
How will Mr. Noonan feel
when he hears of this plan?
I think maybe soon
what Mr. Noonan feels
will be of no concern to me.
- (Knocking)
- Yes?
It's Scott. Can you let Mistress Guthrie
know she's needed?
I'll be down in a minute.
I think, perhaps, you may be
a little longer than that.
Viens ici.
(Giggling)
- (Dog barking)
- (Man shouting)
- (Men laughing)
- (Chicken clucking)
Where is he?
Says he wants to be the first
one Flint sees when it's done.
Prize master's in the tent.
(Men cheering)
MAN:
Show us the color of the gold!
(Men shouting)
Rum and snatch for each and all.
- (Cheering)
- Gentlemen, I understand your excitement,
but do we really think
it is a good idea
to open up what are,
to be fair, depleted reserves
and start spending money
we haven't earned yet?
- MAN: Money we haven't earned yet?
- DUFRESNE: Gentlemen.
(Men cheering)
MAN:
Gold for the whores!
(Laughing)
GATES:
Billy.
Billy. Billy.
Jesus.
What did I do?
MAN:
Have some whores!
(Men cheering)
MAN:
Drinks and whores!
We don't like thieves.
Beg pardon?
You shouldn't steal.
That's what happens.
I see that.
I'm hungry.
All right. I'll see what I can do.
You mustn't steal.
He wasn't no thief, Randall.
(Laughing)
Here.
Not now.
Don't be stupid.
The schedule is here on the island.
How do you know?
Whoever stole it
came back to read the log,
find out exactly
what it was they had.
Someone on that deck
out there is our thief.
Well, it can't be one of our men.
How would they have
known to look for it?
And the men taken from the
prize were all searched.
What?
The cook.
I found him hiding in the armory
standing over a dead body.
Said it was suicide.
Did you search him?
SILVER:
Hold that boat.
- There will be another.
- I'm sure you're right, but...
I understand everyone
wants to get laid,
but we disembark by seniority.
Perhaps if you made
the men some food,
it would take the edge off the
spree they're about to go on.
Careful.
Unless you want everybody
to know what he's got.
Where the fuck is he going?
Ah!
CREW:
Ooh!
(Screams)
(Laughing)
That kid must really
want to get laid.
(Laughs)
Come on, give us your hand.
(Bird squawking)
I know it's late.
(Coins clink)
For Max.
What happened to you?
She worked late
with the Ranger crew.
Noonan know about this?
He's just gonna let it go?
50 pieces they paid her.
That's worth a few nicks
to the hull, wouldn't you say?
I have news.
Please tell me it's the good kind.
A crew of 10 have just
arrived out of Carolina.
Captain's waiting for us
at the warehouse.
He bring a prize with him?
50 barrels of tobacco and a
fluyt's worth of rare silks.
Let's go say hello.
I had hoped we'd have a word first
before we start work.
You walked away from me last night
and did something very foolish
to a man whose temper you can
no longer afford to provoke.
He moved on Flint.
I responded.
And what did that accomplish?
It made me feel better.
Eleanor,
you can never forget
who these men are.
They are not our friends.
They are not our subjects.
They want your father's business.
That is the only reason we do not
find their knives at our throats.
Tell me you understand.
Be honest, is it bad?
5,000 pesos in pearls.
Don't leave much in the reserves.
An investment, if you'll allow.
Good morning, Captain.
What are you up to, Jack?
There's been a development.
It seems that Captain Flint
has for weeks
been chasing a piece of information
that would enable the bearer
to know the precise whereabouts
of the Spanish treasure galleon
Urca de Lima.
And you know this how?
Because the thief
who stole it from him
has offered to sell it to me.
- You've met this person?
- His agent.
The thief's too smart
to show us his face.
He's asking 5,000 pesos
for a chance at five million.
I'm sorry,
have I said something funny?
You'd empty our reserves
to purchase what?
A scrap of paper someone told
you may be worth something?
They have no reason to lie to me.
They have 5,000 reasons
to lie to you.
Please tell me
I don't need to explain further.
Well, I doubt the crew
will share your sentiments
with what they stand to gain.
Unless you have a score
of your own to present.
Or are we to sit here patiently waiting
for Eleanor Guthrie to arrive,
place one at our feet?
Remind me how many leads
have the Guthries brought us
since you two had your falling out?
Please tell me I don't
have to explain further.
Find me when Singleton's
back and it's done.
The fuck's his problem?
He thought that Flint
was the only one
standing in the way
of his being crowned king.
He thought wrong.
Hey, friend, can you point
me to the blacksmith?
- Which way to the butcher?
- In the square.
I need a new shirt.
Hey, anybody know
where the cook went?
- That way.
Oh, Jesus.
What do we do?
Don't get too comfortable
in there, you twats.
A couple of fucks
and you're back on this beach.
We got a score to chase.
(Rhythmic slapping)
I want to fuck, Max.
- Max.
- Yes?
- I want to fuck.
- You know the rules.
That bitch keeps you all to herself.
And she pays for the privilege.
It's not fair.
(Breathing heavily)
It's not... it's not f...
it's... it's not fair.
It's not...
- What are you doing?
- Apologies.
Don't let me interrupt.
Wait your fucking turn!
Certainly.
BOTH:
Outside!
Okay.
Okay, this is going to require
a bit of an explanation.
Fuck.
Come back later, mon cher.
(Muttering)
Have you no decency?
Who do you think you are that
you can cost me this money?
Necessary, I'm afraid.
We have a problem.
- Flint's onto me.
- And so you come here?
- What if you were followed?
- No, I was careful.
Careful? You just told
me you've been caught.
Well, that's true.
You fucked me.
There's no need to panic.
We can still make the deal and...
And then what?
How long before Flint discovers
I had a part in this?
When a man is being fucked,
he wants to know
whose cock was in him.
True, but by that time,
these two cocks will be in a
boat halfway to Port Royal.
Port Royal?
After I get payment,
we meet at the boat
in the cove and leave tonight.
Unless there's something
else keeping you here.
MAN: I was told Richard Guthrie
was the fence in Nassau.
Brought his ships down from Boston.
Hides his plunder in sugar barrels.
But unless he went
and sprouted tits,
you're not him.
(Laughs)
I'm his daughter Eleanor.
I run the operation here
alongside my retainer Mr. Scott.
A schoolgirl and a sugar monkey.
We pay in coin, trade, or credit
the moment your goods
enter my warehouse.
And while we're off selling it at
rates you couldn't hope to match,
you and your men get to enjoy the many
pleasantries Nassau has to offer.
And what will that cost us exactly?
- Around four reales on the dollar.
- Half our profits go to you?
At first.
But the more you earn,
the better the terms.
Oh, you enjoy setting terms, do you?
Since I sprouted tits.
Well, Port Royal is not that far.
I think I'll keep
my haul and my profits.
- No offense.
- None taken.
Though you might want to keep
that decision to yourself.
And why is that?
Because the last fool
who turned her down
was never seen or heard from again.
Though the same can't
be said for his plunder.
A seller brought it to Mistress Guthrie
the very next day.
And that seller would be you?
Well, perhaps you'll find me
more of a match
than that other craven bastard.
James Bridge of the Demeter.
Charles Vane of the Ranger.
The Negro gentleman
takes our goods, does he?
- Come on. We're off. Come on.
- Let's go.
That wasn't necessary.
But fun, nonetheless.
I'd like a word in private.
We have some business
to get sorted.
Wonderful.
I don't have time for this,
so if there's something...
I want to talk about our business.
I noticed lately that my crew
hasn't been given the same
kind of information from you
about potential prizes
that we once did.
That others currently do receive.
You've noticed that, have you?
I believe it to be personal
and I'd like to put an end to it.
Things were better... are better
for the both of us
when you and I are on
the same side of things.
I would like to return to that.
You have an odd way of showing it.
Excuse me?
I have responsibilities here...
commerce to oversee,
profits to maintain.
The idea that I would
withhold valuable leads
for personal reasons
is fucking absurd.
Is that so?
I stopped providing you
with intelligence
because I don't like
the way you run your ship.
Your men are undisciplined, unruly.
For as much money as they bring in,
they cause twice as much damage.
They're fucking animals.
You encourage it.
And that makes you
a poor investment.
You expect me to believe
this is about business?
I don't give a fuck what you believe.
I know that last night...
last night,
you killed a member of a crew
that has value to me
in order to depose a captain
that has value to me.
And now not only do you
expect to be forgiven,
you wish to be rewarded for it.
Flint's so weak he needed
protection from you
and I'm the poor investment?
From where I sit, you coming here
means one of two things.
Either you're under the
illusion that with Flint gone,
I have no other choice
than to give you what you want
or you think because
you and I used to fuck,
you can cross me
without any consequences.
(People shouting)
I'm not sure which of
the two is more stupid.
Be careful, Eleanor.
Fuck you, Charles.
(Shouting continues)
MAN:
Captain says we're gonna be rich!
Son of a bitch. You made it.
I did.
What happened?
I thought Singleton had the votes.
Turns out Mr. Singleton
was unfit for command.
We have more pressing
issues to attend to.
Shall I wait?
Captain Vane was just leaving.
Hey, what the fuck
happened on that ship?
Where is Singleton?
Fruit. Fruit.
Tits. Tits.
Plant. Plant.
It's the fucking same.
Yes, Captain, I'm sure
they look the same.
What the hell are you doing?
Watch this.
As I explained, this is the
work of Adriaen Hanneman.
A masterwork, unmistakably.
This is an abomination.
To suggest that the value of one
has any bearing on the other
simply strains
the very bounds of reason.
Fruit. Fruit.
Tits. Tits.
I love this town.
I'm so glad you're entertained.
I'm sorry, weren't we supposed
to be looking for the cook?
- We are. Any luck?
- No, and I've looked all over.
Meanwhile, you haven't moved
from this stump all day.
Billy,
take a load off.
Fruit. Fruit. Tits. Tits.
Plant. Plant.
I've always been straight
with you, haven't I?
Never lied. Never hedged.
You did the right thing.
Yesterday when you sent me with
the captain to Harbour Island,
you told me to restrain him
if he tried to go too far.
I did.
Singleton wasn't a thief.
Flint baited him into that fight,
then he killed him.
That's not going too far?
Singleton was no saint.
That's not the point.
The point is I lied to my own crew
to protect the captain.
You lied to protect the crew.
You saw the Scarborough, mate.
You know what's coming.
We can't thieve forever.
Flint said we need a king.
Is that what you think?
I think we need something.
Five million pieces
is a good place to start.
I guess we just keep looking, then.
No need.
- There's a man up there.
- Where?
- The brothel.
- Ah, the brothel.
Take them inside.
Why are we following the appraiser?
Because if I'm this cook and
I want to sell the schedule
and leave this place a rich man,
I need two things...
I need a boat and I need
a method of payment.
BILLY:
A method of payment?
What about gold coins?
Gold is too heavy,
attracts too much attention.
So I need a bill of exchange
- or...
- Jewels.
I was thinking pearls.
And I'd want to know the exact
value of what I'm getting.
- (Music playing)
- (Chatter)
LOGAN:
Mr. Gates.
Hello, boys.
Where the fuck have you two been?
(Laughs)
Come join us.
We'll be right with you.
Any chance he's up
for a quick fuck?
With Anne Bonny standing guard?
Excellent luster and orient.
Rest assured, young lady,
the quality is quite good.
200 pieces of eight at any clearinghouse
in the civilized colonies.
And the rest of them?
- No offense.
- None taken.
Sure I can't suck your cock
while you do that?
Uh, thank you, no.
Use my hand? Sing you a song?
Something worth paying money for?
Fucking peepers.
My father's under arrest?
A fugitive, technically.
I have him on the Walrus.
He was injured in the escape,
but he'll survive.
Unfortunately, the same can't
be said for his reputation.
This is impossible.
He's been bribing
the Lords Proprietor for years.
They've agreed to make
him governor here.
It would appear they've had
a change of heart.
You don't seem concerned about this.
I never much liked your father.
Too caught up in appearances.
She's not talking about
your opinion of the man.
Once news spreads
of Mr. Guthrie's arrest,
our operation here
will no longer be viable.
No legitimate port will have us.
And his ships, the ships that
take your cargo to market,
if they are not impounded already,
will be on their way
back to Boston.
Captain, we are finished here.
Under normal circumstances,
I'd agree with you.
- However...
- However what?
Let me tell you a story
about a Spaniard named Vazquez.
Happy to be of service.
Thank you for your patience
in these matters.
You understand my partner
simply wishes to be careful.
I wouldn't fault him
in the slightest.
Now, shall we discuss delivery?
The wrecks at sundown.
Once he sees the pouch
with the seal unbroken,
he will hand over the page.
Is something wrong?
It's unclear
which is more appealing,
your beauty or your intelligence.
You are very kind, monsieur.
Well, let's not get carried away.
You.
Is there a problem, Captain?
She doesn't have your page.
Flint does.
He killed Singleton,
took it off his body.
His crew's skipping around the island
like the prize is as good as theirs.
That is impossible.
My partner has the page.
What?
Mr. Singleton is not the seller,
I assure you.
- What did you just say?
- RACKHAM: Charles.
Shut up, Jack.
You really want to keep pushing this?
- Play me for a fool?
- You are mistaken.
- Yeah, the fuck I am.
- (Whimpers)
I need a weapon.
Tell me the truth.
- The page is gone.
- No.
Do you have a candlestick
or perhaps a heavy shoe?
- That'll do.
- VANE: Play me for a fucking fool?
- MAX: You are mistaken.
- VANE: Yeah, the fuck I am.
- Don't fucking lie to me!
- (Whimpers)
She isn't lying, Charles.
Flint is.
- What?
- He lost the page.
So what does he do?
He bluffs.
He makes Singleton
the thief and kills him
to prevent counterargument,
putting a tidy end
to his mutiny in the process,
then hopes he can recover it
before anyone's the wiser.
Honestly, Charles, are we
to believe that Singleton,
while conspiring with you
to depose Flint,
was using this whore to try and
bilk your crew out of its money?
Say what you want about Singleton,
but he was neither
that clever nor that dumb.
Now will you please put her down so
we can complete our transaction?
Is that what you thought?
You could fuck us out of our money
and then hide behind Eleanor?
You think I'd really let that happen?
You think I'm that fucking pathetic?
Jesus, lady.
(Choking)
(Shouts)
Unless Mr. Singleton rose from
the grave to eavesdrop on us...
it would appear
she's telling the truth.
(Gasps)
If he's wrong about this,
he'll answer to our crew.
If you're lying,
you'll answer to me.
(Max coughing)
Yes, all right.
(Panting)
The Urca de Lima?
That's correct.
You're talking about
a floating castle.
No one has ever taken a treasure
galleon like that as a prize.
Let me worry about hunting her.
It's what comes after
for which I'll need your help.
After?
Why return at all to Nassau?
With money like that and my father
out of business, why not run?
What's coming our way
can't be outrun.
But with the money
I strip from the Hulk,
we could add 50 guns to the fort.
We could build ships
to defend our shores
and train new men to sail them.
We could work the land,
grow crops and raise cattle.
Then whoever arrives
on our shores first,
be it England or Spain,
will be in for a most
unwelcome surprise.
- A nation of thieves.
- (Laughing)
You have your doubts?
Of turning pirates
into farmers and soldiers?
Of fighting a war against Whitehall
from a sliver in the Atlantic?
Doubt, Captain Flint,
does not begin to describe
how I am feeling.
If there's to be a war, that
will be Whitehall's choice.
I'd settle for a pardon,
title on lands,
and a governor that I could trust.
And so would most
of the men out there.
They're not animals, Mr. Scott.
They're men starved of hope.
Give that back to them,
who's to say what could happen?
Why do this?
Why here?
Odysseus,
on his journey home to Ithaca,
was visited by a ghost.
The ghost tells him
that once he reaches his home,
once he slays all his enemies
and sets his house in order,
he must do one last thing
before he can rest.
The ghost tells him
to pick up an oar
and walk inland.
And keep walking
until somebody mistakes
that oar for a shovel.
For that would be
the place that no man
had ever been troubled by the sea.
And that's where he'd find peace.
In the end, that's all I want.
To walk away from the sea
and find some peace.
(Door opens)
I think we found it.
Found what?
The Urca's schedule
was taken from me.
When were you planning
on mentioning that?
Everything's under control.
We're close to recovering it.
Vane just met with Frasier
at the brothel.
I assume he's the buyer.
We missed the thief, but he's
using a whore as a go-between.
I left Billy
to keep an eye on things.
If we get moving, there's half a
chance to get in front of this.
Find the cook...
(Voice fades)
(Door opens)
Good.
Maybe you can get her to talk.
- I'm fine.
- Huh, the fuck you are.
She nearly got herself
killed by Captain Vane.
I want to know why.
Leave us alone, Noonan.
Come on.
- Max, I...
- I'm glad you are here.
I was going to send word for you.
You and I have a decision to make
and it must be made right now.
I'm about to receive a great deal
of money for a service I provided.
Max, I need you
to give me the schedule.
Flint's schedule.
When you were talking
this morning about being free
from Noonan,
that's what you meant, wasn't it?
How do you know this?
It doesn't matter.
Max, Flint needs that page.
The money he can get
from his prize,
it can give this place a future.
It can give us a future here.
If the page isn't delivered to Vane,
he will kill me.
I can protect you.
Scott can protect you.
You have to trust me.
Leave with me.
- What?
- I have a boat waiting.
I will have enough money
for us to start anew.
- But I can't leave here.
- Why not?
Because I've spent my life
trying to build something here.
It's all I have.
I can't just walk away.
It is not all you have!
Eleanor, this place is just sand.
It cannot love you back.
You know this.
You must know this.
Your father left you.
Your mother was taken from you.
Everyone you have
ever loved you have lost
and it terrifies you.
But not me.
I will never, ever leave you.
I love you.
- (Knocks)
- GATES: Miss Guthrie.
- You brought them here?
- I...
Come with me. Right now.
The boat is waiting.
We can be free of this place.
We can have a life together.
And it can start this very minute.
All you have to do is say yes.
Set us both free.
Come in.
(Door opens)
Max, I need you to tell me
where the page is.
And if I don't, then what?
This doesn't have to go badly.
I want her to say it.
I want her to say that
she would sit there and watch
as you beat the answer
out of me to save this place.
Say it.
The wrecks at sundown.
- Max, please.
- Get the fuck out.
I meant what I said.
I can protect you.
Get the fuck out!
- (Sobbing)
- (Door closes)
(Men chattering)
- Frightened, Jack?
- Please.
There's nothing in there
but opium addicts,
lunatics, and men who thought
themselves too good to wear a condom.
The pearls.
He says you give me the pearls.
Did he say anything else?
No. I want him out here.
Captain.
I know you can hear me!
You want your money,
you show your fucking face!
That's the only way this gets done.
Captain, I'm afraid
our friend out there
has all the leverage in
this particular situation.
Now, we can rail and shout
and stamp our feet,
but that doesn't change the fact
that unless we give this fellow...
(Groans)
You were saying?
Now, come out here and face me
or these pearls go back
where they belong!
Fuck.
RACKHAM:
Charles, it is important
this deal goes through tonight.
This is a potential prize
that changes everything for us.
- Do not scuttle it by...
- (Soft clatter)
He says you give me the pearls.
(Gunshot echoes)
Ah!
(Screams)
(Gasps)
(Coughing)
(Grunts)
- Where's the page?
- You can't have it.
Not at the moment.
And, please, we should go.
Where have you hidden it?
You're looking at it.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Well, I couldn't be certain I would
escape both the madman and you,
so I took drastic measures
for the sake of my survival.
Your schedule is up here.
Fuck!
You don't have to do this.
Mr. Noonan has men at your door.
And Guthrie's put
three more downstairs.
Vane can't get to you here.
I know.
But I cannot stay.
Will you help me?
(Sniffles)
Meet our thief.
- Why is he still alive?
- It's a long story.
Do you mind if we stash
him here for the night?
Billy can stand guard.
Flint will want
our answer in the morning.
(Pouring liquid)
I know you don't approve of this,
but I need to do this.
I need it.
Please.
Stay with me.
All right.
(Sighs)
- (Drums beating)
- (Whooping and cheering)
(Fortepiano playing)
(Playing)
(Horse whinnying)
(Stops playing)
(Door opens)
Take off your boots.
I'll boil some water.
(Grunts)
(Exhales)
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player