Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
I'm not wrong about Flint.
- To him we're all disposable.
- I don't believe that.
That's because you don't know about
Mrs. Barlow.
You found the schedule.
What if I forgo payment
for the schedule
in exchange for my share
of the prize?
We'll need some
additional items.
- New guns... 12-pounders.
- You'll have it.
Without the Urca
we have nothing.
Without Vane
we don't have the Urca.
Our friend tried to protect you.
You left anyway.
- Why?
- How did you feel when
she threw you aside?
Eleanor, wait.
- Listen to me carefully.
- You are finished.
Unless you decide to join
the crew of Captain Flint.
Looks like she just
gave us a ship.
Ship with no captain.
- So sorry he did this to you.
- He didn't do this to me.
You did.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Captain Gates.
It's time.
First item for the council
concerns leadership.
As you know, I've been
asked to serve as captain
of the Ranger when next we sail.
Obviously that means less
time spent with you idiots.
So...
you will need somebody to act
as your quartermaster in the meantime.
Unless anybody's got
any better ideas,
I was thinking Billy Bones.
I thought so.
Billy.
Ahem.
Next item... careening.
Bad start, Billy.
She's long overdue.
If we're gonna win the Urca,
the Walrus must be shipshape.
That means we tip her.
Plain and simple.
The question is,
where do we do the tipping?
Wherever there's plenty of rum.
As always, the ship's
account is open.
Rum casks and Mr. Simpson's buttered
oranges are on their way.
And the pigs are being readied
for Mr. Silver's spit.
Now, to return to the issue
of location.
What about the fuck tent?
That's probably something
we can discuss.
Fuck tent! Fuck tent!
Mr. De Groot.
You may not like
what I have to say,
but if it remains unsaid,
I fear the worst.
I've inspected the shoreline
proposed by the captain
for this undertaking
and it is simply unsuitable
to the task at hand.
The anchorage is poor.
The incline too steep.
I cannot endorse it.
The risk for calamity is too high.
With the crew's assent,
I ask for time to find
a more suitable beach.
And delay our efforts
by how long?
Two weeks?
A month?
A clean hull
means an extra knot
or two in speed,
five degrees or more
in coming about.
It's essential
to the job at hand.
If we had weeks,
we'd surely take them.
But we must sail within days
if we are to meet the Urca.
Now, Mr. De Groot's
concerns are valid...
but they come at a price.
$5 million in Spanish gold,
to be exact.
All those in favor
of the captain's plan
to careen here near the bay?
Aye!
It would appear
the ayes have it.
Nay.
Mr. Morley's dissent is
noted along with Mr. De Groot's.
All right,
let's beach this bitch.
Yeah, quick question, then. Where are
we on the issue of the fuck tent?
- Yeah!
- This job is gonna happen fast.
That means more risk,
more danger.
Now you've put a great
deal of trust in me
to serve in Mr. Gates' absence,
and I take that seriously.
So given the potential
for distraction and delay
at a time that we need
to be at our best,
perhaps we can all
agree to forgo,
just this once, a fuck tent.
You shouldn't have.
Stale winds, still waters.
Don't be such an old lady.
The men will rise to it.
What say you,
Mr. Quartermaster?
You think it's a good idea?
Yeah, I think the captain
knows what he's doing.
That's because you don't
know about Mrs. Barlow.
Who's Mrs. Barlow?
Number of years back,
before you crewed up with us,
Flint had us hunting
a merchant ship,
the Maria Aleyne.
Sephardic trade...
gold, pearls, jewels.
"More than we'd ever know
what to do with," he said.
But that's Flint's gift,
isn't it?
Always knows just what
to say to push us harder,
further, make us all
pull together for the cause.
We tracked that bitch for months
without refitting or careening,
till finally we spotted her.
We lost good men taking her
for a haul nowhere near
what Flint had promised.
While I was exploring the hold,
I chanced upon a cabin
and that's when I heard it.
'Twas a man and a woman
begging for their lives.
"Spare us,
and our fortune's yours."
For a moment, I thought
all our shares
were gonna be worth
a whole lot more.
But that's when
the screams began.
And when I watched
the murderer leave,
I saw him plain.
Did you tell anyone?
Gates.
He was unmoved,
to say the least.
"Just one rich bastard less
in the world," he said.
At the time, I'll admit,
I took his point.
But days later we come ashore.
I see a lady waiting for Flint.
The rest of the crew thought she's
just some fancy bit of Puritan tail.
But when Flint reaches her,
two words escape his lips.
"They're dead."
Hunting the Maria Aleyne
was never about money.
It was an execution.
All those men we lost
taking her,
they died so Flint could settle
some personal vendetta for her.
You watch.
Good men will die
for some hidden agenda.
The Barlow woman's agenda.
Mark my words, Billy.
It's all happening again.
Will you be staying long?
I have to get back.
If you're upset with me,
I'd appreciate you saying so.
You know why I'm upset.
Because I read to him?
There's a whole shelf
full of books.
Why'd you have
to read him that one?
Perhaps because
I am no longer willing
to bury it on a shelf and
pretend it has no meaning for me.
That book is something
I shared with Thomas.
I just missed it.
Our life then
when he was alive.
I can feel myself forgetting it
and I don't want to forget it.
This place, this life
that we've been living here,
it doesn't feel like
living anymore.
I can't be alone
in feeling this way.
Some part of you
must feel it, too.
Things will get better here.
I promise you they will.
Here you go.
Christ.
One week without a ship
and you go completely to hell.
Is it too much to ask
that you not pick a fight
over every insult
thrown our way?
Especially when I'm out there swallowing
what little pride I have left
trying to set things right.
I see we've graduated to opium.
Miss Guthrie has
dealt us quite a blow.
But we still have assets.
Eight loyal men, my wits,
and an unshakable captain.
I'm doing what I can
to regain us our livelihood,
but once that's done,
this crew, such as it is,
will need its captain back.
See what you can do
about finding him.
Fuck you, Jack.
It was an isolated incident.
No cause for concern.
Your girl humiliated one of
this island's strongest earners,
threatened his crew
with embargoes
so they had no choice
but to toss him aside.
I've had three other
captains approach me
all asking the same question...
who's next to lose
their livelihood
because they crossed her
on the wrong day?
No one is next.
Every morning for months now
when I walk the beach into town,
I see Captain Lilywhite
standing on his stoop
and jabbering away
to anyone who will listen
about the evils
of a centralized fence.
Arguing that this island
will never be free
until we all come together
to cast off the tyrannical yoke
of Queen Eleanor.
I see him out there, too.
And I have never seen
any more than three men
paying him any attention.
Half-wits,
all of them.
There were 12 of them
this morning.
This business with Vane
has changed things.
Get control of her,
Mr. Scott,
before it's too late.
Sail spotted.
The Andromache.
Captain Bryson is arriving
on the Andromache.
You'd best get down
to the beach.
What did Captain Hornigold want?
Let me guess.
The captains grousing
about last week
think I've lost
my grip on reason.
Fuck Hornigold.
Fuck the captains
and fuck anyone else
who doesn't like the way
I manage this place.
What we're about to attempt
with Captain Bryson,
it is very risky.
If he will not cooperate,
we cannot,
under any circumstances,
attempt to detain him.
- What makes you think I'd try?
- 'Cause I know you.
I know what you think
is at stake.
And I know you think you
cannot take no for an answer.
Why should I?
Eleanor, if you make a move
against Captain Bryson
or his ship,
you'll be making a move against
the Guthrie Trading Company.
A direct affront
to your grandfather
and his interests in Boston.
That ship belongs to him.
When he finds out
what you've done,
no one...
not I nor your father...
will able to protect you
from the consequences.
If Bryson balks,
we must let him go.
And the guns Flint needs?
What about them?
We'll find them some other way.
I never ask anything of you.
This I must insist on.
Tell me you understand.
I understand.
- How we doing?
- Ahead of schedule.
Ready to raise the keel.
I think we might actually pull it off.
We'll have Billy
to thank for that.
I have no idea how he's done it,
but he's kept them
to a schedule.
I don't think
I've ever seen a crew
work this fast and this hard.
A few more days,
we'll have the keel cleared
and tarred and she'll be ready
to go back into the water.
Excuse me, Captain.
That's it.
Secure these ropes.
Listen here,
you smart-mouthed fuck.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
I said I've got the shits. What part
of that don't you understand?
What's going on?
His rotten pig gave the lot of us
the bloody squirts.
It's possible it wasn't
the pig, you know.
Some people have
weak constitutions.
Hey!
Settle down.
Mmm. It's delicious.
It's likely as not
it wasn't the pig.
It's just something that's going around.
Get back to work.
Thank you.
I'm glad someone here likes...
What the fuck
did you do to that?
I cooked it...?
You absolutely did not.
The men seemed to think
it looked done.
Yes, well, they'd eat it raw if left
to their own devices.
That's awfully cynical.
Go get another pig.
Do exactly as I say.
Now you see how it can be?
When I'm made
to feel comfortable,
you are made to feel
le toucher de dieu.
It's like our bodies
are all made up of these
secret little
compartments, she says,
what's got pleasures
hidden inside 'em.
And it just takes someone
who knows how to unlock 'em.
That's it.
Your friends,
they have seen the reward
for gentle obedience.
If pleasure is what you want,
I assure you I can give it to you
if you let me.
Indeed.
- Captain Bryson.
- Mistress Guthrie.
I trust your passage
was comfortable.
My cargo will be inventoried
and off-loaded in the morning.
You'll find the books
in good order.
That's good to hear, but I was
hoping we could have a word.
Seeing as our every word only
prolongs my stay in this cesspool,
I trust you'll make it quick.
I thought it best
you heard from me first.
One of our crews intends
to hunt the Urca de Lima.
A move against a state asset?
And your father
hasn't quashed it?
- No, he hasn't.
- Why on earth not?
Why don't you ask him yourself?
He'll be in my tavern shortly.
I understood you meant
to hide his presence here.
We did until this morning.
Stand up, please, sir.
Once upon a time Mr. Scott
was my personal houseboy.
Until he proved himself worthy
of greater responsibility.
That earned him an education
which he then
passed on to my daughter.
And look where that's gotten me.
I'm afraid I still don't follow.
Captain Bryson commands the largest
of my supply ships.
My daughter needs
the guns from that ship
to arm Captain Flint
for his move against
the Spanish treasure galleon.
Parting Bryson
from his guns, however,
will require some convincing.
Evidently, Eleanor knows
better than to try to do it herself.
And how can she be sure
you won't betray her
and alert Captain Bryson
to the fact of your arrest?
Because Bryson would have no choice
but to liquidate our holdings here
and return me to Boston
a failure.
Therefore, whatever resentments
I might feel towards my daughter
and your friend the captain,
I must put aside.
Absorb the blow, as it were.
Like a rocky promontory.
At any rate, I have
a meeting to attend.
Shall we?
When I get my share
of that Spanish gold,
I'm going to fuck my way
through high society.
Nary a duchess's
snatch be uncharted.
What the fuck is this?
You said tie it to the palm.
That palm.
That one.
You tied it to
the wrong fucking tree.
Yes, it matters.
Jesus, fix it, will you, please?
Christ.
Give a man a little
bit of power.
What the fuck
difference does it make?
They're both trees, ain't they?
Agreed.
Quick fuck?
Shove over, Randall.
The shade's mine
for the next hour.
Don't want no arguments.
Did you bring me barnacle?
Oh, fuck.
Sorry, mate.
I forgot.
You promised.
For Betsy.
You're right.
Hold my spot.
What the...?
Hey, what the fuck
is your problem?
No problem at all, sir.
Just doing my share
for a worthy cause.
Oh, so what is it?
You tell me a story
and I'm supposed to fall
in lockstep behind you?
You wouldn't even
raise your voice
to question the captain's plan.
Didn't even consider it.
Maybe I considered it and
decided it was making sense.
Maybe.
Or maybe there's something
you'd rather not say out loud.
Thought when that lackey
Gates stepped aside,
we might have finally
gotten a quartermaster
who wasn't fully in
the captain's pocket.
Guess I was mistaken.
How exactly does the most feared
captain of the high seas
learn how to spice
and glaze a pig?
What do you care?
Well, I don't, really.
It's just that there's something
we need to talk about
and I thought a little
small talk beforehand
might be better
than diving right in.
What the hell
are you talking about?
What are we going
to do about Billy?
Beg your pardon?
As much as it pains
me to say this,
as he has been nothing but warm
and welcoming to me,
he appears to be
straining at the seams.
- I thought maybe we ought to have...
- Stop.
There is no we. Billy Bones is
a dutiful boatswain
who commands enormous respect
from his crew as well as from myself.
I trust him
a thousand times more
than I would a rodent
like yourself.
Understood.
- All that being said...
- Oh, Jesus Christ.
I saw Billy speaking
with Mr. Morley
late last week.
At night.
In secret.
That supposed to mean
something to me?
Well, he lied about
the page being blank.
I believe it's wearing on him.
I told you once,
I won't tell you again.
I trust Billy.
Trust me.
I'm purely in this for
myself and you know this.
I've no reason to tell you anything
other than the truth.
Both our futures depend on this.
I haven't decided yet
whether you even have a future.
But I can tell you this,
trying to play me
against my own crew
will not help your cause.
Turn your pig.
It's almost done.
- I can't do it, Jack.
- Of course you can.
You simply present my crew's haul
to Miss Guthrie as if it were your own.
You get a percentage.
Everybody wins.
I get caught selling
a grain of salt for you,
the girl puts my crew
on the outs same as you.
I just can't risk it.
It ain't you she has
a problem with, Jack.
Why stick with him?
It's a good question.
No, it's not.
There are other ships.
Had a few offers, have you?
Makes sense.
You'd be an asset to any crew.
Now ask how many offers
good old Jack has received
since our run-in
with the lady Guthrie.
My only assets are my wits,
and as the man who just lost
5,000 pesos
of his ship's own money,
they are ill-valued
at the moment.
Join another crew right now,
the only task
I will be trusted with is swabbing out
the piss buckets.
And that, my darling, I feel
compelled to state out loud,
life is simply
too fucking short!
What, you're angry with me, too?
Hey! Jack Rackham!
- Oh, for fuck's sake.
- A word.
I'm sorry, I'd prefer you made
an appointment. Quite a full day ahead.
You took one of my best
whores for your private use.
Every day she's not under
my roof fucking costs me money.
Ah, yes, but my crew
sees her as responsible
for the loss of a great deal
of their money.
They see this as a debt
being repaid, nothing more.
Well, I see it
as thieving bullshit.
Then I believe
we're at an impasse.
Disagreement without
prospect of resolution.
Fuck you, Jack.
Give me back the whore.
You'd take her back yourself
if you had the balls.
A few less men outside
that tent than yesterday,
which had fewer
than the day before.
Maybe I'll take you
up on that offer
sooner than later.
What the hell was that?
Do you have some problem with us
holding onto that whore?
You do realize she's the only thing keeping
what's left of our crew at our side.
Fuck you.
You want the guns
from my ship...
to hand over to a pirate?
That is correct.
Have you lost your mind?
You know as well as I do your family
would never approve of this.
What my family approves
or does not approve
rests solely on one thing...
Eleanor...?
Profit.
Eleanor's arranged
a plan to deliver them
quite a bit of it upon the success
of this operation.
Enough to assuage any fears they
may have about repercussions.
I find that hard to believe.
You're a brilliant
seaman, Dyfed.
But in this instance,
you're out of your depth.
Commerce in this place
requires bold moves.
I'm fortunate enough to have a daughter
who has found one for us.
Perhaps you're right.
Maybe I am out of my depth.
And yet this feeling persists.
And what feeling is that?
I wonder, Mr. Guthrie,
if this might have something to do
with His Majesty's Ship the Scarborough
currently docked at Harbour Island.
Docked outside your home.
My intent was to stop there first
and unload the slaves in my hold,
but when I saw her,
I thought better of it.
His Majesty's ships
often use my port for resupply.
What are you implying?
I'd like to speak
with your father alone.
Whatever you can say to him,
you can say to me.
Eleanor, it's all right.
Your father can handle this.
He'll get you those guns.
Perhaps.
I couldn't leave it to chance.
Let us be frank.
You and I both know
the low regard
in which your family
in Boston holds you.
Quite frank, it seems.
If I returned unarmed
and they find
that I did so under
these circumstances
with only your orders
as justification,
I'll be buried in a shallow grave
somewhere out in Cambridge.
And what exactly do you believe "these
circumstances" to be?
The Navy on your doorstep.
You and your daughter
supporting a plan
as reckless as this.
It would seem, sir, that something's gone
terribly wrong with the operation here
and you two are scrambling
to save yourselves.
Tell me I'm wrong.
Let me tell you
how wrong you are.
I knew you wouldn't approve.
But I couldn't let him leave here
without giving up those guns.
I'm sorry.
With everything
we've been through,
with everything
I've done for you...
- I'm doing this for us both.
- You lied.
Shame on you.
The guns are yours.
Mr. Hayes.
Truly something
to behold, this place.
You should be proud.
Come now, Mr. Scott.
It's as much your work
as Eleanor's.
What is this if not the moment
of your vindication?
It's time we got you back.
She'll get herself killed.
If she proceeds with
this Spanish galleon business,
attempting to steal
treasure from one empire
to finance a war
against another,
she will get herself killed.
Whether by English noose
or Spanish sword,
it's inevitable and you know it.
If she proceeds...
what did you say
to Bryson in that room?
Rest assured I had a plan.
Not just to end this insanity,
but to contend with
what comes next.
To keep her safe.
I don't envy you.
You know that she'll stop at nothing
to save this place.
A place where she matters.
A place where you matter.
Except that in your heart
you know the truth.
Places like this
aren't meant to last.
Help me, Mr. Scott.
Please.
Help me save her from herself.
Well, hello.
There's no need to be afraid.
You could help me if you like.
Aren't you the Gladwin boy?
Does your father know
you're out here all alone?
I can take you to him.
Oh!
Witch!
Captain. Visitor.
The guns are yours.
Captain Bryson's preparing
to off-load them as we speak.
Mr. O'Malley is on
the lookout to ensure he complies.
Take a seat.
To our endeavor
and success close at hand.
What's wrong?
Your father step out of line?
It's Mr. Scott.
In order to guarantee
Captain Bryson's acquiescence,
I put a plan into place
without Mr. Scott's knowledge.
I lied to him.
Betrayed his trust.
I didn't want to, but I just
didn't think he would understand.
Well, you can't expect him to.
Nobody will believe
it's possible until we show them.
But when that day comes,
you know what they'll say?
They'll say
that it was inevitable.
Get back!
Back off! Back off!
Get away!
Everyone, get up to the beach now!
Come on!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- Let's go!
She's going!
Get out!
Oh, shit.
Randall!
- I'll go.
- Captain, there's no time.
The mainmast is holding
too much weight.
We have to cut her loose!
Save the mast.
Don't wait for me.
He's dug in.
Help me.
Me leg! Me leg!
Pull! Pull!
One, two, three, pull!
It's taking too long.
How much time do we have?
We don't.
Billy, the time is now!
It's no bloody use.
Your belt.
Give me your belt.
- Billy.
- Cut the ropes!
- Billy!
- All right!
Right.
Do it!
Bite.
Bite down on it.
Hold on, Randall.
Hold on.
All right, pull!
Shit.
I talked to De Groot.
You did everything you could.
Not everything.
I should have stopped Flint.
Honestly, son,
how could you have done that?
Careful, Billy.
Flint pushed it through and
I went along when I knew better.
Because you know
what's at stake here.
You know he's right.
That's not why I...
It's because I'm afraid of him.
Billy and Morley.
That night on the ship,
what were they talking about?
Well, I didn't hear much,
but it sounded like they
were talking about a woman.
Somebody Barlow.
Success?
Would you mind?
The music you were playing,
that's Purcell's Chaconne
if I'm not mistaken.
You have an educated ear.
My father employed a tutor
for all his children
so that they might learn
to appreciate music.
I took to it the least
of my siblings.
But for reasons beyond me,
some of it stuck.
There's a pronounced
sense of sadness
in Purcell's pieces.
Considering your circumstances,
I can understand their appeal.
And what is it you think you understand
of my circumstances?
Truthfully,
I might know everything,
Mrs. Hamilton.
Don't be alarmed.
I have no intention of
disclosing your identity to anyone.
I'm sorry, sir. I think you have me
mistaken for someone else.
The portrait
in your room depicts you
alongside Lord Thomas Hamilton,
son of Alfred Hamilton,
the lord proprietor
of these Bahama Islands.
Forgive me.
I must have gotten
disoriented and wandered.
You see, I've had extensive dealings
with the earl over the years,
and so I'd long heard
of the tragedy
that befell his eldest son.
But Thomas's wife,
long rumored to be
the cheating sort,
had begun a torrid affair
with her husband's
closest friend,
a promising young officer
in His Majesty's Navy.
And upon discovering the affair,
Thomas went mad with grief.
His despair so great,
even the asylum couldn't
protect him from himself.
As for Thomas's wife,
she's said to have fled
London along with her lover.
Partly out of shame,
partly to escape retribution.
Given the facts at hand,
I am forced to assume
that the lover is none other
than our friend Captain Flint.
Please understand,
I raise this issue
not to disturb or harass you.
In fact, I wish to help you.
Help me?
I can only assume that
your exile in this place
has been less than ideal.
I understand how desperation
may have driven you here,
but perhaps it's time
you were offered a hand
and a return to civilization.
And you could offer me that?
Boston is quite a different animal
from London.
More forgiving of one's past
in a general sense.
And in this specific sense,
with my family's assistance,
one might find
total absolution there.
New identities.
A clean start.
A new life.
I could do that for you.
Why on earth would you?
Because I know what it is
to be judged unfairly.
And because
it's just possible that,
while I am uniquely situated
to offer you your freedom,
you may be able
to do the same for me.
Hello, Charles.
You've looked better.
Fuck you.
We're alone.
You don't have
to pretend with me.
The fuck did I ever do to you?
You made me look weak.
Standing beside you,
I was your lesser.
I was a girl.
From the moment you met me,
you must have known
I'd never settle for that.
For being less than.
That's why I loved you.
And you destroyed me.
I exposed you.
The weakness behind the mask.
The fear.
So much I have taken from you.
And yet still...
you know you could
take it all back.
You could be strong again.
You could resist me.
You could take this whole
fucking island from me.
You know exactly what
it is you need to do.
Where it is
you need to go to do it.
If only you weren't
so goddamn afraid.
Ain't this a sad sight?
Miss Guthrie should
have just had you killed.
It would have been
more merciful.
Now, are you going
to give me back me whore?
Jesus!
On my shoe!
Oh, fuck it.
Put him out of his misery.
Oh, for Christ...
Wait!
Listen to me!
The whorehouse,
I'll cut you in for half.
We'll be partners.
Please.
Do you know who I am, Pastor?
I do.
You're the reason this island
is infested with criminals.
God teaches us not to cheer
when others stumble.
In your case,
I may ask His forgiveness.
And what does God
say about redemption?
Accept His love
and you'll find it.
What if I was prepared
to go further?
Further?
Penance for my past sins.
Good works.
And they begin tonight.
Who's there?
Mr. Scott.
What are you doing here?
I thought you might use a hand.
Bastard's finally bringing in the first
of the guns.
Took him long enough.
He takes his cargo seriously.
You look tired.
Why don't I take over?
Miss Guthrie told me I was to see
those guns off with my own eyes.
I understand.
I brought the fiends
to this place.
Encouraged them.
Enriched them.
Empowered them.
It seems as though my penance
ought to be a simple one.
I will see to it
that they are cast
out of this place.
Soon.
And for good.
The Andromache.
It can't be.
Captain Bryson
hasn't had time to unload.
He didn't.
She's riding low.
Those guns are still on board.
What are we going to do?
Get them back.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player