Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Help.
Help me!
Help me, Lord.
I'm dying.
What is this?
Cancer?
Mother Mary, full of
grace, protect me
and guide me in
my hour of death.
It's a test.
Cut it down.
Shh.
Sue Snell
and Tommy Ross, come on.
Let's go, ladies! In the water!
Caps on, please!
Chris and Sue,
let's go!
I want you to keep it
in the air three times. All right?
We are graduating,
Ms. Desjardin.
Yeah, Sue!
Get that.
Don't be afraid
of the ball, ladies.
All right, here we go.
All right, Carrie White. Let's
get Carrie into the game.
You can't stand on the sidelines
all the time. Come on.
Whoo!
Carrie's serve.
Yeah, Carrie White!
Do it, Carrie!
Yeah, yeah.
Throw it.
Do it. Serve it.
Oh. Ow.
What the hell?
It's so funny,
Chris.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
You eat shit.
- No, he didn't.
- Yes, he did.
No, he didn't.
You're making it up.
He came up to me and I said, "Well,
you have to extend your hand..."
Now you're lying.
Help! Help! Help me!
Help me.
Get off me, you freak!
Please.
Oh, my God. Look what
you did to my shirt.
Please!
Stop! Stop!
Settle down.
I think I'm bleeding
to death. Please.
Oh, my God.
It's period blood.
I'm bleeding.
I think I'm dying.
What? Oh, my God.
Please help me!
It's just your period.
Just plug it up.
Help me!
Oh, God!
Oh! She got you.
Help me!
God, just plug it up!
Help!
Plug it up!
I'm sorry. No!
No!
Plug it up!
Girls, come on!
Move!
Ladies.
Oh, my God. Okay. All right.
Help me.
Okay, honey, stand up.
Let's get you cleaned up.
Help me, help me.
Oh, Carrie, come on.
Stand up.
Come on, can you stand up?
It hurts! It hurts!
It hurts! Something's not right.
Something's not right.
Okay, okay. What are
you talking about?
Ms. Desjardin, I don't think
she knows it's her period.
No!
All right, Sue. Get out of here!
You're not helping.
No! No!
Calm down!
Everyone get out!
Now! Out!
Okay, deep breaths.
Come here.
Come on. It's okay.
You're okay, sweetie.
It's totally normal.
Shh.
Do you know
what it means?
Okay, sweetie.
Are you, uh,
feeling better?
Can I get you
some aspirin?
Some juice or something?
Juice?
Really, Henry?
Maybe you just
want us to leave you alone.
Carrie, honey, I am so
sorry that I slapped you.
I should have
handled it better.
It's totally normal for young
girls to get their periods.
It usually actually happens
a little bit earlier.
Is this your first time?
Honey, do you understand
what's happening to your body?
Do you know
what it means?
What?
I don't know. I felt
something moving down there.
Oh, honey.
Whoa!
Maybe you could, uh, talk
to a counselor about that
or a nurse.
Um, what I need to know
is who started throwing...
...things.
It was Chris Hargensen
and all of her friends.
Cassie...
"Carrie."
Carrie, did Chris
Hargensen start this?
Honey, you don't
have to protect them.
What they did
was unforgiveable.
Okay, uh...
It doesn't seem that Carrie
is going to point the finger,
so Ms. Desjardin, I need you
to get to the bottom of this.
Let the punishment
fit the crime.
Okay.
Carrie, you're excused from P.E.
class for the rest of the week.
Just take study hall, okay?
At the library.
Yeah. We're going
to have to call your mom.
What?
We're going to have to
call your mother, Carrie.
I know she's had problems
with us in the past,
ever since the state
stopped her from
homeschooling you anymore,
but we've got to bring
her into this, okay?
Mmm-mmm. No.
Sweetie, we have
no choice.
We have to tell your
mom what happened. No.
Carrie.
Hey. Hey, you.
Tina, give it to me.
Give it here.
This is brilliant.
Look at this video.
Plug it up!
She got her period. On my hand.
That is so disgusting.
It was on my hand and Sue's shirt.
It was so disgusting.
Mmm.
I'm sorry you had to come
to school today, Mom.
Let's go inside,
little girl.
You need to come
inside with me.
Mama, why didn't
you tell me?
I was so scared, Mama. I
thought I was going to die.
Mama, they laughed at me
and they threw things at me.
We'll talk about
this inside, Carrie.
No.
I want to talk
about it right here.
I don't want to
go inside with you.
Crazy Carrie, Crazy Carrie!
Crazy Carrie,
Crazy Carrie.
Oh, Lord,
help my child.
She's lost.
Mama, stop it.
Mama!
I don't want
to upset you.
So, you're a woman now.
And God made Eve
from the rib of Adam.
And what, Carrie? Say it.
No, Mama.
Say it.
Talk to me.
Please just talk to me.
And Eve was weak.
I just want you
to talk to me.
And the first sin was
the sin of intercourse.
Why didn't you
tell me, Mama?
And God visited
Eve with a curse.
And the curse was
a curse of blood.
I'm not going
to say that.
That's not even in the Bible.
It doesn't say that anywhere.
Oh, Lord. Help this little girl
see the sin of her days and ways.
Show her if she had
remained innocent,
the curse of blood would not have
come upon her as it did on Eve.
I'm not Eve, Mama.
I didn't sin.
You showered with
those other girls.
You had
lust-filled thoughts.
Everyone has to shower, Mama. Everyone.
That's just the rules.
You must be different,
because He can see you.
I don't want to be different, Mama.
I want to be like them.
He can smell
the sin on you.
And He will punish you.
I will not let that come down upon you.
I will not.
Lord have mercy.
No. "The Lord is good. His
unfailing love endures forever,
"and his faithfulness continues
through all generations."
Psalms 100, verse 5.
I'm going to keep you
away from that school.
You can't. We'll pray.
We'll pray together.
To save our women-weak,
wicked, sinning souls.
You didn't tell me
and they laughed.
I didn't sin,
you sinned.
I did not.
I did not sin.
Go to your closet.
No, Mama.
Go to your closet
and pray.
You pray.
No.
No!
Get off me! Mama! Stop it!
Go to your closet and
pray for forgiveness.
No!
You pray.
Mama! Help!
No, Mommy!
Come on.
Please! Help!
You pray, little girl.
Pray for forgiveness.
Mommy, let me go!
Let me out!
Mom!
God, you suck!
Help me. Help me.
What?
I'm sorry.
Hey. What's wrong?
I really messed
up today, Tommy.
What, that thing
with Carrie?
You know about that?
Yeah, everyone
knows about it,
but you're not responsible
for what Chris does.
Yeah, but it
was me, too.
You threw tampons
at Carrie White?
I kicked a kid
in the ribs once.
Yeah, while he
was knocked out.
Because this kid,
he used to beat the living shit out
of me every day in sixth grade.
Danny Patrick.
Did you apologize
to Carrie?
to Danny Patrick?
No, but we're not in
sixth grade anymore.
Don't.
He was a dick to me.
What did Carrie White
ever do to you?
Whoo!
And that, ladies and gentlemen,
is why he lost his license.
Then why
are you still driving?
I don't need a license
if they can't catch me.
Jackie's email,
Jackie's email!
Chris no. No!
Wow. Why don't you two kiss or
something while you're at it?
Oh, baby.
Don't be stupid.
Wait.
Do you think we're going to get
detention because of that?
Because that would suck.
No.
They should be thanking us for helping
her through her first period.
I got her a tampon.
So what?
You were only trying
to help her, right?
We should post it.
No, I'm in it.
No one's going to
see you, Teenie.
What?
What are you doing?
Carrie White.
Favorite movie?
Bloodsport.
Favorite drink?
Bloody Mary.
Brightly beams
Our Father's mercy
From His
lighthouse evermore
But to us
He gives the keeping
Of the lights
along the shore
Let the lower
lights be burning
Did you finish
your prayers, little girl?
Yes, Mama.
That's my good girl.
I love you.
I love you,
too, Mama.
All right, stand up.
Line up, please.
You have a big week coming up.
A big month, actually.
Probably the biggest month of your lives.
Prom and then graduation.
Are you excited?
You probably all
have your dresses.
You have
your dates by now.
What about you, Chris?
Who's the lucky guy?
Billy Nolan.
You don't know him.
He doesn't go
to this school.
Are you going to
get him a boutonniere?
Or are you just going to pin a
bloody tampon to his lapel?
I so don't need
to hear this.
You're not going anywhere.
What about you, Sue?
Are you and Tommy busy campaigning
to be Prom King and Queen?
I would have
voted for you.
Not now.
You all did a shitty
thing yesterday.
A really shitty thing.
And one of you had the
audacity to post a video.
Somebody made
a video of it?
This is bullshit.
That's it. Thanks to Miss Hargensen,
you're all running suicides.
I'm not doing it.
That's up to you.
That's up to all of you, but anyone
who stops running is suspended.
And if you're suspended,
you're not going to prom.
While you're running, I'd like
for you to think long and hard
about what it would be
like to be Carrie White.
I'll be okay, Mama.
I'm going to leave work early today
and pick you up after school.
She can't do
this to me.
Just let it go, Chris.
We're almost done.
Then every day
this week?
All because
of Carrie White?
Like hell I Will.
Keep moving, Hargensen.
Keep running or
you're not going to prom.
Fuck you!
This is child abuse.
What did you say to me?
I'm not going to run
another goddamn inch
because Carrie White
got her period
and was too stupid
to know what it was.
- What?
- You're suspended.
You're out of prom and
you're out of my class. Now.
No.
No?
You can't decide that.
She can't do this to us.
Goodbye, Chris. The rest
of you, keep at it.
Someone could die
of dehydration.
Tina, you have
a heart condition, right?
If we all stick together, they're
not going to suspend all of us.
They're not going to keep us all from prom.
There would be no prom.
Nik, Lizzy?
Let's go, ladies!
Heather?
This is bullshit! We
didn't do anything wrong.
All right, let's go.
Right, Sue? You're with
me on this, right?
Come on.
Sue.
Keep going, ladies.
This isn't over.
This isn't over
by a long shot.
That's Carrie White.
Um, you know... Sorry.
I was just going to say, you can
make it full-screen. Watch.
All right, who's next?
Uh, Carrie. Favorite poem.
Did you bring one?
Yeah.
Why don't you come to
the front of the class
and share it
with us all?
"This unfrequented place
to find some ease
"Ease to the body some,
none to the mind
"Times past, and what once
I was and what am now
"O wherefore was my birth
from Heaven foretold
"Twice by an Angel,
who at last in sight
"Of both my Parents
all in flames...
"...ascended."
Okay, uh, that was, uh...
disturbing.
That is the most
you've said in class all year.
Is there anything
else you'd like to share
or are you done
scaring us for the day?
Asshole.
Excuse me, Mr. Ross.
Did you say something?
I said, "Awesome."
I just thought what
Carrie read was awesome.
Didn't you,
Mr. Ulmann?
All right,
who's next? Uh...
Nicki.
I mean, Lizzy.
Is anyone working?
Excuse me.
ls anybody working?
Oh, Margaret.
I'm sorry to disturb you. I don't
know where Hugo and Gloria...
Can I help you, Mrs. Snell?
Yes, I'm picking up.
Margaret, I want to say
how sorry I am
about what happened
at the school.
There's no excuse for what Sue
did, but she's a good girl.
Are any of those
girls good?
Oh, that is beautiful
work, Margaret.
Thank you.
I love what you've done
with the neckline.
And the stitches.
You can barely see them.
So few people can
sew like this anymore.
I could never do anything
like this myself.
Sue's going
to look beautiful.
I am so excited for her.
I remember my prom.
Anyway,
she's going to love it.
These are Godless times,
Mrs. Snell.
This gym teacher
was running Chrissie
into the ground
and used profanity.
I believe the term
"shitty" was used.
She can't do that.
It's abuse of power.
You're right, Daddy.
That's what she said.
"Shitty."
She's really abusive.
Ms. Desjardin was reprimanded for
what happened in class today.
But you know we've had
a lot of problems
with your daughter
in the past.
And now, with what she did to
her classmate, Carrie White.
The girl was having her...
What your daughter
and her posse...
I'm not going to sit here
and listen to half-truths.
I know my daughter. She
said she didn't do it.
I want her prom
privileges restored.
You can't prove she did
anything, can you?
I believe that there is a
video of the incident.
And I think your
daughter is the one who took it.
I think a video like
that would probably
be pretty damning
to anyone in it
and to the person
who made it.
Don't you,
Mr. Hargensen?
I don't know.
I'm just a gym teacher,
but it seems like
a video like that
would probably affect
college admissions,
possibly a lawsuit,
tons of bad publicity.
I wonder what The Today Show
would do with a video like that.
I think we should just look at
her phone and if it's not there,
I owe you a huge apology and she
should be allowed to go to prom.
Chris.
Daddy, I'm not
going to give them my phone.
I have personal
things on here.
Isn't that invasion
of privacy or something?
Chrissie, if you want
to go to prom,
just give them the damn phone
and we can be done with this.
I have to get
back to work.
Dad.
God damn it, just give
them your phone, Chris.
No.
So, I'm officially
out of the prom.
I bet that cocksucker Morton
loses his job, though.
My dad is suing him.
Jesus, Sue, why didn't
you stand up for me?
We could have had
them by the balls.
We deserved it for what
we did to Carrie White.
I thought
I deserved it.
Desjardin was right. We did a
shitty thing for no reason.
Bullshit!
That Carrie goes around saying that
everyone but her and her mother
are going to hell and you
stuck up for her? Come on!
You can be such
a pig sometimes, Chris.
What did Carrie White
ever do to you?
She's been begging for it
since the sixth grade, Sue.
I got to go.
I seem to remember
you were in there
throwing shit
with the rest of us.
What was it that
she was calling her?
"Freak"?
I stopped.
Oh, you stopped?
Yeah.
Why did you keep running?
Hmm?
Why did you keep running, Sue?
Stop it, Chris!
You kept running,
Sue, little Suze,
because you've been
dreaming about senior year
and the perfect boyfriend
and the perfect prom
your whole
goddamned life.
You already booked
the hotel,
already practiced the sounds
you're going to make
when you and Tommy make love.
That's why you had this
bullshit change of heart.
You don't give a shit
about Carrie White.
And everybody knows it.
Okay. I'll see you
around, Sue.
Carrie?
I'm not going to let anyone
hurt you, little girl.
You're safe here with me.
Got it.
Hey.
How are you doing?
Good.
Good?
Yeah.
What's up?
I want you to take
Carrie White to prom.
Good one, babe.
Come on.
Are you serious?
I'm just trying
to fix what I did.
Yeah.
I get that, but this is...
Sue, it's nuts.
Okay, so it's nuts.
But after what we did to
her, I have to do something.
I have to do something
that counts.
Uh...
What even makes you
think that she would say yes to me?
She'd say yes.
We've barely even spoken.
I saw how she looked at you in
class when you rescued her.
What girl doesn't
want to go to prom?
want one magical night?
Maybe I can give
that up for her.
No. Babe, I want you
to have that magic night.
I don't want to go to prom
with Carrie White.
I want to go
to prom with you.
I can't go.
Hey, Carrie.
I was looking for you
at the library
because that's where
they said you were.
But, uh, you weren't there, so
I figured maybe you were here.
"Telekinesis:
Unlocking the Mind."
No, no.
Is that about, uh, hypnosis?
Because me and my friends,
we tried that.
We actually hypnotized
my boy's dog.
Anyway, um...
How are you doing?
I'm okay.
Cool.
So you know how, um,
prom is next week?
You know?
Um, I was wondering, if you don't have a
date already, maybe you want to go with me.
What?
The prom.
Next week.
Carrie.
Hey.
Stop!
Please, just stop
trying to trick me.
No, I'm not trying to trick you.
I'm not tricking you.
Aren't you
with Sue Snell?
Yeah, I'm with Sue Snell,
but she doesn't want to go.
I'm sorry.
Did one of the girls
try something again?
No.
I got invited to prom.
Really?
That's great news.
With who?
It's Tommy Ross.
Wow. Tommy Ross?
He is pretty dreamy, huh?
Yeah.
I know who he
goes around with.
They're just going
to trick me again.
Right?
Maybe he really meant it.
No.
Yes, of course he did.
Why?
Why would he
want to go with me?
Come here.
Do you know
what I see?
I see a beautiful
young woman.
Maybe wear
a little make-up.
Pinch your cheeks
a little bit,
put some color in there.
Curl your hair.
Stand up straight.
There you go.
Come on, Sue.
You and Chris are best friends.
If you two...
If you three are planning
on playing a joke
on a lonely,
defenseless girl...
This has nothing
to do with Chris.
Or you, Miss Desjardin.
And for me...
Listen, with due respect, Miss
Desjardin, this is between Sue and me.
It's kind of like
a private thing.
And what is
the big deal anyway?
It's just for
one night, right?
Famous athletes
like Tim Tebow,
he takes kids to prom all the time
and everyone loves him for it.
Really?
You're hardly
a famous athlete.
This is a really big deal for her.
Listen.
It doesn't matter.
She said no.
So you'll try again.
Don't.
Okay.
It's not okay.
Tommy,
when you show up to prom with
Carrie White on your arm,
don't you think you're going to
look the tiniest bit ridiculous?
We don't care how we look.
Do we?
No.
Come on.
What are you doing here?
Aren't you
going to ask me in?
What do you want?
You can't be here.
Right to the point, huh?
Cool. About the prom.
You kind of
left me hanging.
I already told you.
I know, but I was hoping
that you'd change your mind.
Girls change their
mind all the time.
Why are you doing this?
Because I want to.
You need to leave.
I'm not leaving
until you say yes.
Why is this so
important to you?
Because I think that we
would have a good time.
And because I think that what
you read in class was cool.
I looked up that book
in the library myself.
That's the guy who brought the
temple down. Samson, right?
Yes.
Yes, okay, I'll go.
I have to be back
by 10:30.
Sure, okay. Um...
I'll pick you up
here at 7:00?
Okay.
Crazy, right?
Tommy Ross and Carrie White.
Where have you been? I was worried sick.
Come on. Come inside.
I'm sorry I'm late, Mama.
Just get inside.
Your supper's cold. I'm going
to have to heat it up.
I didn't know...
You're immodest.
I didn't know where you were.
I didn't know.
No, Mama. I took a
bus to Main Street
and I bought cloth
for a dress.
You are not to go anywhere but to
school and back. You know that.
Mama, before you say anything
else, I've been asked to prom.
Mama, I've been
asked to prom.
Oh, God, why?
It's next Saturday and
he's a very nice boy.
And he'll come and
meet you before
and he promised to
have me home by 10:30.
No, no, no.
I already accepted.
I know this scares you.
It scares me, too.
The other kids,
they think I'm weird.
But I don't want to be.
I have to try to be
a whole person.
Before it's too late.
He'll hurt you.
No, Mama.
No, Mama, there are bad
people, but not Tommy.
He's good. You'll like him.
He's a very nice boy.
Boys, boys.
After the blood,
comes the boys sniffing,
slobbering like dogs.
Stop it, Mama.
He's going to paw at you until he finds
where that blood smell comes from.
He's going to
take you, Carrie,
in his car out
to the wilderness,
out where it's cold and the
roadhouses are and the whiskey.
Stop being so crazy.
You tell that boy
you're not going.
No.
We'll move from here. We're
never going to stop moving.
You're going to go to your
closet and you're going to pray.
You're going to get in there and
you're going to pray for forgiveness.
No, never again, Mama!
Mama, stand up.
Mama, stand up!
Mama, I'm going.
Witch.
I'm not a witch, Mama.
There are no witches.
The devil's got her now.
Like he did before.
It's not the devil, Mama. There are
other people out there like me
who can do
what I can do.
You poor child. Don't you know
he's working through you?
Mama, it's inherited. it was
passed down from Grandma
and it skipped you.
You know that.
Maybe it came from Daddy.
He gave me a cancer.
I thought you were cancer.
That's awful. Don't say that.
She's lost to me.
Pray all you want, Mama,
but I'm going.
And nothing's going
to stop me.
And I don't want to
talk about it anymore.
What are we doing?
What does this have to do
with Carrie White?
Baby, you said you wanted us
to do something about her.
It's a piggy!
Here, piggy, piggy.
It smells
like shit in here.
Chris, pick one. Pick one
that looks like her.
Pig's blood for a pig.
That one.
Go on.
One quick swing,
all right?
I got this.
Don't worry,
little piggy,
Uncle Jack is going
to bash your head right in.
You're not going
to feel one...
Shut up!
Do it already. Jesus.
I can't.
God, you guys are
such goddamn pussies.
Shut up!
I'm sorry, Billy.
Come on, you got this.
All right, it's just
one quick slice and...
Oh, my God.
Good job, baby.
Sue.
Hey, are you okay?
There we go.
Billy. Hurry up.
Oh, my God.
When the time comes, I'll let
you pull the rope, okay?
Oh, I plan on it.
Did you guys
see Sue today?
She looked awful.
I know Chris isn't coming.
She's suspended.
Do you think she'll crash?
You never know
with Chris, right?
So, I think I'm going
to have the after-party.
No.
What do you think?
Down?
No.
Yeah.
Whoo!
Will you pin it
on me, Mama?
Red.
I might have known
it would be red.
It's pink.
I can see your dirty pillows.
Everyone will.
Breasts, Mama.
Breasts. You have them
and every woman has them.
Take off
that dress, Carrie.
No.
Take it off and we'll burn it
together and pray for forgiveness.
Mama, it's modest.
Call that boy and tell
him you're not going.
You just tell him
you're sick.
I don't want you
to get hurt.
Or you could just
be happy for me.
Mama, stop hurting yourself.
You know it's not going
to make me stay.
He's not coming.
It's a trick.
Same as always.
He's going to come.
They're going
to laugh at you.
They're all going
Mama, stop it.
I'm nervous enough
as it is.
Thank you, sir.
You see, Mama?
You see, it's all
going to be okay.
Oh, repent.
It's not too late.
Mama, don't ruin this for me.
I'll be home early.
I'm going to have to
tell that boy the truth
that your father took me
and you were born of sin.
You'll say nothing, Mama.
And from that sin...
From that sin
was born another.
The worst sin.
"A man or a woman
who is a witch
"among you is to
be put to death.
"You are to stone them."
I'm warning you, Mama.
The devil's hand.
Please don't do this.
There will be
a judgment, Carrie.
As Jezebel fell from
the tower, you too...
Mama, you're not going to say
another word until I'm gone.
Mommy, I'm sorry.
I love you.
I'll be home early.
Hi.
Do I look okay?
You look beautiful.
Tommy, can we
wait a minute?
Yeah, sure, we can wait
as long as you want.
Are you scared?
They're not that bad.
Besides, I need you
in there.
Dancing by myself all night,
I'd look awful silly.
Here, let me fix this.
I think this is supposed
to go on your wrist.
There.
Are you ready?
God, you look
handsome, Ross.
Dawson!
Don't worry. If they kill each
other, I'll dance with you.
Carrie, this is my best
buddy, George Dawson.
And this is his girlfriend, Erika.
She goes to Dover.
Hi.
Come on, I'll show
you the table.
I love your dress.
Where did you get it?
I made it.
No kidding. Really?
Yeah.
That's amazing.
Do you want
to dance?
Or, if you want, we could
wait for a slower song.
Yeah.
I'll be back.
Miss Desjardin.
You look beautiful.
I'll let you two ladies talk.
Uh, do you want
some punch?
I heard Greg
and Harry spiked it.
Really?
No, I'm just kidding.
You're doing okay?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Listen.
Do you really have
to be home so early?
I promised.
Yeah, I know.
I understand.
But, um, a bunch of people, we're
going to the Cavalier after.
That's okay.
What is?
I know you want to hang out with
your friends, and that's...
No.
It's a slow song.
Yeah. Come on.
No, Tommy.
I've never danced before.
It's okay. No, I can't.
I can't do it.
You can't go to prom and not
have at least one dance.
I can't.
Carrie White, will you
have this dance with me?
Come on.
It's so easy. Take this hand in my hand.
Like this, see?
You're going to put this
hand on my shoulder.
And I put my hand
on your hip.
Then we sway.
See, it's easy.
You've got nothing
to worry about.
And you're good,
you're a good learner.
And then, if you want
to get fancy with it,
we can do the
Dancing With The Stars.
Yeah.
No.
Yeah. Ready? Look.
To the first one.
This is fun, right?
Tommy, why am I here?
Because I invited you.
But why?
Carrie, we're here.
We're at prom. I'm having
such a great time with you.
You are?
Yeah.
And I hope that you're
having a good time with me.
Yeah.
So, what do you say
we dance a little longer,
and then we see which poor fool
they crown King and Queen,
and then we go to the Cavalier?
And I'll have you home by 10:30.
How does that sound to you?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Maybe 11:00.
Whatever you want.
11:00.
All right, everyone,
take your seats. Take your seats.
It's now time to
vote for your King
and Queen of the prom. All right.
Ballots are on the table.
Everyone gets their own, please.
Guys, take your seats.
Here.
Make an "X" beside
the candidate of your choice.
Let's have
the best prom ever.
Whoo!
All right.
Tommy, we're on here.
Don't you want
to be on there?
Do you?
Why not?
If we win, the only
thing that happens is
we have to go up there
on those thrones,
wave a scepter around while
they play the school song,
and then, uh, do a little dance so
everyone can see how idiotic we look.
They are beautiful.
You're beautiful.
So, who do we vote for?
I guess they're
more your crowd than mine.
I don't really have a crowd.
Well, I think we vote
for ourselves, right?
No. No,
don't vote for us.
To the devil
with false modesty.
To the devil.
Hurt yourself?
No.
To my boy, George Dawson,
to the Fearsome Four,
Mike, Matt, Brian, and Brad.
I'm going to miss you guys.
- All set?
- Oh, yeah.
Good luck, kids.
You've got my vote.
More ballots for you.
Hey, girl.
Here you go.
As soon as that
bucket goes, we run.
We don't stick around for the
laughs or the screams or anything.
All right?
You got it?
Are you listening? Hey.
What?
When they get up there,
what's happening? You're pulling
the rope and when the...
Shut up so I can hear.
Hey. Listen to me. Listen.
If you get caught and you say
anything about what we did,
I will fucking kill you.
This isn't what you bitches
did in the shower.
This is criminal assault.
This is fucking jail time
if we're caught.
I get it.
Hey. Whatever happens
tonight, you're Queen, okay?
And the results are in.
And it was very, very close.
A drum roll, please.
By one vote,
our winners are...
Tommy Ross
and Carrie White!
Come on.
Way to go, Carrie.
Heather, where's Chris?
What are you talking about?
She's not here.
Hey, what's wrong? Come on, go.
You can do this.
We are fucking doing this.
It's too late to go back now.
Ewen High...
I give you your newly crowned
King and Queen of the prom,
Tommy Ross
and Carrie White.
Pull it!
Shut up, Billy!
Chris.
Sue?
Sue.
What are you doing? Come on.
Come on, let's go.
No! Miss Desjardin,
it's not me. It's Chris.
Pull it, Billy, pull it!
Don't ruin this
for Carrie.
It's not me!
Come on. Out.
Let her have this.
No, wait!
What the hell?
Plug it up!
Please help me!
Carrie, wait.
Carrie.
Help me.
No!
Freak! Freak!
Come on.
Carrie, come on.
Tommy.
Tommy, no.
No.
Fuck.
You have an inch.
Yeah. Come on.
Go, go. Come on.
Come on.
Are you seeing this?
Wait.
Come on.
There's been an explosion.
Don't panic!
Bleachers!
We have to
get to the door.
Nicki!
Lizzy!
- Come on! We got to go!
- Okay.
Tina, come on!
We're all going to die!
Come on!
What are you doing?
Nothing. Do you think
this is a fucking game?
Shut up.
What are we going to do?
We're going to leave town and
we're never going to come back.
Okay? It's okay.
It's going to be okay.
Okay.
Oh, my God!
Watch out!
Shit town!
Go, move!
Oh, my God.
It's Carrie.
Run her down.
Kill her.
Kill her, Billy.
Kill her, Billy! Kill her!
Shut up! I got this.
Come on!
Billy?
No.
Mommy. Mommy. Mommy.
Mama?
Mama!
No.
I'm so sorry.
Mama?
Oh, Mama.
Mama, you were right.
They laughed at me, Mommy.
They all laughed at me.
I knew they'd hurt
my little girl.
I should have killed myself
when he put it in me.
We slept in
the same bed,
lived together sinlessly.
Then one night, I saw him
look at me in that way.
And we got down on our knees
to pray for strength.
And that's when
he took me.
No, Mama.
I don't want to hear it.
And I liked it.
Mama, no.
I should have given you to God
when you were born, but...
I was weak.
And I loved you so much.
And I said, "God,
"let me keep
my little girl.
"Let me keep her."
Let's pray.
Yes, Mama.
Yes, we'll pray.
I'll be the preacher.
You'll be my congregation.
"Our Father,
Who art in heaven,
"hallowed be Thy name.
"Thy kingdom come,
"Thy will be done
"on earth
"as it is in heaven."
Mama!
Mama, please.
No, Mama. Mama, please.
This isn't your fault,
Carrie. It's mine.
Mommy, this isn't right.
You know the devil never dies.
He keeps coming back.
You've got to keep killin' him.
No, Mama.
Over and over again.
Mama, please. Mama!
No!
No, Mama.
Mama, stop it!
Carrie.
I'm sorry.
Carrie!
Okay.
It's okay.
It's okay. No one's
going to hurt you.
No one's going to hurt you.
Carrie?
Let me help you,
Carrie.
Why couldn't you
leave me alone?
I'm sorry.
Look what you
turned me into.
Don't hurt me,
Carrie.
Why not?
I've been hurt
my whole life.
I killed my mom.
I want her back.
I'm scared.
We've got to
get out of here!
Give me your hand.
Come on!
It's a girl.
What?
You don't know?
Oh, my God.
Get out!
It's okay.
You're doing great.
That's just another contraction.
Okay.
Sue, do me
a favor and push.
No, something doesn't feel right.
It doesn't feel right.
Come on now, breathe.
Try again, Sue. Try again.
Everything's okay.
There we go. Ready?
It hurts! Please help me!
Just lay back, okay, Sue?
There you go.
Almost there.
Is it normal?
All right, just push!
Everything's gonna be okay.
Hold her still!
Sue, push!
Sue, I need you
to breathe!
Now, get ready
for the next one.
Push! You can do it!
Come on!
Wake up, baby!
It's okay, it's okay.
I gotcha.
It's over, baby! It's over!
Sue, you're all right!
You're all right!
Baby, wake up!
I can hardly make you mine
Tell it to you all the time
At the end of a long day
and when I wake
If you could just
give me a sign
We could leave it all behind
Stop taking the long
way before we play
I don't think I can make it
and I know you're the one
Staring into the tears
like a loaded gun
Well, I can hardly
make you mine
Tell it to you all the time
But you never wanted,
but you had to take
So I can never give you up
I guess it's 'cause
it's just a crush
Before the end of a long
day and then I wake
But I know you're not
the one or the only
But we both know what
it's like to be lonely
Well, these fantasies,
they left us lonely
Boy, just bring all
your love back to me
I guess for now
this is how it'll be
I don't think I can make it
Oh, you're the one
Staring into the tears
like a loaded gun
I don't think I can make it
Oh, you're the one
Staring into the tears
like a loaded gun
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player