[Doctor]
Um... you have no actual
medical training?
No. I have kids.
Learned a lot right there.
I mean, I've seen nurses
give my son throat cultures.
What is it?
You stick a giant Q-Tip
down their throat and wait.
Or a urinalysis, where you
take a dipstick to see whether
or not the white count's high.
[Doctor]
Yes, I understand.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm great with people.
You'd have to observe me
to know for sure,
but you can trust me
on that.
Yeah.
I'm an extremely
fast learner.
You show me
something in a lab once,
and I've got it down.
Mm-hmm.
I always wanted to go
to medical school.
That was my first
interest really,
but then I got married
and had a kid too young
and that kind of blew that.
When I was first out
of high school,
I got a job
with Fleuer Engineers
and Constructors in Irvine.
I fell madly in love
with geology.
Geology?
[Erin]
Yeah.
I learned how to read maps.
I love maps.
Yeah, but I lost my job
because...
my boy came down
with the chicken pox,
had a 104 temperature,
and my ex-husband
was useless, so...
[Softly]
That didn't
really work out.
Uh-huh.
You got
a really nice office.
Thanks.
Look...
Aw, fuck.
[Sighs]
- [Nail Break]
- Goddamn it.
[Sighs]
[Starts Engine]
Good morning,
Mr. Masry.
Rosalind.
How are you doing today?
Fine, thanks.
And you?
Very well.
Thank you for asking.
Good morning.
How ya doing?
Hi, Donald.
[Brenda]
Did you see it last night?
I was out, but I taped it.
Don't tell me what happens.
It was so good.
Your 9:00's here already.
Remind me.
Erin Brockovich.
Car accident.
Not her fault, she says.
She was referred.
Yeah.
All right?
Erin, hi.
Hi.
[Closes Door]
Ed Masry.
Sorry you had to wait.
That's okay.
Here, sit, sit.
Sit down, sit down.
Thank you.
Oh.
I never thought just standing
could take it out of you,
but ever since
that shithead hit me,
I feel like my whole body's
put together wrong.
You poor thing.
Uh, did anyone ask
if you wanted coffee?
Yeah. I'm fine.
[Clears Throat]
[Ed] Good.
Listen, whoever did this to you
made one hell of a mistake,
and, you and me,
we're gonna make him pay for it.
So, uh, why don't you tell me
what happened?
I was pulling out real slow
and, out of nowhere,
his Jaguar comes
racing around the corner
like a bat out of hell.
They took some bone
from my hip and put it
in my neck.
I don't have insurance,
so I'm about $ 17,000
in debt right now.
I couldn't take pain killers
'cause they made me too groggy
to take care of my kids.
Matthew's eight
and Katie's almost six...
and Beth's just nine months.
I just want to be a good mom,
a nice person,
a decent citizen.
I just want to take good care
of my kids, you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
Seventeen thousand in debt?
[Sighs]
Is your ex-husband
helping out?
Which one?
There's more than one?
Yeah, there's two.
Why?
So, you must have been feeling
pretty desperate that afternoon.
What's your point?
[Attorney]
Broke, three kids,
no job.
- A doctor in a Jaguar must have
looked like a good meal ticket.
- Objection.
[Judge]
Sustained.
What? He hit me.
- So you say.
- He came tearing around
the corner, out of control!
An E.R. Doctor,
who spends his day saving lives,
was the one out of control?
That asshole smashed in
my fucking neck.
[Spectators Murmuring]
Open and shut.
Open and fucking shut!
That is exactly
the kind of language
that lost the case.
It was over long before that.
I told you the questions
might get personal.
No, you told me
I'd be set!
I never said that.
You told me
I had a good shot.
I had no shot!
Let's try
and settle down here.
Fuck "settle down"!
I've got $ 74 in the bank.
I can't afford
to settle down.
I'm sorry, Erin.
Do they teach lawyers
to apologize?
Because you suck at it.
Hello? Hi.
Hi, Erin.
You've come so soon.
Yeah.
Oh, were you
a good girl, huh?
You're my little baby.
[Coughs]
What is that,
a little cough?
She's got a little cough.
I sat in the steam with her
to try to loosen it up, but...
I think I've got
some cough medicine.
Ah, bueno.
Um, listen... I didn't want
to tell you before,
Yeah?
You know,
with your worries.
What?
My daughter
bought a big house
with a room for me.
I'm moving in with her.
When?
Next week.
Next week?
I know,
but it's good for me.
Now I can help my daughter
take care of my grandkids.
And it's good for you too.
Now you have money,
you can hire a good baby-sitter,
eh?
Not the old lady
next door.
Thanks.
[Boy Yelling]
Matthew?
Katie, you back here?
[Katie]
Yeah.
Okay, come on in,
would you?
[Laughing]
[Erin]
Hey, get in the house.
No dripping.
[Both]
Okay.
Sweetie, please,
don't get sick on me. Please.
[Cooing]
[Crying]
Let's fix
some dinner.
[Crying Continues]
[Erin Turns On Faucet]
Look at the water.
[Continues Crying]
[Turns Water Off]
[Gasps, Drops Pan]
[Screaming]
Damn it.
I'm sorry.
[Crying]
[Continues Crying]
Matthew! Katie!
We're going out.
You kids go ahead
and order.
Okay, I'm gonna have
a cheeseburger deluxe
with a Coke.
Okay.
Mommy, can I have
a cheeseburger deluxe...
with no cheese
and no bread?
- Did you get that?
- Yes.
And she will have
a cup of chicken broth
and a few crackers, please.
And for you?
Okay.
Just a cup of coffee.
Mommy, you're not eating?
Well, my lawyer took me out
to a fancy lunch to celebrate,
and I'm still stuffed.
How about that?
[Laughing]
[Coughs]
[Beth Crying]
I'm calling about the job ad
in the paper.
Yes, I'm calling
about the job ad.
Great personality, good voice.
I don't have any actual
sales experience.
I don't really have a resume,
but I can...
No, I don't have
any computer skills, but...
Oh. Well, I thought
it was the local store.
Okay. Thanks anyway.
Okay, bye.
[Hangs Up Receiver]
[Clears Throat]
Ed Masry, please.
Yes, I'm holding for Ed Masry.
Is he ever in the office?
No, but I've called
about a dozen times.
Yes, I'd like
to leave another message.
Brockovich.
B-r-o-c-k-o-v-i-c-h.
I'm a client.
I want him to call me.
It's as simple as that.
Okay.
[Sighs]
[Gasps]
Goddamn it!
Brenda!
Yeah?
Who put that there?
Those are the files
you asked for.
I didn't ask for you
to put it in the middle
of the floor.
I mean, look at me.
Get a towel, will ya?
Hey. Hey.
What's she doing here?
Who?
Donald.
What's she doing here?
She works here.
Erin, how's it going?
You never
called me back.
I left messages.
You did?
Well, I didn't know that.
Donald seems to think you...
There's two things that
aggravate me, Mr. Masry:
Being ignored
and being lied to.
I never lied.
You told me
things would be fine.
They're not.
I trusted you.
I'm sorry about that.
I am.
I don't need pity.
I need a paycheck.
I've looked, but when
you've spent the past
six years raising babies,
it's real hard to convince
someone to give you a job
that pays worth a damn.
Are you getting every word
of this, honey, or am I
talking too fast for you?
[Ed]
I'm sorry
about that.
I really am, but we have
a full staff right now...
Bullshit!
If you had a full staff,
this office would return
a client's damn phone call.
I'm smart,
I'm hard-working,
and I'll do anything,
and I'm not leaving here
without a job.
[Softly]
Don't make me beg.
If it doesn't work out,
fire me.
Don't make me beg.
No benefits.
What we do in here
is file all the cases.
That way, at any time,
we can tell the status
of a file.
You know,
where it is in the office,
stuff like that.
Here's where we
organize all the files
alphabetically.
Simple enough.
Okay.
Here's your desk.
Come with me.
I want to show you
where the Xerox machine is.
Everybody has a code,
and you need to know about that.
Do I get to pick
my own code?
We'll see.
[Erin]
Mr. Masry?
Yeah?
I was wondering,
can you tell me who I talk to...
about maybe getting
an advance on my paycheck,
just for the weekend?
Rosalind's the office manager.
She handles the payroll
and petty cash.
But she's gone already.
She leaves early on Fridays.
Okay. Thank you.
Oh, for Pete's sake,
here, here.
I've only got hundreds.
Here.
[Clears Throat]
I don't want your money,
Mr. Masry.
Where do you think
your paycheck comes from?
Here.
Have a good weekend.
Thank you.
See you.
[Employees]
See you. Good night.
[Ed]
See you Monday.
Hey. Hi, my sweetie.
Hello. [Kisses]
How are you?
Matthew? Katie?
Hey, Mom.
Hi, sweetie.
Come on.
How are you?
Thanks a lot.
You're welcome.
[Kisses]
[Engine Revving]
[Revving Continues]
[Revving
Continues]
Hey!
[Revving
Engine]
Hey!
[Continues
Revving Engine]
Hey!
Hello.
What are you doing
making all that goddamn noise?
Well, uh, I don't know.
We were just
introducing ourselves
to the neighborhood, I guess.
Well, I'm the neighbors.
There, we're introduced,
so shut the fuck up.
[Chuckling]
Hey, hey.
Hold on there.
Let's start over,
okay?
My name's George.
What's yours?
Just think of me as the person
next door who likes it quiet.
Hey, come on.
Don't be like that.
Hell, we live next door
to each other.
I feel bad.
I feel terrible. I'm sorry.
Will you accept my apology?
I mean, hell, we're living
right next door to each other.
If you need a cup of sugar...
I don't eat sugar.
You don't need
any sugar?
Why don't I take you
out to dinner to apologize
for my rudeness?
You give me your number.
I already got your address,
so you can't get away.
Huh? I'll call you up proper,
and I'll ask you out
and everything.
[Scoffs]
You want my number?
I do.
I do want your number.
Which number do you want,
George?
Now I like the way
you say "George."
How many numbers you got?
Oh, I got numbers coming out
of my ears. For instance, ten.
"Ten"?
Yeah. That's how many
months old my baby girl is.
You got a little girl?
Yeah. Sexy, huh?
How about this
for a number: Six?
That's how old
my other daughter is.
Eight is the age of my son.
Two is how many times
I've been married and divorced.
Sixteen is the number of dollars
I have in my bank account.
850-3943. That's my
phone number, and with all
the numbers I gave you...
I'm guessing zero is the number
of times you're gonna call it.
Hey, how do you remember
your bank balance off the top
of your head like that?
That impresses me.
You're dead wrong
about that zero thing,
baby.
[Laughing]
[Erin]
How long has she been crying
like that?
She's got that tooth coming in.
Why don't you give her
a cold washcloth to suck on?
I gotta go.
There's a clean one in the bag.
I'll check back later.
- Where's Anna?
- She's out to lunch
with the girls.
Oh.
I have to open a file.
Real estate thing,
pro bono.
Okay.
You know how to do that,
don't you?
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
No problem.
- You're a girl.
- Excuse me?
Why aren't you out to lunch
with the girls?
You're a girl.
I guess I'm not the right kind.
Oh.
Uh, look, now, you may want...
Now that you're working here,
you may want to, uh...
rethink your wardrobe a little.
Why is that?
Well, I think
some of the girls...
are a little uncomfortable...
because of what you wear.
Is that so?
Well, it just so happens,
I think I look nice.
And as long as I have one ass
instead of two,
I'll wear what I like,
if that's all right with you.
Uh-huh.
You might want
to rethink those ties.
[Erin]
Anna?
Huh?
This real estate stuff...
Could you remind me?
I'm a little confused
exactly how we do it.
Why are there medical
records and blood samples
in real estate files?
Erin, you've been here
long enough.
If you don't know how
to do your job by now,
I'm not about to do it
for you.
Hello?
Matthew? Katie?
Matt...
Matthew? Matthew?
[Children Laughing]
[Children Talking,
Laughing]
What the hell happened?
[Matthew, Katie] Hi, Mom.
Hey, hungry?
Am l...
What are they doing here?
I just went to pick them up.
She came by about an hour ago
and said something came up and
she had to drop the kids off.
"Something came up"?
Why didn't she call me at work?
I don't know.
She... I was...
I don't know... why.
That stupid bitch.
Mom.
Sorry. I just can't believe
she dumps my kids off
when nobody's home.
I was home.
We're fine.
Seriously,
we cooked some burgers,
had some milk.
Want a hot dog?
There's an extra one
on the grill.
Or a cheeseburger.
With this mustard,
it's slippery.
[Matthew]
Mom, what do you think
about me getting a tattoo?
One, two, three.
[Chuckling]
[Matthew]
I got all these kings.
You win, you got a joker.
[Continues Putting Cards Down]
King. Joker.
You stole a joker!
[Laughing]
He cheats.
What do you mean,
I cheat?
You cheat!
[Laughing]
Get another one.
Time to go to bed.
[Children
Continue Playing]
Excuse me. Get ready for bed.
Brush your teeth.
[Matthew] Okay.
Play tomorrow?
Yeah.
Good night, buddy.
Good night.
[Both]
- What's that?
- This is a Harley-Davidson.
It's the best damn motorcycle
ever made.
And if I ever catch
either one of you near one,
I'll knock you silly.
[Katie Hopping]
Brush your teeth,
and keep it down.
The baby's asleep.
[Sighs]
Yeah.
You have great kids.
Well, I'm sure
I'll fuck them up eventually.
[Laughing]
Why?
I'm obviously not
a good judge of character...
or I would have never left them
with that idiot...
who cost a fortune
and smelled like chicken fat.
After I find her and kill her,
I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
If you need help with them,
I could do that.
I'm not leaving my kids
with you.
[George]
Why?
I don't even know you.
What do you want
to know? Ask me.
Look, thanks for today.
You're welcome.
It was my pleasure.
How many decks
do you guys have here?
We had more than enough.
What's the matter?
You got so many friends
in this world, you can't
use one more?
Huh? I'm serious.
If you need someone
to look after your kids...
after school
or whatever,
I don't have a job now,
so...
Oh, that's
a great recommendation.
I'm unemployed.
By choice.
I work when I need to.
Yeah?
What do you do
the rest of the time,
live off your trust fund?
No, I do construction,
which pays real good, and
I make it last by living cheap.
[Noise]
I hope that's not supposed
to impress me.
Hey, bed.
[Footsteps Departing, Rapidly]
[George]
Your little ghosts.
You always this hard
on people who try
to help you?
[Sorting Cards]
I'm out of practice.
Yeah, well, let me
remind you then.
The polite thing is
to say, "Thank you."
Let's start with that.
Then you could say,
"Hey, that's a really
nice offer.
I don't mind
taking you up on that."
Why the hell do you want
to watch my kids?
I like kids.
Yeah, I do. I like
hanging out with them.
They keep it simple.
You're home every afternoon?
I'm usually just working
on my bike.
Listen,
it's no big deal.
If it doesn't work out,
you can always
send them back
to the chicken fat lady.
This isn't gonna get you laid,
you know?
[Laughs]
[Snaps Fingers]
Get in bed.
[Footsteps Departing, Rapidly]
That's good, 'cause I don't
find you attractive either.
Good, then we're even.
Right, so we don't have
to worry about that.
I'm so glad we got that
out of the way.
I feel much better.
I do too. Seriously.
Because now I can just
look after the kids,
and I don't have to worry
about you coming on
to me all the time.
[Sorting Cards]
[Beth Cooing]
[Cooing Continues]
[Ed Talking Softly]
Bring the phone
into the changing room.
Mrs. Masry,
don't be such a tease.
Hold on. Just hold on.
Yeah?
Sorry. Would you mind
if I investigate this
a little further?
- Investigate what?
- This real estate thing
with the Jensens.
- The pro bono case.
- Yeah, yeah.
Yeah? Because I just want
to make sure I'm understanding
what I'm reading.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
[Erin]
You don't mind?
Okay, great. Thanks.
[Knocking]
Hi.
Donna Jensen?
Yes.
I'm Erin Brockovich,
with Masry & Vititoe.
Oh. You're a lawyer?
Hell, no.
I hate lawyers.
I just work for them.
[Chuckles]
Um, do you have
a minute?
I don't mean to be a pain
in PG&E's backside,
especially after all
they've done for Hinkley,
but I look around here
and I think,
"If they want this place,
they're gonna have to pay
for it."
So you didn't
put the house up
for sale,
they just came to you
and wanted to buy it?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I don't want to move.
Uproot the kids?
I've got a couple of girls.
Honest to God,
I don't know
if I have the energy.
You know,
I've been sick.
Me and Pete both have.
So, the whole idea
of selling this house,
if they're not
gonna pay us properly,
I just don't see the point.
Yeah, yeah,
I can see that.
But...
I guess the only thing
that confused me is,
not that your medical
problems aren't important,
but how come the files
on that are in with all
the real estate stuff?
Well, there's just
so much correspondence,
I just keep it all in one place.
Right. Right.
Um, I'm sorry,
I just don't see why
you're corresponding
with PG&E...
about your medical problems
in the first place.
Well, they paid
for the doctor's visit.
They did?
You bet.
Paid for a checkup
for the whole family.
Not like with insurance
where you pay...
and a year goes by
and maybe you see some money.
They just took care of it
just like that.
[Snaps Fingers]
We never even saw a bill.
Wow.
Why'd they do that?
Because of the chromium.
The what?
The chromium.
That's what kicked
this whole thing off.
[Sighs]
[Horn Blaring]
[Blaring Continues]
What kind of chromium
is it?
There's more than one type?
Yes, there's straight-up
chromium; does good things
for the body.
There's chrom three,
which is fairly benign.
Then there's chrom six,
hexavalent chromium,
which, depending on the amounts,
can be very harmful.
Harmful how?
What would you get?
With repeated exposure
to toxic levels,
God, anything, really,
from chronic headaches
and nosebleeds...
to respiratory disease,
liver failure,
heart failure,
reproductive failure,
bone or organ deterioration,
plus, of course,
any type of cancer.
So, that stuff,
it kills people?
Yeah, definitely.
Highly toxic,
highly carcinogenic.
It gets into your DNA too,
so you pass the trouble
along to your kids.
It's very, very bad.
What's it used for?
A rust inhibitor.
See, the utility plants
use these piston engines
to compress the gas.
The engines get hot.
You've got to run water
through them.
Chromium's in the water
to prevent corrosion.
Well, how do I find out
what kind of chromium
they use in Hinkley?
Have you been
to their water board?
Uh-uh.
What's that?
Every county has one.
They keep records...
of anything water-related
within their jurisdiction.
You should be able
to find something there.
County water board?
All righty. Thanks.
Uh-huh.
Good luck.
I wouldn't advertise
what you're looking for
if I were you.
Incriminating records
have a way of disappearing
when people smell trouble.
I'll remember that.
Thanks.
[Man Over TV]
This guy's too smart.
[Woman Over TV]
It's only a matter of time
until he makes his move.
He positions
women employees
in such a way...
that they have no other choice
but to respond to what he wants
or they lose their job...
[Turns Off TV]
[Erin Opens Door, Sighs]
Damn, that's a heavy door.
Let me give you
a hand there.
Thank you very much.
Aren't you a gentleman,
Mr...
Uh, Scott.
Mr. Scott.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Erin.
Erin. Erin.
Cool.
What can I do for you,
Erin?
Believe it or not,
I'm on the prowl
for some water records.
You've come to the right place.
[Chuckles]
I guess I did.
You just tell me
what you want to look at,
and I'd be glad
to dig 'em out for you.
I wish I knew.
It's for my boss.
He's in this water dispute,
and he wants me
to find all kinds of papers
from all kinds of places.
Uh...
you know...
it would probably
be easiest...
if I just
squeezed back there
and poked around myself.
Would that be all right
with you?
Heck, yeah. Come on back.
I'm just gonna need you
to sign in here.
Sure.
"Pattee."
Is that your middle name?
No, maiden.
Oh, you're married?
[Softly]
Not anymore.
Oh, that's...
Can I just...
Yeah, just...
I love your pants.
[Stammering]
Oh, thanks.
Well,
this is it.
It's, um...
It's impressive.
[Chuckles]
I'll call you
if I need anything.
A-All right.
Okay.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
[Audience Cheering Over TV]
[Pat Sajak]
All right.
[Contestant]
"W."
[TV Continues,
Indistinct]
[TV Continues]
[Copy Machine Whirring]
[Whirring Continues]
Where's my stuff?
Where have you been?
What the fuck did you do
with my stuff?
Don't use language like that.
Who do you think you are,
Miss Lady?
Someone took my stuff.
Nice to see you, Erin.
We missed you.
[Erin] I had photos
of my kids, a mug...
Toothbrush, toothpaste,
mousse and deodorant.
- Here.
- What's going on?
There may be jobs where you can
disappear for days at a time,
but this isn't one of them.
Here, you don't do the work,
you don't get to stay.
I've been working.
That's all I've been doing.
Ask Mr. Masry. He knows.
You ask Mr. Masry.
He fired you.
- You said to fire me?
- I'll call you back.
You've been gone for a week.
I left a message. I've been
dealing with this real estate
thing. I was gonna write...
a whole damn report!
That's not how we work here.
You don't just leave a message
and take off.
What am I supposed to do,
check in every two seconds?
Yes, it's called accountability.
I'm not talking to you,
bitch!
Excuse me?
Get out
of my face!
That's enough!
Erin, this incident aside,
I don't think this is
the right place for you.
Okay? So, I'm gonna make
a few calls on your behalf
and find something else.
- Don't bother!
- I'm trying to help.
Bullshit. You're trying to make
yourself feel less guilty about
firing someone with three kids.
Well, fuck, if I'm gonna
help you do that!
Get back to work!
[Sighs]
[Metal Clanking]
What the hell
are you doing here?
I'm fixing the leak
under your sink.
Damn it, George,
I don't ask you
to do things like that.
Look at this mess
that you've made,
all this crap!
[Clanking Tools]
[George]
I'm not done with that yet.
Well, get it out...
Oh, Jesus!
Relax.
Shit!
Where did it go?
Where is it?
[George]
Somewhere back there.
It's right behind your foot.
It's going up your leg now.
Jesus!
Who fucking lives
like this, George?
Who lets their kids
run around in a place...
that is crawling with bugs
the size of house cats?
It's a simple thing, Erin.
All we have to do is
call an exterminator.
Everybody gets them.
I can't call
an exterminator.
I can't afford one.
I can't even afford my phone.
[Sighing]
I got fired.
What?
What do you mean you got fired?
You're working so hard.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't make one
fucking bit of difference.
[Sighs]
I don't know
what happened to me.
[Crying]
I mean...
God, I was Miss Wichita,
for Christ's sake.
Did I tell you that?
You are living
next door to a real, live,
fucking beauty queen.
- [Chuckles]
I still have my tiara.
And I thought it meant
I was gonna do something
important with my life,
that it meant I was someone.
You're someone to me.
Are you gonna be
something else that
I have to survive?
'Cause I'll tell you
the truth,
I'm not up to it.
So I get up on the stage,
in the center of the stage,
right?
I had a big bouquet of flowers
and I had my foot out like this
and I say,
[George Chuckles]
"I will devote my entire reign
as Miss Wichita...
"to bringing an end
to world hunger...
"and to the creation
of a peaceful Earth...
[Chuckling Continues]
For every man, woman
and child."
How long were you
gonna be Miss Wichita?
One year.
Of course,
by the time I got through
opening new supermarkets,
I only had a few weeks left
to work on hunger
and world peace.
World peace. Right.
[Fake Laughing] I don't know
what I was thinking about.
What about you, huh?
What about me?
What about you?
[Laughing]
Hey, baby, let me
tell you something.
Let me get that
out of your hair.
Oh.
Thank you.
Nice.
You're a very
special lady.
Don't be too nice to me,
okay?
Why?
Hmm, makes me nervous.
[Sighs]
[Beth Fussing]
Some slim pickings here,
baby.
[Doorbell Chimes]
Maybe that's Ed McMahon.
Let's go see.
Wrong Ed.
I'm sorry?
What are you doing here?
I had an interesting call
this afternoon
from Dr. Frankel...
from UCLA.
Oh, yeah?
He wanted you to know
that the legal limit
for hexavalent chromium...
is.05 parts per million.
And the rate you mentioned,
.58,
it could be responsible
for the cancers...
in that family
you asked about,
the Jensens.
Well, wasn't that
nice of him?
Isn't it funny
how some people go out
of their way to help people...
and others just fire them?
Look, I'm sorry.
You were gone. I assumed
you were off having fun.
Oh, and why the hell
would you assume that?
I don't know.
Maybe you look like someone
who has a lot of fun.
Oh.
So, by that standard, I should
assume you never get laid?
I'm married.
Look, what is all this?
What's the story
on this cancer stuff?
You want to know?
You have to hire me back.
I got a ton of bills to pay.
Fine. Fine.
So, Donna just put in
these new cabinets...
stained the wood and all...
when she gets a call
from somebody at PG&E...
saying there's a freeway
gonna be built...
and they want to buy her house
to put in an off-ramp
to the plant.
Meanwhile, the husband's sick
with Hodgkin's.
She's in and out of the hospital
with tumors,
believing one thing
has nothing to do
with the other.
Because PG&E told her
about the chromium?
Get this.
They had a seminar.
They invited
about 200 residents
from the area,
had it at the plant
in this warehouse,
telling them all
about chromium three
and how good it is for you...
when all the time
they're using chromium six.
[Beth Fussing]
T-T-That document
you found at the water board...
the one that says
about the bad chromium...
You didn't happen
to make a copy, did you?
Of course I did.
Could I have
a look at it?
I want a raise
and benefits,
including dental.
[Sighs]
Erin, this isn't the way
I do business.
What way is that?
Extortion.
Oh.
[Coos]
[Beth Laughs]
[Sighs]
Okay, a five percent raise.
We'll talk about benefits later.
Ten.
There are lots of other places
I could get work.
Ten percent raise
and benefits.
But that's it.
I'm drawing the line.
[Softly]
He's drawing the line.
[Coos]
This the only thing
you got?
So far, but that place
is a pigsty. I wouldn't
be surprised if there's more.
Yeah, I know how
those things are run.
They're a mess.
What makes you think
you can just walk
in there...
and find...
what we need?
They're called boobs, Ed.
[Scott]
Yes. She already is.
[Whirring]
I understand.
Okay, I agree.
I'm going to.
Right now.
[Hangs Receiver Up]
[Erin, Softly]
We're almost done.
So...
how are we doing?
We're doing great.
You...
[Crying]
[Crying Continues]
Good.
You've got quite a lot
done already,
so, um...
I'm sorry, but we need to have
those records back now, okay?
No.
[Crying]
These papers are a matter
of public record,
and I'm not leaving
until they're copied.
[Machine Whirring]
[Scott Sighs]
[Whirring Continues,
Beth Fussing]
[Stammering]
Fax these
to this number,
okay?
All of'em?
All of'em!
[Sighs]
[Beeping]
[Children Laughing]
[Laughing]
[Plant Horn Blaring]
[Blaring Continues]
[Donna]
An on-site monitoring well?
That means that...
It was right up on the PG&E
property over there.
And you say that this stuff,
this... hexavalent chromium...
[Sighs]
It's poisonous.
Yeah.
Well...
Erin...
it's just got to be different
than what's in our water
'cause ours is okay.
The guys from PG&E told me.
They sat right in the kitchen
and told me that it was fine.
I know, I know, but...
the toxicologist that
I've been talking to...
he gave me a list
of problems...
that can come
from hexavalent
chromium exposure.
Everything you all have
is on that list.
No, no, no.
No, that's not what...
That's not what
our doctor said.
He said that...
[Sighs]
Well, that one's
got absolutely nothing
to do with the other.
Right.
But PG&E paid
for that doctor.
[Sighs]
[Children Laughing,
Chattering]
[Laughing, Chattering
Continue]
[Continue Chattering]
[Laughing, Chattering
Continue]
Ashley! Shanna!
Get out of the pool!
How come?
'Cause I said so,
that's why!
That's it.
Okay, okay, girls.
The minute Brenda
sent that fax,
I'm saying the second
she pressed the "send"
button,
PG&E's claim department...
was on the phone to me
scheduling a meeting.
So you think that we...
Let me do it...
'cause you're
driving me nuts.
What?
So you think
we scared them,
don't you?
Well, they're
taking the trouble
to send someone.
Sure as hell sounds like
they're sitting up
and taking notice.
Mr. Foil?
In the interest of putting this
whole thing to rest,
PG&E is willing
to offer the Jensens
$250,000 for their home.
[Scoffs]
Two hundred and fifty thousand?
In terms of land value
out in Hinkley,
Mr. Masry, we feel that's
a more than fair price.
How about in terms
of medical expenses?
Two hundred and fifty thousand
isn't gonna come close...
to what this family's gonna have
to spend on doctors.
I understand they've
had a bad run of luck
healthwise.
They have my sympathies,
but that's not PG&E's fault.
You're kidding,
right?
Look at these readings.
PG&E's own technicians
documented...
toxic levels
of hexavalent chromium...
in those wells
on numerous occasions.
Everything
the Jensens
have had...
is proven reaction
to exposure to hexavalent
chromium.
They have had...
Breast cysts,
uterine cancer,
Hodgkin's disease,
immune deficiencies,
asthma, chronic nosebleeds...
A million things could have
caused those problems.
Poor diet, bad genes,
irresponsible lifestyle.
Our offer is final,
and it's more than fair.
Wait a minute.
I thought we were
negotiating here.
Two hundred and fifty thousand
dollars is all I'm authorized
to offer.
I'll present your offer
to my clients.
I doubt
they'll accept.
Mr. Masry...
before you go off
on some crusade,
you might want
to remember who it is
you're dealing with here.
PG&E's a $28-billion
corporation.
$28 billion!
I didn't know
it was that much!
Wow! 28 billion!
[Sighs]
Holy cow!
At least
they made an offer.
That wasn't an offer.
A million would have
been an offer.
They sent a mail clerk down
to jerk me off, waste my time!
- Why would they do that?
- Because they can.
You heard what that kid said.
They have $28 billion
at their disposal!
- They can afford to waste
all the time in the world.
- And you can't?
- You think I'm made of money?
- What are you yelling
at me for?
- Because I'm pissed off!
- Good!
- Fuck you!
- Fuck you back!
[Laughing]
[Laughing Continues]
[Continues Laughing]
I really hate you sometimes,
you know that?
Ah, you love me.
[Laughing Continues]
[Footsteps Approaching]
[Footsteps Continue]
You've been reading
for hours.
I'm a slow reader.
[Footsteps Departing]
[Door Closes]
[Man]
Uh, Erin Brockovich?
That's probably her
at that desk.
Excuse me.
Are you
Erin Brockovich?
Yeah.
Uh, I'm Tom... Robinson.
This is my wife Mandy.
Hi.
[Tom]
We used to live across
the street from the Jensens.
I think you know Donna.
[Erin]
Yeah.
Uh, PG&E bought our house
last year.
[Tom]
The vets said they had
a bunch of tumors and stuff...
and, you can see,
they couldn't really walk.
How many were born
like this?
Uh, 12 or 13
or so.
Yeah.
When Donna told us about you
and what you told her
about the chromium,
we figured
that might have something
to do with this too.
Yeah, it might.
May I keep these?
Yes.
Okay. Great.
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate it.
Um...
There's something else too.
What?
Um... this, uh...
Um... well, uh...
Mandy here has had...
five miscarriages.
I'm so sorry.
I figured it was
something I did...
like when I smoked
marijuana maybe...
or took
birth control pills.
But then Donna said
you thought chromium might be
to blame for her problems.
So I figured...
maybe it wasn't just me.
[Sighs]
Whoa.
[Kissing]
I have
to take a bath.
You should go in.
They're not asleep?
[Sighs]
Beth and Katie are.
Hey.
How was school?
Fine.
Did you do
your homework?
Yeah.
Any problems?
I know you're upset,
but... the way this job is,
things come up
at the last minute;
real important things
that I gotta deal with.
Fine!
Please don't be mad at me.
I'm doing this for us.
I know it's hard for you
to understand, but...
Don't you want Mommy
to be good at her job?
Hmm?
It's not like
I miss dinner all the time.
We all ate together last night.
You were reading
the whole time.
Okay.
[Honking Horn]
[Man]
You know, there's something
about this whole thing...
I don't quite understand,
Mr. Masry.
If PG&E messed
with our water,
why would they bother
saying anything about it
to us at all?
Why not just
keep quiet about it?
To establish
a statute of limitations.
In a case like this,
you only have one year...
from the time you first learn
about the problem to file suit.
So PG&E figures...
we'll let the cat out
of the bag, tell the people
the water's not perfect,
and if we can ride out the year
with no one suing,
we'll be in the clear forever.
But it was more than a year ago
that they told us.
It's okay.
We're not suing.
Not yet.
All we're doing is using
this information...
to get you a real nice
purchase price
on your house...
and, you two,
a comparable retroactive bonus
on your sale price.
That way,
PG&E can still look good
to their shareholders...
because they're not involved
in an ugly lawsuit.
All they're doing
is buying a little property.
It... doesn't say here
how much this thing
is gonna cost us.
My fee is 40% of whatever
you get awarded.
Boy, do I know
how you feel.
The first time
I heard that number, I said,
"You've got to be kidding me.
Forty goddamn percent?
I'm the one that's injured."
Erin...
"This joker sits at a desk,
and he wants to walk away
with almost half my reward?"
Erin, can l...
But then...
I asked him...
what he makes
if I don't get anything.
Then I don't
get anything either.
[Erin]
Plus he's out
all the costs.
So I realized...
he's taking a chance too.
You got a pen, honey?
Well, all right then.
Oh, I made a bundt cake.
Let me put on some coffee.
Who would like coffee and cake?
I do.
Thanks, but we have
to be getting back.
[Whispers]
Have a fucking
cup of coffee, Ed.
Coffee will be great.
Thank you.
[Donna]
All right.
I'll help you.
My wife makes
really good bundt cake.
I love bundt cake.
[Water Hose Running]
[Bob Linwood] Seems like
everybody in the family
ended up with a rash somehow.
It also seemed like no matter
what we did for it,
it always came back.
Over what kind
of period of time?
Oh... a long time.
You know, years.
Never did keep track of it.
Kids are sick.
Animals need to be fed.
Just couldn't
get rid of it.
That's all.
[Erin]
Well, Mrs. De Soto said...
that she wasn't
exactly sure what you had.
We know what it is.
It's gastro...
Gastrointestinal cancer.
Cancer. Yeah.
She got sick about...
nine months ago.
[Laura Ambrosino] Nine months ago.
[Mike Ambrosino]
They operated on her
about six months ago.
[Laura Ambrosino]
Mm-hmm. The intestine.
Right.
Hi, I'm Erin...
I know who you are.
Donna called me.
Oh.
Can I come in?
I told Donna
we're not interested
in getting involved.
Can I ask why?
What's the point?
Well, Donna told me
that you've been sick...
and that your kids
were sick...
You people don't give a shit.
Anything to get what you want.
[Erin]
It's good of you to have me in
when I just stopped by.
She's feeling
pretty good today.
She's doing well.
Mike Ambrosino remembered he had
seen you folks at the hospital
from time to time.
That's what
brought me out here.
[Chuckles]
Yeah.
We've been there
from time to time.
Yeah.
And you... Wooftie.
Aren't you a beauty?
[Rita Daniels Laughs]
You drive all
the boys crazy,
don't you?
[Chuckling]
I can see it in your eyes.
You drive them wild.
You do, don't you?
You torture them.
It's good for them.
Don't teach her anything
too early.
[Laughs]
Yeah.
She can't wait
to get on her new dress.
Isn't that right?
[Ted Daniels]
She wants to go back to school.
We're trying to do that...
in the next couple months.
Yeah, get her out
of her nightgown.
[Ted Daniels]
She's gonna do it.
Absolutely not.
That's crazy.
Why not?
Because I said no.
The only reason PG&E's
even talking to us...
is because
this is a quiet, little
real estate dispute.
We add plaintiffs,
suddenly we're in the middle
or a toxic tort...
with a statute problem
against a massive utility.
No, thank you.
Okay.
So I'll go
to Ted and Rita Daniels...
two of the nicest people
you could ever hope to meet...
who every single day watch
their little girl, Annabelle,
fight like a dog against cancer,
and I'll tell them
we can't help them because...
you just don't want
to work that hard.
Work hard?
Let me tell you something.
I've worked all my life.
I've built a firm
and managed to keep it alive...
through lawsuits,
injunctions and evictions.
I've survived
a quadruple bypass, cancer,
being born with one kidney
and having diabetes.
I've personally managed
to save a million dollars...
over 30 years of getting
some clients ten times that.
Don't tell me
I don't work hard.
Don't tell me I haven't
earned the right to stop,
take a breath and enjoy life.
And what the hell do you know
about any of this anyway?
Something like this, Erin...
It could take forever.
They're a huge corporation.
They could bury us in paperwork
for the next 15 years.
I'm just a guy
with a small, private firm!
Who happens to know
they poisoned people
and lied about it.
We can get these people.
With a little effort,
I really think we can just
nail their asses to the wall.
You do? With all
your legal expertise,
you believe that?
Don't you ever just know?
You also "just know" where
the money's coming from?
That's why most
of these cases settle:
Lack of money.
Do you know
what toxicologists
and geology experts cost?
We're looking
at 100 grand a month, easy.
I've already made
a huge dent in my savings.
We'll figure it out.
I don't know shit about shit,
but I know the difference
between right and wrong!
Lovers'quarrel?
Oh, bite my ass,
Krispy Kreme.
I feel you looking at me.
I'm sorry.
How many families
are we talking about?
Four more.
Eleven people so far.
You mean there's more?
I found one document
at the Water Board...
that was a toxic test well
reading from 1967.
A lot more people have lived
on that land since then.
[Sighs] This is
a whole different ball game,
a much bigger deal.
Kind of like David
and what's-his-name.
[Laughs]
It's kind of like David
and what's-his-name's
whole fucking family.
[Sighs]
Okay, here's the deal.
Lf, and only if,
you find all the evidence
to back this up,
I'll take it on.
You're doing the right thing,
Mr. Masry.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Remind me of that when
I'm filing for bankruptcy.
Of course,
gathering evidence is a big job.
A hell of a lot bigger
than just filing.
I'll be working a lot harder,
taking on more responsibility.
I don't believe this.
Another raise wouldn't hurt.
And I'm gonna be spending
a lot of time in my car,
so I'll probably be needing
one of those cell phones.
I don't believe this.
Just a little phone?
[Office Phone Ringing]
[Groans]
[Starts, Revs Engine]
Thank you!
[Katie Giggling]
Whoever's behind you.
[Matthew]
Just go ahead
and play. Go.
Roll the dice and play.
[Giggling]
Come on.
Aren't you gonna play?
Roll the dice.
Come on.
[Continues Giggling]
[Phone Ringing]
Come on.
Roll the dice.
Got it?
Hello.
Is this the Erin Pattee
Brockovich that's been snooping
around the water board?
Yeah. Who's this?
You should
watch your step.
A lady with three young children
really should think again.
Who is this?
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
[Caller Hangs Up]
[Children
Chattering]
[Turns Phone Off]
[Matthew]
No, no, no.
I'm not gonna quit because
of one creepy phone call.
Come on, Erin.
A job is supposed
to pay your bills,
not put you in danger.
I'm not in danger.
The phone might be tapped,
but that's usual.
What?
We've got a dead bolt.
It's not a big deal.
You don't think you're
a little out of your league?
No. See? See?
That's what those arrogant
PG&E fucks want me to think,
but they're wrong.
Erin, it doesn't have to be
so complicated. There are
plenty of jobs out there.
How would you know?
You mind telling me what
that's supposed to mean?
Nothing.
If you've got a problem
with me taking care
of your kids, just say so.
I didn't say that.
Because
I can get a job...
and you can leave
the kids with the chicken
fat lady again, okay?
Jesus, I said I'm sorry.
Keep your voice down.
Erin, I know what
these kids can sleep through.
I probably know better than you.
Hey, Scott,
tell me something.
Does PG&E pay you
to cover their ass...
or do you just do it
out of the kindness
of your heart?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
The fuck you don't.
Nobody calls me Pattee.
That heavy-breathing sicko
that called could have only
found out about me from you.
People are dying, Scott.
You've got document
after document here
that says why,
and you haven't said
one word about it.
I want to know how the hell
you sleep at night?
[Phone Ringing]
[Continues Ringing]
[Phone Beeps]
Hello.
I'm about to drive off the road,
I'm so tired.
[Yawning]
Keep me awake, will you?
What do you want, a joke?
No, I don't want a joke.
Tell me about your day.
What went on back there?
Come to think of it, we had
a pretty big event around here.
Yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Beth... started talking.
[Gasps]
What?
Beth? My Beth?
We're all
sitting around at lunch,
and she pointed at a ball
and said:
"Ball."
Out of the blue like that.
It was pretty intense,
seeing somebody's
first word.
All the words they'll
say out of their life,
that's the first word: Ball.
She just pointed
her little finger...
with her beautiful,
soft, chubby, little arm
and her little cheeks.
She was looking at it like
she had been looking at it
for nine months...
and just couldn't
get it out, but
knowing what it was.
She didn't look away
or anything.
She was just sitting there
with her arm out.
You should have seen
Matthew and Katie and me.
[Crying Softly]
Our jaws just dropped.
We must have stood there
for three or four minutes.
She just had
her arm out like that,
you know? "Ball."
Her little lips
wrapped around it.
[Laughs Softly]
[Sighs]
It was great.
It was intense.
(sing)(sing)
Hi. I brought
some stuff you might be
interested in seeing.
My name's Erin,
and I'll be here all day.
Let's go over
to these nice ladies.
Hi. How are you?
[Woman] Good.
My name is Erin.
I brought some information.
If you want to have a look
and if you have any questions,
just let me know.
Excuse me, ladies.
I'm Ed Masry.
I'm the lawyer involved
in the case.
I thought you might
like to read these.
If you have any questions,
I'll be here all day.
Sounds good.
Thanks so much.
Your phone number
in this?
There's more important
information than that
in there. Trust me.
Hey.
I'm bored.
So are the kids.
Okay.
Well, I'm a little
busy here, honey.
We invited all these
people here, and I have to...
I'm sorry. You know what?
I have an idea.
Please, please.
Can you just take her?
She's getting very heavy.
I can do my work faster
if you take her.
(sing)(sing) [George Singing
Lullaby Softly]
Got a knee for me?
Hello.
Hello, sweetness.
Guess what.
What?
I would like to go home.
You get everything done?
We got a lot of work done.
Sweetie.
I think I ate
three watermelons.
Piggyback.
Let's go, brother.
Get on.
Be careful.
[Woman]
Erin?
Get on me now.
Erin, excuse me.
This is Nelson Perez.
Oh, hi.
He works
at the compressor station.
Hi, nice to meet you.
PG&E.
Oh, hi.
Wow. Uh...
I've come
at a bad time?
No, no, no.
Can you just
give me one...
Of course. Sure.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
Uh... you know what?
Why don't you guys
go ahead without me,
[Scoffs]
And I will
get a ride with Ed.
No, Mom.
No, sweetie, I'll be
right behind you.
I'll be right behind you,
all right? Okay?
I really...
This is so...
Fine. Go, go, go, go.
I'll see you tonight, okay?
Okay?
Get down, bud.
[Sighs]
Hey, you all right?
Hang on tight there.
Help your sister
with her shoes.
Come on, let's go.
[Motorcycle Engines Roaring]
Mr. Perez, this is so helpful.
Is it okay if I write some
of this down?
Sure, sure.
I have so many questions.
I want to know...
how the plant works,
the cooling towers,
just everything, so...
They use the hexachrome here,
in these cooling towers,
as an anticorrosive.
Then they dump
the excess water
into these ponds.
I don't remember seeing
any ponds out there.
This is an old picture.
They've been covered over,
and not too carefully.
If you dig one inch
under the surface,
dirt's as green
as a fucking shamrock.
That's what caused
the contamination?
Well, it didn't help,
but, no, the problem
actually started on the bottom.
According to...
this...
in most cases, you
would line these ponds...
so this shit didn't
seep into the ground.
But guess what?
They skipped that step?
Mm-hmm.
Here are the ponds.
The plume comes down like this,
and Hinkley is down here.
It's like 14 years
of hexachrome just flowing
into the groundwater.
Jesus.
And this guy just offered
all this information?
Yeah. Nelson cares
what's in those ponds.
He used to spend half the day
wading around in them.
That was his job.
Shit.
What's the matter?
I don't know
if we can pull this off.
This is a monster case.
We're up to 411 plaintiffs.
We've taken
162 declarations.
Probably hundreds more
out there have moved away.
We'll have to find them.
It's taking time, manpower.
Money's going out.
Nothing's coming in.
I'll have to take
a second mortgage
on the house.
So?
"So?"
So... I have to tell you.
I've been making inquiries
with other firms,
bigger firms,
to share some of the cost.
They all said,
"No, we don't have it."
That's bullshit.
We've got PG&E by the balls.
PG&E Hinkley by the balls,
but nobody's going
to get rich...
unless we can pin this
on PG&E corporate
in San Francisco.
What do you mean?
PG&E corporate
is claiming...
they had no way of knowing
what was going on
in Hinkley.
- Oh, they knew.
- Show me the document
that proves it.
Then they didn't know.
If they didn't know, we can't
hit them with punitive damages.
With punitive damages, we're
talking about a sum of money...
that can actually
have some effect...
on these
people's lives.
So what do we do now?
Let's assume there are documents
connecting PG&E Hinkley
with PG&E corporate,
and they know
these documents exist.
We take our 400 or so plaintiffs
and everything you've dug up,
we file a lawsuit
to provoke a reaction,
to see if they offer
a reasonable settlement
or just throw more paper at us.
That sounds great.
Let's do that.
There's a downside.
PG&E will submit a demurrer,
a list of reasons
attacking each complaint,
claiming that each
cause of action has no merit.
If the judge agrees with them,
he'll dismiss our case.
PG&E will have
no reason to settle,
and it's all over.
[Scoffs]
So, basically,
it all comes down...
to what this
one judge decides.
Basically, yeah.
Jesus.
[Sighs]
I'd got so used
to having them
come up benign...
I guess I just
didn't expect it.
[Sighs]
I wish I had longer
to get used to the idea.
You think
if you got no uterus
and no breasts...
you're still
technically a woman?
Sure, you are.
Yeah, you're just...
You're actually
a happier woman...
because you don't have
to worry about maxi pads
and underwire.
[Stifling Sobs]
[Sobbing]
We're gonna get them,
Erin, aren't we?
You gotta promise me
that we're gonna get them.
[Continues
Crying]
Yeah.
[Sighing]
[Judge]
All right, I have before me...
a complaint
on behalf of the residents
of Hinkley, California,
who have filed this lawsuit
against Pacific Gas
and Electric...
for damages, medical expenses
and personal trauma...
due to contamination
of the groundwater...
in their area
by the defendant.
And I have here
84 motions to strike...
and demurrers
submitted by representatives
of Pacific Gas and Electric,
each attacking the validity
of this complaint.
I have reviewed
all of the information
carefully.
I'm ready to give my decision.
Before I do, is there anything
anyone wants to say?
- No, Your Honor.
Very well.
In the matter of the plaintiffs
of Hinkley, California,
versus Pacific Gas and Electric,
it is the order of this court...
that each of the 84 motions
to strike and demurrers
are denied...
and the causes of action
against Pacific Gas and Electric
are upheld.
On a more personal note,
as a resident here in Barstow,
which is not far from Hinkley,
I am disturbed
by reference to evidence...
that suggests that not only
was hexavalent chromium used...
but that your clients
actually sent these residents...
pamphlets telling them
that it was good for them.
Tell your clients
they're going to trial.
[Erin]
Jesus, they look like
the Secret Service.
Intimidation.
Let the games begin.
Show them
into the conference room.
Donald, Anna,
I want to talk to you
for a minute.
[Ed]
Counselors.
Let's be honest here.
$20 million is more money
than these people
have ever dreamed of.
See, now that
pisses me off.
First of all,
since the demurrer, we have
more than 400 plaintiffs,
and, let's be honest,
we all know there
are more out there.
They may not be
the most sophisticated people,
but they do know how to divide.
$20 million isn't shit
when you split it between them.
Erin...
[Erin]
Second of all,
these people don't dream
about being rich.
They dream about being able
to watch their kids
swim in a pool...
without worrying they'll
have to have a hysterectomy
at the age of 20...
like Rosa Diaz,
a client of ours.
Or have their spine
deteriorate like Stan Bloom,
another client of ours.
So before you come back here
with another lame-ass offer,
I want you to think
real hard about what your
spine is worth, Mr. Walker.
Or what you might expect someone
to pay you for your uterus,
Ms. Sanchez.
Then you take out
your calculator,
and you multiply
that number by a hundred.
Anything less than that
is a waste of our time.
We had that water
brought in special
for you folks.
It came from a well
in Hinkley.
[Stifles Chuckle,
Clears Throat]
I think this meeting's over.
Damn right it is.
[Door Opens, Closes]
What the fuck, George?
Did a bomb blow up?
You letting the kids run wild?
What's that?
I saw them
in a mall one day.
I said, "Damn...
those would look good
on those beautiful ears."
So I bought them and I said,
"Next time Erin does something
nice or says something nice...
I'll surprise her with them."
You know how long ago
that was?
Six months ago.
I'm sorry...
So what
I'm thinking is...
Erin, either you gotta
find a different job
or a different guy.
I mean...
there may be many men
out there who don't mind
being the maid...
and getting nothing in return,
but I sure ain't one of them.
I can't leave my job, George.
Yes, you can.
You can just quit.
People do it all the time.
How can you ask me to do that?
This job...
For the first time in my life,
I got people respecting me.
Up in Hinkley,
I walk into a room
and everybody shuts up...
to hear if
I got something to say.
I never had that before, ever.
Please, don't ask me
to give it up.
What about what
your kids are giving up?
I'm doing more
for my kids now than I did
living with my parents.
One day,
they'll understand that.
- What about me?
- What about you?
[Scoffs]
You think either one of the men
who gave me those children...
asked me what I wanted
before he walked away?
All I've ever done
is bend my life around...
what men decide they need.
Well, not now.
I'm sorry. I won't do it.
Well... Erin, I'm not them.
So... what more do I have to do
to prove that to you?
Stay.
What for? Huh?
You got a raise.
You can afford day care.
You don't need me.
[Radio Announcer]
Let's take a look
at the five-day forecast.
This is what you can expect
in the high desert.
Ninety-three the high tomorrow.
The overnight low will be 60.
Twenty percent chance of showers
for most of the afternoon.
[Announcer Continues,
Indistinct]
[Turns Off Radio]
[Erin]
Hi.
Thank you.
[Erin]
We can get them, Pamela.
We can.
I don't want to feel it
all over again...
and then not have it
come out right.
I don't know
if I could handle that,
put the kids through that.
The thing is,
it doesn't matter...
whether you win, lose
or draw here.
You were lied to.
You're sick,
and your kids are sick
because of those lies.
If for no other reason,
you have to come together...
to stand up in a courtroom
and say that.
I'd bring the kids
into the hospital...
with towels soaked
from their nosebleeds.
They called county services
because they assumed the kids
were being abused.
[Erin]
Am I gonna get the best
behavior in the office?
[Matthew]
No.
What's with the attitude?
I just need cool.
I need quiet. Okay?
Hello? Am I alone
in the car? Yes?
I said, "We'll see."
I don't want to talk about it.
All the other moms
gave permission.
I don't care.
So when can I get
a frickin' answer?
Don't talk to me like that!
Randy's mom
said yes right away.
Goddamn it, Matthew!
Randy's mom doesn't work,
and Randy's dad
did not leave her.
So figuring out who can take who
to roller hockey is probably
easier at Randy's house.
[Erin Sighs]
[Rosalind]
Hey, Erin.
Hey.
Okay.
I'll be as quick as I can.
Matthew, can you watch
your sister?
Matthew?
All right, fine.
Come here, Beth.
Can I come
with you?
No, baby.
I'll just be a second.
[Clears Throat]
[Phone Ringing]
[Ed]
Thank you. I'm only sorry
you didn't get to meet Erin.
[Man]
I will. We have
a lot of work to do together.
[Ed]
Yep. Okay.
Thanks for coming over.
Erin, I was just talking
about you. This is our new
partner, Kurt Potter.
He'll be handling
Hinkley now.
[Sighs]
I see what you mean
about a secret weapon.
It's great to meet you.
You've done a fabulous job.
I'll be seeing you.
Thanks.
I appreciate you
coming over.
Yep.
[Opening Envelope]
- What?
- "Our new partner"?
When was
I gonna hear about this,
in the monthly newsletter?
Just listen.
Did I ever tell you
about that airline case?
What the fuck
are you talking about?
A few years back
I was trying this
airline case,
and I got my ass kicked
by this guy.
He just buried me in paper.
Brutal.
This guy was the toughest mother
I'd ever been up against.
- Make a point.
- It was Kurt Potter.
When we got the PG&E decision
from the judge,
I called him
and asked him to partner.
- He didn't hesitate.
- He wouldn't hesitate now.
We did all the fucking work!
Where was he before?
It doesn't matter.
Erin, will you listen to me?
You want to win this?
He just gave me this check.
It covers all
our expenses to date,
and he's got more
toxic tort experience
than anyone in the state.
This is good news.
By the way,
I got Pamela Duncan.
Hey.
I'll open, Mommy.
You want to open
the can for Mommy?
Here, I'll help you.
Can you turn it?
[Motorcycle Revving]
[Gasps]
Hi, George.
Let's go see.
[Revving
Continues]
Let's go see.
[Revving Continues]
[Motorcycle Departing]
- Erin Brockovich?
- Yeah.
Package
from Masry & Vititoe.
Thank you.
What's in here?
Baby.
There's no baby in here.
What is it?
A dolly.
It's a dolly?
It's...
Look.
"Look" is right.
[Gasps]
Do you see that?
I want that.
I want that too.
It's our lucky day.
Matthew! Katie!
PG&E has requested
that we submit
to binding arbitration.
What's that?
That's where we try
the case without a jury,
just before a judge.
It's called
a test trial.
The judges decision is final.
There is no appeal.
How many plaintiffs
do you have?
Six hundred
and thirty-four.
They'll never try
that many all at once.
So we need to get them
together in groups
of 20 or 30;
worst cases, the most
life-threatened, the sickest
in the first group.
And so on
and so on.
Each one gets a go
before the judge
to determine damages.
PG&E has proposed that
they're liable...
anywhere between 50
and 400 million.
So... Wait a minute.
Let me just get this straight...
If we went to trial,
PG&E could stretch this
over ten years...
with appeal
after appeal.
Those people
in Hinkley...
These people
are expecting a trial.
That's what
we told them.
They won't understand this.
Kurt thinks it's
the best way to go.
[Kurt]
I promise you that we'll be
very sensitive on this point.
We will make sure that they
understand this is the only way
we can go forward at this time.
But we have a lot
of work to do...
before we even broach
that subject.
Why don't I take Erin
down the hall,
so we can start on this stuff,
and I'll fill her in on the rest
of the details.
[Kurt]
Thanks.
Those are my files.
Yeah, we had them
couriered over.
Listen, good work.
They're a great start.
We're just going to have to
spend a little time filling in
the holes in your research.
Excuse me.
Theresa, is it?
There are no holes
in my research.
No offense. There are just
some things we need that you
probably didn't know to ask.
Don't talk to me
like I'm an idiot, okay?
I may not have a law degree,
but I've spent 18 months
on this case,
and I know more about these
plaintiffs than you ever will.
Erin, you don't even have
phone numbers for some of them.
Whose number do you need?
[Theresa]
Everyone's.
This is a lawsuit.
We need to be able
to contact the plaintiffs.
I said,
"Whose number do you need?"
You don't know 600 plaintiffs'
numbers by heart.
- Annabelle Daniels.
- 714-454-9346.
Ten years old, eleven in May.
Lived on the plume since birth.
Wanted to be
a synchronized swimmer,
so she spent every minute
she could in the PG&E pool.
She had a tumor
on her brain stem
detected last November,
an operation on Thanksgiving,
shrunk it with radiation
after that.
Her parents are Ted and Rita.
Ted's got Crohn's disease.
Rita has chronic headaches
and nausea and underwent
a hysterectomy last fall.
Ted grew up in Hinkley.
His brother Robbie
and his wife May...
and their five children...
Robbie, Jr., Martha, Ed,
Rose and Peter...
also lived
on the plume.
Their number is 454-9554.
You want their diseases?
Okay, look, I think we got off
on the wrong foot here.
That's all you got, lady:
Two wrong feet
and fucking ugly shoes.
[Erin]
She insulted me.
Bullshit. It was
a misunderstanding.
Instead of handling it
politely, instead of
treating her with respect,
you insult her.
Why the fuck
should I respect her?
Just because she's not
supporting three kids...
with no husband
and no education,
doesn't make her an idiot.
Just because
she dresses like a lawyer,
doesn't mean she didn't
work her ass off...
in law school
and shit positions
to earn her way.
Excuse me
for not going to law school.
Law school?
I'd settle
for charm school!
[Cow Mooing]
Mister... Mister...
Mr. Linwood!
[Clearing Throat]
Mr. Linwood?
Bob?
[Erin Blowing Nose]
6086 Ridge Road,
[Clears Throat]
Hinkley, California.
714...
[Sneezes]
455...
[Theresa]
Okay, now, if you could
walk me through...
all of the elements of...
Annabelle's illnesses.
Specific details,
when the symptoms began...
prior to the first
medical visit.
If you could reserve
sentimental embellishments,
I'd appreciate it.
They're not gonna help you
in court.
All right.
So I just need facts,
dates... time.
[Erin] I know Theresa
isn't real warm, but they say
she's a good lawyer.
[Ted]
She's asking the same
questions you asked.
I already told you everything.
I don't want her coming
to the house again.
She's kind of stuck-up,
and she upsets Annabelle.
If you don't like Theresa,
that's okay.
You know how important
Annabelle is to me.
Ed and I are still here
for you.
I called Ed two days ago,
and he still hasn't
called me back.
Now I hate to say this,
but... everyone's pretty upset
about this arbitration thing.
What?
Pamela's written a letter
in the Hinkley news...
telling everybody
to get new lawyers,
that we've been lied to.
Is it true?
No.
[Stammering]
Did you?
I'm telling you the truth,
and I will get
to the bottom of all this.
Don't lie to us.
I will take care of this.
I promise.
We're trusting you here.
Thanks.
I'll talk to you soon, okay?
All right. Bye-bye.
Ed, I'm not saying
it's not a strong case.
If it wasn't a strong case,
every demurrer wouldn't
have been dismissed.
I wouldn't be here.
What I am saying
is we still don't have...
a smoking gun that ties
San Francisco to Hinkley;
something that proves
that prior to 1987...
PG&E corporate knew
the water was bad in Hinkley
and did nothing about it.
[Rosalind]
Hey, Erin, I thought
you were taking a sick day.
So did I.
What's going on
in there?
A meeting
about the PG&E thing.
Are you sure?
Yep.
[Kurt]
We can find it
or we don't have a big win.
Can I take a brief break here
for a moment?
I'll be right back.
[Arguing, Indistinct]
[Arguing Continues]
You told me you weren't feeling
great. I wanted you to rest.
You know, that is bullshit.
Get in here.
If I was on my deathbed,
if it helped you,
you'd drag me out of it!
How could you
take this away from me?
Nobody's taking anything.
Bullshit!
You stuck me in Siberia...
dictating to some
goddamn steno clerk...
so you could
finish this without me!
They screwed up, Erin!
Do I have your attention now?
They admit it.
The arbitration proposal
they sent might as well have
been written in Sanskrit...
for all the sense it made
to the people in Hinkley.
I know. L-I spoke to Ted.
Pamela Duncan wouldn't even
get on the phone with me!
Pamela's got everybody
seeing red with that letter
she wrote to the press.
She called us thieves.
They're all listening
to her.
The whole thing
is about to fall apart!
Why? Why?
Before we even go
to arbitration,
we have to get
the plaintiffs to agree.
How many?
Usually they're required
to get about 70%.
PG&E is demanding 90.
In other words, everybody.
Now do you understand?
This is serious.
And what?
I'm not serious?
You're emotional.
You're erratic.
You say any goddamn thing
that comes into your head.
You make this personal
and it isn't.
Not personal?
That is my work, my sweat,
my time away from my kids!
If that's not personal,
I don't know what is!
[Coughing]
Come on.
Go home.
Get well.
You're no good
to me sick.
I need you,
all right?
This case needs you.
Did you tell them that?
Binding arbitration
isn't all that different
from a trial.
It's overseen by a judge,
evidence is presented
in much the same way.
[Man]
And then a jury decides?
[Coughs]
Oh, no. Sorry I forgot
to mention that.
There's no jury
in binding arbitration.
[Crowd Murmuring Loudly]
- No jury and no appeal.
- [Crowd Continues Murmuring]
What option do we have
if we don't like the result?
You have none.
The judge's decision is final.
Not a good answer.
[Ed] We don't anticipate
that being a problem.
As I already told you,
it's definitely between
$50 and $400 million.
Well, which?
There's a big
difference there.
I wouldn't like
to speculate at this point.
[Tom Mumbling]
Well, how does it
get divided?
- Yeah. Who gets what?
- [Crowd Chattering]
My medical bills
started two years ago, before
some of the other people here.
My daughter has been in and out
of hospitals more than his.
It shouldn't matter
when it started.
[Crowd Agreeing]
Just a minute, please.
People, listen, please!
The point we have
to address tonight...
is getting everyone
to agree that going
binding arbitration...
is preferable to a trial
that could go on for ten years
before you see any money.
Maybe some of us want
to wait ten years.
[Crowd Chattering]
Everyone has to agree
or no one has a chance.
Those of you about to leave,
I'd like you to keep
this date in mind:
1978.
That's the year
of the Love Canal controversy,
and those people are still
waiting for their money.
Think about where you'll be
in 15 or 20 years. Huh?
[Crowd Murmuring]
Look, everyone,
is this a big decision?
Absolutely.
But I do not believe
this is a sellout.
This is the best shot
at getting everyone
some money now!
You and I both know...
there are people in this room
who can't afford to wait...
to take that chance.
Are you gonna make them wait?
So how many
altogether?
[Sighs]
We got just about everybody
that came here tonight,
but that still leaves us
about 150 short.
Oh, shit.
[Clears Throat]
We'll have to go
door-to-door.
I gotta go
pick up my kids.
You need a hand
with that?
No, I got it.
Hey... you did good.
We'll see.
Yeah.
Hey.
Thanks for coming.
[Sighs]
Don't take them anywhere
on your bike, okay?
I'll give you some money
for a cab if you want
to go somewhere.
[Chuckles]
I got money.
So how long
is this gonna take?
Uh... I don't know.
A few days.
You got your own room.
I am really sorry, George.
Have the kids eaten?
No.
(sing)(music) I've wept for those
who suffer long (music)
(sing)(music) But how I weep
for those who've gone (music)
(sing)(music) Into rooms of grief
and questioned wrong (music)
(sing)(music) But keep on killing (music)
(sing)(music) It's in the soul
to feel such things (music)
(sing)(music) But weak to watch
without speaking (music)
(sing)(music) Oh, what mercy
sadness brings (music)
(sing)(music) If God be willing (music)
[George]
You want to get some pancakes?
Let's go. Everybody, up.
Everybody, up today.
All right.
Let's get some pancakes.
[Erin]
What time is it?
It's early.
I'm gonna take your car
and get some breakfast.
Mm-hmm.
No, I need my car.
We'll be back in a minute.
Okay.
Get some sleep.
Hey, Matt, buddy.
Let's go.
What?
Put it down.
Let's go.
I'll be there in a minute.
Let's go get some
pancakes, girlie.
Come on.
Baby, don't play with that.
It took me so long
to get it organized.
Will you put that back?
Please?
This girl is
the same age as me.
She's one of the sick people?
Uh... she is, but...
that's why I'm helping her.
We'll get her some medicine
and make her feel better.
Why can't her own mama
help her?
Because her own mom
is real sick too.
[Sighs]
I'll bring you back
some breakfast.
You want eggs?
Eggs would be great.
[Door Closes]
[Chuckles Softly]
Eggs would be perfect.
Hey, Matt.
Hey, Erin,
how are you?
That's good.
So, been at this
all day?
Yeah.
You look tired.
You want some coffee?
I'd love some.
I'll make
a fresh pot.
Thanks.
[Men Laughing]
Hey,
don't I know you?
I don't think so.
Sure, you were
at the barbecue
in Hinkley...
and at the town meeting.
Hmm.
I was watching you.
I had my eye on you.
How nice.
Sure, you were talking
to everybody...
and writing down
a lot of stuff.
When I saw you,
I said to myself,
"There's something
about her.
I really like
that girl."
Matt, can I get that coffee
to go?
Sure thing.
I feel like I can talk
to you too.
Like you're the type
of person I could
say anything to.
Here you go.
Great.
What do I owe you?
There's no charge.
Thanks, Matt.
Well,
nice talking to you.
Would it be important to you
if I told you that when I worked
at the Hinkley plant,
I destroyed documents?
Maybe.
[Sets Down Keys, Purse]
What did you say
your name was?
Charles Embry.
Charles, Erin.
Nice to meet you.
[Sighs]
Can you excuse me
for just a quick...
Sure.
I'm just gonna run
to the...
[Panting]
[Phone Beeping]
Oh, come on.
Oh, you fucking piece of crap
with no signal!
Fuck! Oh.
[Phone Rings]
Yeah?
[Erin]
Ed. Ed, oh, my God.
This guy Charles
said that he destroyed records.
He worked at Hinkley.
Slow down, slow down.
I'm trying to relax
and this guy tells me...
Who? Who?
Charles Embry.
First I thought he was trying
to kill me, but then I thought
he was trying to pick me up.
Maybe he is, but why would
he say that? Why would he
use that as his line?
It's crazy.
[Stammering]
Shit.
Now go back and see
if he'll make a declaration.
A declaration.
Yeah, but be careful.
Don't scare him off.
Now stay calm, stay calm.
Remember, if it weren't for you,
I'd be in Palm Springs now.
You're good at talking
people into things.
Don't pepper him with questions.
Don't do that.
Just... Just let...
People want to tell their story.
Just let him talk.
Let him do all
the talking, all right?
Okay.
[Erin Approaches,
Sighs, Puts Down Purse]
Sorry.
[Clears Throat]
Would you like another beer
or...
My cousin passed away
yesterday.
He had kidney tumors,
no colon.
His intestines
were eaten away.
Forty-one years old.
I remember seeing him
over at the plant.
He's be cleaning
the cooling towers,
wearing one of those...
What do you
call them?
Mask?
Yeah, yeah.
Doctors' masks.
They'd be soaked in red
from the nosebleeds.
I was working
in the compressor.
Out of nowhere,
the supervisor calls me up
to the office...
and says,
"I'm gonna give you
a shredder machine...
and send you on down
to the warehouse to get rid
of the documents stored there."
Did he say why?
Nope...
and I didn't ask.
Did you get a look
at the stuff you destroyed?
A lot of dull stuff.
Vacation schedules
and the like.
But then there were
a few memos...
about the holding ponds,
the water in them...
and readings
from the test wells.
Stuff like that.
You were told
to destroy those?
That's right.
Of course, as it turns out,
I wasn't a very good employee.
[Chuckles]
Good morning.
Ed, Erin,
what's this?
May I?
[Ed]
Definitely. Go ahead.
[Erin Sighs]
Well... you know what,
Mr. Potter?
We completely forgot
your birthday this year,
and seeing as how
you've been so good to me,
it seemed a terrible oversight.
So what Ed and I
have been doing
the last few days...
is putting together
a present for you.
Six hundred
and thirty-four.
They're all signed.
Every single one.
Holy shit.
Now, don't go
getting jealous, Theresa.
She's getting jealous.
We have something
for you too.
Internal PG&E documents
all about the contamination.
The one
that I like best says...
I'm paraphrasing,
but it says: Yes,
the water's poisonous,
but it would be better
for all involved...
if this matter was not discussed
with the neighbors.
It's to the Hinkley station
from PG&E headquarters,
stamped,
"Received March 1966."
[Stammering]
H-How did you do this?
Well, seeing as
I have no brains
or legal expertise...
and Ed was losing all faith
in the system...
[Ed] Completely.
No faith, no faith.
I just went out there
and performed sexual favors:
634 blow jobs
in five days.
I'm really quite tired.
[Chuckles]
[Sighs]
[Ed Chuckling]
I'm still not sure
why you wanted me to come.
I want to show you
what you helped do.
Hey.
[Donna]
Hi.
How are you
feeling today?
Good, good.
It's a good day.
Oh, I'm glad.
Well, come on in.
What a nice surprise
this is.
Um... Donna...
I wanted to come out here
instead of calling...
because the judge
came back with a number.
[Sighs]
Uh...
for the whole group
or... for us?
Both.
He's gonna make them pay
333 million.
[Sighs, Laughs]
Oh, my God.
And...
And, um...
he's gonna make them
give 5 million of that
to your family.
Five million dollars?
Five million dollars.
[Laughing]
I don't even know
how much money that is.
Well, it's enough.
It's enough for whatever
you could ever need...
or whatever your girls need
or your girls' girls need.
It will be enough.
[Crying]
Oh, Erin...
[Continues Crying]
Thank you so much.
[Softly]
It's over now.
[Donna Continues Crying]
I don't know what
I would have done without you.
It's a good day.
[Laughing]
Yes.
This is too much.
[Rosalind]
Masry & Vititoe.
Can l... Shoot.
[Phone Ringing]
Hi, I have a delivery
for Ed Masry.
It's the last office
down the corridor on the right.
Thank you.
Masry & Vititoe...
Damn it. Does anyone...
know anything
about these phones?
[Ed]
Everybody loves the desk
you picked out for me.
It's great.
Yeah.
[Knocking]
And guess who's on the cover
of Los Angeles Lawyer magazine?
Talk to you later, baby.
Bye.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I would rather walk her
through this in person.
There's some things
I want to show her:
Visual aids and documents.
If you could just
tell her I won't take up
too much of her time.
Right.
It's a little more
complicated than Hinkley,
so let me do that.
Tell her I'm not a lawyer.
That may help.
Great.
Why don't you give me
the address now?
Just in case.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
All right.
Thanks so much. Bye.
[Sighs]
What's up?
I, uh...
I have your bonus check.
Oh, yea...
But... now...
I want you to be prepared.
The figure's not exactly
what we discussed.
Why not?
Because,
after careful
consideration,
I felt that figure
was not... appropriate.
Although
you may not agree,
you'll have to trust
my experience...
Trust?
You want me to trust you?
Do me a favor, Ed.
Don't use big words
you don't understand.
It's a complicated issue.
You're not a qualified lawyer.
I did a job.
You should
reward me accordingly.
It's not complicated.
That is
the fucking
problem.
All you lawyers do
is complicate situations
that aren't complicated.
Do you know why people think
all lawyers are backstabbing,
bloodsucking scumbags?
Because they are.
I cannot believe you are
doing this to me now...
when I'm up to my ass
in Kettleman plaintiffs,
which looks like double
the amount we had in Hinkley.
You expect me
to go out there,
leave my kids to be
looked after by strangers,
knock on doors,
get these people to trust you
with their lives, and the whole
time you're screwing me!
I want you to know
something, Ed. It is
not about the number.
It is about the way my work
is valued in this firm.
It's about how no matter
what I do, you're not...
As I was saying,
I decided that
the figure you proposed...
was inappropriate.
So I increased it.
Do they teach beauty queens
how to apologize?
Because you suck at it.
Uh, thank you, Ed.
(sing)(music) I hitched a ride (music)
(sing)(music) With a vending machine
repairman (music)
(sing)(music) He said he's been down
this road more than twice (music)
(sing)(music) He was high
on intellectualism (music)
(sing)(music) I've never been there
but the brochure looks nice (music)
(sing)(music) Jump in
Let's go (music)
(sing)(music) Lay back
Enjoy the show (music)
[Knocking]
(sing)(music) Everybody gets high (music)
(sing)(music) Everybody gets low (music)
(sing)(music) These are the days
when anything goes (music)
(sing)(music) Every day
is a winding road (music)
(sing)(music) I get a little bit closer (music)
(sing)(music) Every day is a faded sign (music)
(sing)(music) I get a little bit closer
to feeling fine (music)
(sing)(music) Every day is a winding road (music)
}}