Our father has
instructed us to tell you
that his alliance
with the North can continue
if his terms are met.
Lord Frey requires
Lord Edmure
to wed one
of his daughters.
It's hard to say
which of the four of us
is getting the worst
of this arrangement.
Probably Sansa.
Though Loras
will certainly come to know
a deep and singular
misery.
Who's going to tell her?
Good afternoon,
Lord Tyrion.
I was just trying on a gown
for King Joffrey's wedding.
Yes, it should be
quite a wedding.
I will allow you
to go to King's Landing
as restitution for the mistakes
my soldiers made.
And you will swear
to tell your father
that I had nothing to do
with your maiming.
- My lady.
- She won't be going with you.
Let's play a game.
Which body part
do you need the least?
How many times has
the Lord brought him back?
Six.
He sent you to us
for a reason.
You have someone
He needs.
You told me
I could be one of you.
this was a brotherhood.
You will make kings
rise and fall.
The visions
take their toll.
He's having one now?
- I saw Jon Snow.
- At Castle Black?
He was on the wrong side
of the Wall,
surrounded by enemies.
♪ Game of Thrones 3x07 ♪
The Bear and the Maiden Fair
Original Air Date on May 12, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪
How far are we?
About a week, I think.
You think?
You don't know?
When we went to Castle Black,
we took the kingsroad.
You and your roads.
Is that how you lot
do your fighting?
You march down the road banging
drums and waving banners?
Most of the time, yes.
How do the men holding
the banners fight?
They don't, really.
It's a great honor
to carry your house sigil.
And the drummers--
is that a great honor, too?
Usually it's the young boys
banging the drums.
So what good are they?
- They help the men march.
- How?
Well, it's--
it's the rhythm.
Oh, you mean right foot,
left foot,
right foot,
left foot, right foot?
You need help
remembering that?
When Mance gives the signal
and we hit Castle Black,
we won't be banging on drums
to let them know we're coming.
No.
No, you're just gonna
light the biggest fire
the North has ever seen
to let them know you're coming.
You know nothing,
Jon Snow.
She's right, you don't.
I know you cut me
loose on the Wall.
Cut her loose, too.
Do you see her
sulking about it?
That's because she understands
the way things are.
And are you gonna
share it with me?
The deep wisdom you found
inside the head of a bird?
People work together
when it suits them.
They're loyal
They love each other
when it suits them.
And they kill each other
She knows that,
you don't.
Which is why you'll
never hold onto her.
That rain will cost us
another day.
Frey will wait.
He knows we're coming.
Lord Walder is prickly
by nature.
Prickly?
That what you call it?
Might be the least
pleasant man I've ever met.
- Yes, and that is why--
- I've seen wet shits
I liked better
than Walder Frey.
Apologies, Your Grace.
Spent too many years around
lancers and pikemen.
I've spent the last two years
nursing wounded men,
watching them
bleed and die.
I'm not afraid
of wet shits.
Lord Frey will take
this delay as a slight.
He can take it
as he likes.
He's getting
the wedding he wanted.
He's getting a wedding.
It was a king he wanted.
Edmure is the best match
a Frey has had
in the history
of their house.
We should all
get some sleep.
If you don't put
some clothes on,
I can't promise
I won't attack you again.
Attack. Attack.
Who are you writing?
My mother.
- Is that Valyrian?
- Gaaa.
Gaaa?
Say hello for me.
Rytsas.
"Ritsas."
That was close enough.
Does she know
her daughter's a queen?
Not yet.
That will be
a surprise, I expect.
Many surprises for her.
How am I supposed
to sit here planning a war
when you're over there
looking like that?
Will you come with me
one day to Volantis?
When all this is over?
I will.
I promise.
I know she'd love
to meet you.
And her grandchild.
What, now?
Are you certain?
Are you angry with me?
Angry?
You're my queen.
And I have your little prince
or princess inside me.
Maybe one of each.
Don't get greedy.
Can you leave the war
for one night?
I love you.
Do you hear me?
Most men fuck like dogs.
No grace, no skill.
A few dozen thrusts
and done.
You need to be patient.
Give her time.
Your cock shouldn't
go near her
till she's slick
as a baby seal.
And then you go inside,
but slowly.
Don't jam it in like
you're spearing a pig.
Come on!
Hey, come on.
You think he loves you,
is that it?
What did he tell you?
He's gonna make you his lady
and live with you
in some castle?
No, he didn't
tell me anything.
He barely talks.
I've seen you two
whispering in the night,
giggling like
a pair of girls.
What, you're jealous?
Of course I'm jealous.
You should be
with one of your own.
And you're one of my own?
I've never heard
a kind word from your mouth.
You would
if you were mine.
I'd tell you
that you're beautiful
and fierce and wild.
I'd be good to you.
You love him?
'Cause he's pretty?
Is that it?
You like his pretty hair
and his pretty eyes?
You think pretty
is gonna make you happy?
Don't touch me.
You won't love him so much when
you find out what he really is.
Growing up at Winterfell, all
I ever wanted was to escape,
to come here
to the capital.
See the southern knights
and their painted armor
and King's Landing
after dark--
all the candles burning
in all those windows.
I'm stupid.
A stupid little girl
with stupid dreams
who never learns.
Come on.
Come walk with me.
I remember the first time
I saw you in the throne room.
I'd never seen anyone
who looked so unhappy.
I want very much for you
to be happy, Sansa,
and so does my grandmother.
You would have been
happy at Highgarden.
But women in our position
must make the best
of our circumstances.
How do I make the best
of my circumstances?
I have to marry him.
- Has Lord Tyrion mistreated you?
- No.
Has he been kind to you?
He's tried.
You don't want
him, though.
He's a Lannister.
Far from the worst Lannister,
wouldn't you say?
I'm sorry.
Here I am
complaining to you...
My son will be king.
Sons learn
from their mothers.
I plan to teach mine
a great deal.
And your son,
if I'm not mistaken,
your son might be
the Lord of Casterly Rock
and the North someday.
What?
My son...
with him.
I'll have to--
we'll have to--
If it's the pain
you're worried about--
I'm not afraid
of the pain.
Not after what
Joffrey's done to me.
What is it, then?
He's rather good-looking
even with the scar.
Especially with the scar.
He's a dwarf.
And Loras--
Loras.
Some women like tall men.
Some like short men.
Some like hairy men.
Some like bald men.
Gentle men, rough men,
ugly men, pretty men,
pretty girls.
Most women don't know
what they like until they've tried it.
And, sadly, so many of us
get to try so little
before we're old and gray.
Tyrion may surprise you.
From what I've heard,
he's quite experienced.
And that's a good thing?
It can be.
We're very complicated,
you know.
Pleasing us
takes practice.
How do you know
all this?
Did your mother teach you?
Yes, sweet girl.
My mother taught me.
She's a child.
She's a foot
taller than you.
A tall child.
What's the youngest
you've ever had?
Not that young.
How much older?
Older.
You're a lord,
she's a lady.
And a beauty at that.
I don't see the problem.
Shae isn't going
to like it.
Shae is a whore.
Are you gonna
marry her? Eh?
How did marrying a whore work
out for you the first time?
I should never have
told you about that.
You want Shae, keep her.
Wed one and bed the other.
All you have to do is get
a son in the Stark girl.
He'll be Lord
of Winterfell one day.
You can rule the North
in his name.
You'll have two women
and a whole kingdom of your own.
Two women to despise me
and a whole kingdom
to join them.
You waste time trying
to get people to love you,
you'll end up the most
popular dead man in town.
You want to fuck
that Stark girl.
You just don't want
to admit it.
I don't pay you to put
evil notions in my head.
The ones already there
don't need company.
You pay me to kill people
who bother you.
Evil notions come free.
Your Grace.
Grandfather.
You wanted
to speak to me?
Yes.
I'd like a report on the meetings
of my small council.
You're welcome
to attend the meetings
of your small council,
Your Grace.
Any or all of them.
I've been very busy.
Many important matters
require a king's attention.
Of course.
You've been holding
the council meetings
in the Tower of the Hand instead of
the small council chamber.
I have, yes.
May I ask why?
The Tower of the Hand
is where I work.
To walk from there
to here would take time,
time I could otherwise
spend productively.
So if I wanted to attend
a council meeting,
I would now have to climb
all the stairs in the Tower of the Hand?
We could arrange
to have you carried.
Tell me about
the Targaryen girl
in the east
and her dragons.
Where did you hear
about this?
Is it true?
Apparently so.
Don't you think we ought
to do something about it?
When I was
Hand of the King
under your father's
predecessor,
the skulls of all
the Targaryen dragons
were kept in this room.
The skull
of the last of them
was right here.
It was the size
of an apple.
And the biggest
was the size of a carriage.
Yes, and the creature
to whom it belonged
died 300 years ago.
Curiosities on the far
side of the world
are no threat to us.
But how do we know
these dragons are just curiosities
and not the beasts that brought
the whole world to heel?
Because we have been told
as much by the many experts
who serve the realm
by counseling the king
on matters about
which he knows nothing.
But I haven't
been counseled.
You are being counseled
at this very moment.
I should be consulted
about such things.
From now on,
I will see to it
that you are
appropriately consulted
on important matters
whenever necessary.
Your Grace.
Yunkai.
The Yellow City.
The Yunkish train
bed slaves, not soldiers.
We can defeat them.
On the field,
with ease.
But they won't
meet us on the field.
They have provisions,
patience, and strong walls.
If they're wise,
they'll hide behind those walls
and chip away at us,
man by man.
I don't want half my army killed
before I've crossed the Narrow Sea.
We don't need
Yunkai, khaleesi.
Taking this city will not bring
you any closer to Westeros
or the Iron Throne.
How many slaves
are there in Yunkai?
200,000,
if not more.
Then we have 200,000 reasons
to take the city.
Now comes the noble
Razdal mo Eraz
of that ancient
and honorable house,
master of men
and speaker to savages,
to offer terms of peace.
Noble lord, you are
in the presence
of Daenerys Stormborn
of House Targaryen,
Queen of the Andals
and the First Men,
Khaleesi
of the Great Grass Sea,
Breaker of Chains,
and Mother of Dragons.
You may approach.
Sit.
Will the noble lord
take refreshment?
Ancient and glorious
is Yunkai.
Our empire was old
before dragons stirred
in old Valyria.
Many an army has broken
against our walls.
You shall find no easy
conquest here, khaleesi.
Good.
My Unsullied need practice.
I was told
to blood them early.
If blood is your desire,
blood shall flow.
But why?
'Tis true you have committed
savageries in Astapor.
But the Yunkai are a forgiving
and generous people.
The wise masters of Yunkai
have sent a gift
for the silver queen.
There is far more than this awaiting
you on the deck of your ship.
- My ship?
- Yes, khaleesi.
As I said,
we are a generous people.
You shall have
as many ships as you require.
And what do you ask
in return?
All we ask is that
you make use of these ships.
Sail them back to Westeros
where you belong
and leave us to conduct
our affairs in peace.
I have a gift
for you as well.
- Your life.
- My life?
And the lives
of your wise masters.
But I also want
something in return.
You will release
every slave in Yunkai.
Every man, woman, and child
shall be given as much food,
clothing, and property
as they can carry
as payment
for their years of servitude.
Reject this gift,
and I shall
show you no mercy.
You are mad.
We are not Astapor
or Qarth.
We are Yunkai and we have
powerful friends.
Friends who would take great
pleasure in destroying you.
Those who survive,
we shall enslave once more.
Perhaps we'll make
a slave of you as well.
You swore me
safe conduct.
I did, but my dragons
made no promises.
And you threatened
their mother.
Take the gold.
My gold.
You gave it to me, remember?
And I shall put it
to good use.
You'd be wise to do the same
with my gift to you.
Now get out.
The Yunkish
are a proud people.
They will not bend.
And what happens to things
that don't bend?
He said he had
powerful friends.
Who was he talking about?
I don't know.
Find out.
Chains?
Solid gold from the mines
outside Lannisport.
Smithed in Casterly Rock.
Golden chains.
You could buy
a ship with these.
- Do I need a ship?
- What?
- Am I going somewhere?
- Of course you're not going anywhere.
So, am I invited
to your wedding?
I didn't ask
for this marriage.
- I didn't want it.
- No?
She's a beautiful girl.
You said so yourself.
That doesn't mean that--
this is duty,
not desire.
Is that what you will tell yourself
when you fuck her?
I don't have a choice.
My father--
Does not rule
the world.
We can still go
across the Narrow Sea.
What would I do there?
Juggle?
I am a Lannister
of Casterly Rock.
And I'm Shae
the funny whore.
My feelings for you
have not changed.
I will marry Sansa Stark
and do my duty by her.
While I empty
her chamber pot
and lick your cock
when you're bored?
I swear to you
it will not be like that.
No?
What will it be like?
I will buy you a good home
somewhere in the city.
You will have
fine clothes,
guards to keep
you safe, servants.
Any children
we might have
will be
well provided for.
Children?
You think I want children
who can never see
their father?
Who would be killed
in their sleep
if their grandfather
found out about them?
Listen.
Listen to me, my lady.
- I'm not your lady.
- You are.
You'll always
be my lady.
I'm your whore.
And when you are tired
of fucking me,
I will be nothing.
- What happened?
- Wildfire.
I should have been here.
After all the running
and fighting,
here I am,
back where I started.
Do you miss it?
- King's Landing?
- Your father's house.
Never had a father.
Never wanted one.
Haven't you ever wondered
where your strength came from?
Your talent for fighting?
I'm lowborn.
As low as can be.
My mother was a tavern wench.
Mine was a slave.
So was I.
Bought and sold,
scourged and branded,
until the Lord of Light
reached down,
took me in his hand
and raised me up.
I was born in Flea Bottom.
Your blood is noble.
Are you saying my father,
he was some lord or...
There.
Your father's house.
I'm just a bastard.
The bastard of Robert
of the House Baratheon,
First of His Name,
King of the Andals
and the First Men.
Why do you think
the gold cloaks wanted you?
There is power
in a king's blood.
Come sit
by the fire, child.
Not talking, eh?
That's a first.
I don't talk
to traitors.
I didn't like
giving up the boy.
But you did.
You took the gold
and you gave him up.
The Red God
is the one true god.
You've seen his power.
When he commands,
we obey.
He's not
my one true god.
No?
Who's yours?
Death.
Spotted a Lannister
raiding party.
- How many?
- No more than 20.
- How far?
- Less than a day's ride south.
What do you say, boys?
Time for a lion hunt?
Yeah!
But what about Riverrun?
It's not south.
It's west of here.
It will still be west of here
two days from now.
- You swore.
- To take you home, and I will.
But we need
to do this first.
Why? So you can
steal their gold?
I swear to you,
this isn't--
I don't care what you swear
because you're a liar.
You lied to Gendry,
you lied to me.
You'll lie to anyone.
I hope the Lannisters kill you all.
One day you'll understand,
but now--
- Anguy, bring her back.
- Come back, girl!
Kick all you like,
wolf girl.
Won't do you no good.
I thought you were gone.
Tomorrow.
Have they told you what
they plan to do with me?
Lord Bolton's traveling
tomorrow as well.
He's going to the Twins
for Edmure Tully's wedding.
You're to remain here.
With Locke?
I owe you a debt.
When Catelyn Stark
released you,
we both made
a promise to her.
Now it's your promise.
You gave your word.
Keep it
and consider
the debt paid.
I will return the Stark
girls to their mother.
I swear it.
Good-bye, Ser Jaime.
Here.
Let me.
It will take time.
Qyburn hopes your father
will force the Citadel
to give him back
his chain.
My father will make him
Grand Maester
if he grows me
a new hand.
You will give my regards
to Lord Tywin, I trust?
Tell Robb Stark I'm sorry I
couldn't make his uncle's wedding.
The Lannisters send
their regards.
Safe journey,
Kingslayer.
Nothing to say?
I liked you
better before.
I don't remember chopping
your balls off, too.
And don't you worry
about your friend.
We'll take
good care of her.
Shh.
Gentle, my lord.
Gentle.
Shh shh shh.
Myranda knows
what she's doing.
Let her.
She trained
as a septa, only...
she had other urges.
So did the septons,
only they lied about it.
Where is he?
Who, my lord?
There's no one here
but you, me, and Violet.
Please.
Don't you want us
to see it?
Oh, come on.
Let us see it.
Everybody talks about it.
He sent you.
Who sent us?
We sent ourselves,
Lord Greyjoy.
We heard so much
about it.
- Please.
- Oh!
There it is.
Oh.
Do you think
we're ugly?
He thinks we're ugly.
Well, he's been
through so much.
Look at his poor face.
Help me.
If he comes back...
We need to make him
feel better.
And how can we make
him feel better?
I have an idea.
Oh, she's shy.
You know how they are,
these religious girls.
Maybe he doesn't
know how we are.
Oh.
I felt something.
Oh, Lord Greyjoy.
- As good as they say?
- Mmm.
And why should you
get all the fun?
What?
You like her better?
Plenty there
for both of us.
I was here first.
I'm sorry.
Terrible timing.
But I was getting jealous.
Well?
Should we see this cock
everyone's always going on about?
Everyone knows
you love girls.
I bet you always thought
they loved you back.
Your famous cock must be
very precious to you.
Would you say it's
your most precious part?
Please.
No.
No!
Mercy, please!
Please, mercy!
Mercy!
This is mercy.
I'm not killing you.
Just making
a few alterations.
No! No! No!
Please, no! No!
No! No, please!
Please!
You're gonna scare it off.
I'm not gonna scare it.
I'm gonna kill it.
It's too far away.
Is that a palace?
It's a windmill.
Windmill.
Who built it?
Some king?
Just the men
who used to live here.
They must have been
great builders,
stacking stones so high.
Winterfell has towers
three times that size.
"I'm Jon Snow
and I'm from Winterfell.
My daddy
was a fancy lord
and I lived in a tower
that touched the clouds."
If you're impressed
by a windmill,
you'd be swooning if you saw
the Great Keep at Winterfell.
What's swooning?
Fainting.
What's fainting?
When a girl sees blood
and collapses.
Why would a girl
see blood and collapse?
Well...
not all girls
are like you.
Well, girls see
more blood than boys.
Or do you like girls
who swoon, Jon Snow?
Oh, a spider!
Save me, Jon Snow.
My dress is made
of the purest silk
from Tralalalaleeday.
I'd like to see you
in a silk dress.
Would you?
So I could
tear it off you.
Well, you rip
my pretty silk dress,
I'll blacken your eye.
Maybe one day
I'll take you to Winterfell.
Or maybe one day
I'll take you there.
After we've taken
our land back.
Ygritte.
You won't win.
I know your people are brave,
no one denies that.
- You know nothing--
- Six times in the last thousand years,
a King-beyond-the-Wall
has attacked the kingdoms.
- Six times they failed.
- And how do you know that?
Every boy in the North
knows it.
We grow up learning it.
Where the battles
were fought,
the names of the heroes,
who died where.
Six times you've invaded
and six times
you've failed.
The seventh
will be the same.
- Mance is different.
- You don't have the discipline.
You don't have the training.
Your army is no army.
You don't know
how to fight together.
- You don't know that.
- I do.
I know it.
If you attack the Wall,
you'll die.
All of you.
All of us.
You're mine
as I'm yours.
And if we die,
we die.
But first we'll live.
Yes, first we'll live.
What's he going on about?
And how come he always
gets to sit and chat
while we do all the work?
Hodor.
- That's where we are.
- What are you telling him?
- It's all right, Osha.
- It's not all right.
You think I can't
hear you every day?
Filling his head
with black magic.
Talking about visions
and three-eyed ravens and worse.
- Leave him alone.
- He can speak for himself.
I don't fill his head
with anything.
So what do you
talk about?
What's happening to him
and what that means.
Go on, then.
Tell us what it means.
It's not like that.
I wish I could
tell him all the answers.
It would be much easier.
I don't want you
talking to him anymore.
Until we get to your brother
at Castle Black.
- We're not going to Castle Black.
- What did you say?
I told you already.
Jon Snow isn't there.
Bran needs to find
the raven beyond the Wall.
Oh, no.
I'm not going back there.
Your brother is at Castle Black.
That's where we're going.
Look at me.
The raven's
been coming to me
ever since I fell
from that tower.
He wants me
to find him.
I don't have
my legs anymore.
This is what I have now.
You have a family.
You need to go back
to Castle Black
so you can get back to them
where you belong.
What if I belong
in the North?
What if I fell from
that tower for a reason?
Is that what
he's telling you?
That it's all
for a reason?
All these bad things happened because
the gods got big plans for you?
I wish it were true,
little lord.
But the gods wouldn't spare a raven's
cold shit for you or me or anyone.
You don't understand.
You don't know.
None of you know.
None of you
have been up there.
I had a man once.
A good man.
Bruni, his name was.
I was his
and he was mine.
But one night
Bruni disappears.
People said he left me,
but I knew him.
He'd never leave me.
Not for long.
I knew he'd come back.
And he did.
He came in through
the back of the hut.
Only it wasn't Bruni.
Not really.
His skin was pale
like a dead man's.
His eyes bluer
than clear sky.
He came at me,
grabbed me by the neck
and squeezed so hard
I could feel the life
slipping out of me.
I don't know
how I got the knife.
When I did, I stuck it
deep into his heart.
And he hardly
seemed to notice.
I had to burn our hut down
with him inside.
I didn't ask the gods
what it meant.
I didn't need to.
I already knew.
It meant the North
was no place for men to be.
Not anymore.
I promised your maester
I'd get you to Castle Black
and no further.
How is the pain,
my lord?
What's the purpose
of an arm with no hand?
Well, we've stymied
the corruption.
Yes, we've stymied
You're a learned man.
All the good
it's done me.
You did well
sewing up this mess.
You're far better
at this sort of work
than Grand Maester
Pycelle.
Faint praise, my lord.
So why did the Citadel
take your chain?
Did you fondle
one boy too many?
No, my lord.
That's not my weakness.
What is?
Curiosity.
The only way to treat disease
is to understand disease.
And the only way
to understand it
is to study the afflicted.
You performed experiments
on living men.
- On dying men.
- With their permission?
My studies
have given me insight
that has saved
many lives.
Dying paupers,
I assume.
Men with no families
to complain.
You found them moaning
in the poorhouse
and had them carted
back to your garret
and opened up their bellies
to see what was inside.
How many men have
you killed, my lord?
I don't know.
50? 100?
Countless.
Countless has
a nice ring to it.
And how many lives
have you saved?
Half a million.
The population
of King's Landing.
You were in charge
of the ravens at Harrenhal.
Did you-- did you get a bird off
to Brienne's father in Tarth?
A bird flew off
and a bird flew back.
Lord Selwyn Tarth
offered 300 gold dragons
for his daughter's safe return.
- A fair offer.
- A fair offer. Locke won't take it.
Why not?
He's convinced Lord Tarth
owns all the sapphire
mines in Westeros.
He feels
he's being cheated.
They'd be fools
to kill her.
These men have been
at war a long time.
Most of them
will be dead by winter.
She'll be their
entertainment tonight.
Beyond tonight,
I don't think
they care very much.
We have to return
to Harrenhal.
Why?
I've left
something behind.
Absolutely not.
I've got orders
from Lord Bolton.
And what are those orders?
To deliver you to your father
at King's Landing.
You think you'll get
a reward.
I serve Lord Bolton.
Any appreciation
your father--
You think
you're getting a reward.
Let me explain
something to you.
When my father sees me,
the first thing
he's going to ask
is what happened to my hand.
And I'm going to tell him
this man chopped it off.
I had nothing--
Or I could tell him
this man saved my life.
We return
to Harrenhal now.
Whoa.
- Eyes open, lads.
- Be quiet.
♪ The bear, the bear
and the maiden fair ♪
♪ From there to here,
from here to there ♪
♪ All black and brown
and covered in hair ♪
♪ He smelled that girl
in the summer air ♪
♪ The bear, the bear,
and the maiden fair! ♪
Don't spare her.
Don't spare her!
Well, this is one shameful
fucking performance.
Stop running and fight.
A wooden sword?
- I thought you'd gone.
- You gave her a wooden sword.
We've only got
one bear.
I'll pay
her bloody ransom.
Gold, sapphires,
whatever you want.
Just get her
out of there.
All you lords and ladies
still think that the only thing
that matters is gold.
This makes me happier
than all your gold ever could.
And that makes me happier
than all her sapphires.
So go buy yourself
a golden hand
and fuck yourself
with it.
Ah!
- Get behind me.
- I will not.
What the fuck are you
doing to my bear?
Lord Bolton charged me
with bringing him back
to King's Landing alive
and that's what I aim to do.
Pull her up.
Hold my legs.
Pull him up!
The bitch stays.
We're taking her
to King's Landing.
Unless you kill me.
She belongs to me.
Lord Bolton's orders.
What do you think is more
important to Lord Bolton?
Getting his pet rat
a reward
or ensuring Tywin Lannister
gets his son back alive?
Well, we must
be on our way.
Sorry about
the sapphires.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==