♪ Game of Thrones 3x02 ♪
Dark Wings, Dark Words
Original Air Date on April 7, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
♪
Don't think
too much, Bran.
Relax your bow arm.
And which one of you
was a marksman at 10?
Father?
You can't kill it,
you know.
Why not?
Because the raven is you.
Hodor.
It's all right, Hodor.
Were you inside the wolf
again, little lord?
No, it was
the three-eyed raven.
He's back.
I tried to kill it,
but I couldn't.
- There was a boy.
- I don't want to hear about it.
- But you asked.
- We've got plenty of worries.
We don't need to pour
black magic on top of them.
I didn't ask
for black magic dreams.
I know you didn't,
little lord.
We need to move.
We don't know
who might be after us.
No one even knows
we're alive.
And who told you that?
The three-eyed raven
tell you?
- No.
- Some good he is, then.
I don't know what other people
know and what they don't.
I only know the Wall
is a long way off.
My mother
always told me
you Westerosi
were a grim lot.
Grim, bearded,
stinking barbarians
that would row
across the Narrow Sea
and steal us
from our beds.
Did you ever think
you'd marry one?
I never thought
I'd marry anyone at all.
Never?
Not until I met
the king of the grim,
bearded,
stinking barbarians.
Pardon me, Your Grace.
- My queen.
- Lord Bolton.
Let me guess which one
is the good news.
Word from Riverrun
and Winterfell.
I hadn't seen
him in years.
I don't even know
how many.
We'll travel
to the funeral together.
Lord Bolton
will garrison here
until we return.
Will I be wearing manacles
when I lay my father to rest?
Something else?
By the time Bolton's
bastard got to Winterfell,
the ironborn were gone.
They massacred everyone
and put the castle to the torch.
And Bran and Rickon
have not been found.
They may have escaped.
Or Theon may have taken them
back to the Iron Islands as hostages.
Have you received
any demands?
No.
Have you heard anything
from Theon at all?
Where am I?
Who are you?
What do you want?
I want to do this.
Do you know how long
it's going to take us
to get to King's Landing walking
through fields and forests?
Yes.
So how shall
we pass the time?
By putting one foot
in front of the other.
It's going to be
a very dull walk.
I'm here to take you
to King's Landing
and bring back
Lady Stark's daughters in exchange.
Dull is fine.
You know, it doesn't matter
how loyal a servant you are,
no one enjoys the company
of a humorless mute.
Trust me on this.
People have been serving me
since I was born.
You think Lady Stark is going
to want a giant towheaded plank
following her around
for the rest of her life?
A week's journey with you and she'll
order you to fall on your sword.
If Lady Stark is unhappy
with any aspect of my service,
I'm sure
she'll let me know.
She's an honest woman.
All the good
it's done her.
How did you come into
Lady Stark's service?
There's something
we can talk about.
Not your concern,
Kingslayer.
It had to be recently.
You weren't with her
at Winterfell.
How would you know?
Because I visited
Winterfell.
I would have noticed
your dour head
smacking into
the archways.
Move.
- Were you pledged to Stannis?
- Gods, no.
Ah, Renly.
Really?
He wasn't fit
to rule over anything
more important than
a 12-course meal.
- Shut your mouth.
- Why?
I lived with him at court since
he was a boy, don't forget.
Could hardly escape
the little tulip.
Skipping down the corridors
in his embroidered silks.
I knew him
far better than you.
as well as anyone.
As a member
of his Kingsguard,
he trusted me
with everything.
He would have been
a wonderful king.
Sounds like you
quite fancied him.
I did not
fancy him.
Oh, gods, you did.
Did you ever tell him?
No, of course not.
You weren't Renly's
type, I'm afraid.
He preferred curly-haired
little girls like Loras Tyrell.
You're far too much
man for him.
I'm not interested
in foul rumors.
Unless they're
about me.
It's all true
about Renly.
His proclivities were the
worst kept secret at court.
It's a shame the throne
isn't made out of cocks.
- They'd have never got him off it.
- Shut your mouth!
I don't blame him.
And I don't
blame you, either.
We don't get to choose
who we love.
- Where are you headed, then?
- South.
- You?
- Riverrun.
Staying off
the kingsroad, are you?
They get you no matter
where you go.
- You can't win.
- No, you really can't.
Looks like you're
safe enough, though.
Meaning no offense,
my lady, but...
I wouldn't tangle
with you.
- Seven blessings to you.
- And you.
He knows who I am.
- He doesn't.
- Maybe you're right.
But what if you're not?
What if he tells someone?
We're not doing it.
He's an innocent man.
More innocent than
Lady Stark's daughters?
Make it tighter here.
That's better.
It makes you look
very strong.
No flowers.
I said no flowers.
All these are wrong.
Bring others.
Yes, Your Grace.
Bloody flowers.
On the king.
Looks like
a Tyrell rose.
Give it to Margaery
for her wedding gown.
Should be more
than enough fabric.
Tell me what
you think of her.
Who?
Margaery.
She's an ideal match.
With the Tyrells beside us,
we'll crush the Northerners.
Hang their lords,
burn their strongholds,
sow their fields
with salt,
and no one will think of
rebelling for another century.
It is a good match, but
what do you think of her?
She's beautiful
and intelligent.
Yes, she is.
Her concern with the well-being of
the common people is interesting.
Not to me.
I only meant that to go out of
your way to endanger yourself--
This is becoming
one of the most boring
conversations
I've ever had.
Margaery Tyrell dotes
on filthy urchins for a reason.
She dresses like
a harlot for a reason.
She married a traitor
and known degenerate
like Renly Baratheon
for a reason.
She married Renly Baratheon
because she was told to.
That's what
intelligent women do--
what they're told.
- You need to ask yourself--
- I don't need to do anything.
Better.
Much better.
I still
don't believe it.
He didn't.
He didn't want anything.
He just takes an interest
because he loved my mother.
Men only want one thing
from a pretty girl.
Littlefinger's not
in love with me.
Love is not
the thing he wants.
He's too old.
They never see it
that way.
He didn't ask you
to do something for him?
Spy on someone or...?
No.
If he does ask you
for anything
or try anything
or touch you,
I want you to tell me.
Why?
What will you do?
I will make him stop.
Ser Loras Tyrell, my lady.
Send him in.
Lady Sansa.
Ser Loras.
My sister Margaery
invites you to take
the air with her
and our grandmother
the Lady Olenna
in the gardens.
May I escort you
to them?
I believe you grow more beautiful
every day, Lady Sansa.
You are too kind,
Ser Loras.
You probably don't remember
the first time we met.
At the Hand's tourney,
you gave me your favor.
A rose,
a red rose.
Of course I did.
It's more your color.
- You take it.
- Thank you.
You're such a dear.
I'll take my leave.
Lady Sansa.
Thank you,
Ser Loras.
Come.
Lady Sansa,
it is my honor
to present
my grandmother...
the Lady Olenna
of House Tyrell.
Kiss me, child.
It's so good of you
to visit me
and my foolish
flock of hens.
We're very sorry
for your losses.
And I was sorry when I heard of
Lord Renly's death, Lady Margaery.
- He was very gallant.
- Gallant, yes.
And charming
and very clean.
He knew how
to dress and smile
and somehow this gave him the
notion he was fit to be king.
Renly was brave
and gentle, Grandmother.
Father liked him
and so did Loras.
Loras is young
and very good
at knocking men
off horses with a stick.
That does not
make him wise.
As to your
fathead father--
Grandmother!
What will Sansa think of us?
She might think we have
some wits about us.
One of us,
at any rate.
It was treason.
I warned them.
Robert has two sons and
Renly has an older brother.
How could he possibly
have any claim
to that ugly
iron chair?
We should have stayed well out
of all this if you ask me.
But once
the cow's been milked,
there's no squirting
the cream back up her udders.
So here we are
to see things through.
What do you say
to that, Sansa?
Shall we have
some lemon cakes?
Lemon cake's my favorite.
So we've been told.
Are you going to bring the food or
do you mean to starve us to death?
Here, Sansa,
come sit with me.
I'm much less boring
than these others.
Do you know my son?
The Lord of Highgarden?
I haven't had
the pleasure.
No great pleasure,
believe me.
A ponderous oaf.
His father
was an oaf as well.
My husband,
the late Lord Luthor.
He managed to ride off
a cliff whilst hawking.
They say he was looking
up at the sky
and paying no mind to where
his horse was taking him.
And now my son
is doing the same,
only this time he's riding
a lion instead of a horse.
Now...
I want you
to tell me the truth
about this royal boy,
this Joffrey.
I... I...
You, you.
Who else
would know better?
We've heard
some troubling tales.
Is there any truth
to them?
Has this boy
mistreated you?
Has he ripped out
your tongue?
Joff-- King Joffrey,
he-- His Grace
is very fair
and handsome
and as brave as a lion.
Yes, all Lannisters
are lions.
And when a Tyrell farts,
it smells like a rose.
But how kind is he?
How clever?
Has he a good heart,
a gentle hand?
I'm to be his wife.
I only want to know
what that means.
Bring me some cheese.
The cheese will be served
after the cakes, my lady.
when I want it served.
And I want it served now.
Are you frightened, child?
No need for that.
We're only women here.
Tell us the truth.
No harm will come to you.
My father always
told the truth.
Yes, he had
that reputation.
And they named him traitor
and took his head.
Joffrey.
Joffrey did that.
He promised he would be merciful
and he cut my father's head off.
And he said
that was mercy.
Then he took me up on the
walls and made me look at it.
Go on.
I-- I can't.
I never meant--
my father was a traitor.
My brother as well.
I have traitor's blood.
Please don't make me
say anymore.
She's terrified,
Grandmother.
- Just look at her.
- Speak freely, child.
We would never betray
your confidence, I swear it.
He's a monster.
Ah.
That's a pity.
Please, don't stop
the wedding.
Have no fear.
The Lord Oaf of Highgarden
is determined that
Margaery shall be queen.
Even so, we thank you
for the truth.
Ah, here comes my cheese.
We're at war.
This march
is a distraction.
My grandfather's funeral
is not a distraction.
- Are we riding to battle at Riverrun?
- No.
Then it's a distraction.
My Uncle Edmure has his
forces garrisoned there.
We need his men.
Unless he's been
breeding them,
he don't have enough
to make a difference.
Have you lost faith
in our cause?
If it's revenge,
I still got faith in it.
If you no longer
believe--
I can believe
till it snows in Dorne.
Don't change the fact
that we've got half the men.
You don't think
we can win?
May I speak my mind,
Your Grace?
Have you not been speaking
your mind, Lord Karstark?
I think you lost this war
the day you married her.
Whoa, whoa.
Your Grace.
You're afraid of her.
- And she knows it.
- I'm not afraid of her.
May I help you,
Lady Stark?
No.
I'm sorry,
I shouldn't have--
You can't help
because a mother
makes one for her
children to protect them.
Only a mother
can make them.
You've made them
before?
Twice.
Did they work?
After a fashion.
I prayed for my son Bran
to survive his fall.
Many years before that,
one of the boys came down
with the pox.
Maester Luwin said if he made it
through the night, he'd live.
But it would be
a very long night.
So I sat with him
all through the darkness.
Listened to his ragged
little breaths,
his coughing,
his whimpering.
Which boy?
Jon Snow.
When my husband brought
that baby home from the war,
I couldn't bear
to look at him.
I didn't want
to see those brown
stranger's eyes
staring up at me.
So I prayed to the gods,
take him away.
Make him die.
He got the pox.
And I knew I was the worst
woman who ever lived.
A murderer.
I'd condemned this poor,
innocent child
to a horrible death
all because I was
jealous of his mother.
A woman he didn't
even know.
So I prayed
to all seven gods,
let the boy live.
Let him live
and I'll love him.
I'll be a mother to him.
I'll beg my husband
to give him a true name,
to call him Stark
and be done with it,
to make him one of us.
And he lived.
And I couldn't keep
my promise.
And everything
that's happened since then...
all this horror
that's come to my family...
it's all because I couldn't
love a motherless child.
Was it hard for you
to kill the Halfhand?
Yes.
You liked him?
I like you, but if
you're playing us false,
it won't be hard
for me to kill you.
I've got wildling
blood in my veins.
- These are my people.
- I understand.
Well, how could
you understand?
You want to protect
your people.
Do you know what it takes
to unite 90 clans,
half of whom want
to massacre the other half
for one insult or another?
They speak seven different
languages in my army.
The Thenns hate
the Hornfoots.
The Hornfoots hate
the ice-river clans.
Everyone hates
the cave people.
So you know how I got
moon worshippers
and cannibals and giants
to march together
in the same army?
No.
I told them we were
all going to die
if we don't get south.
Because that's the truth.
Shouldn't be long now.
What's wrong with him?
He's a warg.
He can enter the mind of
animals, see through their eyes.
He's scouting for us.
What, you've never
met a warg?
Orell.
Where were you
this time?
The Fist
of the First Men.
What did you see?
Dead crows.
What's the matter, Piggy?
You crying
'cause you're cold?
There's 200 brothers
killed by dead men
and you're still here
whimpering.
That seem fair to you?
I seen 'em torn
to pieces fighting
while you was off somewhere
hiding in a hole.
Why don't you lie down
and rest for a while, eh?
You know you want to.
Hey.
Get up, Sam.
- No.
- Get up.
I can't.
If you stop,
you'll die.
'Course if you don't stop,
you'll probably die, too.
- You don't care.
- 'Course we care.
You left me.
When the white walkers came,
you left me.
Aye, we left you.
You're fat and you're slow.
We didn't want to die.
Help me get him up.
Looks like that piggy
is done for.
- Help us get him up.
- He's slowing us down.
Just get him up!
Why? So the rest
of us can die?
We'll move faster
without him.
What is this?
Get up, Tarly.
- Is he all right?
- Aye, I think so.
If he can't, we may as
well just go without him.
That's enough.
Tarly,
I forbid you to die.
Do you hear me?
- Why should the rest of us--
- Rast...
you're responsible
for him.
What am I
supposed to do?
Make sure he gets
back alive.
If he doesn't,
you don't.
Move on!
I'm not dying
for you, Piggy.
You hear me?
Where's Rickon
and Hodor?
Looking for food.
What's out there?
Not another step, boy.
Unless you want to drown
in your own blood.
I'm unarmed.
That was poor planning.
My sister carries
the weapons.
I'm better with them.
Drop the spear.
Drop it.
If you kill me,
that wolf will tear
you to bits.
You must be Summer.
I'm Jojen Reed.
This is my sister Meera.
We've come a long way
to find you, Brandon.
And we have
much farther to go.
I'm just trying
to understand.
Would you please
shut up about it?
Jaqen H'ghar offered
you three kills.
- I'm not listening.
- But just explain it to me.
He offered to kill
any three people you wanted.
Dead. All you had to do
was give him the names.
Anyone.
You could have picked King Joffrey.
- Shut up.
- You could have picked Tywin Lannister.
Jaqen got us
out of Harrenhal,
so why are you
complaining?
But you could have
ended the war.
- Where are we going?
- North.
If we were going north,
we should have come
to the Red Fork River by now.
Maybe we already
passed it.
It's 100 feet wide.
How could we have
passed it?
If we hit the Red Fork,
we can follow it west
to Riverrun.
My mother grew up there.
My grandfather's a lord.
He'll protect us.
Could be a minstrel.
Shut up.
♪ A lion
still has claws... ♪
A minstrel's got
gold sometimes.
We could jump him,
tie him up, steal his gold,
- and buy some food.
- Shh.
♪ And so he spoke,
and so he spoke ♪
♪ That Lord
of Castamere ♪
♪ But now the rains ♪
♪ Weep o'er his hall ♪
♪ With no one there
to hear. ♪
What's lurking
behind that wall?
A lion?
A wolf?
Just a dirty little cub,
I think.
- Loose a few more shafts.
- Don't.
Put the sword down, girl.
You go on down the road.
Just keep on singing
so we know where you are.
Leave us be
and I won't kill you.
Generous.
You're a dangerous person.
I like dangerous people.
Why are your friends
so shy?
What friends?
The fat one to your left
and the lad beside him.
Three young ones
on the run
carrying
castle-forged swords.
You escape
from Harrenhal?
- Who are you?
- Thoros of Myr.
And the fellow here
with the bow is Anguy.
No, who do you
fight for?
The Brotherhood
without Banners.
Now come along.
I want to hear
how two boys
and a very dangerous girl
escaped Harrenhal.
I'm not going with them.
The Brotherhood?
That's who the Mountain
and them lot were looking for.
They'll bring us back
and put rats in us.
You've got nothing
to fear from us, son.
The lords of Westeros
want to burn the countryside.
We're trying to save it.
Now come on.
We'll talk some more
over brown bread and stew.
And then you can go
on your way.
Here's the thing, fat boy.
When I'm done talking,
that arrow's falling down
on your fat head.
So I advise you move,
because I'm done talking.
Half the country's starving
and look at this one.
Maybe he's the reason
half the country's starving.
My lion.
We've spoken of this.
You cannot come here.
But you said I should come
to you with any problems.
Did anyone see you?
- No.
- You sure?
My father does not
make idle threats.
Having you killed would be
the high point of his week.
You have to be
absolutely certain.
All right.
What is this problem?
I'm worried about Sansa.
When she spoke
with Lord Baelish,
his friend warned me
about him.
Baelish doesn't
have friends.
I don't know her name.
- Oh, Ros? The redhead?
- How do you know her?
I try to know
as many people as I can.
You never know
which one you'll need.
She's a whore.
Yes, well, we shouldn't be
judgmental about these things.
- You fucked her.
- Oh, please.
All right, yes,
I fucked her once.
Twice.
But since I met you,
my lady,
I've been with
no one else.
And was she good?
Did you like her?
Not as much
as I like you, obviously,
or she'd be the one
torturing me right now.
What did she say
about Littlefinger?
That Sansa
shouldn't trust him.
Is there an idiot
in any village
who trusts Littlefinger?
We have to protect her.
We can't.
Now that the Lannisters
have discarded her,
Sansa will have
many suitors.
A great beauty
with a very old name.
A great beauty?
Oh, a great beauty?
Yes, she is,
objectively, very.
Her face
is quite pleasing--
to other men
and to women,
people in general.
But not to me,
of course.
I only have eyes
for you.
You pervert.
You want her?
- This child?
- I don't even want to talk about her.
- But you are.
- Only because you're making me.
I didn't force you
to open your mouth
and make words come out.
This is cruel and unfair.
Cruelly unfair.
"Oh, the cruelty.
Shae is so cruel to me."
Hmm, yes.
Now do you think
I'm cruel?
Only if you stop.
But you mustn't
come here again.
Do you hear me?
You've come to
a dangerous place
full of dangerous people.
Dangerous people.
Lady Tyrell, my king.
Send her in.
You wanted to see me,
Your Grace?
I'm leaving
on a hunting trip.
I just wanted
to make sure
you had everything
you need before I left.
That's very thoughtful,
Your Grace.
I have everything
I could want.
Good. Good.
How are you finding life
in the capital?
It must be quite a change
after Renly's camp.
A welcome one.
A military encampment
is no place for a lady.
And the bedside
of a traitor?
Is that a place
for a lady?
Your Grace,
I tried to do my duty
as a wife, that is all.
What was your duty to this
traitor as you saw it?
The duty of any wife
to any husband--
to provide him
with children.
You failed to do this.
- Why?
- I--
I would not speak ill
of the dead, Your Grace.
You think one ought
to speak kindly
of a traitor merely because he's
had a sword put through his heart?
No.
I do beg your pardon.
The subtleties of politics
are often lost on me.
Renly...
I don't believe
he was interested
in the company
of women.
What makes you say this?
Whenever I wanted
to make a child with him,
he--
he had so many
excuses,
so many late-night
war councils.
He never wanted
to try.
Except one evening,
after he'd had far too
much wine to drink,
he suggested something--
something that sounded
very painful
and couldn't possibly
result in children.
Maybe the fault
was with me.
No, he was a known...
degenerate.
It's such a relief to hear
you say so, Your Grace.
Mmm.
I've considered
making his perversion
punishable by death.
As is your right.
You must do whatever
you need to do.
You are the king.
Yes.
I am.
Do you like it?
I just had it made.
Probably one of the finest
weapons in the Seven Kingdoms.
It's beautiful.
Will you show me
how it works?
It's a new design.
Much easier to load.
There's no crank.
You use this lever
to draw the string.
The bolt goes here.
And then you just aim...
and...
Would you take me
hunting sometime?
Forgive me, Your Grace.
I know a hunt
is no place for a woman.
It's not unheard of.
My father would never
let me before--
You no longer
belong to him.
Do you want
to hold it?
May I?
Please.
I imagine it must be
so exciting
to squeeze
your finger here
and watch something
die over there.
Could you do it?
Could you...
kill something?
I don't know, Your Grace.
Do you think I could?
Yes.
Would you like
to watch me?
Yes.
Stop! Stop!
- Tell us the truth.
- About what?
I don't
know what you want.
I want the truth.
What truth?
Why'd you take
Winterfell?
I took it to--
I took it--
- Who gave the orders?
- No one.
- I took it on my own.
- Why?
To take the North
while it was vulnerable.
What were you going
to do once you took it?
Hold it.
Rule it.
Good.
That's very good.
Why did you do that?
I told you.
Why did you take
Winterfell?
I took it to bring glory
to my house and my father.
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
I took it because
I hated the Starks.
I hated them
for holding me prisoner.
I wanted to hurt them.
What are you doing?
Please.
I'll tell you anything.
Just take it off.
Please.
Please, just take it off.
- Your sister sent me.
- Yara?
I'll come for you tonight
when the castle sleeps.
No, don't go.
Please, please.
No, please
don't leave me.
Please, please.
Please,
please don't go!
Please. Please.
Don't leave me.
Please don't go.
Rickon,
stay with us.
It's all right.
The wolves will protect him.
You can get
inside his head,
see through his eyes.
Only when I'm asleep.
That's how it begins until
you learn to control it.
You're a warg.
It's not just wolves.
Sometimes in my dreams
there's a--
- A three-eyed raven?
- You've seen it?
We saw him together.
You haven't forgotten?
Does it have anything
to do with warging?
No, the raven
is something different,
something deeper.
The raven brings
the sight.
Seeing things
that haven't happened yet?
Or things that happened
long before you were born
or things that are happening right
now thousands of miles away.
What's he telling him?
Why don't you ask?
Isn't he ashamed,
your brother,
needing you
to protect him?
Where's the shame in that?
Any boy his age who needs
his sister to protect him
is gonna find himself
needing lots of protecting.
Some people
will always need help.
That doesn't mean
they're not worth helping.
When my father died,
I dreamt it.
You didn't dream it.
You saw it.
So did I.
You have the sight, too?
When I told my father
about your father...
for the first time
in my life, I saw him cry.
Your father
is Howland Reed?
Yeah.
He saved my father's life
during the rebellion.
Your father told you
about the rebellion?
Mine never did.
But I saw that, too.
What else have you seen?
Only one thing
that matters--
you.
I never liked
the skinny ones.
Like drinking
from a puddle.
Not that I'm averse
to drinking from a puddle
every now and again,
you understand.
I don't drink ale.
There's no story so good
a drink won't make it better.
- Yeah!
- You see?
They've all suffered through
my bouts of sobriety.
It's very tedious
for all concerned.
Now, how did
three children--
We're not children.
How did three young persons
such as yourselves,
untrained
in the art of war,
escape from Harrenhal?
Gendry's a smith.
He was apprenticed
in the armory.
A smith, eh?
Where'd you train?
King's Landing.
Tobho Mott's shop.
That criminal.
He charges twice as much
as every other armorer
in the city.
That's because
he's twice as good.
Aha! A smith
and a salesman.
Gendry stole us weapons.
Ah, fought your way
out of Harrenhal, I see.
He knows how to use a
sword and so do I.
My brothers taught me.
Ooh!
To your brothers!
You can finish
your meals before you go.
It may be awhile
before you see another.
- You'll free us?
- I gave you my word.
But before you go,
allow me to raise
a cup to your--
Hey, hey.
Now that is an uncommonly
large person.
How does one
manage to subdue
such an uncommonly
large person?
One waits for him to drink
until he passes out.
Poor man.
You have my sympathy.
Aha, not a man at all.
A Hound!
So good to see
you again, Clegane.
Thoros?
The fuck you doing here?
Drinking and talking
too much.
Same as ever.
- A pretty prize, lads.
- Yeah!
Girl.
What in seven hells
are you doing
with the Stark bitch?
It's a tough decision--
take the bridge
and risk being seen
or cross the great water.
- Silence, Kingslayer.
- Anyone can see us on the bridge,
but cross by water
and the current could take us
or I could escape
down the river.
Good luck.
It's wonderful to watch you
wrestle with these dilemmas.
Which will she choose?
Gambler at heart.
Wouldn't have guessed.
Be quick about it.
- I need to rest.
- Get up.
I have these, you know, on your
feet when you walk too far.
- What do you call them?
- Get up now.
Corns.
I never used to get corns.
Of course I used
to ride everywhere,
not march around
like a common foot soldier
wearing the same shit boots
for over a year.
This heel is ruined.
There's no way--
I never understood why some knights
felt the need to carry two swords.
Ooh.
You move well...
for a great beast
of a woman.
You shouldn't grimace
before you lunge.
It gives away the game.
Bit of a quandary
for you.
If you kill me,
you fail Lady Stark.
But if you don't kill me,
I'm going to kill you.
You're good.
Graceless, but good.
See? If you were
willing to hurt me,
you might have
had me there.
Looks like your woman's
getting the better of you,
if you can
call that a woman.
We enjoy a good fight.
Gets our juices flowing.
The Flayed Man
of House Bolton.
A bit gruesome
for my taste.
- You sure he's the one?
- That's him, all right.
I saw him fight
at the tourney
for Ser Willem Frey's
wedding.
Give the man his silver.
Let us go and my father will pay
you whatever you want.
Enough to buy me
a new head?
If the King in the North
hears I had the Kingslayer
and let him go,
he'll be taking it right off.
I'd rather he takes yours.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==