Previously on
Hannibal
You think this was
a copycat?
I almost feel like he's
mocking her.
Your name is Georgia Madchen.
You're not alone.
- Somebody told him we were coming.
- The man on the phone?
Did you recognize his voice?
How much would I get
if you wrote a book about me?
Nicholas Boyle was gutted
with a hunting knife.
- You knew how to do that.
- You think I did this?
You and I are just gonna have
to have a difference of opinion
- about who Will is, doctor.
- I'm worried about you, Will.
What if you lose time and hurt
yourself? Or someone else?
You look better.
Do I look alive?
You look pretty.
Must be all the oxygen.
They say what's
wrong with you?
No, just the fever.
They're trying to find out
what else.
They won't find anything.
They'll keep looking,
keep taking tests,
keep giving false diagnoses,
bad meds.
But they won't find out
what's wrong.
They'll just know
that you're wrong.
I hope you have
good insurance.
I do too.
They're going to give me
shock treatment.
Electroconvulsive Therapy is
what it's called.
Shock treatment sounds nicer.
People who have what you have can
recover with shock treatment.
You know how many times
I've been told
I could recover with treatment?
They said I might remember
what I did.
But I don't want to remember.
You know what you did,
Georgia.
But I don't remember it.
It feels more like
a horrible dream
where I killed my friend.
You dream about killing
anybody else?
I dream you killed
that doctor.
But I couldn't see your face.
Smells delicious.
Silkie chicken in a broth.
A black-boned
bird prized in China
for its medicinal values
since the 7th century.
Wolfberries, ginseng,
ginger, red dates,
and star anise.
You made me chicken soup?
Yes.
The nurses tell me
you've been wandering, Will.
I was awake... heh...
and wandering with...
purpose
and good intentions.
Visiting that unfortunate
young woman
suffering from delusions.
She's my support group.
And I hope you're hers.
Nothing more isolating
than mental illness.
The hallucinations,
the, um, loss of time,
sleepwalking...
Could that have all just been
the fever?
Fevers can be symptoms
of dementia.
Dementia can be a symptom
of many things happening
in your body or mind that can
no longer be ignored, Will.
Does Jack know?
That this could be more than
a fever? No. I haven't told him.
Shouldn't you?
Not until we know for certain.
What we must do now is continue to
support and monitor your recovery.
This young woman
you were visiting,
how's her recovery?
I don't think she wants
to recover.
Afraid to remember
what she did.
Can't say I blame her.
Hannibal 01x12
Releves
Origianl Air Date June 13, 2013
==sync, correction by dcdah==
for www.addic7ed.com
Hospital speculates that it was
a short circuit that ignited the fire.
Unit looks well maintained.
No exposed wiring.
Horrible way to die.
There was a kid in Italy
who was in one of these things.
A spark of static electricity
from his pajamas set it off.
Two cubic yards of oxygen suddenly
became two cubic yards of fire.
Is it possible
that she set the fire herself?
She wasn't wearing
her grounding bracelet,
which prevents the build-up
of static electricity.
She took it off.
Suicide by immolation?
She was facing
two murder charges...
No. She wasn't
suicidal, Jack.
Sh-she was sick.
I was here.
I spoke to her.
Why did you speak with her?
Because I know how she felt.
She's a murder suspect.
She tried to kill you.
Your trying to be her friend
impacts the case against her.
Well, the case against her
doesn't really matter anymore,
does it, Jack?
We could use the articles
I wrote at the time
of each of the murders
as book chapter headings.
The chapters themselves would be
you telling your story...
Where you were and what you were
thinking when, one by one,
eight girls just like you
all over Minnesota were disappearing.
What are we gonna call it?
I thought about The Last Victim,
but there is already a book about
serial killers called The Last Victim.
Was it a bestseller?
Absolutely.
Especially after the guy
who wrote it killed himself.
Just as well.
Wasn't really my dad's
last victim anyway, was I?
Who was?
Marissa.
Marissa Schuur was killed
by the copycat.
So was Cassie Boyle.
I still blame my dad.
Blame him
for Nick Boyle's death?
I blame Nick Boyle
for Nick Boyle's death.
He killed Marissa.
He got what was coming to him.
Nick Boyle did not
kill your friend.
Then who did?
who killed Nick?
Nick Boyle was just
a dumb kid
who was really messed up
because his sister was murdered.
He wasn't a killer.
I've interviewed enough killers
to know one when I see one.
What gives them away?
A very specific brand
of hostility.
I see it every time I look
at Will Graham.
He did kill my dad.
As far as I'm concerned,
he killed Nick Boyle.
He and Jack Crawford told
everyone Nick was the copycat,
and then someone
murdered him for it.
You really don't think
he did it.
Whoever killed Nicholas Boyle
killed an innocent man.
See?
What are you doing
here?
Checked myself out of
the hospital.
Well, check yourself
back in.
- The fever broke.
- I don't care.
Georgia Madchen didn't
commit suicide,
and whatever happened
to her wasn't an accident.
I'm gonna have Z come down here
and stick a thermometer in you,
and if you've got a
temperature higher than 99...
She was murdered, Jack.
By who?
By whoever killed
Dr. Sutcliffe.
His blood was all over
Georgia Madchen. Her DNA was
- all over him.
- She told me there was
somebody else there.
She couldn't see his face.
There was somebody else there.
It was Dr. Sutcliffe.
She couldn't see his face
because she cut it
in half! Will,
I understand. You're looking
for an explanation,
an explanation
that makes all of this ok.
No! No, no, no. I don't.
That is not what I want. Listen,
something went wrong, and
we will never know what that is,
but for all the doctors she saw,
for all of the help she received,
she was fighting
that wrong alone.
There is nothing you could do
about that.
All her adult life
this woman was misunderstood,
and what I can do
is make sure that her death
isn't misunderstood.
She didn't kill herself.
And this wasn't an accident.
So, we dismantled the oxygen chamber... see
if anyone tampered with the wiring,
or even like a short circuit.
But nothing.
So what sparked the fire?
Inconclusive, but...
Not conclusively inconclusive.
Found this.
Thought it might've been part of
the bed or monitoring equipment,
but mass spectrometer said
it was celluloid plastic.
They don't use plastic
in those things.
Right, right. It generates,
uh, static electricity.
Her hair was melted right in there.
It's preserved like it was in Amber.
Could it have been
a plastic comb?
Well, static charge
from a plastic comb
in a highly oxygenated
environment
would be a powerful accelerant.
Anything combustible
in there would combust.
You're holding
the murder weapon.
Or whatever she used
to kill herself, yeah?
- Will...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoever killed Sutcliffe
wanted to kill him
how Georgia Madchen
killed her victim, but...
but not exactly how. Correct?
Georgia Madchen carved up
her victim's face.
Sutcliffe was, uh, nearly
decapitated at the jaw. I mean...
So she went further
the second time.
- Serial killers often do that.
- She was copied. Like, uh,
whoever killed Marissa Schuur
and Cassie Boyle wanted to copy
how Garret Jacob Hobbs killed
his victims.
But not exactly how.
Wait a minute.
Are you saying
that Dr. Sutcliffe was killed
by Garret Jacob Hobbs' copycat?
So was Georgia Madchen.
Because he thinks
she saw his face.
You said Nicholas Boyle was
the copycat.
His blood was on one of the victims.
Nicholas Boyle is dead.
Well, then he isn't
the copycat.
Could this be more
than just a fever?
Will is connecting murders that
previously had no connections.
Beyond his involvement
- in the investigations?
- That's right.
So you're wondering if the lines are
blurring, or if he's on to something.
I'm wondering
all sorts of things.
What's Will's relationship
with Abigail Hobbs right now?
- You think he's protecting her.
- He has been
ever since he shot her father.
I just don't know from what.
I can't imagine he would hide
anything criminal from you.
I've only ever known Will as a man
striving to be his best self.
You haven't known him
that long.
But we both know him well enough
to know he hasn't been himself.
He needs our support,
whether or not
mental illness is involved.
Mental illness...
Is it really mental illness,
doctor, or is it just that
his mind works so differently
from most people's
that we don't know
what else to call it?
There are days when even Will doesn't
understand his own thinking.
Dr. Dumaurier.
I'm Special Agent Jack Crawford
with the FBI.
I'd like to talk with you
about a patient of yours.
Do you have a court order?
Well I'd rather not get one,
if I don't have to.
So it's not an
official inquiry.
Not yet.
I'd hate to damage
anyone's reputation
unnecessarily.
Whose reputation
would that be?
I suspect that Dr. Hannibal
Lecter may be withholding
pertinent information
involving a murder
investigation.
No, thank you.
So... he hasn't confided
in the FBI.
You are hoping he's confided
in his psychiatrist
and that I'll tell you.
Yes, ma'am.
It's not that I think
Dr. Lecter's dangerous. I don't.
I am concerned
about a relationship he has
with one of his patients,
a man named Will Graham.
Without consent
or a court order,
I'd be in breach
of confidentiality.
That's correct.
So, if we can't discuss
Dr. Lecter,
perhaps we can discuss you.
You were attacked by a patient
not too long ago.
I read the report.
I know that there was
a statement given by Dr. Lecter.
The patient who attacked me
was a former patient
of Dr. Lecter.
And he was referred to you
by Dr. Lecter?
- Yes.
- And this patient almost killed you.
He swallowed his tongue
while he was attacking me.
That's the only thing
that saved my life.
Well, thank God
for small favors.
Yes, thank God.
You should know there was
another attack recently
in Dr. Lecter's office.
It involved another patient.
Two dead, including the patient.
That's not bad psychology,
Agent Crawford.
Putting me in a position
to have to defend
- or not to defend Dr. Lecter.
- You have to admit
he's had some pretty strange
relationships with some of his patients.
Complicated patients are conducive
to complicated relationships.
All right.
How far do you think
Dr. Lecter would go in his therapy
to treat a patient? Specifically,
Will Graham.
Hannibal refers to Will Graham
more as a friend
than as a patient.
How far do you think
he would go to treat a friend?
Well, he doesn't have
many of them,
so I imagine he'd be loyal.
I know that he's concerned
about Will Graham
and I know that he wants
to help him.
Well, I consider Will a friend,
and I'd like to help him too.
It seems to me
that Will Graham would do well
to have more friends like
Dr. Lecter.
Will Graham theorized
that the copycat killer
and Garret Jacob Hobbs were
somehow connected...
That he had insight
into Hobbs' personal life,
that they may have met,
known each other,
perhaps even killed together.
See, I would call that less of
a theory, more of a hypothesis.
- Hm, theories require evidence.
- Hm.
Let's play jeopardy, shall we?
The answer is that
these people were killed
by the copycat, who's connected
to Garret Jacob Hobbs.
You tell me how.
You mean beyond the application
of supposition
and unexplained leaps?
- Yes, that's right.
- I've been yearning
for a return to the fundamentals
of investigation.
Right?
Where is Beverly?
- Jury duty.
- It's... she's deposed in court.
Get her out of court.
Then here's what we're gonna do.
I wanna look at train station,
airport, toll road, hotel details.
I wanna track Garret Jacob Hobbs using
license plate capture from security footage.
I also want to know every phone call
he made and where he made them from.
I'll see if I can get R & I to loan us a
couple of clerks to help us cross-match.
Good. I also want to know every place
that he went that wasn't home.
I want to know how long he was
there, I want to know who he was
there with, and I want to know the
travel time to the nearest missing girl
in the Minnesota Shrike Case.
You got it?
- Yep.
- Ok.
You told me
that killing someone was
the ugliest thing in the world.
One of them.
I finally get it.
I thought there was
something wrong with me
because I didn't feel ugly
when I killed Nick Boyle.
I felt good.
That's why it was so easy
to lie about it.
Like you didn't do
anything wrong.
Feel like you'd done something
wrong when you killed my dad?
I felt terrified.
And then...
I felt powerful.
It felt good...
to get to end it,
to stop it all.
- I thought I got away from him.
- Oh,
I don't think either of us have
gotten away from your father.
I wish I'd killed him.
For killing my mom,
for killing all those girls,
for making me...
Making you what, Abigail?
Part of it.
Part of any of it.
This wasn't supposed
to be my life.
It feels like my dad's
still out there.
In a way, he is.
You mean the copycat.
I think I can catch him.
But I'm gonna need your help.
An agent from the FBI came
to see me.
He asked me questions about your
relationship with Will Graham.
Jack Crawford was here?
Mm.
He had enough doubt
in whatever it is you told him
about your patient
to feel the need to verify.
He believes Abigail Hobbs was
involved in her father's crimes,
and he suspects Will is
protecting her.
And evidently he suspects
you are protecting Will.
Are you?
Are you asking
as my psychiatrist?
I'm stepping out of my role
as your psychiatrist
and I'm speaking to you now
as your colleague.
Whatever you're doing
with Will Graham,
stop.
Will needs my help.
You've crossed
professional lines.
By making a friend?
You cannot function
as an agent of friendship
for a man who is disconnected
from the concept
as a man who is disconnected
from the concept.
I'm protecting Will
from influence.
He has flaws in his intuitive beliefs
about what makes him who he is.
I'm trying to help him
understand.
You may not be able to.
I'm not comfortable
telling Will
that my very best attempts
to help him may fail
and that my loyalty to him and his
treatment could be compromised.
Then tell him something else.
Agent Crawford also asked me
about my attack.
I see.
What did you tell him?
Half truths.
That a violent patient swallowed his
tongue while he was attacking me.
I didn't tell him how or why
or who was responsible.
You protect your patient from Jack
Crawford, but I can't protect mine.
Not anymore.
Even the very best
psychiatrists
have an inherent limitation
to their professional abilities.
You may find that difficult
to accept.
You're right. It is.
You have to maintain
boundaries, Hannibal.
When the pressures
of my personal
and professional relationships
with Will grow too great,
I assure you...
I'll find a way
to relieve them.
Much better now.
I feel clearer.
It had to be the fever.
I am finally thinking clearly
about the copycat.
The murders you're attributing
to the copycat have suspects
- whose DNA was found on the victims.
- So what?
You're choosing to ignore that?
Both of those suspects are
dead. I'm choosing
to factor that into my
psychological profile of a killer.
Georgia Madchen followed me
to Sutcliffe's office,
she witnessed his murder,
she saw the copycat.
Why not kill her
then and there?
Well, maybe h-he didn't have
the time. You know, she was
an unreliable witness,
so that bought him time.
So he framed her
for the murder.
But he wasn't planning
on framing her.
He was planning
on framing me.
You believe this is personal?
If it wasn't before,
it is now.
This could be someone
at the Bureau,
someone in the police
department, someone who knows
the crimes and has access
to the investigations.
Someone like you.
There will be evidence.
I found a pattern and now I'm
gonna reconstruct his thinking.
How do you intend to do that?
By taking Abigail
back to Minnesota.
Start where the copycat started
when he called
Garret Jacob Hobbs.
Will, this is venturing
into the paranoid.
I can't allow you to pull
Abigail into your delusion.
This isn't a delusion.
I'm not hallucinating.
I haven't lost time.
I am awake and this is real.
We found
train tickets
- purchased by Garret Jacob Hobbs.
- Tickets?
Two.
For the same train line that
one of his victims was using.
Elise Nichols?
Found more instances of Hobbs
crossing with victims.
Dinner receipts for two,
and two hotel rooms
- near the same campuses.
- We know
- he wasn't traveling alone.
- He was traveling with his daughter?
They were both registered
for the same orientation program
at St. Cloud State
on the Mississippi,
which is where the Nichols girl
was going to school.
Abigail Hobbs attended
orientations at every school
where a girl was abducted by the Minnesota
Shrike within days of the abduction.
She was with him when he was
choosing these girls.
She was the bait.
She was helping him
choose the girls.
The connection between the copycat killer
and Garret Jacob Hobbs might be family.
She kills Cassie Boyle
to impress dad?
She kills Marissa Schuur
in memoriam,
then she kills Nicholas Boyle
to cover her tracks?
Then why kill Dr. Sutcliffe?
Or the Madchen girl?
Because she's got a taste
for it now.
Or she wants to impress
someone new.
Hello, Agent Crawford.
Freddie Lounds.
You look like you came here
to arrest somebody.
Is it Abigail Hobbs,
or Will Graham?
Will Graham was here?
- Oh, then it was Abigail Hobbs.
- Where is she?
One of the other girls said Special
Agent Graham snuck her out.
I don't know why he would
feel the need to be sneaky.
He is registered as one
of her guardians. The irony.
Give us a minute here.
How's the book coming?
There's plot holes.
Tell me how you're
filling them in.
Did Abigail Hobbs kill
Nick Boyle?
Why do you say that?
Abigail is one
of those very smart girls
who hasn't quite figured out
that very smart girls grow up
and know all the moves
they're making
when they're trying
to hide something.
What is Will Graham trying
to hide?
Sorry to barge in on you,
doctor. Couldn't wait.
You want to tell me what the hell is going
on between Will Graham and Abigail Hobbs?
Will has been victim of many
unusual and irrational thoughts.
- Has he acted on these thoughts?
- Not that I'm aware of.
Or he's aware of,
for that matter.
But he has experienced periods
of lost time.
Yes, I've seen him confused
at crime scenes.
I've seen him disoriented.
He may have been confused
because he was waking up.
Might not have known where
he was or how he got there.
Waking up?
From a dissociated
personality state.
He would appear perfectly normal
and not remember a thing.
But a fractured part
of him would.
And how long have you been
aware of this?
He's only recently started
to discuss these episodes.
Well, unless recently means
just before I walked
into your office, you failed
to mention any of this to me.
Because I was trying to determine if it was
trauma and stress from the work he's doing
for you, or mental illness.
I thought it wise
to be sure before making any kind of
claim about Will Graham's sanity.
He's taken Abigail Hobbs.
You have any idea
where they might be going?
- No.
- We have evidence
that she was involved
in some of her father's crimes.
We just don't know how involved.
Is it possible that Will knew
what Abigail was doing?
Is that why he's protecting her?
There's something
you should hear.
How did you feel seeing Marissa
Schuur impaled in his antler room?
Guilty.
Because
you couldn't save her?
Because I felt
like I killed her.
Where was Will the night
that Marissa Schuur was killed?
He was supposed to be
in his hotel room.
I knocked on his door.
He didn't answer.
We know he was in Dr. Sutcliffe's
office the night that he was killed.
And Will was the last person to visit
Georgia Madchen before she died.
This dissociative personality
state you say he goes into...
whose personality is it?
He said he got so close
to Garret Jacob Hobbs
and what he had done...
that he felt he
was becoming him.
And now he has Hobbs' daughter.
Who Hobbs intended to kill.
I'm so sorry, Jack.
You look a little pasty.
Maybe you shouldn't have checked
yourself out of the hospital.
I feel fine.
It would've been
my mom's birthday next week.
We were gonna climb
Eagle Mountain to celebrate.
Highest point
in Minnesota, but...
it's not really that high.
Less than three hours
to summit. You can see
- Lake Superior from there.
- I could take you
if-if you wanna go.
I think it would
just make me sad.
Some places are
stained now.
Some people too.
I know I am.
The copycat knew your father well
enough to know about this place.
You felt like you knew
my father?
I wanted to understand him.
I felt like I had
to understand him.
Do you ever hunt?
- I fish.
- It's the same thing,
isn't it?
One you stalk,
the other you lure.
Were you more a fisherman
or a hunter?
My dad taught me how to hunt.
No, that's not
what I'm asking.
All those girls your dad
killed...
Did you fish,
or did you hunt, Abigail?
I was the lure.
Did Hannibal tell you?
No, he didn't.
He said you'd protect me,
that you'd keep it a secret.
There is something wrong
with you.
I think you're still sick.
Oh, God,
oh, God.
Jack Crawford was right
about you.
He knew.
You killed Nick Boyle,
and you helped your father kill
all of those girls.
No. I didn't help my dad
kill anybody.
No, you lured them.
You killed them.
How many other people
have you killed?
Do you think I'm the copycat?
You think I killed Marissa?
If you didn't kill her, Abigail,
then somebody you know did.
Ever think that somebody
could be you?
You were there,
you saw Marissa.
You knew about this place,
and there is something
wrong with you.
What?
Sir. I'm afraid
you're gonna have to leave.
We're preparing the cabin
for the next passengers.
I'm sorry, where...
- Where are we?
- Dulles international, Virginia.
Was there a young
woman traveling with me?
All the other passengers are
disembarked. It's just you, sir.
Abigail.
- What are you doing here?
- I was so worried about you.
Will told me he was taking you
to Minnesota,
and I strongly advised
against it.
Where is Will?
I left him at the cabin.
I didn't feel safe with him,
so I left him.
He knows everything.
So does Jack Crawford.
If I run, they'll catch me,
won't they?
You can't protect me anymore.
They'll arrest you
when they find you, yes.
And Will.
Did he kill Marissa?
They will believe he did.
They will believe he killed
others too.
Will always said whoever
called the house that morning
was the serial killer.
Why did you really call?
I wanted to warn your father
that Will Graham was coming
for him.
Why?
I was curious
what would happen.
I was curious what would happen
when I killed Marissa.
I was curious
what you would do.
You wanted me
to kill Nick Boyle.
I was hoping.
I wanted to see how much
like your father you were.
Oh, my God.
Nicholas Boyle is more
important for you gutting him.
He changed you, Abigail.
That's more important
than the life he clamored after.
How many people
have you killed?
Many more than your father.
Are you going to kill me?
I'm so sorry, Abigail.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you
in this life.
==sync, correction by dcdah==
for www.addic7ed.com