Previously on Hannibal
You entered into a Devil's
Bargain with Jack Crawford.
You know what looking
at this does.
Am I your psychiatrist, or are
we simply having conversations?
I don't want to get
in the middle of you and Jack.
- I like you as a buffer.
- Graham likes you.
Because I want
to be his friend, and I am.
Well, it seems a shame
not to take advantage.
- This is my friend Tobias.
- Good evening.
- I hate being this neurotic.
- If you weren't neurotic,
Franklyn, you would be
something much worse.
Whatever the Ripper was doing,
it worked.
These strings are harder
to bow than the regular ones.
You have to learn how to bow
authentic strings
to better bow strings
how they're made today.
I should learn to play
the easier strings first,
then the harder ones.
No, you shouldn't.
Are they really made
from cat guts?
Not always.
That's better.
Good.
If it wasn't a coyote,
the coyotes probably got it.
Probably got it
even if it was a coyote.
You're not expecting
to find it alive, are you?
We'll be lucky to find a paw.
So, you invited me over
to help you
collect animal parts?
I invited you over on the
off chance we do find it alive.
It's hard for me to wrangle
a wounded animal by myself.
Did you think it was a date?
Honestly,
it never crossed my mind.
Oh.
Why not?
You just don't seem
like you date.
Oh. Too broken to date?
You're not broken.
- What's your excuse?
- For not dating?
Why are you assuming
I don't date?
Do you?
No.
Seems like something
for somebody else.
I'm sure I'll become
that somebody someday,
but right now I think too much.
So,
what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna try to think less,
or are you just gonna wait
till it happens naturally?
I haven't thought about it.
Are you seeing anything?
Uh, no, actually.
I'm not even seeing any tracks.
I mean, except for the ones
we made.
Good morning.
Please, come in.
I have a lot of respect
for you.
Since we can't be friends,
or... you're not comfortable
with that,
I found myself looking
at my friends through your eyes,
imagining what your diagnosis
might be.
So you become
the psychoanalyst?
I become you.
Who are you psychoanalyzing?
My friend Tobias.
I... Googled "psychopaths",
went down the checklist,
and I was a little surprised
to see how many boxes
I had checked.
Why were you so curious
to Google?
He's been saying
very dark things
and then saying,
"just kidding!" A lot.
It started to seem
kind of crazy.
Psychopaths are not crazy.
They're fully aware
of what they do
and the consequences
of those actions.
Would you diagnose someone
like Tobias as a psychopath?
Or, uh, are you supposed
to diagnose other people
in front of me? Do you... would
you rather just talk about me?
Not at all.
Are you bored with me?
No.
This is your hour,
Franklyn.
We will talk about whatever
you would like to talk about.
I'd like to talk about Tobias.
Perhaps you can
- help me analyze him.
- I'm not analyzing
your friend; I'm analyzing
your perception of him.
It may help you know yourself
better. You could be
projecting onto him what
you consider to be your flaws.
Does that mean
that I'm a psychopath?
You're not a psychopath,
although you may be attracted
to them.
The victim is Douglas Wilson,
a member
of the Baltimore Metropolitan
Orchestra's brass section...
A trombone player.
He was killed shortly after
his last performance.
Blunt force trauma
to the back of the head.
His killer brought him here
to... put on a show.
Will, is it me, or is it
becoming easier for you to look?
I tell myself...
It's purely
an intellectual exercise.
Well, in the narrow view
of forensics,
- that's exactly what it is.
- They're not any easier, Jack.
I shake it off,
keep on looking.
Good.
You shake it off.
Get to work.
We'll come back in
when you're ready for us.
I open his throat
from the outside
to open the trachea
and expose the vocal chords.
I open his throat
from the inside
using the neck of a cello.
Powder on the wound.
Rosin from the bow.
I wanted to play him.
I wanted to create a sound.
My sound.
This... is my design.
I worry that I've made
Franklyn feel powerless.
He wants to be my friend.
His obsession with me is
interfering with his progress.
I'm considering referring
him to another doctor.
Referrals can be complicated.
I referred you
to another psychiatrist.
You refused.
I'm more tenacious
than Franklyn.
Why were you so tenacious?
I feel protective of you.
You support me
as a colleague and psychiatrist,
and as a human being.
I want to be supportive
of you... after what happened.
I'm not the only psychiatrist who's
ever been attacked by a patient.
I hesitated to even bring up
the subject
of an obsessive patient because
of your traumatic experience.
Hannibal...
I'm your psychiatrist;
you're not mine.
Played him
like a fiddle.
Along with rosin powder,
we found sodium carbonate,
sulfur dioxide, lye,
and olive oil in the wounds.
What is the deal with
the olive oil?
- Sure wasn't making salad.
- He removed anything
non-muscular or fatty
from around the vocal folds.
The chords themselves were treated
with a sulfur dioxide solution.
The sulfur dioxide had the effect
of hardening the vocal chords.
Made them easier to play.
Had to open you up to get
a decent sound out of you.
You pick it up and can't play
it, he'll put you down and play you.
He took the time to whiten
the vocal chords before playing them.
It's not about whitening them; It was
about, um, increasing elasticity.
He treated the vocal chords the
same way you treat catgut string.
Yes, I played the violin.
This takes a steady hand.
A confidence.
He's killed before.
- Like this?
- No, not like this.
This is a skilled musician
trying a new instrument.
Among the first musical
instruments were flutes
carved from human bone.
This murder was
a performance.
Every life is a piece of music.
Like music, we are finite
events, unique arrangements,
sometimes harmonious,
sometimes dissonant.
Sometimes
not worth hearing again.
- He's a poet and a psychopath.
- And a craftsman.
He was shrinking and tanning
the vocal chords.
Like turning iron wire
into musical steel string.
Was there olive oil?
- Yes.
- Whatever sound
he was trying to produce,
it was an authentic one.
Olive oil hasn't been used in the
production of catgut for over a century.
It was said to increase
the life of the strings
and create a sweeter,
more melodic sound.
No, I hear what
he was playing
behind my eyes
when I close them.
What do you see
behind closed eyes?
Um... I see myself.
You said the killer was
performing.
- Who was he performing for?
- I don't know. Um...
Patron of the arts?
A fellow musician? Or...
Another killer?
It's a serenade.
No, this isn't how he kills. Normally,
he doesn't kill for an audience.
And you believe he risked
getting caught for a serenade?
I believe...
he wants to show someone
how well he plays.
Do you remember
when I said Tobias was saying
very dark things?
- I made note of it.
- Well, he said that he wanted
to cut someone's throat
and play it like a violin.
They found somebody
whose throat was cut
and played like a violin.
So you think Tobias killed
that man at the symphony?
I don't know.
I-I...
If I do, do I have
to report it?
Do you have a reason not to?
What if I'm wrong?
What if you're right?
I'm always wrong.
I don't know. Why would he say
something like that to me?
Why do you think?
'Cause he knows I'd tell you.
You're Franklyn's therapist,
Dr. Lecter.
- Nice to see you again.
- Is it Tobias?
Yes.
Your strings are all gut.
I also carry steel and polymer
strings, if you prefer.
I prefer gut.
Harps strung with gut still make
music after 2,000 years.
I didn't
- hear you ring the bell.
- I didn't want you to stop playing.
- Was it an original composition?
- Something I've been writing.
- You compose?
- I discover.
Can't impose
traditional composition
on an instrument
that's inherently free form.
What instrument
would that be?
The Theremin.
It can generate any pitch
throughout its range...
Even those
between conventional notes.
And so can a violin,
or a trombone.
It seems we are both comfortable
playing between conventional notes.
I hear the symphony's
looking for a new trombonist.
Altogether horrible
what happened.
Not altogether.
It's an unfortunate way
to leave the symphony, yes,
but I can't help thinking
the orchestra will be better
-for it.
- At least the brass section.
What brings you here
looking for gut?
My harpsichord needs new strings.
It's making an awful noise.
Perhaps you could help.
What kind of animal was it?
It might've been a raccoon.
Might've been?
Well, by the time
I knocked a hole in the chimney,
it climbed out the top.
Well, at least it got out.
What are you doing out?
I thought I'd come over,
make some noise,
shoo away any predators
at your door.
It looks like you're making
plenty of noise all by yourself.
You avoided being in a room
alone with me essentially
since I met you.
You were smooth about it.
- Evidently not smooth enough.
- And now you're making
house calls?
Just a drive-by
on my way home.
Since you're not my patient.
No.
I'm not.
I’m confused.
You have to stop thinking
so much.
I can stop the thinking
if we're not...
- But if we're...
- Intimate.
The way that I am
in relationships...
Not that this is a relationship;
it's just a kiss.
A great kiss.
But I...
the way that I am isn't
- compatible with the way that...
- The way I am.
I wouldn't be good for you.
You wouldn't be good for me,
and I wouldn't be able
to stop analyzing,
because I have this
professional curiosity
about you and...
I am not your patient.
If I were
my patient, my advice to me...
don't do this.
I have to follow my own advice.
I'm gonna go ahead
and go now.
Goodnight, Will.
More wine?
A late harvest Vidal
from Linden.
Oh, Virginia.
I thought it was French.
The Virginia wine revolution
is upon us.
I apologize for being
so blunt, Tobias,
but I have to ask.
Did you kill that trombonist?
Do you really have to ask?
No. Just changing the subject.
Franklyn gave you my message.
The murder is being
investigated by the FBI.
They're going to find you.
Let them.
You want to get caught?
I want them to try.
They may investigate me
because I own a string shop.
They'll send men
to investigate,
and I'll kill them.
Then I'll find Franklyn
and kill him.
Then I would disappear.
- Don't kill Franklyn.
- I've been looking forward to it.
Actually...
- I was going to kill you.
- Of course you were.
I'm lean.
Lean animals yield
the toughest gut.
What stopped you
from wanting to kill me?
Or have you stopped?
I stopped after I followed you
one night. Out of town.
To a lonely road.
To a bus yard.
You're reckless, Tobias.
I'm not going to tell anyone
what I saw you do and do well.
So my recklessness doesn't
concern you.
It concerns me
because you won't be drawing
attention just to yourself.
I could use a friend.
Someone who can
understand me.
Who thinks like I do and can see
the world and the people in it
the way I do.
I know exactly how you feel.
But I don't want
to be your friend.
Then why did you invite me
here for dinner?
Wasn't just to restring
your harpsichord.
I was going to kill you.
I didn't poison you, Tobias.
I wouldn't do that to the food.
Expecting someone?
No.
Well, I kissed Alana Bloom.
Well, come in.
You have a guest?
A colleague.
You just missed him.
Didn't finish his dinner.
An urgent call of some sort.
He had to leave suddenly.
This benefits you,
because I have dessert for two.
Tell me,
what was Alana's reaction?
She said she wouldn't be good
for me,
and I wouldn't be good for her.
I don't disagree.
She would feel an obligation to her
field of study to observe you,
and you would resent her for it.
- I know.
- Wondering then
why you kissed her,
and felt compelled
to drive an hour in the snow
to tell me about it.
Well, I wanted to kiss her
since I met her. She's very kissable.
You waited a long time,
which suggests you were
kissing her for a reason,
in addition to wanting to.
I heard an animal
trapped in my chimney.
Um...
Broke through the wall
to get it out.
Didn't find anything inside.
Alana showed up,
she looked at me...
I... maybe her face changed.
I don't know.
But, um, she knew.
What did she know, Will?
There was no animal
in the chimney.
It was only in my head.
I sleepwalk.
I get headaches.
I am hearing things.
I feel unstable.
That's why you kissed her.
A clutch for balance.
You said yourself
what you do is not good for you.
Well, unfortunately,
I am good for it.
Are you still hearing
this killer's serenade
behind your eyes?
Well, it's our song.
I hesitate telling you this, as it
borders on a violation of doctor-patient
confidentiality.
A patient told me today
he suspects a friend of his may
be involved with the murder
at the symphony.
Right, um...
Um... what did he say
about his friend?
He owns a music store
in Baltimore,
specializing
in string instruments.
Perhaps
you should interview him.
Yeah.
For the first time in a long while,
I see a possibility of friendship.
Is there someone new
in your life?
I met a man much like myself.
Same hobbies, same worldviews,
but I'm not interested in being his friend.
I'm curious about him,
and that got me curious
about friendship.
Whose friendship
are you considering?
Oddly enough, a colleague
and a patient,
not unlike how I'm a colleague
and a patient of yours.
We've discussed him before.
- Will Graham.
- He's nothing like me.
We see the world
in different ways,
yet he can
assume my point of view.
By profiling
the criminally insane.
As good a demonstration as any.
I find it reassuring.
It's nice
when someone sees us, Hannibal.
Or has the ability to see us.
It requires trust.
Trust is difficult for you.
You've helped me
to better understand what I want
in a friendship,
and what I don't.
Someone worthy
of your friendship.
- Yes.
- You spend
a lot of time
building walls, Hannibal.
It's natural to want to see
if someone is clever enough
to climb over them.
JSB's Suite No.1.
Okay.
Special agent Will Graham
with the FBI.
- Are you the owner?
- Yes. Tobias Budge.
I'm just showing one of my students out.
Can I have a moment?
Adagio.
For Saturday.
What can I help you with?
We're investigating the death
of Douglas Wilson. He was...
The trombonist.
That's right.
Did you know him?
I was aware of him.
Baltimore is a small town,
and the cultural arts community
is an even smaller one.
Well, that's why
we're here, Mr. Budge.
I hear someone cut his throat
and tried to play it with a bow.
Why do you say "try"?
The strings have to be treated.
You can't just
open somebody up and draw a bow
across their innards
and expect to produce a sound.
The vocal chords were chemically treated, uh,
similar to how catgut string is treated.
We kept those details
out of the press.
Looking for someone who knows
how to manufacture gut strings?
Anybody leap to mind?
Mine are imported from Italy.
Best catgut is.
The string section
of the Baltimore Metropolitan
Orchestra refuses
to play anything else.
More authentic.
A richer, darker sound.
Allows music
to say what words can't.
Something wrong?
Didn't you hear that?
I didn't hear anything.
Excuse me a minute.
Sorry about that.
Officers?
I need ERT at Chordophone
Strings, downtown Baltimore.
Officer down.
Nine.
Nine times.
I can count on two hands
the number of times I've been
dumped by a psychiatrist.
I'm sorry, Franklyn,
but I think you should
see another doctor.
- You're giving me a referral?
- Yes, I am.
- You were a referral!
- I am also a part of the problem.
You focus too much
on your therapist,
and not enough on your therapy.
You lost respect for me
because I wouldn't
- report Tobias, didn't you?
- Report Tobias for what?
Tobias.
I came to say goodbye,
Franklyn.
What do you mean, goodbye?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, is that your blood?
I just killed two men.
The police came to question me
about the murder.
Ok... you have
to give yourself up right now.
This plane is going down.
Let it have
a controlled descent.
We can get you back up
in the air again.
There's rehabilitation
for everyone.
Franklyn, I want you
to leave now.
Stay right where you are,
Franklyn.
You've done
a horrible thing,
and... I know...
that you wish to God
that you didn't.
But you did.
And there's nothing you can do
to change that.
Only thing you can change is
your future.
Right?
No? You're probably scared.
You probably feel
- like you're all alone.
- I'm not alone.
That's right.
You're not alone. Nothing has
happened in our relationship that
you and I can't...
I was looking forward to that.
I saved you the trouble.
Ah!
Ahhh!
I was worried you were dead.
Tobias Budge
killed two
Baltimore police officers,
nearly killed
an FBI special agent,
and after all of that,
his first stop
is here, at your office.
He came to kill my patient.
Your patient. Is that
who Budge was serenading?
I don't know.
Franklyn knew more
than he was telling me.
He told Mr. Budge
that he didn't have
to kill anymore.
And then he broke Franklyn's
neck, and then he attacked me.
You killed him?
Yeah.
Could Franklyn have been
involved
in whatever Budge was doing?
I thought this was a simple
matter of poor choice in friends.
This doesn't feel simple to me.
I feel like I've...
dragged you into my world.
I got here on my own.
But I appreciate the company.
I'm going to start
seeing patients again.
It's strange, thinking about
going back to daily practice.
Well, it's good
you stepped away.
Even if it was
only for a few days.
Patients will sit
where Franklyn died.
I will sit where I almost died,
and I will offer therapy.
It's easy to understand
why you retired after you were
attacked.
Will you ever feel comfortable
returning to psychiatric work?
This is psychiatric work.
One patient isn't a practice.
I can't help
feeling responsible
for what happened to Franklyn.
Every person has an intrinsic responsibility
for their own life, Hannibal.
No one else can take on
that responsibility.
Not even you.
Did you take responsibility
when you were attacked
by your patient?
Yes.
But I don't take
responsibility for his death.
Nor should you.
==sync, correction by dcdah==
for www.addic7ed.com