Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Previously on Hannibal...
Special Agent Jack Crawford.
I head
the behavioral science unit.
Will Graham.
Works for the FBI but isn't FBI.
He catches insane men
because he can think like them.
This is Dr. Lecter.
What you need
is a way out of dark places
when Jack sends you there.
Will is connecting murders
that previously
had no connections.
You catch these killers
by getting into their heads.
But you also allow them
into your own.
I hallucinated
that I killed her,
but it wasn't real.
Will Graham, you're under
arrest for murder.
Whoever's doing this to me,
they'll be close to you.
You have to be careful,
Hannibal.
They're starting
to see your pattern.
Jack Crawford's beliefs
about you might unravel.
[Dramatic music]
(Both grunting)
(Jack yelling)
Oh!
Ah!
(Yelling)
♪
(Classical piano music)
This course is called
Mukozuke -
seasonal sashimi,
sea urchin, water clam,
and squid.
What a beautiful
presentation, doctor.
Kaiseki -
a Japanese art form that honors
- the taste and aesthetic of what we eat.
- Well,
I almost feel guilty
about eating it.
I never feel guilty
eating anything.
Mmm.
I can't quite place the fish.
He was a flounder.
I last prepared this meal
for my aunt
Murasaki,
under similarly
unfortunate circumstances.
Well, what circumstances
were those?
A loss.
This is a loss.
Will is a loss
and we're mourning a death.
Will's death is on me, not you.
- It's on both of us.
- I can't stop thinking that
Will may be convicted of five murders
while I am only maybe convicted of one.
Well, you're not on trial.
I will be -
in the halls of the FBI.
And so will you.
I mean, according to
Will Graham, this was all you.
Will was your bloodhound.
You can't ignore where
- he points.
- I'm not ignoring it.
You have to investigate me. It's
in my best interest, and yours.
Yes, it is.
But I also can't ignore
the fact that
my bloodhound went mad
before he pointed
in your direction.
We can't define Will
only by his maddest edges.
We can't define Will at all.
(Stag huffing)
(Inaudible speaking)
What did you say?
I said, how does that
make you feel?
Makes me feel...
like...
I'm sitting in a dunking tank
and you're lobbing softballs,
hoping to make a splash,
but you keep
missing the target.
Fortunately, I have time
for a few more lobs.
You are in my hospital.
You're my patient now, Will.
I'm not talking to you,
Frederick.
(Sigh)
I want to talk
to Dr. Lecter.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
According to Dr. Bloom,
you were warned against putting someone
with Will Graham's issues into the field.
Yes. That's correct.
Were you aware that Dr. Bloom
would be filing this report?
Yes. She told me
what she was going to do.
Did you advise her
- against it?
- I told her she should do
whatever she felt was
necessary. Evidently,
she felt it was necessary
to file the report.
These are allegations
of misconduct.
- It's damning stuff, Jack.
- I never stated anywhere
that this was misconduct.
In my opinion,
it was a lapse in judgment.
A lapse in judgment is
misconduct.
There'll be an internal
investigation.
There should be.
A federal
examiner is someone who arrives
at a battlefield
after the battle
and bayonets the wounded.
You have wounded
Agent Crawford.
Who do you think is gonna be
getting the bayonet?
There is a general desire
to see this go away
quickly and quietly.
In light of that,
Dr. Bloom,
I would greatly appreciate it
if you would recant your report.
No. Will Graham's life has
been destroyed.
How that happened has to be
a matter of record.
I'm sorry, Jack.
Dr. Bloom is not
easily swayed.
This is going to get ugly.
It already has.
- Was there a storm?
- Ah, it looks like someone's
- blasting beaver dams again.
- Aw, man.
It smells real bad down here!
Probably dead beavers!
(He shouts.)
Get me out of here! Ah!
Will Graham has asked
to see me.
I would like to see him.
I continue to be curious
about the way he thinks,
despite all that's happened.
He's still influencing you.
Will Graham asking to see you betrays
his clear intent to manipulate you.
And if I agree to see Will?
It betrays your clear intent
to manipulate him.
I miss him.
You are obsessed
with Will Graham.
I'm intrigued.
Obsessively.
And he will
take advantage of that.
Will is my friend.
Why?
Why is he your friend?
He sees his own mentality
as grotesque but useful.
Like a chair of antlers.
He can't repress who he is.
There's an honesty in that
I admire.
I imagine there's an honesty
in that you can relate to.
What can't you repress,
Hannibal?
(Door buzzer)
(Door opening)
(Footsteps)
Hello, Will.
Dr. Lecter.
Lost in thought?
Not lost.
Not anymore.
(Will chuckles softly.)
I used to hear my thoughts
inside my skull
with the same, um...
tone, timbre, accent,
as if the words were
coming out of my mouth.
- And now?
- Now...
...my inner voice sounds
like you.
I can't get you out of my head.
Friendship can sometimes involve a
breach of individual separateness.
You're not my friend.
The, uh, light from friendship
won't reach us
for a million years. That's how
far away from friendship we are.
I imagine it's easier
to believe I am responsible
for those murders than it is
to accept that you are.
Sure is.
Your inner voice can provide a method
of taking control of your behavior,
accepting responsibility
for what you've done.
Giving your thoughts words
encourages clarity.
Oh, I have clarity.
About you.
Our conversations, Will,
were only ever about you
opening your eyes to the truth
of who you are.
What you did to me
is in my head,
and I will find it.
I'm going to remember,
Dr. Lecter,
and when I do,
there will be a reckoning.
I have huge faith in you, Will.
I always have.
I'm amazed what falls off
the best of us when moving through a room.
Lessons learned
from cellular decay:
Enjoy
the world while we have it
and give a little bit back.
When possible, I try to leave
an indelible mark wherever I go.
Hopefully not with your DNA.
How long
will you have my suits?
You might want to think about
supplementing your wardrobe.
- I frequently do.
- You know,
this is just a formality.
Nobody expects
to find anything.
Except for maybe Will Graham.
He'll have to be disappointed.
The beauty of what you do, Ms. Katz,
is in its certainty.
It'll be your evidence
that convicts Will.
Well, I found enough of it.
No need to infer or intuit
or trust.
So much simpler
than psychiatry.
Will is doing his best
to understand where he is
and why.
You were supposed
to protect him.
From himself?
Yeah.
I'm not mad at you -
not any more than I'm mad
at myself. We all missed it,
whatever it was - is.
We all are not suspects.
You're not a suspect;
You're the new Will Graham.
Thank you for coming,
Dr. Lecter.
Jack, what can I do for you?
I was hoping you would help me
with a psychological profile.
(Man): We found
another body.
(Camera click)
This way, doctor.
This is the fourth body
we've recovered so far. There's
- at least one more down there.
- How long have they been here?
Hard to say,
but someone went through a lot
of trouble to make sure
that they were well preserved.
They've been coated
in some kind of resin.
The big one was partially sealed,
rotting from the inside out.
The other three look
like they were embalmed.
(Jack): Whatever he's doing, he's
still figuring out how to do it.
Were they injected
with silicone?
- They were injected with something.
- Silicone?
A technique for making
resin-coated models out of fish.
Helps the body retain shape
in death.
He's making human models.
You make models of things
that you want to keep;
these were tossed in the river.
Maybe they were imperfect.
(Jack): These are
his discards.
I'm giving you informed consent
to discuss me as your patient.
With whom?
Jack Crawford.
Disclosure of patient
information should be limited
to the requirements
of the situation.
What is the situation,
Hannibal?
Will Graham made accusations.
Jack's only being thorough.
You're keeping
Agent Crawford close.
We share an obsession.
I got to be Will Graham today.
I consulted
at an FBI crime scene.
I stood in Will's shoes,
looked through his eyes,
and I saw death...
...how I imagined
he would see it.
Why would you be inviting
the scrutiny of the FBI?
I'm being as open and honest
as I know how.
You maintain an air
of transparency...
...while putting me
in the position to lie for you.
Again.
You're not just lying for me.
How far will this flirtation
with the FBI go?
It would seem Jack Crawford is less
suspicious of me than you are.
Jack Crawford doesn't know
what you're capable of.
Neither do you.
Come on! Come on!
(Dog barking)
Whoa!
(She laughs.)
- (Will): And how are the dogs?
- (Alana): Good. Well,
Winston keeps running away,
but the others are adjusting.
Where does Winston go?
Home.
- Well, he's not gonna find me there.
- Not today.
But maybe someday he might.
With the right defense.
I don't currently have
legal representation.
- You keep firing your lawyers.
- No, they're the FBI's lawyers.
Then I'll find you a lawyer who's
not affiliated with the FBI.
What defense
do you think I have?
Automatism.
Allows a defendant to argue
they shouldn't be held
criminally liable for their
actions due to unconsciousness.
- Unconsciousness?
- Will...
...your mind was on fire.
You had no control
of what you were doing,
much less remember doing it.
What if I could remember?
What if I could remember
how this was done to me?
What if you could remember
how you did it?
You believe Hannibal.
I believe the Will Graham
standing in front of me now
is incapable of that violence.
I believe you lost your mind,
and for periods of
time, you weren't
the Will Graham I know.
I hear Hannibal's voice
in the well of my mind.
I hear him saying words
that he's never said to me.
It isn't my imagination.
It's... it's something else.
Have you ever helped a patient
recover memories?
(Metronome ticking)
Close your eyes.
(Whispering): Feel the happiness
in your limbs.
Imagine yourself in a safe...
and relaxing place.
Safe to relax completely.
No matter how deeply you go...
my voice will go with you.
This... this isn't working.
(Will panting)
What did you see?
Will,
what did you see?
Salted and ash-baked celeriac
with foraged sel fou.
Frederick, you have tested me.
♪
(Classical piano music)
It's rare that I cook
a meatless meal.
I lost a kidney; I have to
watch my protein intake.
You didn't lose it, Frederick;
it was taken from you.
I remain impressed
with your recovery.
One can grow to love beets.
Alana Bloom was
visiting with your former
patient today.
Will was never my patient.
The irony is
that he is my patient,
but he refuses to speak to me.
Makes me feel
like I'm fumbling with his head
like a freshman
pulling at a panty girdle.
Will is going to be a challenge
for any psychiatrist.
He is so lucid, so perceptive.
He's trained
in criminal psychology,
and he is a mass murderer.
He's a prize patient.
Or should be.
How was Dr. Bloom's visit?
He asked her to hypnotize him
so he could
recover his memories.
This is delicious.
Was he successful?
Only in playing
Dr. Bloom.
It's sad to see
a brilliant psychiatrist
fall for such hoary
old chestnuts.
She wants to believe him;
I do too.
You do realize you're his
favorite topic of conversation.
Hannibal, Hannibal, Hannibal.
Not with me, of course,
but with everyone else
who will listen. He tells
everyone that you are
a monster.
Well, in that case, you are dining with
a psychopathic murderer, Frederick.
(Man): You have nice skin.
(Honking continuously)
(Alarm chirps.)
(Honking stops.)
Dental medical records
placed the six - all adults,
both men and women,
different ages, different ethnicities,
all from different states;
nothing in common except they all disappeared
from their homes with their vehicles.
And they all had large amounts
of heroin in their systems.
Enough to be
the cause of death?
And then some.
What's this strange skin
discoloration on these bodies?
We found traces of BHT,
which is a color preservative.
He wants them to look alive.
Shot them up
with a little China white,
injected them
with preservatives,
then filled the bodies with
silicone so they don't emaciate,
then he seals them
with, like, a hard resin shell.
What are these puncture wounds?
Those are like eyelets.
Um, something was
threaded through.
They were strung up, mounted,
- presented.
- So how's he choosing them?
We got nothing.
Appears to be random,
but if this is
the discard pile,
I'm curious to know
how many were keepers.
All right, I want a list
of any missing persons
that disappeared
along with their vehicles
in the neighboring states.
Got it?
Got it.
(Door buzzer)
It's good to see you.
Don't know how I feel
about seeing you.
I'll let you know when I do.
- Does Jack know you're here?
- No,
- but he shouldn't be surprised.
- I'm surprised.
I'm...compartmentalizing.
There are
a lot of people missing.
Ah.
- You have the file with you?
- Yes.
And pictures?
Yes.
The first six bodies
were found in the same place - dumped
in a river, caught in a beaver dam.
What's he do to 'em?
He targets them,
follows them home,
abducts them,
and preserves them.
You want to know how he's
choosing them, don't you?
I thought you would
have some ideas.
These are DMV pictures
of people who are
still missing
under similar circumstances
from three different states.
Tell me what you see.
It's a color palette.
(Exhaling)
(Person choking)
(Will choking)
(Choking)
(Spitting)
(Coughing)
(Dog whining)
Hi, Winston.
Come here, boy.
There you go.
I suppose
you blame me too, huh?
Hello, Jack.
You need to take
better care of this dog.
Mm. I feel horrible.
I got all the dogs chipped,
but at least they're not
running away to anywhere
I can't find 'em.
He's just looking for Will.
Hmm? Yeah.
Isn't that why you're here?
Listen, uh...
...I understand why you felt
you had to file that report.
You questioned my judgment
when it needed to be questioned.
Yes, it did.
And it will help in Will's
defense if it's in the record.
Declaring Hannibal's guilt is
more important to Will
than establishing
his own defense.
Hannibal's not guilty.
Neither is Will.
But he's clinging to the hope
Hannibal did this so he doesn't
have to face what he did.
Convince me he didn't know
what he was doing.
I would really like
to be convinced, Alana.
A psychopath wouldn't be
so scared of the truth, Jack.
Will's terrified,
but that's not stopping him
from trying to find it.
Somebody's gotta find
the truth, eh, Winston?
If Will doesn't remember
what he did...
he'll never accept the truth.
(Jack):Will?
Will?
Hey, Will.
Hi, Jack.
Where were you just now?
Gone fishin'.
What are you doing here?
I needed to remind myself
of who you once were.
You know, that man
whose classroom
I walked into months ago.
I remember that man.
Memories are all I have.
Imagine how
nice it is
to stumble on a new one.
I was
almost certain Hannibal Lecter
did this to me.
And it's a funny thing, doubt.
I had nothing to prove to myself
or... or anyone else
that Hannibal was responsible -
not even a memory.
You have something now?
You've recovered a memory?
Yes.
That's meaningless.
Not to me.
He did it so well.
I... there... there wasn't
an orgy of evidence.
There was just enough
to convince you.
We investigated your claims
about Dr. Lecter, Will - thoroughly.
We went over every fiber
of every stitch of clothing.
We took his DNA.
We took his fingerprints.
We found nothing.
You let the fox
into the henhouse.
You stood over Cassie Boyle's body in that
field and you described yourself to me.
No, I described
Hannibal Lecter.
I can't hear this anymore.
I... I am not the intelligent
psychopath you are looking for.
Goodbye, Will.
(Dejected sigh)
You may not believe me now.
You will.
(Shuddering)
(Grunting with effort)
(Yelling)
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player