Four of the *** are made
from materials including human remains.
Kade Purnell,
Office of the Inspector General,
FBI Oversight.
I'm pleading innocent.
You'll be found guilty and
given the federal death penalty.
What defense
do you think I have?
You had no control of what
you were doing, much less
remember doing it.
(coughing)
Betrayal was
the only thing that felt
real to me.
I trusted you.
- Let me help you.
- I need your help.
(Jack): We investigated
your claims about Dr. Lecter.
We found nothing. You stood over
Cassie Boyle's body in that field and
- you described yourself to me.
- (Will): No, I described Hannibal Lecter.
- (Beverly): You think Will is innocent.
- I don't know what I think.
I think he still wants to save
lives. That's what I think.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
(electricity buzzing)
(man):Mr. Graham, it's time.
(breathing quickly)
(opera music)
Let me tell you the story of
a mild-mannered FBI instructor
who was asked to create a
psychological profile of a murderer -
Garret Jacob Hobbs,
the Minnesota Shrike.
He killed young women
that looked
just like his daughter.
He killed them
and he ate them.
Will Graham understood the way Hobbs
thought. That's how he caught him.
He shot Hobbs dead while he cut
his daughter's throat.
So, Will Graham was able
to save Abigail
Hobbs' life. But
the profile that he created
of her father was so vivid
that he couldn't escape it.
See.
And in an unconscious state...
he killed
four more women.
Cassie Boyle.
Marissa Schuur.
Georgia Madchen.
Abigail Hobbs.
He was able to save
Abigail Hobbs
from her father, but he wasn't
able to save her from himself.
He killed her
and he ate her.
At the very least,
he ate her ear. What happened
to the rest of Abigail Hobbs
is locked away
in the recesses of Will Graham's
traumatized mind,
or so he would
have you believe.
Something else you should know
about Will Graham: he has
remarkable visual memory;
he's keenly insightful
to the human condition; and...
I would argue,
the smartest person
in this room.
He's capable
of creating
a psychological profile
of a completely different kind
of murderer.
One that would
become his alibi.
Moment of truth.
If I only knew
what the truth was.
There's nothing wrong
with your instincts.
My instincts have not yet
arrived at conviction.
Mine have, with the benefit
of no previous involvement
and no personal connections
to the accused.
- Meaning I can't be impartial?
- Of course you can be impartial,
but right now you're not.
You have to believe something,
as long as there is reason
and evidence to believe.
You've got reason;
you've got evidence.
Will Graham is playing a game.
I understand why that might be
hard for you to accept.
Do you?
It's easier to be a man who
missed his friend's suffering
than it is to be the head
of Behavioral Sciences
at the FBI who missed a killer
standing right in front of him.
There's a reason
that you're a witness for
the prosecution, Agent Crawford.
Remind me what that reason is.
If you can't represent
your own beliefs,
represent the Bureau's.
(door opening)
(woman): Agent Crawford?
Let yourself
off the hook, Jack.
- How did you meet Will Graham? - I met
him at the opening of the Evil Minds
Research Museum. He didn't agree
with what we called it.
He told me that the title
mythologized banal and cruel men
who didn't deserve to be
thought of as super-villains.
- And what was your first impression?
- He was intelligent.
And arrogant.
And very likely
on the spectrum.
Which is why he wasn't
real FBI. He didn't pass
- the screening procedures.
- Yes.
- But you felt that he was qualified to
work in the field. - Under my supervision.
And you believed that he was valuable
because he could think like a killer?
- He could think like anybody.
- Sounds like a super-villain.
Five horrendous murders,
over 40 different
pieces of forensic
and physical evidence
that tell us that Will Graham can think
like a killer because he is one.
Rather than feel tormented
by the work he did,
Will Graham enjoyed the cover
his role at the FBI gave him
- to commit his terrible crimes.
- I don't believe that to be true.
Agent Crawford?
Will hated every second
of the work. He hated it.
He didn't fake that.
He hated it
and I kept making him do it.
Why then is it that when you offered him
an opportunity to quit, he refused?
(firmly): Because he was
saving lives.
I had been warned
by more than one person
that if I pushed Will,
I'd break him.
I put those checks and balances
in place, then ignored them.
And here we are.
What does Jack Crawford drink?
Whatever it is, I need to send
him a very expensive bottle.
He said I'm a killer
because he drove me insane.
No, he paved the road
for your defense.
Well, he didn't say
I'm innocent.
Innocence isn't a verdict,
Mr. Graham, but "not guilty" is.
This isn't law;
it's advertising.
Advertising trivializes;
it, uh, manipulates;
it's vulgar.
Boo-hoo.
So is the law.
We have to create desire
to find you "not guilty,"
which is nonexistent
in this courtroom right now.
We're manipulating people into
buying something they don't need.
- Mr. Brauer? - They don't want
your innocence. Thank you.
Unconsciousness
in a pretty package,
that I can sell.
If I take the moral high ground
with you, I'll get you killed.
I think I opened your mail.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
That was a good and brave
thing you did for Will today.
It may have cost me my job.
The prospect doesn't seem
to trouble you as much
as I would have thought.
Haven't felt better in weeks.
(glasses touched)
Clarity will do that.
Mm.
Tell me, Jack.
Was your testimony meant
to be a resignation?
There is something appealing
about walking away
from all of the noise.
I'm...
content to let the chips fall.
The magic door is
always attractive -
step through and leave
all your burdens behind.
I've given my life...
to death.
And now death has
followed you home...
...come to live
in your house.
(taking a breath)
Bella has kept our bedroom from
looking too much like a sickroom.
There are flowers,
but not too many.
You know.
She insists that there are
no pills in sight.
So, I've been thinking about
taking her to Italy where we met.
We could...
She could die there.
Jack.
You're not sick.
You don't have to go
into the ground with her.
When Bella's lost to you,
the FBI could still be there.
You're telling me not
to commit professional suicide?
As a friend, I'm telling you
not to force an issue
for the short-term emotional
satisfaction it can have.
(inaudible)
...shrunken capillaries.
The ear was cut from a corpse
no more than 48 hours ago.
- Before the trial started.
- We fumed it all -
ear's clean, no prints
on either of the envelopes,
besides the courier,
paralegal, and lawyer.
We know
Will Graham didn't do it.
- It wouldn't surprise me.
- The timing's deliberate.
It was choreographed to drop the ear
at the beginning of Will's trial.
Such a gift has
great significance.
- A gift from who?
- Will claimed
someone else committed
the crimes he's accused of.
He said that person was you.
Perhaps he was half right.
Oh, you've gotta be kidding me.
It seems you have an admirer.
You think someone sent me
an ear because they admire me?
The boundaries
of what's considered normal
are getting narrower.
Outside those boundaries,
this may be intended
as a helpful gesture.
How far would you go
to help me?
It hadn't occurred to me
to send you an ear.
But I'm grateful someone has.
Gratitude has
a short half-life.
So can doubt.
I have new thoughts
about who you are.
There may very well be
another killer.
(softly): I want there to be.
Some part of you
still suspects me.
I don't know what anyone is
capable of anymore,
least of all myself.
But, um...
...I know there is
no evidence against you.
There never was.
And accusing you
makes me look insane.
I'm not insane.
Not anymore.
And you may not be guilty.
This ear you were sent
is an opportunity.
If someone else is responsible
for your crimes,
perhaps he now wants
to be seen.
Why would he want
to be seen now?
He cares what happens to you.
The prosecution calls
Freddie *** to the stand.
I swear to tell the truth, the whole
truth, nothing but the truth.
Could you please describe
your relationship
with Abigail Hobbs?
We were very close.
I was helping her write a book
about surviving her father.
Did you ever discuss
- Will Graham with Abigail?
- Abigail told me
she believed Will Graham wanted
to kill her and cannibalize her
like her father wanted to do.
She was right.
I should've listened to her.
Do you blame yourself
for her death?
I blame Will Graham.
Thank you.
Your witness.
Miss Lounds.
Could you please...
remind me how many times
you've been sued for libel?
(quietly): Six.
Sorry?
- Six.
And how many times
did you settle?
Six.
Thank you.
Nothing further.
The defense calls
Dr. Alana Bloom.
I believe Will's
empathy disorder...
...combined with the effects
of viral encephalitis...
Do we have to do this
like this?
I don't want the first time
you do this to be in court.
Dr. Bloom, weren't
you and the accused
romantically involved?
How is this relevant
to the case?
It's relevant
to your testimony.
In that court, your feelings,
your emotions,
your pro-everything-Will-Graham
will be on trial.
You get all starey
and non-blinky like that,
it'll undermine you and me,
but mainly him.
My testimony is based
on my professional--
- You are smitten
with the accused, Miss Bloom,
And it is adorable,
but not our brand of defense.
And Ms. Vega will
smell it on you
like you stepped in Young Adult and
tracked it into the courtroom.
Were you and Will Graham
involved romantically?
I have no romantic feelings
for Will Graham.
I have
a professional curiosity.
I like that.
"Professional curiosity."
It seems so...
heh, it seems so indifferent.
Unless you look like you're
lying when you say it.
But you didn't.
- (Jack): You've identified the ear?
- (Brian): We identified
- the knife that cut it off.
- It's Will Graham's.
The blade matches the cuts on Abigail
Hobbs's ear and on this one.
It was presented in court
as evidence, then it was sent
to the courthouse evidence room
where it was checked out
by the bailiff in Will's trial,
Andrew Sykes,
- and it never went back.
- Pretty good, right?
(quietly): Go.
(siren)
They wanted to give us a warm welcome
and to make sure we found something.
An arresting piece of theater.
Our bailiff was mounted
on a stag's head.
Glasgow smile. Killer lopped off
his ear and set him on fire.
Will Graham's greatest hits.
- Could we have been that wrong?
- About Will Graham? No.
We could not. He practically
takes selfies with his victims.
The evidence we found was
immediate and almost
presentational. May as well
have been gift-wrapped.
That's what Will said
about Cassie Boyle
when we found her in that field.
"Field kabuki."
There was no evidence before Will was
apprehended and there hasn't been any since.
He ate a girl's ear!
It was in his stomach. God knows
what else of her was in there.
We should've taken
a stool sample.
- Yes! We should have.
- Well, why didn't we?
- I was the one that said we should have.
- Knock it off.
What impact could
this have on Will's trial?
This murder raises
serious doubts about
- the case against Will Graham.
- Your team provided the evidence.
- The overwhelming evidence.
- So you understand the significance
- of my questioning it.
- Agent Crawford,
we all heard your testimony. Are you
sure you're not just trying to assuage
- your own guilt?
- Yes, I'm sure.
- I'm not.
- Andrew Sykes was mutilated
in the exact same manner
Will Graham allegedly
mutilated his victims -
ways that have not been
made public. - Will Graham isn't saying
he didn't kill those people.
His lawyer is running
an unconsciousness defense.
In effect, he's admitting the acts,
but just not the responsibility.
Will's maintained his innocence all
along, in spite of memory gaps.
Whatever Mr. Brauer's strategy is,
this will offer a new line of defense.
That's for Mr. Brauer to tell
me, Agent Crawford, not you.
Yes, Your Honor.
(Chilton):Will Graham
manifests publicly
as an introverted personality.
He would like us to believe he
places on the spectrum somewhere
near Asperger's and autism.
Yet he also claims
an empathy disorder.
You choose your words
very carefully, Dr. Chilton.
You chose the word "claims."
Will Graham has
never been diagnosed.
He will not allow anyone
to test him.
He has carefully constructed
a persona to hide
his real nature from the world.
He wears it so well
even Jack Crawford could
not see past it.
(Vega): But you did?
Mr. Graham and I had
no personal relationship
for him to manipulate.
I have objectively examined him
and the crimes of which he is
accused.
These murders
were measured and controlled.
The confused man Will Graham
presents to the world
could not commit those crimes,
because that man is a fiction.
So,
you discount the encephalitis
he was suffering as a cause?
He managed his illness with
the help of his neurologist,
whom he murdered
for his trouble.
Is Will Graham
an intelligent psychopath?
There is not yet a name
for whatever Will Graham is.
He kills methodically,
and I believe would kill again,
given the opportunity.
Thank you,
Dr. Chilton.
Your witness.
Dr. Chilton,
Will Graham spent his time
catching murderers for the FBI.
You don't see a contradiction
between that
and your description
of a coldblooded killer?
No, I do not.
Will Graham is driven by vanity
and his own whims.
He has a very high opinion
of his intelligence.
Ergo, he caught
the other killers
simply to prove
he was smarter
than all of them too.
Saving lives is just as arousing
as ending them.
He likes to play God.
(keypad beeping)
(door buzzer)
- My admirer?
- Yes.
The forensic report
from the crime scene.
What do you see?
(soft ambient pulse)
(steady heartbeat)
(door opening and closing)
I shoot Mr. Sykes once,
collapsing lungs,
tearing through his heart's
aorta and pulmonary arteries.
(silenced gunshot)
He will die
believing we were friends.
It is his last thought.
(panting)
His death isn't personal.
He is merely the ink
from which flows my poem.
My tribute.
This is my design.
It's not the same killer.
He murdered his victim first,
and then mutilated him.
Cassie Boyle's lungs were removed
when she was still breathing.
Georgia Madchen was burned
alive. What I...
what... what I found
of Abigail was cut off
while her heart was beating.
Then this...
is blunt reproduction?
You knew that already.
Would've liked
to have been wrong.
Occam's broom.
You intentionally ignored facts
that refute your argument
- hoping nobody'd notice.
- You noticed.
Mm-hmm.
I wanted to dispel your doubts
once and for all.
My doubts about what?
Me.
I want you to believe
in the best of me,
just as I believe
in the best of you.
This crime offered us both
reasonable doubt.
It offered us a distraction.
Maybe this acolyte is giving
you your path to freedom.
Even Jack is ready
to believe, Will.
It would be a lie.
- I don't want you to be here.
- I don't want me to be here
- either.
- Then you have a choice.
This killer wrote you a poem.
Are you going to let his love
go to waste?
I'm confused.
You're going to abandon
your defense strategy,
the entire case
you've built, mid-trial.
Exciting, isn't it?
And this seems reasonable
to you?
It's not only reasonable;
it's fashionable.
There's a killer on the loose,
demonstrating all the hallmarks
of Will Graham's
- alleged murders.
- Do you think this killer
- committed the crimes that you're accused of?
- Don't answer that,
not in front of me.
It's inconsequential.
- But is it true? - You're being awfully
high and mighty, Dr. Bloom.
Very ivory tower,
very reductive.
Very far from the point, which is
the exoneration of your friend
- Will Graham.
- And the point you're trying
- to make is reasonable doubt.
- That's a win, yes.
- The best you can hope for is mistrial.
- That's also a win.
You won't be able to plead
unconsciousness again.
Your fast, triumphant diagnosis
of unconsciousness was
the best play we had.
Now we have a better play.
Needless to say,
I won't be calling you
to the witness stand.
Who's taking the stand
in my place?
I swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth,
so help me God.
Good morning, Doctor.
Please describe your
relationship with Will Graham.
I was asked by Jack Crawford
to monitor Will's
emotional well-being
while he worked on cases.
I was never officially
his psychiatrist.
If you weren't his
psychiatrist, what were you?
I was meant
to be his stability.
- I failed him in that.
- How did you fail him?
I was unable to determine
if Will's condition was due
to mental illness or stress
from his work at the FBI.
My mistake was
never considering his innocence
until the murder of a bailiff
from this courthouse.
And how did you know
about that, Dr. Lecter?
I have been asked to consult
on the case by Jack Crawford.
He wanted a profile
of the bailiff's killer.
So, you believe
the bailiff's murder was
committed by the same person
guilty of Will Graham's
alleged crimes, yes?
Profiles aren't evidence; they're opinion.
This is hearsay.
I will allow it.
Thank you, Your Honor.
I believe there are alarming
similarities in the crimes, yes.
Will Graham accused you
of the crimes for which
he now stands trial, and yet
here you are, testifying
on his behalf for the defense.
Will rightfully couldn't
accept these actions to be his.
A mind faced with the possibility
of committing such deeds
will find an alternative reality
to believe in.
You don't blame him for that?
No.
Will Graham is
and will always be my friend.
Your witness.
Dr. Lecter,
what was the cause
of death
in the bailiff's murder?
A bullet to the heart.
Mm. And in Will Graham's
victims, or alleged victims,
what was
their cause of death?
Mutilation.
That's very different
from a bullet.
No two crimes
of any killer are going
to be exactly the same.
The similarities-- - Your Honor,
the witness's personal beliefs and biases
are driving his conclusions.
There are clearly
two different killers
and two different cases.
Your Honor, there are sufficient
similarities to consider this a defense.
I'm ruling this defense
inadmissible, Mr. Brauer.
Thank you, Your Honor.
(judge): All previous testimony on the
matter will be stricken from the record.
♪ (classical piano)
(Jack): So, it appears that the judge
was murdered in his chambers
and then he was hauled out here
to be put on display.
Not only is justice blind;
it's mindless and heartless.
How did the killer get
so close?
No sign of a struggle.
Mutilation was post-mortem.
He was shot in the chest
just like the bailiff.
Can't see the, uh, entry wound
because he removed the heart.
But there is an exit wound. No slug
- must have taken it with him.
A trophy.
Doctor.
With this judge's death,
there will be no verdict.
No ending.
It'll start again,
like the trial never happened.
But why?
Psychopathic violence is
predominantly goal-oriented,
a means to a very
particular end.
So, the killer wanted
a mistrial?
It's an elegant,
if rather unorthodox, solution.
He spares Will a guilty verdict
and his life for the moment.
- Yes.
- The question is,
is it the same killer?
Is Will still on trial,
in your mind?
The use of a gun;
death first, mutilation last.
I feel like St. Peter ready
to deny Will for the third time.
I'm not sure this is
the same killer, Jack.
Excuse me.
The killer exerted careful
control of the environment.
He left very little
evidence behind.
Jeez, Jack.
The trial was supposed
to put an end to this.
Instead, the circus has
just added another ring.
- And we're the clowns.
- Who's "we,"
Jack?
I got off track.
You have to force yourself
out of this train of thought.
The trial was going wrong
before this murder.
because you wanted
to believe Will Graham.
Who is he to you that makes you
want to risk everything for him?
A very cogent reminder of the pitfalls of
having faith in one's fellow man, thank you.
Everyone at one point or another
has to leave somebody behind.
You've got to cut him loose.
Otherwise, the someone
being left behind,
today or tomorrow...
is gonna be you.
(door buzzer)
(door opening)
(footsteps)
(Hannibal): Will.
I was hoping the verdict would have
helped focus your mind to get better;
make what happened to you
less terrifying and confusing.
I can't exactly blame
your lawyer.
Faith in any sort
of legal justice has never been
any more comforting
than a nightlight.
There are so many
miscarriages of justice
when it comes to
identifying a psychopath.
You could easily have been
misdiagnosed.
I've already been misdiagnosed.
Not by the court.
No. Not yet.
I walked out of that courtroom,
and I could hear my blood,
like, uh...
...a hollow drumming
of wings.
And I had the...
absurd feeling
that whoever this killer is...
...he walked out
of that courtroom with me.
He's gonna reach out to me.
What does he want?
He wants to know me.
What do you want?
I want to save you.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player