Previously onHannibal...
Do not discuss me
with Hannibal Lecter.
I brought gideon back
because I thought he may be
useful in Will Graham's therapy.
I'm going to give you a chance
to save Will from himself.
Who does he want
to kill, doctor?
I want you to kill
Hannibal Lecter.
Will Graham is not a murderer.
He asked you to do this.
Get an ambulance!
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
You're moving smoothly
and slowly, Jack.
Carrying your concentration
like a brimming cup.
Hannibal Lecter was
almost murdered...
By an employee
of this hospital.
An attendant
who we believe is
the person that...
Killed the bailiff and the judge
at your murder trial.
He killed the bailiff;
He didn't kill the judge.
That was the chesapeake ripper.
You know this?
He told me.
Then you told him
to kill Hannibal.
Nothing I said
made that happen, Jack.
It just happened.
You don't seem to be
too broken up about it.
There's a common emotion
we all recognize
and have not yet named.
The happy anticipation of being
able to feel contempt.
You feel contempt
for Hannibal?
Well, I have contempt for
the ripper. I have contempt
for what he does.
- And what does he do?
- What does he do?
What is the first and principal
thing he does?
What need does he serve
by killing?
- He harvests organs.
- No, that's only
the action of what he does.
Why does he need to do it?
The ripper kills in sounders
of three or four in quick order.
Do you know why?
I know why.
Then tell me.
Because if he waits too long,
then the meat spoils.
He's eating them?
Hannibal is like Garrett
Jacob hobbs? A cannibal?
No, not like
Garrett Jacob hobbs.
Hobbs ate his victims
to honor them;
the ripper eats his victims
because they're no better
to him than pigs.
With the exception
of Beverly katz, there is no
connection between Hannibal
and any ripper victims.
No immediate connection.
Hannibal Lecter is not
the chesapeake ripper.
If the ripper's killing,
you can bet Hannibal Lecter's
planning a dinner party.
You and I probably sipped wine
while swallowing the people
to whom we were trying
to give justice, Jack.
Who does he have to kill
before you open your eyes?
A remarkably lean organ,
the heart, yet such a potent
symbol of life...
And the things
that make us human -
good and bad, love and ache.
All of them skewered.
It's a thematic dish.
My heart certainly
feels skewered.
You have the scars
to prove it.
It feels as if that noose is
still around my neck.
Strange having nightmares;
I never used to.
Don't make the same
mistake I've made -
being your own psychiatrist.
I'm always assessing my feelings
instead of acting on them.
It's the safest course.
You have to find a way to deal
with what happened to you.
I'm metabolizing
the experience
by composing
a new piece of music.
Harpsichord or theremin?
Harpsichord.
Stravinsky said a true composer
thinks about his unfinished work
the whole time.
He's not always conscious
of this, but he's aware of it
when he suddenly knows
what to do.
And do you know what to do?
I need to get
my appetite back.
What do we got?
He's literally grafted
in place. These are
living roots.
He's got varicose vines.
Threaded through, uh,
from his heels,
under his legs, his back,
through his torso, out
his fingertips.
Followed some pretty tricky
endoscopic surgical paths.
Chesapeake ripper usually
cherry-picks his organs.
He took almost all of them;
Everything but the lungs.
The time that he devotes
to his work...
He really takes pride.
Belladonna for the heart.
Chain of white oleander
for the intestines.
Ragwort for the liver.
These flowers are
all poisonous.
Yes. This is a judgment.
The ripper believes
that his victim was...
Toxic somehow, a poisonous man.
He's so damn certain
he makes me sick.
There is a pattern taking shape.
I just have to convince my eyes
to see it.
I've convinced myself
of something I had refused
to see for a long time.
And it only took Will Graham
trying to kill you to see it?
Yes.
I can't help Will.
I can't trust him.
He's in a dark place
where the shadows move
and it's not safe
to stand with him anymore.
I feel the same way.
We, um... Found another
ripper victim...
I'm sorry, Jack. I can't.
Not only do I have to
let Will go;
I have to let this all go.
I nearly died.
I would have,
if it weren't for you.
I'm sorry,
but I can't dwell
on death anymore.
I don't blame you.
We both have to transform
our misfortunes
into life-enhancing events.
Well, when you figure out
how to do that, do let me know.
I'm going to start
by hosting a dinner party.
And please tell me you'll come.
I wouldn't miss it.
You should've let him die.
Shoulda, coulda, woulda.
He's gonna kill you,
you know.
Can't get me in here.
No, here is exactly
where he'll get you, Abel.
The moment I convinced
the chief of staff to put you
in a cell next to me, you were
stamped with an expiration date.
Anyone who gets too close
gets got.
He's the devil,
remember? Smoke.
I'd be very nervous
if I was Dr. chilton.
He's getting close too.
The only way
you and Frederick are gonna
get out of this alive
is if the chesapeake
ripper is stopped.
Hannibal Lecter deserves
to die.
You didn't bring me here to
help you kill Hannibal Lecter.
No, I didn't; I brought you
here to bear witness.
To tell Jack Crawford
that I sat
in Hannibal Lecter's
cobalt-blue dining room,
an ostentatious herb garden
with leda and the swan
over the fireplace and you
having a fit in the corner.
That's where I asked him
if he was the chesapeake ripper,
and he avoided the question and
suggested I kill alana bloom.
Yes.
Tell Jack that.
I'll tell Jack Crawford
everything
if you tell me
why Hannibal did it.
Because he wanted to see
what would happen.
That's where I asked him
if he was the chesapeake ripper
and he avoided the question and
suggested I kill alana bloom.
Abel gideon is a lunatic.
He is psychotic, not psychic.
We know that gideon has
a history of being
susceptible to suggestion.
The simplest explanation
as to why he can describe
Hannibal Lecter's home
is that he was
in Hannibal Lecter's home.
Will Graham could've
given him the details.
No such details were given.
There has not been a word
exchanged between those two men
in my hospital
that I have not heard.
Then you're aware what Will is
accusing Hannibal Lecter of.
Oh, yes.
I am aware.
And I am grateful
that I have trouble digesting
animal proteins,
as the last meals I have shared
with Hannibal Lecter
have all been salads.
Do you believe him?
Hannibal once served me tongue
and then made a joke
about eating mine.
It would be narrow
to not at least consider it.
Will is delusional.
He would like
to reinforce his delusion
with you, with me,
with Abel gideon.
That doesn't mean
he is not right.
No, it doesn't.
The chesapeake ripper is
killing again...
And Hannibal Lecter is
throwing a dinner party.
Jack, he fits the profile.
He is attracted to medical
and psychological fields because
they offer power over man.
Cannibalism...
Cannibalism is
an act of dominance.
His name's Sheldon isley!
A Baltimore city councilman!
Ripper's a politician now!
At least a conservationist.
Five, six years ago, isley
brokered a woodlands
development deal despite
the disapproval of the epa.
So the councilman paved
paradise and put up
a parking lot.
Well, what he paved was
an important nesting habitat
for endangered songbirds.
The son of a bitch.
He was wearing this
as a crown.
Autopsy report
gave us what you'd expect
from the chesapeake ripper -
pre-mortem surgical dissection,
latex glove impressions,
body was posed
before rigor set in.
- What did the lungs cough up?
- Water.
The councilman was drowned,
lungs filled with aspirated
water. He was standing in water
up to his thighs for
48 to 72 hours before he died.
- To feed the tree.
- Possibly.
Now, here's
the exciting part.
Tree man actually bears fruit.
Diatoms. Unicellular colonies.
Good as fingerprints -
no two water sources have
the same diatom population.
Water in the lungs gives us
location of death. Show me.
Here, in a 50-mile radius.
My head is filled
with conspiracies.
Too many versions of events
he said she said.
He said she said he said.
It's just maddening.
In my experience, that means
a lot of people are lying
about a lot of different things.
Well, the one thing I have
clarity on is Will Graham
tried to kill Hannibal.
And thinks
it was a righteous act.
Well, that says more about
Will than it does
about Hannibal.
Hannibal's been a teacher,
a mentor, and a friend.
I've known him before
you or Will or any of this.
I don't claim to know anyone.
I look at these dogs,
I see the best part of Will.
But he's lying.
He's manipulating.
He's playing a game and
he's not scared, not anymore.
That's what's
making him dangerous.
Hello, Dr. Lecter.
I feel like I've been
watching our friendship
on a split-screen.
The friendship
I perceived on one side
and the truth on the other.
It's a terrible
feeling, isn't it?
You've been lying
to me, Will.
Well, I-I don't have
a gauge for reality
that works well enough
to know if I've been lying.
But you understand the reality
of Beverly katz's death.
You understand
your role in that.
What was my role?
Beverly died at your behest.
You are as angry with yourself
as you are
with whoever murdered her.
Actually...
I am singularly angry
with whoever murdered her.
You tried to kill me, Will.
It's hard
not to take that personally.
However, if I were
Beverly's murderer...
I'd applaud your effort.
Oh, I'm no more guilty
of what you've accused me of
than you are
of what I've accused you of.
I don't expect you
to feel self-loathing
or regret, or shame.
You knew what you were doing,
and you made
your own decisions,
decisions that were
under your control.
Oh, you think I'm in control?
I think you are
more in control now
than you have ever been.
You found a way to hurt me.
I wonder how many more people
are going to get hurt
by what you do.
I'll give alana bloom
your best.
Goodbye, Will.
So, it seems all the king's
horses and all the king's men
could indeed put humpty
together again.
Is everything back
where I found it?
With one or two exceptions.
I know people
who consider me autocratic.
I'm not the most loved
of administrators,
but that nurse you murdered,
she was well-liked.
And so were the attendants
you killed.
There is nothing
like grief and trauma
to pull people together.
Jack Crawford would like
to have a word with you.
I trust you Will
behave yourself, Abel.
I'm sure you and Frederick
have had many a conversation
about my bad behavior, Jack.
How does he describe me?
A pure sociopath,
by the book.
- Is that by your book,
Frederick?
- Yes.
I'd just like to point out
that the word "sociopath" has
not been used by any respected
psychiatrist since 1968.
Dr. gideon, do you have
any information about the
chesapeake ripper, or not?
- Down to brass tacks.
- You told Will Graham that
you were in Dr. Lecter's home.
Why were you there?
I have never set foot
in Dr. Lecter's home.
I only met the man a week ago.
However, Dr. chilton was kind
enough to share the details
of his dining room.
Why would he do that?
Yes, why would he do that?
Will Graham is
very keen to believe
that Hannibal Lecter is
the chesapeake ripper.
Dr. chilton did very little
to disavow him
of that notion, and encouraged
me to do the same.
I apologize, agent Crawford,
for wasting your time.
It's not your actions
and betrayal that I resent,
Dr. chilton;
It's just the lies.
Mmhmm.
I'll walk you out.
Thank you.
Dr. chilton hired a nurse
who's had experience
in mental hospitals,
but not as an employee.
That nurse attempted to murder
Hannibal Lecter, and you blame
Will Graham.
You got the right box
there, Jack,
but you're looking
in the wrong corner.
All the coiled resentment
in this place,
it's gotta be bad
for the digestion.
You know that poor nurse shell
that I murdered?
I know she's seen
as some kind of beloved sister,
but wasn't she also
kind of a good-time girl
with a beer or two inside her?
I asked her if she had eyes
for me, and she said no.
So I had to take 'em.
Prosciutto roses.
Heart tartare.
Beef roulade.
Whatever this is.
Needless to say,
I will not be eating the food.
Nice to see you again,
Dr. chilton.
Hm. Hannibal
the cannibal.
That is what they'll call him,
you know.
Not according to Abel gideon.
Gideon has given me enough
trouble for one day. The fact
that he lied to you makes
me even more certain he was
telling Will Graham the truth.
Why did you come here tonight
if you're so convinced?
Darwinism.
I do not want him to think
I suspect anything.
I really shouldn't be
seen speaking to you.
I don't want to be perceived
as a threat.
Jack.
I'm so happy you're here.
After all, you are the guest
of honor. You saved my life.
Unfortunately, my friend,
I can't stay.
Um... ooh.
I would love to take some food
to go, if that's all right.
Of course. I'll get
one of the staff to get you
something from the kitchen.
No, no. That's all right.
Just, uh, bring me a container
and I'll serve myself
from here. Um,
with your permission,
of course, Dr. Lecter.
- Hello, Jack.
- Hello, alana.
I do have your permission,
Dr. Lecter?
- Help yourself.
- Thank you.
Eat it soon or it'll spoil.
Thank you. Good evening.
Good evening.
Z.
Test this.
Well, the ending
to my composition has been
eluding me, but you may just
have solved that problem
with "chopsticks."
If only every problem could be
solved with a simple waltz.
Jack's treating you
like a suspect.
Pointing fingers in the dark.
I've walked away from Will,
but I'm still trailing
his accusations.
I've walked away too.
I can't forgive Will
for what he did to you.
I just want to walk away
from all of it.
What does walking away
leave us?
Each other.
Hello, Dr. gideon.
Put the heart monitor on
the guard so no one knew gideon
was missing, at least as long as
it took for the guard to die,
which wasn't long.
- It was long enough.
- He was strung up with
fish hooks.
Hand-tied flies,
just like Will Graham
used to make.
This one has
a human hair in it,
and a tooth.
Jack,
there is no way gideon could've
done any of this
with the injuries he had,
much less get out of bed.
Well, the last time
gideon escaped custody,
he went looking
for the chesapeake ripper.
He found him, all right.
Last night... The
ripper found gideon.
You're awake.
So are you.
I was thinking
about funerals,
and how often
they make us want sex.
It's one in the eye
for death.
Not that...
This wasn't...
Funeral sex or...
- Of course it was.
We both just buried a friend.
We buried Will.
There's something liberating
about finally letting him go.
Yes. There is.
We have a lot of reasons
to do this;
not just funeral reasons.
Last time someone rang
my doorbell this early,
it was a census taker.
I'll see who it is.
Jack.
Hannibal.
What can I do for you?
We need to talk.
Abel gideon fell
down a stairwell last night.
He was hospitalized.
The security guard
standing watch has been killed
in what appears to be another
chesapeake ripper murder.
Gideon is nowhere to be found.
He escaped?
We know he didn't leave
the hospital on his own.
His back was broken.
He was taken by someone -
someone who knew him.
Where were you last night?
I was here.
All night?
Yes.
Anyone other than yourself
that can verify that?
I can.
I was with Hannibal
all night, Jack.
What are you accusing him of?
I'm not accusing him
of anything;
Only asking his whereabouts.
That's not all you're asking.
Rôti de cuisse.
Clay-roasted thigh.
And canoe-cut marrow bone.
I love cooking with Clay.
It creates
a more succulent dish
and adds a little
theatricality to dinner.
We come from Clay,
return to Clay.
Shall I carve?
I think you already have.
Your legs are
no good to you anymore.
You've got a t-4 fracture
of the vertebra.
This is a far more
practical use
for those limbs.
Hard to have anything,
isn't it, Dr. Lecter?
Rare to get it,
hard to keep it.
A damn slippery life.
You were determined to know
the chesapeake ripper,
Dr. gideon.
Now is your opportunity.
You intend me to be
my own last supper?
Yes.
How does one
politely refuse a dish
in circumstances such as these?
One doesn't.
The tragedy is not
to die, Abel,
but to be wasted.
My compliments to the chef.
- Goose, pig, cow.
- Not just cow; Wagyu beef.
There's about $100 worth
right there.
How do you know it's not kobe?
Well, all kobe is wagyu;
Not all wagyu is kobe.
- Ok.
- Well, at least we know
Dr. Lecter wasn't serving up
people.
You want people?
The chesapeake ripper has been
tying flies with them,
just like Will Graham
allegedly did.
Hair woven into the
monofilaments is Beverly's;
bone fragments of Miriam lass;
veining from Sheldon isley, uh,
optical nerve and arteries
from judge Davies,
and a toenail from James gray,
our muralist -
all victims
of the chesapeake ripper.
These four lures are almost
identical to what we found
in Will's house,
made with material from
the exact same human remains:
Abigail hobbs,
Donald Sutcliffe,
Marissa schuur,
Georgia madchen.
Will didn't kill
any of these people.
There was no copycat;
Never was.
It was always the ripper.
Finally taking credit
for all of his murders.
Maybe too much credit.
Found something else
in the lures.
Madrona bark
a tree almost non-existent
on the east coast,
but this bark was
peeled recently.
There's a small stand
of madrona bark in Virginia.
Inside your diatom
search area?
Yep.
Here.
Miriam.
Closed captioning by sette inc.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player