- I thought it might be
the chesapeake ripper, but there
Were no surgical trophies taken.
I'm gonna need you to prepare
Yourself on this one.
- I'm prepared.
- Yeah, prepare yourself some
more. It's soup in there.
- Jack gave you his word
He would protect your headspace,
yet he leaves you to your
mental devices.
- Are you trying to alienate me
from jack crawford?
- It's difficult to lie still
and fear going to sleep when
it's there to think about.
(siren)
- do you have a history
of sleepwalking, mr. Graham?
- My wife and I need to talk.
May we use your waiting room?
- Lung cancer.
- When were you gonna tell me?
- Do I seem different?
- But you've always been
a little different.
- It's getting harder and harder
to make myself look.
- I'm not gonna tell you
what you ought to do.
- I don't know how much longer
I can be all that useful
to you, jack.
- Really? The last three we had,
you caught.
- You can't arrest me
for writing an article.
- You don't write another word
about will graham and
I won't have to.
- This is your final opportunity
to comply.
On your feet, dr. Gideon,
or we will restrain you.
(door buzzer)
Alright, lace your fingers
behind your head!
Get a gurney!
(monitor beeping)
(flatline tone)
- Well, thanks
to freddie lounds,
There's an unconfirmed story
floating out there
That the chesapeake ripper's
already in custody.
- Unconfirmed.
Am I confirming?
Fact-checking
for freddie lounds...
- You're fact-checking
for me.
- I always feel a little nervous
going into these places.
- Why's that?
- Afraid they won't let me out.
- Don't worry.
I won't leave you here.
- Yeah, not today.
- Dr. Bloom just called me
about you,
Mr. Graham--or should I call you
dr. Graham?
- I'm not a doctor.
- You're not fbi either.
That's a temporary
identification.
- Mr. Graham teaches
at the academy.
- Ah, a teacher. Please,
gentlemen, take a seat.
- Thank you.
Dr. Chilton, we're going
to need to see
The crime scene while it's
still relatively undisturbed.
- I assure you, for something
so disturbing, it is quite
undisturbed.
- Why was a nurse left alone
with a prisoner
In a high-security
psychiatric hospital?
- For the two years
since he was brought here,
Gideon behaved perfectly
And gave every appearance
Of cooperating with attempts
at therapy. As dictated
By our present administrator,
security around him was
slightly... Relaxed.
I cannot help
feeling responsible
Myself for what happened.
He sat directly across from me
And I had no idea
what he was hiding.
And now one
of our staff is dead.
- I understand, doctor.
Mr. Graham's going to need
to see the crime scene
With as much privacy
as you can provide.
- Oh, yes, that thing you do.
You're quite the topic
of conversation in, uh,
psychiatric circles, mr. Graham.
- Am I?
- Uh, yes.
A unique cocktail
Of personality disorders
and neuroses that make you
a highly skilled profiler.
- He's not here to be analyzed.
- Perhaps he should be.
We are woefully short
of material
On your sort of thing,
mr. Graham.
Would you mind speaking
to some of the staff?
- Doctor.
- No, no, no. Not this trip.
Maybe a special visit.
- Thank you, dr. Chilton.
I'd like to see
the crime scene now.
- So, gideon was restrained?
- Handcuffed.
- Hm.
- He concealed a fork tine
in the palm of his hand
And used it to pick the lock.
- Where is he now?
- In his cell.
You'll note
The removal of organs
and the abdominal mutilations
Are all consistent
with the chesapeake ripper.
- So is the brutalization
of the corpses, but that doesn't
Change the fact that
the ripper is still out there.
- Jack, what I'm about
to show you
Suggests otherwise.
(door buzzer)
- Dr. Chilton consulted
on the case when we failed
To catch the ripper after
his last series of murders.
- The reason you failed
And kept failing to capture
the chesapeake ripper...
Was I already had him.
(monitor beeping)
(flatline tone)
(nurse crying out)
- Um...
It's been over two years since
the chesapeake ripper killed?
- That's correct.
- When was gideon admitted?
- Almost two years ago.
Lass, miriam regina.
Come in.
- Morning, agent crawford.
- Sorry to pull you out
of class. There's nothing wrong.
Uh, no reason
to be nervous.
- I'm not nervous.
Curious.
- Your instructors tell me
That you are in the top 10%?
- Top five, sir.
- You're gonna have
to stop correcting me
if we're gonna get along, lass.
Take a seat.
You wrote me
A letter when you qualified
for the academy.
- I wasn't sure you got it.
You never replied.
- Never do. Odds are against any
trainee completing the program.
But I'm glad to see
you're still here.
In your letter, you said
you wanted to work for me
In the violent criminal
apprehension program.
- Yes, sir.
- There might be an opportunity.
I'm assuming
that you're familiar
With the chesapeake ripper.
- Yes.
- The ripper's very hot
right now. Killed his last two
victims in six days. There'll be
At least one more body
and then nothing for months.
- They say
he's a true sociopath.
- What do you say?
- I say they don't know
what else to label him.
He has some
of the characteristics
Of what they call a sociopath--
no remorse or guilt at all.
He won't have any
of the other marks.
He won't be a drifter.
He'll have no history
of trouble with the law.
He'll be hard to catch.
- I'm assigning you to the
chesapeake ripper task force.
You're gonna work
directly under me.
- I'm grateful for
the opportunity, agent crawford.
But I can't help
wondering... Why me?
- You have
a forensics fellowship,
Six years of law enforcement,
A degree in psychology,
doctorate in criminology.
And what I don't have are
enough warm bodies.
So, I'm gonna need
your full attention on this.
- (miriam): Yes, sir.
- The volume of abel gideon's
mail is becoming a nuisance.
Sometimes I feel
like his secretary
rather than his keeper.
- Any specific correspondences
that stood out from the others?
- Mostly researchers
or phd candidates
Requesting interviews.
A scattered dozen lonely hearts
Seeking his hand in marriage.
- He butchered
His last wife and her family
on thanksgiving.
- There's no accounting
for taste--or intelligence.
- Murdering his wife was
impulsive. The chesapeake ripper
Is methodical, meticulous.
That's why he's so hard
to catch.
- Was so hard to catch.
Will you be conducting
a joint interview?
- Separate.
Compare and contrast.
- I know you're anxious
to get on with it.
You have talked to gideon
before, for some length of time.
- Well, I saw him mainly
in court. I wrote an article
About him in the journal
of criminal psychology.
- He is very familiar
with you.
He has given you
a lot of thought.
- You had some sessions
with him?
- Yes, two, a couple years
ago when he was first
institutionalized.
- I've read your notes,
of course. They were
more or less helpful
As I conducted my own interviews
with dr. Gideon over the years.
- Well, I'm glad I was helpful.
- (will): More or less.
- I'll go first.
(door buzzer)
- Why, dr. Bloom.
How wonderful to see you again.
- You remembered.
- I've met a lot
Of psychiatrists in the last
two years. It's hard to forget
One so sublime.
- Thank you for your time,
dr. Gideon. I won't waste it.
Shall we begin?
- Dr. Bloom,
what is this to be?
I was caught red-handed.
I mean, literally.
There's no mystery
as to whodunit. I did it.
- The mystery is whether you are
who you say you are.
Or not.
- Never liked being called
The chesapeake ripper.
Maybe something
with a little more wit.
- Is that why you didn't take
credit for the ripper murders
before now?
- Just watching the goose chase
from the box seats.
- Two years of goose chasing.
You must be a very patient man.
- Are you just gonna run
The psychopathic checklist here?
I have had my personality
Inventoried by the minnesota
multiphasic.
- Would you prefer
a rorschach test?
- Well, if you're gonna
show me those pictures,
Maybe you should put a blood
pressure cuff to my genitals.
I find it gives
a much truer gauge of reaction.
- What effect were you hoping
to have by killing
The night nurse?
- The effect I was hoping
to have was her death.
Mission accomplished.
- Brutalization of the body was
done posthumously.
- Chesapeake ripper usually
Does that sort of thing during,
Not after.
- I do not have to convince you
that I am the chesapeake ripper.
- Seems that's what you need
to do.
- Certainly what somebody needs.
- Jack.
Come in.
- I'm sorry. Um...
I was just, uh...
- In the neighborhood.
- Yeah, something
like that.
- How's mrs. Crawford?
- Yeah, that's why I was
in the neighborhood.
She's fine.
Well, she tells me
that she's fine
And she tells me
when she's not.
- You expect me
to tell you more?
- Look, bella's
at a nato conference.
I can't talk to her.
She's working.
I doubt I could talk
to her if she was here.
- About her condition?
- Yeah. About her cancer,
about her dying.
She doesn't want to talk
to me about it.
- I am prohibited from talking
about it--doctor-patient
confidentiality.
- You talk to me
about will graham.
- Will graham is not
officially my patient.
We have conversations.
- What do you
consider this?
- Desperate coping.
- You don't think I have a right
to know what's happening
with my wife?
- You have every right to know
what's happening,
but not from me.
- Well, I'm not just gonna
stand outside my marriage
and watch this happen.
If that's what she wants,
too bad.
She married the wrong guy
for that.
- I'll offer one insight.
She doesn't think
she married the wrong guy.
- I can't stop thinking about
when my wife is gonna die.
I look at her side of the bed
and I think,
"is she gonna die there?"
I can't stop thinking about it,
you understand? I can't stop.
- You're dreading the loss
of your wife.
- Yes.
And I'm thinking
about other losses too.
- What other losses are
you dreading?
Jack, you can't save her.
She won't let you.
The cancer won't let you.
Who else couldn't
you save?
- (miriam): Where is everyone?
- It's just you and me
for the time being.
Take a look around here.
Tell me what you see.
- He did it all here.
Did it while he was alive.
He struck the throat
So he couldn't call for help.
- Do you think
He was unconscious
when the ripper did the ripping?
- No, he'd want him awake.
Organs were removed.
Not all of them. He was choosy.
He took the liver, thymus,
But left the heart.
- What's he doing
with the organs?
- Surgical trophies.
He's a medical doctor, isn't he?
Is that why you call him
the ripper?
- Why do you say that?
- Psychopaths are attracted
to surgical fields.
They offer power.
They require the ability
To make objective clinical
decisions without feeling.
- White male?
Forties? Fifties?
- I don't know
that he's white.
He's exotic somehow,
Which is why
you're gonna catch him.
- I'm gonna catch him?
- We call you the guru.
You have a peculiar
cleverness.
- I'll take that
as a compliment.
- You should.
You'll probably spot him
before anybody else.
- Or you will.
Now I want you
to take a look at this.
- There's no
detectable consistency
with the ripper victims.
He doesn't hunt exclusively
within his own ethnic group.
He's killed all creeds,
colors, men and women.
- She has the exact same
wound pattern as the last-known
victim of the chesapeake ripper.
I mean exact.
- We never found a body
for his last-known victim.
- Then the victim before that.
- I see the ripper,
but I don't...
Feel the ripper.
This is plagiarism.
- We never made
The wound patterns for any
of the ripper's victims public.
- Well, maybe he is the ripper.
I don't know.
But if he's a plagiarist,
the real chesapeake ripper is
Gonna make sure
everybody knows it.
(jack sighs.)
(phone ringing)
- Hello.
- [jack. Jack.]
- Who is this?
- [jack, it's miriam.]
[I don't know where I am.
I can't see anything.]
- miriam?
- [I was so wrong.
I was so wrong.]
- Miriam?
- [please... Jack. Please.]
(signal cuts out.)
- I'm hooked in
to every carrier database
And telephone provider
in the United States.
Nothing.
- Look again.
- I did my agains.
And my again and again
And agains. I can't find
any electronic trace
Of any call made to your home
at 2:46am.
- I am telling you
that the phone rang.
- Wake your wife up?
- I was alone.
- Whoever made that call could
have made it from that little
box outside your house
Or a junction
in your neighborhood.
Either way, there would be
no trace signal
To track.
- You're sure
it was miriam lass?
- It was miriam.
- You haven't heard
her voice in two years, jack.
- You gonna continue
to question me on this, z?
If so, maybe I should ask you
to leave the room while it's
still safe for you to be here.
The chesapeake ripper recorded
miriam lass two years ago
as he was killing her.
Last night, he called my house
at 2:46am. He played
that recording for me.
- Well, then we know
the chesapeake ripper is
not dr. Gideon, because
We know the call wasn't made
from the baltimore
State hospital
for the criminally insane.
- That we would've been able
To trace.
- Are you certain
it was a recording?
Jack, you said
yourself there's no body.
- Miriam lass is dead!
The chesapeake ripper is making
it very clear that someone is
plagiarizing his work!
- It was 2:46 in the morning,
jack. You're in a deep sleep,
you're roused, you're
Disoriented. You might not even
know you're still asleep.
- I know when I'm awake.
(sigh)
(stag bellowing)
- Will? You look
like you were dreaming.
- I was, uh, thinking
about something else.
- Well, here's something
for you to think about.
We have a direct way
of communicating
With the chesapeake ripper,
and we'd like to see
if we can push him.
- Push him toward what?
- We might be able
to influence him
To become visible.
- If we can enrage him.
- To what purpose, jack?
I-I don't see what
you're asking.
- Do you think there's a way
to push the chesapeake ripper
and focus his attention?
- Well, he's already focused
on gideon as his adversary.
Don't fool around.
- Gideon is just a tabloid rumor
right now. We think we need
to make him the truth.
- You might push the ripper
to kill again just to prove
He isn't in a hospital
for the criminally insane.
- I have to push, will.
- Are you thinking about getting
into bed with freddie lounds?
- You yourself know
it's the best way to bait
the real chesapeake ripper.
- Morning, agent crawford.
Thank you for inviting me.
- Miss lounds.
This is dr. Alana bloom.
She's one of our psychiatric
consultants.
I believe you know will graham.
- Mr. Graham.
So good to see you.
- Miss lounds.
You have all the qualities
of a good reporter. You have
Intelligence, guts,
a good eye.
So how is it that you wind up
where you've ended up?
- Where I wound up being
criminal justice journalism?
- "criminal justice journalism"
being a euphemism for
tabloid reporting.
- You ran an unconfirmed story
about the chesapeake ripper.
What I want is
for you to confirm it.
- An exclusive story would be
a coup.
- Mm, yes, it would.
And you would get
The satisfaction of seeing
the    los angeles times,
The sanctified
washington post,
Nd even the holy new york times
un copyrighted material
Under your byline,
With a picture credit.
- What's against you,
And by association us,
Is that your brand
of journalism is obnoxious
And therefore disliked.
- Yes. That is an obstacle.
Tried to get an interview
with dr. Gideon.
I was denied. Evidently some
trouble with my euphemism.
- I'm friendly
with the new chief of staff.
I can get you an interview.
- Not to snap bubble gum and
crack wise, but what's my angle?
Is he the chesapeake ripper,
Or do you just want me
to tell everybody that he is?
- He could be, and certain
personalities are attracted
to certain professions.
- Do you know what profession
Psychopaths disproportionately
gravitate to?
- Ceos, lawyers, the clergy.
- Number five on the list is
surgeons.
- I know the list.
- Well, then you know
what number six is.
- Journalists.
Know what number seven is,
mr. Graham?
- Law enforcement.
- Here we are,
A bunch of psychopaths
helping each other out.
(door buzzer)
(beeping)
Dr. Gideon.
I'm freddie lounds.
May I call you dr. Gideon?
Or do you prefer
the chesapeake ripper?
His name is dr. Abel gideon,
And strong evidence has surfaced
that he's far more
Than a mild-mannered surgeon
who cruelly murdered his wife.
Maybe, just maybe,
Gideon is the most sought-after
serial killer at large,
A killer who's eluded the fbi
for years
And has baffled
their most gifted profilers.
That serial killer? None other
than the chesapeake ripper.
This would explain why
the ripper has been silent
For more than two years.
- (gideon): So, are you enjoying
reading my mail?
- No, not particularly.
- Looking for something
instructional?
Diagrams? Don't believe
I can recreate
One of my own murders
from memory?
- You wouldn't be recreating
them from your memory, doctor.
You're not
the chesapeake ripper.
- Ooh, have to agree
to disagree.
- Then why
the surgical trophies?
- Agent crawford, there are just
some things you're not allowed
To do in a state-certified
operating room.
- You didn't take any trophies
when you murdered your wife
And her family on thanksgiving.
You didn't put any of them
on display. Why not?
- Crime of passion.
You know how stressful
the holidays can get.
Anyway, you didn't come here
to talk about my wife--
Or the little nursey.
- Oh. What am I here
to talk about?
- Your trainee.
Miriam... Somebody.
- You're telling me
you killed miriam lass.
- Yes. Didn't mean
to kill her.
Don't get mad at me.
- I'm not mad at you.
I know where you are.
I know how you got here.
I read your file.
I'm curious, why are you being
so forthcoming all of a sudden?
- Well, what have I got
to lose?
You know where I am
and you know how I got here.
- Why didn't you put her
on display?
- What makes you think
I didn't?
(cell phone ringing)
- Excuse me.
- The polite thing to do is
to ask them to call back.
(door buzzer)
Unless it's not an option.
- You're home early.
Bella? Something wrong?
- [jack, it's miriam.
I don't know where I am.]
[I can't see anything.]
[I was so wrong.
I was so wrong.]
[please... Jack. Please.]
(signal cuts out.)
- In my house.
In my bedroom.
Where my wife sleeps.
- I've dusted the phone.
Got a lot of usable prints.
Nice detail too. I got
three distinct beauties here.
Yours, your wife's,
And presumably
the chesapeake ripper.
- I can't imagine the chesapeake
ripper would start
leaving prints
At his crime scenes now.
- The ripper put his head
on your wife's pillow.
- Now somebody's sleeping
in my bed.
- There he is.
Or there she is.
Was miriam lass a blonde?
- Yes.
- I pulled her fingerprints
from the vicap database, jack,
And I got a match.
- She's dead.
She wasn't here.
- Jack. Did miriam lass know
where you live?
- If she wanted to know, she was
smart enough to find out.
- She could've told
The chesapeake ripper
before he killed her.
Did you know you were
sending her after him?
- I sent her
after information.
- Whoever made that call thinks
you were close to miriam lass
And feel responsible
for her death.
- Don't you have classes today?
Aren't you still in school?
- Yes, sir. I thought this might
be more important
Than "exclusionary rules
of search and seizure".
- Is that
what you thought?
- I left a report here for you
last night.
I don't know if you got it.
- I got it.
- Did you read it?
- Go back to class.
You feeling
frustrated, lass?
If so, you should start
forming calluses,
Some thick ones,
'cause frustration's
gonna wear you thin.
- You could have
at least read the report.
- I read it.
- Your assessment? Sir.
- My assessment is that
instead of being here
You should be in a lecture hall
boning up on "good faith
warrant exceptions".
What you're proposing
in your report breaks
Confidentiality laws.
You know that.
You shouldn't be so dismissive
Of what you're learning here.
- If the chesapeake ripper is
a surgeon,
We should check medical records
for all of the known victims.
I knew we couldn't get a warrant
if we didn't have something
substantial.
- It's one thing for a trainee
to go poking around
In private medical records
without a warrant;
Very different
if the guru did it.
- Better for a trainee to ask
for forgiveness than an fbi
agent to ask for permission?
- In my experience.
- Then I hope you forgive me
For skipping class today.
- If someone were using
manipulative methods
To subvert your sense
of control, you may
not realize it
Until those methods are
pointed out to you.
- Which may be
a manipulative method in itself.
- You were
a model patient.
You behaved yourself
for two years.
- Well, no opportunity
to be naughty.
- You could have
been pushed.
- Well, that would be unethical.
- We can help you find out.
But I need your trust
to do that.
- Oh, I trust you, dr. Bloom.
- To the chesapeake ripper.
Dr. Gideon is going
To provide us with a singular
opportunity to analyze
A pure sociopath.
It is so rare
to find one in captivity.
(classical music playing)
Ah. Dinner is served.
- Inspired by auguste escoffier,
we are having long tangyuan
En papillotte,
Served with a sauce of duxelles
and oyster mushrooms.
Picked myself.
- I don't think
I've ever had tongue before.
- It was a particularly
chatty lamb.
(dr. Chilton laughs.)
- (alana): It smells delicious.
- The romans used to kill
flamingos just to eat
their tongues.
- Don't give me ideas.
Your tongue is very feisty.
And as this evening has already
proven, it's nice to have
an old friend for dinner.
- Mm.
- I see three possibilities.
- Mm-hmm.
- Gideon is
the chesapeake ripper,
Or he just thinks he is,
or he knows he isn't.
- He is, he knows he is,
so do I.
- Did you discuss the chesapeake
ripper's crimes with dr. Gideon
Before he murdered
the night nurse?
- Mm-hmm. When I began
To suspect what he was.
Fearing he might be exposed
may have, uh...
Spurred him into action.
- Is it possible
you inadvertently planted
The suggestion in gideon's mind
that he was the ripper?
- You're not suggesting
coercive persuasion.
- No, I said
inadvertently.
- Psychic driving is
unethical.
- But reasonable
in certain circumstances.
- What circumstances?
- It may have been useful trying
to remind gideon he's the
chesapeake ripper.
- Mm-hmm.
- If he repressed
those memories.
But he seems to have come
to that awareness
all by himself.
- Dr. Bloom,
If he has been
Unethically manipulated
somehow,
I need to know.
I would love
your insight.
- Dr. Chilton,
Would you care to assist me
with dessert?
- Pleasure.
- I love norton grapes.
Same color inside as outside.
Peel it...
And the flesh is also purple.
Not like other grapes
Where flesh is white
and color comes from the skin.
- A grape with nothing to hide.
- Were I in your position,
I would have attempted
psychic driving.
Perhaps you already have.
I promise
I am much more forgiving
of the unorthodox
than dr. Bloom.
Shall we?
(phone ringing)
- [jack. Jack, it's miriam.]
- the last call was made
To jack's cell from
a disposable phone traced here--
Or within 100 feet of here.
- What was miriam lass
looking into?
- Medical records.
If the ripper was a surgeon,
She thought he might've
treated one of his victims.
- Have they retraced her steps?
- The ones they could find.
She made a jump somewhere
they couldn't explain.
You make those jumps.
- The evidence has to be there.
- Every surgeon that came
into contact with any
Of the ripper victims has been
thoroughly vetted or currently
under observation.
- Including dr. Gideon?
- Dr. Gideon wasn't
in my bedroom;
The chesapeake ripper was.
The last call left
Something
the others didn't--
A phone number.
(phone ringing inside)
(phone ringing)
- What would be the benefit
Of making you believe
your trainee was alive?
- Hope. The ripper wanted
to cloud my vision with hope.
- It can sometimes be brave
to allow yourself hope.
- Not the false kind.
- Don't give up hope
for your wife. Not yet.
She's lost hope,
which means you can't.
- I don't have any control
over that.
- Take control.
I'm sorry
about your wife, jack.
I truly am.
I believe the world is
A better place
with her in it.
I am sorry
about your trainee.
- Whatever the ripper was doing,
it worked.
I mean, I thought she was alive.
For a moment, anyway.
I actually let myself believe
something that I knew
was impossible.
- Talk to me about her.
What was her name?
- My name is miriam lass.
I'm with the fbi.
I would show you my credentials,
but I'm actually just a trainee.
- Never just a trainee.
An agent in training.
Please. Come in.
- I was hoping to talk to you
about a former patient--
Not necessarily one of yours,
but someone you may have
Come into contact with when
you were a practicing physician.
- I haven't practiced medicine
for some time,
But fortunately for you, I have
a very good memory. Please.
- His name was jeremy olmstead.
- Perhaps not so good
a memory after all.
I don't recall a patient
with that name, but
it sounds familiar.
- He was recently found
murdered in his workshop.
We think he may be a victim
Of the chesapeake ripper.
- That's why he sounds familiar.
It was all over the news.
- He had two old scars
on his thigh.
Pathology checked with the local
hospital. He had fallen
Out of a tree-blind five years
ago while bow hunting--
stuck an arrow
Through his leg.
The doctor of record was
A resident surgeon, but you were
on duty in the er that night.
- I was?
- Your name was
on the admissions log.
- Let me think.
You'll have to forgive me.
I saw so many people in the er,
but not so many hunters.
- It's been a long time
since the accident,
But I thought you may remember
if anything was fishy
with the arrow wound.
- If it's the gentleman
I'm thinking of,
I vaguely remember
a fellow hunter bringing him in,
But I recall
very little else.
- Figured it was
a long shot.
- I did keep detailed journals
during those days.
If you like, I can get them
for you. Maybe you'll find
something helpful.
- That would be great--
if you don't mind.
- Not at all. If you'll wait
here, I'll be right back.
- Thank you.
- She was a very brave
young woman.
Closed captioning by sette inc.