Previously on Hannibal...
Where were you last night?
I was withHannibal all night, Jeff.
- My name is Miriam Lass. I'm with the FBI.
- Come in.
The Chesapeake Ripper recorded Miriam Lass
2 years ago.
Jack, I was so wrong.
You said yourself there's no body.
Miriam Lass is dead.
Found something else in the woods.
Madrona bark.
Will didn't kill any of these people.
There's a small stand in Virginia.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Jack, it's Miriam.
I don't know where I am.
I can't see anything.
I was so wrong.
Please, Jack.
I don't want to die like this.
Jack, it's Miriam.
I don't know where I am.
I can't see anything.
I was so wrong.
Thank you.
I knew you'd never
stop looking.
Can I see him?
We haven't caught the Ripper.
He's... he's still...?
We need your help, Miriam.
You know who he is.
I don't.
Know who he is.
You found him.
I don't remember finding him.
He got inside my head.
I remember a dream
about drowning.
And then being awake.
And not awake.
Being myself, and not myself.
I'd wake up to the smell
of fresh flowers
and the sting of a needle.
I wasn't afraid.
Fear and pain were so...
far away.
I was reckless with your life.
- I was reckless with my life.
- I saw
what I needed in you
and I used you.
I let you break the rules on my behalf
while I hid behind deniability.
Agent Crawford, please do not
apologize to me for my mistakes.
He treated me very well,
until the end,
until he put me in the ground.
Even when...
he took my arm.
He told me
what he was going to do.
I went to sleep, woke up,
it was gone.
He said he wanted
to give it to you.
Can you identify him?
I could hear his voice,
but I couldn't see his face.
All I could see...
...was light.
Why didn't he kill you, Miriam?
Why were you spared?
I wasn't spared.
He was saving me for last.
They found a witness.
A survivor.
The only victim
of the Chesapeake Ripper
who lived to tell.
Is this witness
watching me now?
(Alana):Yes.
(Hannibal):It seems I am
the usual suspect.
I keep having angry, imaginary conversations
with Jack Crawford about that.
I wish I could tell you
why this is happening.
His witness must not be able
to identify the Ripper by sight.
Jack wants them
to hear my voice;
otherwise,
I'd be in here alone.
Right?
Still...
I appreciate your company.
It's not him.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
He's not the Ripper.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
This is very sudden.
The federal prosecutor dropped
all charges.
Since you were not convicted
of killing anyone,
the basis for your sentencing
to this institution is
null and void.
The Chesapeake Ripper has
set you free.
Mazel Tov.
(door buzzer) (door unlocked)
I would love nothing more
than to see you trade places
with Dr. Lecter.
I have no intention
of ending up on his menu.
Well, then confess, Frederick.
Might be the only thing
saves your life.
Confess to what?
Confess to bonding
with Hannibal Lecter
over your shared practice
of unorthodox therapies.
Dr. Lecter with me,
you with Abel Gideon.
Gideon is playing his own game;
was wheeled out of that hospital
by the Chesapeake Ripper.
Curious what bargain
they struck.
No, there's no bargaining
with smoke.
No, Gideon's dead.
You're next.
Unless I unburden myself?
Confession is
good for the soul.
Shine a light on your relationship
with Hannibal Lecter.
He works in the shadows.
Deny them to him.
Tell Jack Crawford everything.
Are you suggesting I kill my career
before Hannibal can kill me?
I'm suggesting you convince
Jack Crawford however you can.
Like your life depends on it.
Why did Hannibal
not just kill you?
Because he wants
to be my friend.
You need a ride?
I was gonna call a cab.
We found Miriam Lass.
Alive.
You catch the Ripper?
How is she? Miriam.
Traumatized.
Miriam thanked me
after we found her.
Thanked me for not
giving up on her.
But I had.
I had given up on her.
And I gave up on you too.
I thought she was dead.
I thought you were crazy.
And I gave up on trying
to find the both of you.
You didn't have to
find me, Jack.
You just had to listen to me.
I put Miriam in a room
with Hannibal Lecter.
She stated definitively
he is not
the Chesapeake Ripper.
That definitive enough for you?
No.
It wasn't.
Where'd you find Miriam, Jack?
The property was condemned
years ago.
Apparently the Ripper has been
using it since that time.
Will.
In here.
It's Beverly Katz's blood.
He drained her before he froze
her before he cut into her.
Chesapeake Ripper's
latest victim,
he was found
in the other cistern.
The water in his lungs
is what led us here.
We found Miriam down there.
She believed the Ripper
brought her here to kill her.
He was saving her
to be his last victim.
He knows we're close
to catching him.
He's been caught before.
Catch a fish once
and it gets away...
...it's a lot harder to catch
a second time.
(steady heartbeat)
I sowed the seeds...
and watched them grow.
I cultivated...
a long chain of events
leading to this.
All of this...
...has been my design.
It's theater.
Every time the Ripper kills
someone, it's theater.
The Ripper didn't bring
Miriam here to kill her.
He brought her here
for you to find.
But the Ripper's
not self-destructive.
- He doesn't want to get caught.
- He wants you to catch someone.
Like he wanted you to catch me.
Somewhere,
in all of this evidence,
you will find something
that will lead you away
from Hannibal Lecter.
Miriam Lass has
already done that.
Two years -
it's a long time
to have Hannibal in your head.
You can't trust her, Jack.
You can't trust any of this
to be what it seems.
(dogs barking)
Hey!
(He whistles.)
Hey.
Welcome home.
Thank you.
Thank you
for looking after them.
They seem happy.
Happy to see you.
Who's this?
Applesauce.
She's mine.
She likes applesauce.
I rescued her.
Picking up
some of my bad habits?
Picking up your good habits.
You challenged
my whole framework
of assumptions
about the way you are.
- The way I think you are.
- Well, the way you think I am
isn't always a reliable guide
to who I am.
I was wrong about you.
Because you didn't believe me?
Or in me?
Because you
let me question my sanity,
my sense of reality?
Because you tried
to kill Hannibal.
You're wrong about him, Will.
No, you're wrong about him,
Alana. You see the best in him.
I... don't.
- Hey?
- What was done to you
doesn't excuse what you did.
Are you going to try
to hurt Hannibal again?
Is he safe?
From me, or for you?
He's dangerous, Alana.
I suggest you stay as far away
from Hannibal Lecter as you can.
Come on.
(He whistles.)
(dog barking)
What can I do for you,
- Dr. Chilton?
- It is what I can do for you.
I would like to offer my services
on the Ripper case - pro bono,
- of course.
- I see.
You wish to be helpful expediting
Hannibal Lecter's arrest?
I have consulted with the FBI
on previous Ripper murders.
You have an agenda
with this case, Doctor.
Yes, I have an agenda:
living.
I should be assigned
an FBI escort.
Everyone who believed Will Graham
about Hannibal Lecter is dead.
- Except you.
- Except me.
I would like to remain not dead
for the foreseeable future.
Do you have something substantial
to contribute, or just an opinion?
- I have a witness.
- A witness?
If Will is not a suspect,
then he is a witness.
- To his own manipulation?
- We have had
remarkable success
recovering memory.
He remembers so much
of what was done to him.
Why hasn't Will
told me this himself?
Because you told him
his memories were meaningless.
I imagine Hannibal Lecter used
the same coercive techniques
on Miriam Lass that he used
on Will Graham.
He buried memories
in both of them.
Jack, I dug those memories out of
Will; I can dig them out of Miriam.
Miriam Lass is not
your patient, Doctor.
Over the shoulder...
Are you an FBI agent?
No. Uh...
I used to teach at the academy.
And, uh, two days ago,
I was an inmate
at the Baltimore State Hospital
for the Criminally Insane...
...courtesy of
the Chesapeake Ripper.
Well, the Guru told me
the only person who had
any practical understanding
of the Ripper was you.
But he didn't mention
that you were a victim.
Guru?
- Jack Crawford.
- Oh.
He has a peculiar cleverness.
The Guru tells me
that you don't remember much
about what the Ripper
did to you.
I couldn't remember either.
- Couldn't?
- Oh, I remember now.
Uh... not all of it.
Pieces.
I was...
under his influence.
He used some kind of light
to induce a seizure response
in my brain.
It created blackouts
and lost time.
I remember the light.
He, uh, would stand
in front of it,
at a distance from me,
silhouetted, very still.
He would
listen to chamber music.
I still hear that.
(Hannibal): You're waking now.
And his voice, low and even,
would pull me to him.
(Hannibal):Waking
in a pleasant room. Safe...
Like a current.
(Hannibal):You're waking now.
Waking, calm.
Waking in a pleasant room,
safe.
You and I
are... part
of his design.
He wanted you to be free.
He wanted me to be free too.
Neither of us are really free.
He's not done.
The same unfortunate
aftershave.
Too long in the bottle.
Our last kitchen conversation
was interrupted
by Jack Crawford.
I'd like to pick up
where we left off.
If memory serves,
you were asking me...
if it would feel good
to kill you.
You've given that some thought.
You wanted me to embrace
my nature, Doctor.
I'm just following the urges
I kept down for so long,
cultivating them
as the inspirations they are.
You never answered my question.
How would killing me
make you feel?
Righteous.
Aren't you curious, Will?
Why you?
Why Miriam Lass?
What does the Chesapeake Ripper
want with you?
No, you tell me.
How did Miriam Lass find you?
You made sure no one could
find you that way again.
If I'm not the Ripper,
you murder an innocent man.
You better than anyone
know what it means
to be wrongly accused.
You were innocent
and no one saw it.
No, I'm not innocent.
You saw to that.
If I am the Ripper and you kill me,
who will answer your questions?
Don't you want to know
how this ends?
My name is Miriam Lass.
I'm with the FBI.
I would show you my credentials,
but I'm actually just a trainee.
Never just a trainee.
An agent in training. Please,
come in.
I would have been happy
- to come to your office, Jack.
- I understand,
but I wanted to do this here.
I'm sure you have your reasons.
The most-important aspect
of a successful recovery is
recognizing that life will
never be the same.
Then I must be well on my way
to a successful recovery.
That's beautiful. Yours?
Yes.
I enjoy portraiture.
A subject's mental process
betrayed
only by the expression
on their face.
Miriam.
The Chesapeake Ripper
sent me a message from you.
It was recorded
shortly after you were taken.
It's me? My voice?
Yes.
I want to hear it.
Very well.
Jack, it's Miriam.
I don't know where I am.
I can't see anything.
I was so wrong.
Please, Jack.
I don't wanna die like this.
I don't remember.
Would you like to try?
You're waking now.
Waking, calm.
Waking in a pleasant room.
Safe.
Open your eyes.
Jack.
Jack, it's Miriam.
Tell me where you are.
I don't know where I am.
What do you see?
I... I can't see
anything.
I was so wrong.
Jack, please.
I don't wanna die like this.
Miriam... what was
the last thing you remember
before making the call?
The wound man.
We found a fingerprint
on a flower petal.
A partial, smudged.
Not enough points for
a courtroom, but it triggered
a match in the system.
Hannibal Lecter.
After all
these murders, the Ripper's
gonna leave a print now?
Will said whatever evidence we found,
it would lead us away from the Ripper.
We also found sodium amytal
and scopolamine
in Miriam's blood.
Dr. Chilton used
scopolamine
and sodium amytal
on both Gideon and Will
during their therapy.
One claimed
to be the Chesapeake Ripper
and the other accused Hannibal.
"You've got the right box,
but you're looking
in the wrong corner."
Gideon pointed me at Chilton,
told me that he was the Ripper.
Wait. I'm confused.
So, who are we saying is
the Chesapeake Ripper?
Dr. Lecter, or Dr. Chilton?
Bring 'em both in.
(faint steady beeping)
(continuous steady beeping)
(flatline tone)
Hello, Frederick.
Oh, my god.
(knocking)
That will be the FBI.
When you wake up,
your only choice will be to run.
(doorbell) One moment, please.
(dogs barking)
May I use your shower, please?
Gideon hasn't
been dead for long,
no more than a couple of hours.
Chilton's been carving steaks
off of him for days.
Chilton's shelves are filled
with a lot of old medical books.
- The wound man.
- Mm-hmm.
This illustration shows up
in a lot of early texts.
It's the Ripper's sixth victim.
Chilton was consulting on the Ripper
case when Miriam disappeared.
She must've talked to him,
made the connection.
Beverly made a connection too.
Chilton's been a part
of the Ripper case
since before Will Graham,
Hannibal Lecter, Miriam Lass.
He had access to case files.
He would know everything
the Ripper would need to know.
I have the same profile
as Hannibal Lecter.
Same medical
and psychological background.
We are both doctors of note
in our field.
Of course it would be me!
Hannibal was never going
to kill me.
I'm his patsy. I...
I have to leave the country.
I am leaving the country.
No, if you run,
you look guilty.
You did not run
and you looked plenty guilty.
Abel Gideon was half-eaten
in my guest room.
I have corpses on my property.
- You just threw up an ear.
- There's an APB on you
right now. They've canceled credit
cards, they're tracing your phone.
I have cash
and I tossed my phone.
Jack Crawford thinks I killed
two agents - three agents.
You know what tends to happen to
people who do that? Shoot on sight.
I'm going to prove Hannibal
Lecter is the Chesapeake Ripper.
I know you will.
And when you do,
I will read about it
from a secure location
and I will reintroduce myself
to society at that time.
(dogs barking)
Will... what have you done?
- I called Jack Crawford.
- No.
N...
No. No.
No.
No! No!
No, stay there!
You're not a killer, Frederick.
Why'd you come alone,
Jack? Why'd you come alone?
Where is he? Where is he?!
Hey, I told you, everything is
not what it seems.
The Chesapeake Ripper is still
playing with us. All of us.
The Chesapeake Ripper is not playing
all of us, Will; he's playing you.
Jack, wait.
I'll bring him out.
- He's got a gun.
- Good.
CHILTON!
Chilton, stop where you are!
Please.
One navy blue sweater,
one pair of men's dress pants
in charcoal gray,
one black and red pea coat,
one black leather billfold
containing
$443, various credit cards,
one set of car keys.
I need to speak to Will Graham.
I don't care what you need.
One Montblanc fountain pen
in silver and black.
Does it have to be you?
It seems like one
final indignity.
Not like you
- to hide an achievement.
- The achievement
is not mine.
Whose is it?
Hannibal Lecter's?
Those are just words
coming out of your mouth.
No weight to them.
No consideration
they may be true.
They're not true.
You were using
coercive therapies,
influencing Abel Gideon
and Will Graham
to point the Ripper investigations
in false directions.
You cannot see it,
and you will not see it
until it is too late.
Don't say I did not
warn you, Dr. Bloom.
In fact, I believe
these should be my last words
on the subject of the Ripper
until my lawyer arrives.
You're waking now.
Waking, calm.
Waking in a quiet room.
You're waking now.
Waking in a quiet room. Safe.
It's him. It's him.
(stuttering): It's him... It--
(Miriam crying)
It's all right.
(knocking on door)
Hello, Will.
May I come in?
Do you intend
to point a gun at me?
Not tonight.
Are you expecting someone?
Only you.
Kept my standing
appointment open?
And you're right on time.
I have to deal with you.
And my feelings about you.
I think it's best
if I do that directly.
First you have to grieve
for what is lost
and what has changed.
I've changed;
you changed me.
The friendship
that we had is over.
The Chesapeake Ripper is over.
It had to be Miriam, didn't it?
She was compelled
to take his life
so she could take her own back.
How will you
take your life back?
I'd like to resume my therapy.
Where shall we begin?
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player