Previously on Hannibal
You're quite the topic of conversation
in the psychiatric circles.
The reason you failed to
capture the Chesapeake Ripper
is I already had him.
I did it.
Miriam Lass is dead. The Chesapeake Ripper
is making it very clear that someone is
plagiarizing his work.
Is it possible you
inadvertently planted
the suggestion in Gideon's mind
that the was the Ripper?
Psychic driving is unethical.
I have feelings for you.
I can't just have an affair with you.
Why?
I think you're unstable.
You're the subject of a lot
of speculation at the Bureau.
Jack pushed you right up to the edge
and now you're pushing yourself over.
(Jack): What happened in there?
I saw the look on your face.
You must overcome these delusions
that are disguising your reality.
It's anti-nmda receptor
encephalitis.
Now that we have confirmed what it is,
it'll be easier to hide from him.
Someone who already doubts
their own identity
can be more susceptible
to manipulation.
Dr. Gideon is a psychopath.
Psychopaths are narcissists.
They rarely doubt who they are.
I tried to appeal
to his narcissism.
By convincing him
he was the Chesapeake Ripper.
If only I had been more curious
about the common mind.
I have no interest in understanding
sheep; only eating them.
Kudal. A South Indian curry.
Made from sheep, of course.
In a coconut-coriander-
chili sauce.
It feels like a last supper.
You're not the only psychiatrist accused
by a patient of making them kill.
Poke around a psychopath's mind,
bound to get poked back.
What would you do
in my position?
Deny everything.
I thought psychic driving would have
been more effective in breaking down
his personality. Psychic driving
fails because its methods are
too obvious. You were trying too
hard, Frederick. If force is used,
the subject will only surrender temporarily.
Once a patient is exposed
to the method of manipulation,
it becomes much less effective.
When Dr. Gideon began
- to suspect he was being pushed...
- He pushed back.
The subject mustn't be aware
of any influence.
(Insects chirping)
(Breathing rapidly)
(Startled shouting)
(Catching his breath)
So, you get to
dress up and I don't?
This might affect how well
my testimony goes over
with the judge.
- Testimony speaks for itself.
- Frederick, don't look so worried.
- I forgive you your trespasses.
- What trespasses are those?
You made me kill the nurse.
I take responsibility for
killing my wife and her family.
- The nurse is your fault.
- I cannot
accept responsibility
for your actions, Abel.
Au contraire.
It's why I'm suing you.
You made me think I was
somebody else,
and now...
who knows what I'm thinking?
Dr. Gideon, you told me you
were the Chesapeake Ripper.
Dr. Chilton, you told me
I was the Chesapeake Ripper,
and that's what I'm
going to tell everyone.
See you in court.
You married?
You're married.
How long you married?
That long?
Regarding divorce...
not that you're getting one;
just I can see the clock
in your eyes...
Word of advice:
it's easier just to kill 'em.
Kill 'em, kill everyone
at the table.
Less paperwork.
Worked for me.
I'm doing ok.
Your wife is
probably fantastic.
My wife? Horrible.
So maybe I'm not supposed
to be in a relationship.
There's people like that.
How do you keep those whites
so clean? That's...
always amazes me.
♪
Hannibal 01x11
Roti
Original Air Date June 6, 2013
==sync, correction by dcdah==
for www.addic7ed.com
(Heartbeat sounds)
All I need is one hand free.
(Neck snapping)
(Man yelling)
(Will breathing rapidly)
So, does Abel Gideon
still believe that he's
the Chesapeake Ripper?
Abel Gideon is having
a difference of opinion
about who he is.
The man who escaped
from that van was not
in the same state of mind
when he did this.
He took a uniform,
police radio,
two 9mm handguns, pepper spray,
taser, and handcuffs.
Well, it's what he didn't take.
(Bev): He hung the organs
from the branch with vein
from the victims.
He even tied little bows
with some of them.
Yeah, it's really impressive.
The Chesapeake Ripper would
not have left the organs behind.
Well, if Gideon isn't
the Chesapeake Ripper,
he's certainly trying
to get his attention.
Local PD picked up
a foot trail leading
out of the woods. Boot soles are
consistent with the ones
- we found at the crime scene.
- How fresh are the tracks?
- Two, three hours old.
- Which direction they headed?
Back to Baltimore.
(Jack sighs.)
(Door opening)
I suppose this is
my fault too?
You did dodge a bullet.
Gideon's escape
foregoes a trial
and a very public humiliation
for you.
And now you are hosting
a private one.
Next you'll be accusing me
- of arranging his escape.
- No one's making
- that accusation.
- If we're tossing around
the blame, Dr. Bloom,
you're due your fair share.
You planted the idea that I was
unethically manipulating Gideon.
Well, according to Gideon,
you were.
- After you told him I was.
- You thought I was manipulating
him? He was manipulating you.
- You were pushing him.
- He gave me informed consent to treat him,
said that he was grateful
for my help
- in understanding who he is.
- What did you help him
- understand?
- He was not insane
when he killed his wife;
killing her drove him insane.
I did not convince him
that he was a serial killer;
I just reminded him of the fact.
Gideon is not
the Chesapeake Ripper,
although he might have thought
he was under your care, doctor.
Whether he is or he isn't
doesn't really matter
right now. If he thinks he is
or even if he's confused
- on that issue, he will kill again.
- I hope he does not,
I mean for your sake.
Cannot imagine
how you would sleep
with that on your shoulders.
(Chilton's voice distant) During those
three minutes, Gideon did horrible things.
How did you sleep
when Gideon killed your nurse?
What does Gideon want?
The last thing Abel Gideon
said to me is that he intends
to tell everyone that he is
the Chesapeake Ripper.
Our fugitive is Abel Gideon.
Transplant surgeon.
Convicted in the first degree
in the murders of his wife
and her family.
Institutionalized at the Baltimore State
Hospital for the Criminally Insane,
where he killed a nurse
and claimed to be
the Chesapeake Ripper.
(Jack's voice becoming distant)
Dr. Gideon escaped this morning
after killing three people.
He is armed and dangerous. He is
believed to be...
(Jack's voice echoing)
In the first degree
in the murders of his wife and
her family. Institutionalized
at the Baltimore State Hospital
for the Criminally Insane.
Insane.
(Jack's voice distant)
Escaped this morning.
He is armed, he is dangerous...
you escaped this morning.
He escaped this morning.
He is armed and he is
extremely dangerous.
You escaped this morning.
Institutionalized at the Baltimore State...
(Cacophony of Jack's voice)
What kind of crazy are you?!
You kill! You will kill again!
(Jack's voice echoing)
(Jack speaking indistinctly)
(People murmuring quietly)
Hannibal:
What did you see?
A thicket of antlers.
All I heard was my heart,
dim but... but fast,
like, um... footsteps
fleeing into silence.
I don't know how to gauge
who I am anymore.
I don't feel like myself.
I feel like I have been
gradually becoming different
for a while.
I just feel like somebody else.
What do you feel like?
I feel crazy.
(Will breathing shakily)
And that is what
you fear most.
I fear not knowing who I am.
That's what Abel Gideon's
afraid of, isn't it?
He's like a blind man.
Somebody got inside his head
and...
moved all the
furniture around.
I imagine Abel Gideon would
want to find
the Chesapeake Ripper
to gauge who he is.
And who he isn't.
Will.
You have me as your gauge.
Gideon didn't leave
a manifesto. We confiscated
all correspondence
from his outside admirers. We're
going through everything now.
Good.
Any secret communiqués or coded
messages written in bodily fluids
or anything else,
we'll find them.
You won't find anything.
Whatever's going on
with Gideon, it's in his head.
Well, there's not much left
in these heads.
All organ removal was done postmortem,
including the transorbital lobotomies.
It wasn't technically
a lobotomy.
He didn't remove any of the
brain; He just scrambled them.
Went in through the top
of the eye socket...
(Jack): Ok, ok.
Tell me something.
Why remove
all of the other organs
from the bodies
and leave them intact
and just scramble
the brains?
That's what they did to him.
What who did to him?
Dr. Chilton, every
psychiatrist and PhD candidate
who attempted any kind
of therapy,
pushed and prodded,
gave him tests, told him
who he was, who he wasn't.
All right. I want a list
of every therapist,
every doctor, any kind
of psychiatric professional
that worked with or talked to
Dr. Gideon.
Alana Bloom will be
on that list.
Are you my protective custody?
You heard?
I heard I get an armed escort
until Gideon's apprehended.
You'll have a real FBI agent,
not a teacher
with a temporary badge.
Too bad.
Would have been fun to cozy up with
your dogs in front of a space heater.
You don't need protective
custody to cozy up with my dogs.
Or me, for that matter.
Just need a little more, um...
stability on my part.
You're really warm.
Yeah, I tend to run hot.
They say stress raises
body temperature.
Maybe you should take
an aspirin.
Way ahead of you.
They're gonna kill Gideon,
aren't they?
Whatever happens to him has
nothing to do
- with you.
- Gideon can't be
completely responsible
for his actions
if he was subjected
to an outside influence.
What, like Chilton telling him
he's the Chesapeake Ripper?
Like me
telling him he's not in a state
of mind to know who he is.
Well, he's gonna want somebody to tell
him who he is, and I think he'll be
looking for the Ripper
to do that.
What do you think will happen if
Gideon finds the Chesapeake Ripper?
The Chesapeake Ripper will
kill him.
He took credit for his work.
The Ripper would
consider that rude.
(Cell phone ringtone)
Freddie Lounds.
Gideon: My name is Paul
Carruthers. I'm a psychiatrist.
I read your article
on Abel Gideon.
And I yours, Dr. Carruthers.
So you're aware of my work?
I found your paper
on narcissistic
personality disorder insightful,
especially as it pertains
to your opinions of Abel Gideon.
Well, thank you.
That's very kind of you.
You're calling
about his escape?
Well, yes. I'd like
to collaborate
On an article for the "Journal
of Abnormal Psychology".
You want a writing partner?
Could we meet?
Hello?
Dr. Carruthers?
Ms. Lounds, come on in.
Now, you wrote
in your tattler archive
that the Chesapeake Ripper
once removed a man's tongue
and used it as a bookmark
for his Bible.
They call this
a Colombian neck tie.
What do you think?
Ee...
Dr. Paul Carruthers wrote an article for
the Journal of Criminal Psychology in which
he described Dr. Gideon
as being a pathological narcissist
who suffers from
psychotic episodes.
Let's hope he got some satisfaction
from being proved right.
I think this is about more than
just getting the Chesapeake
- Ripper's attention.
- Gideon's mind was
dissected by psychiatrists
and, as a surgeon, he is
applying his own skill set.
He gave you something better to
do with your tongue than wag it.
No, that's not how he died.
Drained him
till his heart stopped.
Got a little on his collar.
Other than that,
- didn't spill a drop.
- That's because it's all in here.
Four-and-a-half liters
all packed in ice.
"Please deliver
to the Red Cross."
- (Bev): That's considerate.
- He's peacocking for the Ripper.
This is like flowers and
chocolate before a first date.
How is this news already?
Somebody from the Baltimore PD must've
taken a picture with their phone and sold it
- to Tattlecrime.
- The photo was taken
before the blood was put on ice.
Dr. Gideon was still here.
He has Freddie Lounds.
You might be working out
the emergency exits,
or at least considering them.
Let me just tell you
there are three.
They're all terribly
locked down.
Now, this relationship
between you and me,
this can do us both some good.
I could write
a big story on you,
anything you want to say.
I did enjoy the article
you wrote about that poor nurse
who I killed,
but it didn't really seem
like genuine Freddie Lounds.
- Jack Crawford told me to write it.
- Of course he did.
- To flush out the Chesapeake Ripper.
- And flushed out he was.
That's why he waved
Jack Crawford's
dead trainee's arm
around his head
right here like a flag
in this very room.
Aren't you
the Chesapeake Ripper?
Miss Lounds, I might be
slightly fuzzy in this area,
but there's no need
to patronize me.
I'm sorry.
It's like remembering
something from your childhood,
and you're not sure
if it's your memory
or a friend's memory,
and then you realize sadly it's
just some photo in an old book.
You're waiting
for the Chesapeake Ripper
to come back here.
Let's hope he
gets the invitation.
There's one thing we know
about your writing:
he is an avid fan.
Dr. Carson Nahn.
He's the psychiatric attending
at Western General.
He interviewed Dr. Gideon
for the same psychopathy survey
I participated in two years ago.
Total frenectomy,
webbing under the tongue;
even the connective tissue all the way into
the throat is cut free and pulled through
for the, uh, desired effect.
(Jack sighs.)
Still no word
from Dr. Chilton?
He hasn't answered his phone
since yesterday,
didn't show up to work today.
Gideon wants
to lure the Ripper.
He's going to offer up the man who
disrespected both their identities.
Every detail
of Dr. Carruthers' murder
as described meticulously
in Freddie Lounds' article
has been faithfully
reproduced except...
for one.
What's different about Carson?
Why amputate his arm?
(Jack): Did Freddie write
anything about this?
(Brian): Not that I know of,
no.
Abel Gideon didn't kill
this man;
the Chesapeake Ripper did.
You said the Chesapeake Ripper
would want to kill Gideon
for taking credit for his work.
Gideon isn't alone anymore,
and the Ripper isn't going
to risk exposure,
so, no, he's...
he's, um...
He's telling us
where to catch him.
Actually, he's telling you.
Me?
Where's the last place
you saw a severed arm, Jack?
With experience, I have found
surgeries are best performed
on a local anesthetic
or epidural
with the patient awake.
Reminds me there' a real person
here entrusting me with their life
rather than a lump of meat
that I'm about to reorganize.
And in this instance,
I would like to see the look
on your face.
Please... you're not
the Chesapeake Ripper.
You got inside my mind,
Frederick.
It's only fair
I get inside your belly.
This is of course
Freddie Lounds, who you know.
She will be assisting me today...
or assisting you...
by manually pumping the ventilator
should you stop breathing.
Oh, my God.
The real Chesapeake Ripper is
a collector
of surgical trophies.
I'm gonna leave him
a little gift.
In fact, I'm gonna leave him
a gift basket.
You know, it is truly amazing
how many organs the body can offer up
before it really begins to suffer.
All right, stay awake now!
Come on, Frederick.
I'm gonna ask you
to hold a few things.
Hmm. What next?
(Jack):
I want you to wait outside.
That's probably best.
You look like hell, Will.
I feel like hell.
Actually, no, I feel...
Uh, fluid,
like I'm spilling.
Must have come down
with something.
I hope it's not contagious.
(Jack's voice distant)
This work that we do...
(Jack's voice normal) ...It will compromise
your immune system, if you allow it.
You've got to keep things in perspective.
You've got to keep yourself in perspective.
Well, myself is a little hazy
at the moment.
You've gotta start
taking better care of yourself.
- Build my resistance?
- You just can't take it all in.
You've got to let go
of as much of it as you can.
- You just gotta let go.
- You know, it's hard
to shake off something
that's already under your skin.
Mark.
Go!
- Clear.
No sign of Gideon.
Gideon's gone.
He's still alive.
I need medical in here now!
I was expecting
the Chesapeake Ripper.
Or are you he?
Turn around. Don't look at me.
You are looking a little peaky,
Mr. Graham,
if you don't mind my saying.
I may be crazy,
but you look ill.
Drive.
Who is your doctor?
I'm having a hard time
thinking.
(Will panting)
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
I-I don't know what's real.
It's 7:27 pm.
You're in Baltimore, Maryland, and
your name is Will Graham.
No I don't care who I am!
Just tell me...
if he's real.
Who do you see, Will?
Garret Jacob Hobbs.
Who do you see?
I don't see anyone.
No, he's right there.
- There's no one there, Will.
- No, no, you're lying.
We're alone. You came here alone.
Do you remember coming here?
- No, please don't lie to me!
- Garret Jacob Hobbs is dead.
You killed him.
You watched him die.
- What's happening to me?
- Will,
Will, Will, you're having
an episode. I want you
to hand me over the gun. Will,
I want you to hand me your...
Will?
Will.
He's had a mild seizure.
That doesn't seem
to bother you.
I said it was mild.
Are you the man who claimed
to be the Chesapeake Ripper?
Why do you say "claimed"?
Because you're not.
You know you're not,
and you don't know much more
about who you are beyond that.
Are you the Ripper?
A terrible thing...
to have your identity taken
from you.
Well, I'm taking it back,
one piece at a time.
You should see the pieces
I got out of my psychiatrist.
Alana Bloom was
one of your psychiatrists too.
Is that right?
Yes. Dr. Bloom.
I can tell you
where to find her.
(Hannibal):
Will can you hear me?
Repeat after me.
(Hannibal):
My name is Will Graham.
Raise both of your arms.
More.
Good.
Although you may not feel
like it, I need you to smile.
Good. It wasn't a stroke.
You may have had a seizure.
Tell me the last thing
you remember.
I...
(Will panting)
I was with Garret Jacob Hobbs.
You have a fever.
You were hallucinating.
You thought he was alive,
- here in the room with you.
- I saw him.
He's a delusion
disguising reality.
Don't let that
let you slip away.
You killed
Garret Jacob Hobbs once.
You can find
a way to kill him again.
- Where are you going?
- Abel Gideon is still
at large.
He mutilated Dr. Chilton.
They found him
clinging to life.
I'm worried about Alana.
- Alana.
- No, no, no, no, no, no. Will.
You're in no state to go
anywhere but the hospital.
I'll call Jack
and tell him where you are.
I have to make a phone call.
Can I ask you to step out?
I don't know if I will
ever be myself again.
I don't know if I've got
any "self" left over.
I spent so long thinking
I was him,
it's gotten really hard to remember
who I was when I wasn't him.
Who are you now?
Now I'm you.
We're both here,
looking at her,
just those kind of people that
shouldn't be in a relationship.
You and I are
already committed.
It's hard to be
with another person when you...
can't get out of
your own head.
I want to get out.
Yeah, well,
we all want things
that we can't have.
But if I kill her
like he would kill her,
then maybe
I could understand him better.
I wonder if then you would finally
understand what you've become.
(Gunshot)
They will be sewing up
Dr. Chilton until the morning...
That is, if he makes it
through the night.
At least Will remains
in one piece...
for now.
His temperature is 105.
White blood cell count is
twice normal, and they still can't
identify the source of his infection.
They will.
You seem confident.
I am.
Even with a temperature
of 105 degrees, Will was able
to bring Gideon down.
I told you, he'll be fine.
Jack...
I would recommend you suspend
his license to carry firearms.
You and I are just gonna have to
have a difference of opinion
about who Will is, doctor.
I know who Will is.
Will knows who he is.
Yes.
But our experiences shape us,
Jack.
How is this experience going
to shape Will?
(Monitor beeping)
(Ventilator pumping)
(Birds singing)
Will Graham is troubled.
And that troubles you?
Beyond a professional concern
for a patient?
I see his madness
and I want to contain it,
like an oil spill.
Oil is valuable.
What value does Will Graham's
madness have for you?
You're suggesting I'm more fascinated
with the madness than the man?
Are you?
No.
He realized early on
that he saw things differently
than other people,
felt things differently.
So did you.
I see myself in Will.
Do you see yourself
in his madness?
Madness can be a medicine
for the modern world.
You take it in moderation,
it's beneficial.
You overdose and it can have
unfortunate side effects.
Side effects can be temporary.
They can be a boost
to our psychological
immune systems to help fight
the existential crises
of normal life.
Will Graham does not
present you with problems
from normal life.
No. He doesn't.
What does he present you with?
The opportunity for friendship.
He is still your patient,
Hannibal.
Where Will Graham
is concerned,
if you feel the impulse
to step forward,
you must force yourself
to take a step back.
And just watch him
lose his mind?
Sometimes all we can do
is watch.
==sync, correction by dcdah==
for www.addic7ed.com