Jack: Previously on
Hannibal
The reason you kept failing
to capture
the Chesapeake Ripper is
I already had him.
I see the Ripper,
but I don't feel the Ripper.
- Franklyn, the lion is not in the room.
- He's, um, he's eating them.
The real Chesapeake Ripper is gonna
make sure everybody knows it.
I don't think we've ever been alone
in a room together, have we?
My name is Mariam Lass.
I'm actually just a trainee.
She was a very brave
young woman.
Jack, it's Miriam.
I don't want to die like this.
The Chesapeake Ripper kills
in sounders of three.
He did his first victims
in nine days.
Annapolis, Essex,
Baltimore. He didn't kill again
for 18 months. Then there was another
sounder of three in as many days,
all of them in Baltimore.
I use the term
"sounders" because it refers
to a small group of pigs.
That's how he sees his victims;
not as people,
not as prey.
Pigs.
Eleven months after the sixth
victim, there was a seventh.
Two days later, the eighth is
killed in his workshop.
Every tool on the pegboard where
they hung was used against him,
and, as with previous murders,
organs were removed.
The removal of organs
and abdominal mutilations means
someone with anatomical
or surgical know-how.
There...
is a distinctive brutality.
An FBI trainee named
Miriam Lass
was investigating private
medical records
of all the known victims
when she disappeared.
She's believed to be the
Ripper's ninth, but no trace
of her was found...
until recently,
two years later,
when her severed arm was
discovered.
Only because he
wanted it to be.
True to
his established pattern,
the Chesapeake Ripper has
remained consistently theatrical.
(Baroque opera music)
(Singing in Italian)
It's been too long since you've
properly cooked for us, Hannibal.
Come over and I will cook
for you.
I said properly.
Means dinner and the show.
Have you seen him cook?
It's an entire performance.
He used to throw
such exquisite dinner parties.
You heard me. Used to.
And I will again,
once inspiration strikes.
I cannot force a feast.
A feast must present itself.
It's a dinner party,
- not a unicorn.
- Oh, but the feast is life.
You put the life in your belly
and you live.
(She chuckles.)
I believe this young man is
trying to get your attention.
Hello.
Hi. It's so good to see you.
- This is my friend Tobias.
- Good evening.
How do you two
know each other?
There should remain
some mystery to my life
outside the opera.
I'm one of his patients.
- Did you enjoy the performance?
- I did. I loved it. Every minute.
His eyes kept wandering. More interested
in you than what was happening on stage.
Oh, don't say too much.
You must leave something
for us to discuss next week.
Franklyn, good to see you.
- You too.
- Tobias.
Who's hungry?
(She chuckles.)
♪
Hannibal 01x07
Sorbet
Original Air Date May 8, 2013
==sync, correction by dcdah==
for www.addic7ed.com
(Phone ringing)
(Vibrating and ringing)
Hello?
The victim was found
in a hotel room bathtub.
There were abdominal mutilations
and organ removal on the scene.
Sounds more like an urban legend
than the Chesapeake Ripper, no?
I've had the room sealed.
You'll get it fresh.
Fresh?
Fresh as a Daisy?
Fresh enough for to tell me
whether or not it's the Ripper.
Then you can go back to class.
Oh, you don't want me
in a classroom.
You want me to wrap my head
so tight around the Ripper
I won't go back to class
until he's caught.
Your bad luck
that you're the best, pal.
Expecting another couple
of bodies after this one?
If it's the Ripper, yes, I am.
Don't let the Ripper
stir you up.
The reason he left you
Miriam Lass's arm
is so he could poke you
with it.
Why not the rest of her?
His other victims...
He wanted to humiliate in death,
like... like a public
dissection. She was different.
He was probably impressed
that she was able to find him.
He may be starting
another cycle, Will.
The Ripper contacted you
directly.
If he was killing again,
he wouldn't be subtle about it;
he would just pick up the phone.
Any more phone calls, Jack?
No.
Look, if this is the Ripper,
there'll be at least
two more bodies and then nothing
for months, maybe a year.
We'll have a window
of opportunity to catch him
and that window will close.
The last time the window closed,
I lost the Ripper and I lost Miriam Lass.
I don't intend to do that again.
(Police radio chatter)
(Camera shutter click)
- Has anyone touched the body?
- For once, local police behaved themselves.
It's fairly evident the man's
dead just by looking at him.
I touched the body.
A lot going on with that body.
Surgery was performed
and then un-performed.
Surgery was un-performed with
bare hands, sutures clawed open.
I, uh, I also... did
a little bit of touching.
Pieces of him were torn off
from the bed to the bathroom,
like breadcrumbs.
Surgery wasn't performed here.
There would be a lot more blood.
If he's moving his victims,
he could be
performing the mutilations
in the same transport.
Find the car, find the killer.
- He tore open his own sutures.
- It wasn't the kidney.
The Ripper already took it with him.
Or her. I'd say him.
- What did he take out of the chest?
- Going for the heart.
Probably interrupted.
It's intact. Traumatized,
but it's intact.
Everybody out.
(Soft ambient pulse)
Will: Signs of a struggle
indicate
he's suffering from a severe, violent
emergence from deep sedation.
Oh!
(Both grunting with effort)
His heart seizes up.
I open his chest wall.
I spread the ribs.
I... I take his heart
in my hand.
Internal cardiac massage.
(Breathing shakily)
J--Jack?
This wasn't brutal.
The killer wasn't killing;
He was trying to save his life.
The Ripper ever do that?
- it's the Chesapeake Ripper.
- (Will): It's not the Ripper.
- There are too many similarities.
- There aren't enough.
Knife wounds are cuts,
not stabs.
Anatomical knowledge,
dissection skills, mutilation,
organs removed,
victim clothed, on display.
We got 22 signature components
all attributable
- to the same killer.
- Twenty two possible
- signature components.
- It's the Ripper.
- Are you sure?
- More or less.
Tell me why you're sure.
The Ripper left his last victim
in a church pew using his tongue
as a page marker
in the Bible he was holding.
This isn't that.
This is a medical student
or a trainee or someone trying
to make an extra buck
in a back-alley surgery,
and it went bad.
Actively bad.
You'll catch the Ripper
eventually.
Yeah, well,
I want to catch him now.
And when I do, you're not gonna
get a chance to shoot him,
'cause I'm gonna do that.
You can't just jack up the law
and get underneath it.
Can't I?
Tell me how you see the Ripper,
Will.
I see him
as one of those pitiful things
sometimes born
in hospitals.
They feed it, keep it warm,
but they don't put it
on the machines.
They let it die.
But he doesn't die.
He looks normal.
And nobody can tell what he is.
Good morning. Please come in.
Would you like to discuss
our chance encounter?
(Franklyn chuckles.)
It wasn't altogether
by chance.
I kind of... kinda thought
you'd be there...
which isn't why I was there.
I-I... I was there
because I like
that sort of thing.
Uh, it just occurred to me that...
that you might like it too.
In fact, I do.
I tried to get your attention.
I was aware of that.
I knew that you were aware,
even though you were
pretending that you weren't.
It would be unethical
to approach a patient
or acknowledge in any way our
relationship outside this room
until that patient gives
consent.
But I really don't know
who you are outside this room.
I'm your psychiatrist.
- I want you to be my friend.
- Of course you do.
I have intimate knowledge
of you.
And we like the same things. I think
that we would make good friends.
It makes me sad
that I have to pay to see you.
(Franklyn sighs.)
I am a source of stability
and clarity, Franklyn.
I'm not your friend.
I'm a great friend.
I was listening to, uh,
Michael Jackson last night,
and I burst into tears, and...
my eyes are burning right now
just talking about it.
You know what I think is
the saddest thing
about him dying is that I will
never get to meet him,
and I feel like
if I was his friend
that I... I would have
been able to...
help save him from himself.
In this Michael Jackson fantasy,
how is your friendship returned?
I just get to touch greatness.
Hello. Come on in.
This always goes better if I'm
perfectly honest with you.
What would be the point
otherwise?
Well, one of us has
to be honest.
I'm honest.
Not perfectly.
As honest as anyone.
Not really.
I have conversations
with a version of you
and hope that the actual you
gets what he needs.
A version of me?
Naturally,
I respect
its meticulous construction,
but you are wearing
a very well-tailored
"person suit".
Do you refer to me
as "person suit"
with your psychiatrist friends?
I don't discuss patients
with my psychiatrist friends,
especially since I only have
one patient who chose to ignore
my retirement.
A patient who wears
a person suit.
Maybe it's less of a person
suit and more of a human veil.
That must be lonely.
I have friends.
And the opportunities
for friends.
You and I are friendly.
You are my patient
and my colleague, not my friend.
At the end of your hour,
I will pour you
a glass of wine.
Nevertheless,
you will be drinking it
on the other side of the veil.
Why do you bother?
I see enough of you
to see the truth of you.
And I like you.
Red or white?
I think something pink,
don't you?
Good evening, Will.
Please come in.
Oh, you've been drinking.
I had a glass of wine
with my last appointment, yes.
Drinking with a patient.
Ah, she was drinking
with a patient.
I have an unconventional
psychiatrist.
Well, we have that in common.
Am I your psychiatrist,
or are we simply having
conversations?
"Yes" I think is the answer
to that.
Then having a glass of wine
before seeing a patient,
I assure you,
is very conventional.
Especially
for evening appointments.
Huh. How long have you been
seeing a psychiatrist?
Since I chose
to be a psychiatrist.
Thank you.
I read the Freddy Lounds article.
Chesapeake Ripper has struck again.
No, no, no.
No, it's not the same guy.
Maybe it's never been
the same guy.
Oh, what, now he has a friend?
(Will chuckles.)
Any variations in the murders
that might suggest there could be more
than one Ripper? Some variations.
The victims were
all brutalized.
What was the brutalization
hiding?
The careful
surgical removal
and preservation of vital
organs.
Valuable organs.
Organ harvesters?
Jack's looking for a serial
killer he can't seem to catch.
It's a brilliant diversion.
That's an interesting theory.
I will keep it in mind
if another body drops.
Please do.
(Doctor): Any other
infections?
(Hannibal): You seem convinced
I'm diseased.
I was asking a broader question.
A disease is an infection.
An infection isn't
always a disease.
- That is true.
- You should just tell me now,
because I'm going to find out,
and it will affect
your insurance if you lie.
May I ask
for your business card, please,
for my records?
(Baritone singing in Italian)
(Frustrated shout): Agh!
Do you need a hand?
I think I must have hit
a rock or something.
It gouged my gas tank.
Have we met before?
Found him in a school bus, sitting
across the asile from himself.
Not only did the Ripper take
his kidney...
but he also took his heart,
which, if you'll recall, is what
he tried to do in the hotel but was interrupted
before he could paint his picture.
The Ripper wasn't painting a picture
in the hotel. Someone else was.
You still think that he was ripping
out a heart to save a life?
- Yes, I do.
- The Ripper painted this picture, for sure.
In big, broad strokes.
Could both victims' organs have
been harvested for transplant?
Subtle variation on waking up in
a tub of ice missing a kidney?
I love a good urban legend.
You could put the organs
on a ventilator long enough
to coordinate the donation.
At the hotel,
the victim's abdominal aorta
and inferior vena cava...
that's like the kidney's
in-and-out for blood...
were entirely removed.
They're like USB cables. You keep
them intact for an easy reconnect.
Were Mr. Caldwell's heart
and kidney disconnected
for easy reconnect?
Yeah.
Um, other Ripper victims...
Organs and USB cables missing?
It's inconclusive
due to the degree
of mutilation, but yes,
that is how the Ripper rips. Two
different killers, same agenda?
Is the organ harvester
disguising his work
as the crimes of a serial killer,
or is the serial killer disguising
his crimes as the work
of an organ harvester?
The Chesapeake Ripper wants
to perform.
Every brutal choice has...
elegance,
grace.
His mutilations hide
the true nature of his crimes.
(Concerto for Two Violins,
"Largo", by J.S. Bach)
I've been unspeakably rude.
I Haven't offered you a drink.
I appreciate beer
more than wine.
It's not what you appreciate;
It's that you appreciate.
A compromise?
Beer brewed in a wine barrel.
Two years.
I bottled it myself.
(Pop!)
A cabernet sauvignon
wine barrel.
I love your pallet.
I love your beer.
I taste oak.
What else do I taste in there?
I will only answer that
yes or no.
Are you serving this
at your dinner party?
No. This is your reserve.
My own private reserve?
Why, thank you.
I'm curious about something.
Are you purposefully avoiding
the subject of Will Graham?
Absolutely.
Not on my account, I hope.
I'm happy
to get your perspective.
No, it's on Jack Crawford's
account.
I don't want any information
about Will
that I shouldn't have
as his friend.
Did Jack ask you
to profile the Ripper?
Not since I consulted
on the case with Miriam
before she disappeared.
- Crawford's trainee.
- Yeah.
Very sad.
You had me examining
PhD candidates that week.
And I'm grateful you were examining
PhD students and not the Ripper.
You realize those candidates
thought we were having an affair.
Why didn't we?
You were already
having an affair.
Will does that too,
you know.
What?
Have affairs?
Flirtatiously change the subject.
You have that pathology in common.
Or we just have you in common.
I recall even before I met Will,
you never spoke about him.
Probably because
I just want everybody
to leave him alone.
It's not even about Will.
Jack's obsessed with
the Chesapeake Ripper and he's
grooming Will to catch him.
And I sincerely hope he does.
(Opera music)
(Baritone singing in Italian)
They're all missing
different organs.
Before, we were looking at waiting
lists for a heart or a kidney.
Now we're looking at hearts,
kidneys, livers, stomachs,
pancreases, lungs.
This guy,
he's missing a spleen.
A spleen!
Who the hell gets
a spleen transplant?
Intestines were the only organ
missing from this body?
Yes, right, so we're either
looking for someone
with short bowels or...
Ripper's making sausage.
(Piano Sonata No.11,
"Alla Turca", by Mozart)
He's selling
these organs to someone.
We don't even know
if he's transplanting them
within the US. He could be exporting
them to China. The Chinese have a cultural
taboo that restricts voluntary
donation. You gotta die
with all your parts
or you dishonor mommy and daddy.
I mean, you could still kill a guy
for parts. That doesn't break that taboo.
I was agreeing with you.
- Well, I was.
- Your tone was a little...
(Jack): Ok, ok.
(They clear their throats.)
How many killers?
Two.
You confident one of them is
the Chesapeake Ripper?
At least one of them, yep.
Good morning.
Please come in.
I discovered
that we are cheese folk.
I saw you shopping for cheese.
I didn't say hello,
because you were
so uncomfortable the last time
that I did.
This city is very small.
Yes. José's.
José's has the best selection
of artisanal cheeses
in Baltimore, city or county.
(Franklyn chuckles.)
Cheese is my passion.
You ever heard of Tyromancy?
Divination by cheese.
It was my gateway to cheeses.
It was like a magic 8 ball
that you can eat.
Tobias, he, um...
He doesn't eat dairy.
Do you desire Tobias sexually?
No.
God, no. Uh... no.
Not to be defensive.
I just, um...
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I was in a "fraternity".
I-I-I tried things, you know?
Uh, um...
It's just not my brand.
You care deeply about Tobias
despite differences.
He's your best friend,
but you're not his.
Well, it's sad when you say it
like that.
You often worry
about being alone?
I worry about hurting.
Being alone comes with a...
A dull ache.
Doesn't it?
It can.
(Requiem, "Lacrimosa",
by Mozart)
It's better that it's
just the two of us.
(Distant voice):Will?
Dad.
Yes?
There's someone else here.
Will?
I have a 24-hour
cancellation policy.
What time is it?
Nearly nine o'clock.
- Oh, God, I'm sorry.
- No apology necessary.
I must have fallen asleep.
Was I sleepwalking?
Your eyes were open,
but you were not present.
Jeez.
I felt as if I was asleep.
I need to stop sleeping
altogether.
Best way to avoid
bad dreams.
Well, I can see
why you have bad dreams.
What do you see, doctor?
Sum up the Ripper
in so many words?
Choose them wisely.
Oh, I always do.
Words are living things.
They have personality,
point of view,
agenda.
They're pack hunters.
Displaying one's enemy
after death
has its appeal
in many cultures.
These aren't
the Ripper's enemies,
these are pests
he's swatted.
Their reward
for their cruelty.
Oh, he doesn't have a problem
with cruelty.
Their reward is
for undignified behavior.
These dissections are
to disgrace them.
It's... it's
a public shaming.
Takes their organs away
because, in his mind,
they don't deserve them.
In some way.
What's this?
It's Jack Crawford's trainee.
She's not like
the other victims.
The Ripper had no reason
to humiliate Miriam Lass.
Seems to me
he was humiliating someone.
Yeah, he was humiliating Jack.
Did it work?
I'd say it worked really well.
I've been looking for
the kill truck... a van or SUV...
But it was a whole lot easier
than that.
- What am I looking at here?
- One of the hotel security cameras.
- Kill truck?
- It's a private ambulance.
The city works with dozens
of private ambulance companies.
Including this one.
But not as a first responder. A first
responder driving away from the emergency?
Have a seat.
Ambulance would be
a smart place to perform
surgery.
If the cops show up,
blend in and drive away.
Where's Will Graham?
Will. There you are.
And Dr. Lecter.
What a surprise. We have a lead.
Would you care to, uh, help us
catch the Ripper?
How could I refuse?
That ambulance isn't in rotation. It
hasn't even been out of the shed.
Surveillance footage says
it has been.
Well, nobody's signed her out. My road
sheet's got her down for repairs.
And who signed her in
for repairs?
Devon Silvestri. He's one
of our part-time drivers.
- Does he want to be a doctor?
- He's taking the MCATs.
What?
It was there this morning.
Well. Is Mr. Silvestri working
- today?
- He's not on the schedule.
Is there GPS on that ambulance?
- Mm-hmm.
- Encrypted messaging, or remote tracking?
We can't afford that kind of
hardware. We use consumer grade.
- Digital trunk system.
- Yeah.
Jack. If the ambulance radio is on,
I can use a DF sweep to find it.
Good.
This is very educational.
(Classical choral music)
- Show me your hands.
- I can't.
Show me your hands.
He'll die.
Dr. Lecter!
I need you to assess
the situation here, doctor.
He was removing his kidney.
Poorly.
- I can stop the bleeding.
- Do it.
- Have you got it?
- I've got it.
Mr. Silvestri, put your hands
behind your head
and exit the vehicle slowly.
Do it.
On the ground. On your knees.
(Handcuffs clicking)
(Violin Concerto in F Minor,
RV 297, "Largo", by Vivaldi)
I have a butcher who carries
sow's blood.
Centrifugate...
Separate the matter
from the water...
Creates a transparent liquid.
Serve with tomatoes
in suspension
and everybody will
love the sweet taste.
Are you sure you can't stay?
Uh, I don't think
I would be good company.
I disagree.
But before you go,
what became
of Mr. Sylvestri's donor?
You saved his life.
Been a long time since I used a
scalpel on anything but a pencil.
Why'd you stop being a surgeon?
I killed someone...
or, more accurately,
I couldn't save someone.
But it felt like killing them.
You were an emergency room surgeon.
It has to happen from time to time.
It happened one time too many.
I transferred my passion for
anatomy into the culinary arts.
I fix minds instead of bodies,
and no one's died as a result
of my therapy.
(Will chuckles.)
I have to go.
I have a date
with the Chesapeake Ripper.
Or is that rippers?
Devon Silvestri was harvesting organs,
but not with the Ripper.
There's no connection
between them.
Jack must be devastated.
Will: I imagine he is.
Enjoy the wine.
Thank you.
(Applause)
(Symphony No.40,
"Molto Allegro", by Mozart)
Before we begin,
you must all be warned:
nothing here...
is vegetarian.
(Quiet chuckles)
Bon appétit.
==sync, correction by dcdah==
for www.addic7ed.com