(man):This killer doesn't
think like anyone else, Jack.
You'll have to find someone who doesn't
think like anyone else to catch him.
- There's no evidence I did it.
- Let him go.
- You're making a mistake, Jack.
- I know what it's like
to point at a killer
and have no one listen.
You pointed in
the wrong direction.
Don't lie to me, Dr. Lecter.
- I believe my brother won't stop.
- If you really want to kill
your brother, Margot, wait until you can get
away with it or find someone to do it for you.
You're Hannibal
Lecter therapist.
(whispering): I believe you.
(Hannibal): Which answer is it
you want to hear, Will?
What's happening now
and about to happen
is an answer.
I want an admission.
I want you to admit
what you are.
Must I denounce myself
as a monster
while you still refuse to see
the one growing inside you?
(He whistles.)
Why not appeal
to my better nature?
I wasn't aware you had one.
No one can be fully aware
of another human being
unless we love them.
By that love we see potential
in our beloved.
Through that love,
we allow our beloved
to see their potential.
Expressing that love,
our beloved's potential
comes true.
(He whistles.)
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
I promised you a reckoning.
Here it is.
(panting)
Mmm, that smells wonderful.
Sacromonte omelet
with liver and sweetbreads.
Sacromonte was
the gypsy hood of Granada.
I visited Granada
when I was a young man.
- I've never been.
- No?
I fell in love with many things,
in particular, this dish.
I remember my time there
so vividly,
like I frescoed
the walls of my mind.
I used to be afraid
of losing my memory.
What I wouldn't give to forget
a thing or two now.
Mmm...
My compliments
to the gypsy hood of Granada.
Memory gives moments
immortality, but forgetfulness
promotes a healthy mind.
It's good to forget.
What are you trying
to forget, Jack?
Doubt.
I let doubt in.
About me?
About Will.
I can no longer discuss
Will's state of mind with you
or anyone else
without his consent.
Will's officially my patient.
He employs me now, not the FBI.
Well, let's hope
your therapy works.
Therapy only works when
we have a genuine desire
to know ourselves as we are,
not as we would like to be.
(banging)
(roaring)
(man screaming)
(theme music)
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Ah.
(man gasping and sobbing)
Do you have any regrets?
With every choice lies
the possibility of regret.
However, if I choose
not to do something,
it's usually for a good reason.
I'm...
riddled with regrets.
A life without regret
would be no life at all.
I regret what I did
in the stable.
Then, you were lucky
I was there.
Oh, no, no, no.
Being lucky
isn't the same
as making a mistake.
The mistake was allowing you
to stop me.
So, it's not pulling
the trigger that you regret...
...it's not pulling it
effectively.
That would be more accurate.
You must adapt your behaviour
to avoid feeling
the same way again, Will.
Adapt.
Evolve.
Become.
Yes.
I want you to close your eyes.
Imagine a version of events
you wouldn't have regretted.
What did you see?
A missed opportunity...
to feel...
like I felt when I killed
Garret Jacob Hobbs.
To feel like...
...like I felt when I thought
I'd killed you.
And what does that feel like?
I felt...
...a quiet sense...
of...
power.
Good.
Remember that feeling.
I tend to walk out
of this building
in a very similar state.
You must be a patient
of Dr. Lecter's.
I'm sorry?
You look familiar.
I either know you
or I know of you.
I'm the guy who didn't
kill all those people.
We all have a gauge
for humanity that twitches
when we see other people.
Tell me, Margot, what twitches
when you see your brother?
Not my gauge for humanity.
You don't recognize in
your brother basic human traits.
You dehumanize him
as much as he dehumanizes you.
At least, I'll never be
the worst person I know.
The tendency to see others as less
human than ourselves is universal.
My brother is less human.
And you are less human for it.
Did you just dehumanize me?
Psychiatrists
who dehumanize patients
are more comfortable
with painful
but effective treatments.
I met a patient of yours.
Will Graham.
Wonder what sort of painful
but effective treatment
you prescribed him?
What do you imagine?
You're very supportive
of me killing my brother.
And I appreciate that support,
I really do.
But I can only imagine
what you'd be supportive
of Will Graham doing.
What kind of
psychiatrist are you?
You already had my reputation
and bona fides verified.
You know what kind
of psychiatrist I am.
I'm beginning to.
(camera clicking)
Since when the FBI
get involved
in animal attacks, Jack?
When there's somebody
holding the leash
of whatever it is
that's doing the killing.
Esophagus is destroyed. The
bite almost severed his head!
Whatever it was, it's not
afraid of humans. Not anymore.
So I'm thinking
a bear or a wolf.
Wolves or bears don't eat
where they kill.
It'd have dragged him off.
There's no eating here.
We're gonna find everything.
The viscera's exposed,
the belly's laid bare,
but there's no sign
of rutting or gnawing, Jack.
A rabid animal attacks victims at random
and doesn't eat any part of them.
Found the same wound patterns
on a series of
livestock mutilations
in the area. Evisceration,
dismemberment,
yet everything accounted for.
Livestock mutilations...
that was practice?
He's going to kill again.
He's gonna get better at it.
And he's urbanizing his animal,
moving it closer to the city...
adapting it for bigger prey.
And he's not denying
its natural instincts,
he's evolving them.
It's blood sport.
A wolf or a bear?
Oh...
(laughing)
Hey, hey, this is
K-Kevin. Uh,
try not to stare.
They'll... Or they'll
take him away from me.
Oh, sorry.
It's OK.
Bear. Wolf.
Do bears and wolves
hunt together?
Um, I mean, you could
you could train, train a bear
to be a wolf,
or a wolf to be a bear.
Train, train them long enough,
and they will hunt together,
feed together.
Hmm... OK.
En-enough-enough
time, there's,
there's a great deal
I could train even you
to do, Will.
Hm.
That kind of friendship can
keep you on your toes.
Haha!
Animals, they, they do have...
they have friendships
just-just like us.
We're the same.
Yeah, I'll try to remember that.
Please, don't-don't
blame-blame the animals.
- No.
- Don't.
Man is the only creature
that kills to... kill.
(metallic clapping)
(stapling)
(buzzing)
(woman): Oh, God!
(indistinct talking)
(soft music playing)
(woman laughing)
(loud breathing)
(servo-motor sound)
(footsteps)
Argh!
(screaming)
(servo-motor sounds)
(deep breath)
(heartbeat)
(woman laughing)
Kill.
Ah!
(screaming)
It's not an animal.
It's a man who wants
to be an animal.
(Jack sighs.)
Does he believe he's an animal?
It's not what he believes;
it's what he imagines.
(Jack): Well,
what does he want?
He wants to maul.
Nothing personal about this.
He doesn't know them.
He doesn't need to know them.
They're just...
meat to him.
Prey.
This kind of psychosis
doesn't just slip
through the system.
Somewhere, someone
would have noticed this.
If it is psychosis,
he got inside of it somehow,
tamed it,
made a suit out of it.
He's an engineer...
or he understands engineering.
He knows how to build.
He built his beast.
He is a student of predators.
(Hannibal): "No beast
is more savage than man
when possessed with power
answerable to his own rage."
It's not rage.
Rage is an emotional response
to being provoked.
This is something else.
What is it?
Instinct.
- It's the way he thinks.
- The way any animal thinks
depends on limitations
of mind and body.
If we learn
our limitations too soon,
we never learn our power.
His victims are torn apart;
I'd say he learned his power.
He claimed his power.
Can you imagine
tearing someone apart?
Or would you prefer
to use a gun?
Guns lack intimacy.
You set an event in motion
with a gun;
you don't complete it.
You fantasized about killing me
with your hands.
Wouldn't that be more satisfying
than pulling a trigger?
Yes.
When you sent
the man to kill me,
were you imagining
killing me yourself?
Living vicariously
through him as if...
your hands tightened
the noose around my neck?
Or were you simply hiding?
I wasn't hiding from
anything the first time
- I tried to kill you.
- You were hiding...
behind the gun.
You must allow yourself to be
intimate with your instincts, Will.
The closest comparative
bite radius we could match
to the victims' wounds
is a cave bear.
Even the dire wolf,
which is the largest species
of the genus Canis,
is itty-bitty by comparison.
But a cave bear did not do this.
Mostly because
they're vegetarian,
and have been extinct
for 28,000 years.
Mostly because the bite force
relative to the skull size
doesn't match the kind of damage
we've been seeing.
What could?
Pull-ratchets
and pneumatics, maybe.
Pretty sophisticated ingenuity
for any kind of animal,
- man or beast.
- Animals are far more
like humans than
we ever realized.
And humans are far more
like animals.
One thin barrier between us.
And for some,
that barrier is way too thin.
Hello, Dr. Lecter.
How does something
like this present?
Someone affected by this kind
of species dysphoria
typically has other conditions.
Mood disorders,
clinical depression,
- schizophrenia.
- Typically?
They may not present at all.
Your killer could have
built a bridge between
who he appears to be and
what he now knows he's become.
He didn't build
a bridge, Doctor...
he built a suit.
What he seeks is transformation.
Have you ever seen
anything like this before?
This threatens
to be a violation of
doctor-patient confidentiality,
so I will thread carefully.
You've seen something like this?
Years ago, I treated a patient
who fits the profile.
A teenage boy who suffered
from what I would describe
as an identity disorder.
This boy fancied
himself a beast?
During our therapy,
he reported a moment of clarity.
He understood in that moment,
he was an animal
born in the body of a man.
He kept a solitary life.
He would hide and behave in ways
resembling animal behaviour.
- He was delusional.
- Not necessarily.
He didn't believe metamorphosis
could physically take place,
but that wouldn't stop him
from trying to achieve it.
He'd be a grown man now?
And as he grew
in wisdom and confidence,
he would no longer feel he had
to meet his needs in hiding.
What are his needs,
Dr. Lecter?
Savagery.
(footsteps)
Museum's closed.
Hello, Randall.
Dr. Lecter.
You will always be ruled
by your fascination with teeth.
That's what you said to me
when they brought in your office
the very first time.
Is that what I said?
Yeah.
I was crying.
I was dreading telling you
what was wrong with me and...
you made it easier.
Other visits too.
A therapist's life is equal
parts counsel and curiosity.
We set a patient on a path,
but are left to wonder
where that path
will take them.
You've come
so very far, Randall.
A long time
since you treated me.
Which is why I wanted
to talk to you
about your wonderful progress,
just for a moment, privately.
I've seen what you've done.
What have I done?
You bore screams...
like a sculptor bears dust
from the beaten stone.
That crying boy doesn't
cling to you anymore.
What clings to you now?
What clings to your teeth?
Ragged bits of scalp...
...trailing their tails of hair
like comets.
Beautiful.
They are looking for you.
I don't think I can stop.
I don't want you to.
But they will find you, Randall.
When they do,
it's important you do
exactly what I say.
You wanted to speak to me?
Ah, Randall Tier.
Special Agent Jack
Crawford with the FBI.
This is Will Graham.
Uh... did you...
put all that together?
- Yes, I did.
- Nice work.
What is that?
That is a cave bear.
You put together
a lot of cave bears, do you?
Yeah. I put them together, take them
apart, put them back together again.
You understand their mechanics
and how they're engineered?
We understand a lot about
cave bears. Their fossils
have been found in the tens of thousands,
all over southern Europe. Very common.
The reason I ask is because a...
a cave bear skull
was used recently
as a murder weapon.
Prehistoric jaws and claws
are designed to do
what they do best.
The victims were torn apart.
Used the right tool for the job.
Well, look inside the skull
and you'll find what the job is.
You have a history of trouble
with things inside your head.
Isn't that right, Mr. Tier?
Is that what this is about?
You think I killed
someone with a fossil?
I had an identity disorder.
The doctors told me
the internal map
of my body didn't match reality.
Do you know what it's like
when the skin you're wearing
doesn't fit?
- I can imagine.
- I know who I am now.
And I'm doing much better.
I'm socializing.
I take my medication.
I'm employed. And I work
very hard.
And I'm proof that
mental illness is treatable.
(dogs barking)
Shh, shh.
(dogs stop barking)
Hi.
I don't know if you remember me,
but I met you outside
of Dr. Lecter's office.
I remember it.
How did you find me?
Well, as it turns out,
you are famous.
Uh...
You're not exactly anonymous
yourself, Margot.
Did you, uh, sneak a peek
inside Dr. Lecter's calendar?
Yeah, it is exactly what I did.
It's cold.
Do you have any whiskey?
What is the heir to the Verger
Meat Packing dynasty
doing at my door?
Oh, my brother is the heir,
not me.
I have the wrong parts and
the wrong proclivity for parts.
You didn't answer my question.
Came for a character reference.
Patient to patient.
What do you think
of Dr. Lecter's therapy?
It depends what
you're in therapy for.
Oh, I'm in therapy
for all kinds of reasons.
The Vergers slaughter
86,000 cattle a day
and 36,000 pigs,
depending on the season,
but that's just
the public carnage.
What's your private carnage?
I tried to kill my brother.
Well, I assume he had it coming.
Did he ever.
What's your private carnage?
I tried to murder Dr. Lecter.
Did he have it coming?
What do you think?
I can't say that I know.
Neither can I.
We have some
very similar issues.
Although I doubt
that Dr. Lecter
gave you the same advice
on murder that he gave me.
And what's that?
He said...
"If at first you don't succeed,
try, try again."
I'm curious what would happen
if your patients started
comparing notes, Dr. Lecter.
What would Randall Tier
have to say to me?
What did Randall Tier
say to you?
He said he was much better now,
that mental illness
was treatable.
Randall Tier is a success story.
You believe he's innocent?
I believe...
your therapy was successful.
You can be persuasive.
How many have there been?
Like Randall Tier?
Like me?
Every patient is unique.
Your psychiatrist came
to visit me
at the hospital before my trial.
Dr. Du Maurier.
She told me she believed me.
She knew there were
others like me.
Fascinating.
Did you kill her?
No.
What do you think about
when you think about killing?
I think about God.
Good and evil?
Good and evil has
nothing to do with God.
I collect church collapses.
Did you see the recent one
in Sicily?
The facade fell
on 65 grandmothers
during a special mass.
Was that evil? Was that God?
If he's up there,
he just loves it.
Typhoid and swans,
it all comes
from the same place.
Does Randall Tier
believe in God?
Perhaps you should have
a more personal conversation
with Mr. Tier
and ask him what he believes.
The solitude of what you do
is to be respected,
and I intend to honour that.
I've only come to offer
words of encouragement.
You are becoming, Randall,
and this beast
is your higher self.
Your bodies, voices,
and wills are one.
Revel in what you are.
(dogs barking)
(dog yelping)
Hey!
(dog barking)
Buster! Buster!
(dogs barking)
(dog whimpering)
Oh, shh, shh.
(branch cracking)
(dogs barking)
(Will panting)
(dog yelping)
He I'd say this makes us even.
I sent someone to kill you...
you sent someone to kill me.
Even Steven.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player