- Previously on Hannibal...
- Who stitched him into the mural?
- You have an idea who that might be?
- I do.
He consults me with cases if I keep
investigating murders he's accused of.
Good. It seems
you have an admirer.
You think someone sent me
in here because they admire me?
This killer wrote you a poem.
This is of course Freddie
Lounds, who you know.
She will be assisting me today,
or assisting you--
- What have you taken, Bella?
- My morphine.
- Have you seen Jack? - No. There was
some sort of emergency with his wife.
If Hannibal's the ripper, what's
he doing with his trophies?
Stay away from Hannibal Lecter.
(gunshot)
♪
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
You have to eat something,
Jack. You've been up all night.
Feed the body, feed the mind.
She knew she couldn't
beat the cancer, so she...
decided to beat it
to the finish line.
I suppose I can't blame her for
wanting to control how she dies.
I believe those who
can no longer function
at an acceptable level
have the right to die.
She cast you as an executioner.
She wanted to die.
I can't tell you how grateful I am
that you didn't allow it to happen.
As a doctor, I had no choice.
As a philosopher,
I had too many.
It wasn't what I could do for Bella, it
was what I couldn't do to you, Jack.
I guess I'm a better friend
than therapist.
You're a great friend,
Hannibal.
(trickling sound)
Send someone else, Jack.
She's one of yours.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
At aproximately 9AM this morning I've
received a phone call from Freddie Lounds.
Acting on an anonymous tip,
she discovered a female body,
immediately contacted my office.
I was amongst the first
on the scene.
The victim has been identified
as our colleague,
Special Agent Beverly Katz.
She will be memorialized
at FBI Headquarters and Field Offices
so that her ultimate sacrifice
will always be remembered.
That's all.
(trickling sound)
(inaudible)
I want to see her.
Leave us alone.
Let's go!
You said you just
interpret the evidence.
So interpret the evidence.
(yelping)
I strangle Beverly Katz...
...looking in her eyes.
She knows me.
And I know her.
I expertly squeeze
the life from her...
...rendering her unconscious.
I freeze her body...
...preserving shape and form
so I can more cleanly
dismantle her.
She cuts like stone.
I pull her apart,
layer by layer...
...like she would a crime scene.
This is my design.
I will leave
no usable evidence,
but she found something.
She found me.
What she found is already gone.
What did I take from her?
It's the Chesapeake Ripper.
It's the Ripper
and the Copycat.
It's the same killer.
Two masks...
Beverly helped me see it.
Help me see it.
She was looking
for a connection between
the Copycat and the Ripper.
You think she found it?
She found something.
Where were you last night?
In the hospital.
With my wife.
I told Beverly
to go to you,
tell you everything she knew.
Instead, she went
looking for evidence.
She met the Ripper
last night, Jack.
She...
she will be...
missing organs.
He had to take his trophies.
Who is he, Will?
Beverly made her
connection to the Ripper.
You have to make
your own, Jack.
Then what did I
bring you here for?
To say goodbye.
Would you like to talk
about what happened at the observatory?
You discussed my therapy
with Hannibal Lecter, Frederick.
Counter to our agreement.
I gave him a peek before
I snatched down the shades.
I have appearances to maintain.
Beverly Katz paid you a visit
before she was murdered.
- What did the two of you discuss?
- What, you weren't listening to that one?
You met her in
the privacy room.
It is the only room in the facility I
am not legally allowed to monitor.
And you let that stop you?
We talked about
the Chesapeake Ripper.
Then she went and found him.
Psychopaths can be indifferent
to those sorts of setbacks.
I know something of the monster
you are dealing with.
He is a well-educated man.
A socially competent man.
He has surgical experience or,
at the very least, know-how.
You thought Abel Gideon
was the Chesapeake Ripper.
Evidently, I was
wrong about that.
- Gideon knows who the Ripper is.
- And I suppose you do, too.
Wouldn't it be interesting if we
both said it was the same man?
Yes, it would.
It's a shame we can't
talk to Abel Gideon
about the Chesapeake Ripper.
Well, just think, Frederick,
you could be the one
who catches him after all.
Beverly isn't
your responsibility.
You should be allowed to grieve. You
shouldn't have to wade through it.
We're not running away
from this, Jack.
Beverly wouldn't.
Good.
I double-checked
the autopsy report.
What you found at that
observatory wasn't all Beverly.
What do you mean?
These kidneys, they were
placed inside her body
after she was killed. I typed
them against DNA samples
and, uh, they belong to the
Mural Killer. James Gray. - James Gray.
So, whoever killed
James Gray and sewed him
into his mural also murdered Beverly.
Swapped out their kidneys.
Right now, the only thing
we have to go on
is we find her kidneys
and we find her killer.
♪
Mr. Graham.
You always did look
like the boy next door.
Is it true you ate
that poor Hobbs girl?
You can call me Will,
now we're of equal
social standing.
Is this Frederick's
idea of punishment?
Group therapy with the man
who tried to kill me.
No. I'd like to talk to you
about the Chesapeake Ripper.
- Thought I was the Chesapeake Ripper.
- No,
you are the pretender
to the throne.
What did you offer Frederick
to bring me back?
I'm the last person
he wants to see.
I give him a visceral
chill in the guts.
Whatever's left of them. - You know who
the Chesapeake Ripper is. You've met him.
So Frederick gets to catch
the Ripper after all.
What do you get?
I remember that night
at Dr. Lecter's.
- The night I brought you there.
- The night you tried to kill me.
Yes, how do you think
I found you?
He sent me to kill you, Abel.
Am I your evidence?
Oh, you're in trouble,
Mr. Graham.
Why would you protect him?
You were quite happy to try
and kill me yourself.
You have it "in you,"
as they say.
He is the Devil,
Mr. Graham.
He is smoke.
You'll never
"catch" the Ripper.
He won't be caught.
If you want him...
...you will have
to kill him.
Fair enough.
You and I are both proponents
of unorthodox treatments of the mind.
Strategies others might not
choose to understand.
What I'm trying to understand
is why you would transfer Abel
Gideon back to your hospital
for the unworried unwell.
It was not for selfish reasons.
Ah, selfishness.
The original sin of man,
according to Judeo-
Christian morality.
We are not talking about
morality or ethics here,
are we, Dr. Lecter? But rather,
concealing their absence.
Gideon disemboweled you,
Frederick.
Brave of you, or perhaps wise,
to keep the evidence
of your misdeeds
- under your own roof.
- My misdeeds and yours.
Neither of us
controls our stories well enough
to get anything from exposing
the other's misdeeds.
Here's to that.
I brought Gideon back because...
I thought he may be useful
in Will Graham's therapy.
He shot Gideon, yet
he has no memory of it.
We know memories, emotions,
and even spiritual experiences
can be manipulated
while under hypnotics.
I'm trying to set Will on the path
to rebuilding his broken brain,
picking up your pieces,
as it were.
You've analyzed my patient;
perhaps you'll allow me
to analyze yours.
I'd like to interview
Abel Gideon.
You don't need
to stand way over there.
I'm a cutter, not a pisser.
Hello, Dr. Gideon.
Our brains devote more space
to reading the details of faces
than any other object.
Dare I say,
I've never seen yours before.
I'm Dr. Hannibal Lecter.
I was Will Graham's
psychiatrist.
Well, he's not
a very good advertisement
for your abilities,
Dr. Lecter.
That remains to be seen.
Oh,
I bet you're a devil
at the bridge table.
- It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance.
- The pleasure's mine.
[But now I know your name,]
[of course I am aware
of you by reputation]
[and I see why Chilton]
[both reveres you
and resents you.]
Esteem in psychiatric circles
still eludes him,
yet it clings to you
like soap to a baby's eyes.
He very much wants to be you.
He should be more careful
what he wishes for.
And you should have been
more careful with Will Graham.
That young man
has got a bone to pick.
As a therapist, I'm
concerned with finding ways
of overcoming resistance.
Not building it up.
Well, you built up something,
Dr. Lecter.
(birds chirping)
(camera shutter clicking)
That was rude, Miss Lounds.
Did you really think I was
above that sort of thing?
Hm... you seem
- disappointed.
- We evolved
the ability to communicate
disappointment to teach those around us
good manners.
Unfortunately, I did not evolve
the ability to feel shame.
You should explore
that in therapy.
I saw a psychiatrist once and
it was under false pretenses.
Happy to entertain you for
a more genuine conversation.
So, what brings you
to the Baltimore State Hospital
for the Criminally Insane?
I am interviewing Will Graham.
At his request.
Imagine that.
I'm trying.
Do not pass anything but soft
paper. No pens, no pencils.
Do not accept anything he gives
you. Do not let him touch you.
You do not touch him.
- I will be right outside.
- I know the drill.
It's good to see you again,
Will. Let me rephrase that.
It is good to see you in here.
Where you belong.
Thank you for coming.
- Why am I here?
- I have an admirer.
And he seems to fit
your demographic.
My demographic
is murderers and people
obsessed with murderers.
I'm talking about the man who killed
the bailiff and the judge at my trial.
Ah.
And you think he's your admirer?
He killed the bailiff
to give me an alibi.
He killed the judge
because he threw that alibi out.
So is your admirer crazy?
I don't think anybody
as careful as he is
could be crazy.
I think-I think he's different.
Maybe a lot of people
believe him to be crazy,
and the reason for that is, he
hasn't let people understand much
- about him.
- But you understand him.
Are you trying to catch him
or contact him?
I would like to establish
a line of communication.
And your website
seems like a good place
to do that.
I could open it up for you.
Ads, editorial,
online chat rooms, monitoring
incoming mail. I could be discreet.
In exchange for?
Exclusive rights to your story.
It's all yours, Freddie.
You want to talk
to your admirer,
we'll have to send
an invitation.
"Sadly, other killers have drawn
inspiration from Graham.
"As he stood trial for his life,
"one such killer
even constructed an ode
"to Graham's grisly techniques.
"Graham believed this man
wanted to help,
"even though his motives
for that are unclear.
"He killed people in his name,
and he'd like to ask him why."
Would you like
a book, Mr. Graham?
I have my imagination.
I read your TattleCrime
interview.
You're a very articulate man.
I agreed with a lot
of what you said.
You're right.
People don't understand much
about me.
Or about you.
But at least
we understand each other.
There's something
we don't have.
Or maybe we just
evolved not to need.
You were hiding in the FBI.
That's talent.
If you hadn't gotten sick,
they never would've found you.
You found a great
place to hide.
Spend time in
a mental hospital,
you pick up the drill.
You could pass as an orderly,
get a job doing it
when you get out.
They may never
know you were in.
Obviously you realize
Chilton records
every word said in here.
Who do you think
wired the mics?
- Or unwired the mics, as they currently are.
- You killed the bailiff
- during my trial.
- I thought it would exonerate you.
I had read your file
often enough.
Easy to recreate your work.
It was so specific.
Though the bailiff was a bitch
to get on that stag's head.
And the judge?
I killed the bailiff.
The judge was...
somebody else.
(keys jingling)
Why are you trying to help me?
Have you seen the way
that smaller birds
will mob a hawk on a wire?
You and me, we are
hawks, Mr. Graham.
Hawks are solitary.
And that's their weakness.
Enough of those smaller birds get
together, and they chase hawks away.
Imagine if the hawks
started working together.
Why did you want to talk to me?
(door unlocking)
I need a favor.
I'm always happy to do
a favor for a friend.
Just say the words.
I want you to kill
Hannibal Lecter.
Will?
Hi.
I'm sorry to drop in
unannounced like this.
- What's on your mind, Dr. Bloom?
- You.
You gave an interview
to Freddie Lounds.
You despise Freddie Lounds.
It just seemed, um...
What, suspicious?
And slightly worrying.
You don't have
to worry about me.
I know you feel powerless
about what happened to Beverly,
and you want to do
something about it.
Would that be so bad?
Depends on what you're
thinking about doing.
But there's no solution
to grief, Will. It just is.
Beverly died because of me.
Because she listened to me.
I'm not gonna let that
happen again.
Will, what have you done?
Just what I had to do.
What is it about you,
Dr. Bloom?
The most sinister
neurochemistry in the field
cannot help percolating
in your presence.
The interesting ones
all fall at your feet.
Will Graham, Abel Gideon,
they're chatty as can be.
You are like
catnip for killers.
I see Abel Gideon
has returned to the roost.
I believe you and I are his
only surviving psychiatrists.
Pulled the tongues
out of all the rest.
Pulled more than
that out of you.
Have you noticed anything
different about Will
- since Gideon arrived?
- Gideon is here
as part of Will's therapy,
helping him reclaim his past.
Can I see him?
Dr. Bloom--
You are like a flower
blossoming amongst the weeds.
I'm glad to see you
alive, Dr. Gideon.
Well, Mr. Graham didn't do
a particularly good job
of killing me. He was sick.
- And a very poor shot.
- Good enough shot
to get a bullet in you
before you put a blade in me.
And for that,
I am sincerely grateful.
Been wondering
about that night.
How do you know where I live?
A little birdie
wanted me to kill you.
Or a little birdie
wanted Mr. Graham
to have reason to kill me.
But either way,
you and I are equally
expendable.
You were trying to find
the Ripper that night.
- Did you?
- I found Will Graham.
Will isn't
the Chesapeake Ripper.
Not yet.
All the things
that make us who we are...
What has to happen
to make those things change?
So much has happened
to Mr. Graham.
He is a changed man.
Maybe he's looking
for redemption.
But revenge,
now that is a trinket
he could value.
He thinks that he knows
who killed Beverly Katz?
For the courtesy
you have always shown me,
I am going to give you a gift.
I'm going to give you a chance
to save Will from himself.
How?
He is in a biblical
place right now,
but that rage will pass.
And when it does,
Will Graham will either be
a murderer or he will not.
Up to you.
He's institutionalized.
He's really
in no position to be
killing anyone.
Not with his own hands.
But if he only had
a little birdie
who could whisper murder
into a sympathetic ear...
Who does he want
to kill, doctor?
He's not here.
There's nothing
in his calendar.
What is it you think Will's done?
(phone ringing)
Hold that thought.
This is Jack Crawford.
Yes. Thank you.
We've got a trace
on his cell phone.
Judas had the decency
to hang himself in shame
at his betrayal.
But I thought
you needed help.
Did you know that the phrase
"to kick the bucket" came
from exactly this situation? You could kick it
out right now yourself and it'd all be over.
Quicker than bleeding out.
You're a nurse at the hospital.
You're setting a new
standard of care.
Will Graham is not
what you think.
He's not a murderer.
He is now.
By proxy.
(grunting)
He asked you to do this?
What are friends for?
Now I'm going to ask you
a few yes or no questions
while you still have enough blood
coursing through your brain
to answer them. You ready?
Ready.
Did you kill that judge?
I can ask you
yes-or-no questions,
you don't have to say a word,
and I'll know
what the answer is.
The pupil dilates
with specific mental efforts.
You dilate, that's a "yes."
No dilation equals "no."
Are you the Chesapeake Ripper?
How many times have you watched
someone cling on to a life
that's not really worth living?
Eking out a few extra seconds.
Wondering why they bother.
I know why.
Life is precious.
The Chesapeake Ripper.
I wonder what
they're gonna call me.
You know, the Iroquois
used to eat their enemies
to take their strength.
Maybe your murders
will become my murders.
I'll be the Chesapeake
Ripper now.
Only if you eat me.
(laughing)
Put your hands
where I can see them.
He's got a gun, Jack!
Hold on!
Hold on, hold on.
Get an ambulance!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player