Previously in Hannibal...
- He's some kind of special consultant for the FBI.
- I asked you to get close
To the Hobbs thing. I need to
know you didn't get too close.
- What you need is a way out
of dark places when jack sends you there.
- Last time he sent me
into a dark place,
I brought something back.
- A surrogate daughter?
- Abigail Hobbs is a suspect?
- She would make the ideal bait.
Wouldn't she?
- Just a second. Dad?
It's for you.
- Hello?
- They know.
- Be patient.
Wait for your shot.
(gunshot)
(soft thud)
Ready?
And three, two, one.
Go.
- She was so pretty.
- She is so pretty.
- Aren't deer are supposed to be
Complex emotional creatures?
- Yeah.
- I read they're like the equivalent
of a four-year-old human being.
- They're smarter
than a four-year-old.
- And they care
about each other.
They care
about their environment.
They tread lightly
through the underbrush
Because they don't want
to hurt the plants.
- They're a lot like us.
And we're gonna honor
every part of her.
Her hide is gonna
make a beautiful rug.
Her leg bones we can
carve into knives.
None of her is gonna
go to waste.
Just like we talked about.
Start at the sternum.
Keep the blade pointed up.
Damage the organs,
you ruin the meat.
- I don't know how I'm gonna
feel about eating her after all this.
- Eating her is honoring her.
Otherwise,
it's... It's just...
Murder.
Ok.
Nice and easy.
Big breath.
Good.
(monitors beeping)
(muffled whimpering
and coughing)
(dog barking)
- Morning.
- Didn't hear you drive up.
- Hybrid.
Great car for stalking.
- Um,
I'm compelled
to go cover myself.
- I have brothers.
- Well, I'll put a robe on
Just the same.
You want a cup of coffee?
And more immediately,
why are you here?
- Yes, and Abigail Hobbs
woke up.
- Well, you know how
to bury the lede.
- You want me to get you
a cup of coffee?
- No. I want to get my coat.
- Let's have a cup of coffee.
(ringing)
(cell phone vibrating)
- Is he gonna keep calling?
- Jack wants you
to go see her.
- And you don't.
- Eventually.
Jack thinks Abigail was
An accomplice
to her father's crimes.
I don't want to get
in the middle of you and jack,
But if I can be helpful
to you as a buffer--
- I--I like you as a buffer.
I also like the fact
that you rattle jack.
He respects you far too much
to yell at you,
No matter how much
he wants to.
- And I take advantage
of that.
- Abigail Hobbs
doesn't have anyone.
- You can't be
her everyone.
When I said what I was going
to say in my head,
It sounded really insulting,
so I'm going to find
Another way to say it.
- Say it the insulting way.
- Dogs keep a promise
a person can't.
- I'm not collecting
another stray.
- The first person Abigail
talks to about what happened
Can't be anyone who
was there when it happened.
So that means
no dr. Lecter either.
- Yeah, much less the guy
who killed dad.
Jack's wrong
about Abigail.
- Let me reach out to her
my own way.
Hi.
I'm alana bloom.
- Are you a doctor?
- Not medicine.
I'm a psychiatrist.
- What do you specialize in?
- Among other things,
Family trauma.
- I asked the nurses
if my parents were dead,
And they wouldn't tell me.
Said I had to wait for you.
- I'm sorry
you had to wait.
- I know they're dead.
Who buried them?
- They haven't been buried.
- Don't you think
they should be?
- Your mother was cremated
per the instructions in her living will.
(she clears her throat.)
- my dad?
- Your father is
more complicated.
- Because he was crazy?
- The nurses said
you didn't remember.
- I remember. I just didn't want
to talk to them about it.
I want to sell the house.
I guess it's mine now.
I can use the money for college,
get an apartment.
What are all those?
- I brought you some clothes.
Thought a change might
feel good.
I guessed your size,
so anything you don't want,
Leave the tags on,
I'll bring it back.
And I brought you
some music too.
- Your music?
- If there isn't
anything you like,
I've got a stack
of itunes gift cards.
I--I've got a stack
of gift cards.
I don't... Do well
redeeming gift cards.
- Probably says something
about you.
- Probably does.
- I got seven families waiting.
No, let me rephrase: Demanding that we find
whatever's left of their daughters.
Abigail Hobbs may be the only
person who knows the truth.
- You can't ask her
right now, jack.
We have to create a safe place
for her first
Or you won't get any answers.
- I respect your sympathy
For her, dr. Bloom. I hope one day
you'll appreciate my lack of it.
- You really think Abigail Hobbs
helped her father kill those girls?
- I think it's a possibility
that needs to be ruled out.
If Abigail didn't help her
father, maybe she knows who did.
- How was she
when you saw her?
- Surprisingly practical.
- Suspiciously practical?
- I would suggest
She can be practical
without being a murderer.
- I think she's
hiding something.
- It may simply be her trauma.
- Yeah, it could also be more.
She has a penchant
for manipulation;
Withheld information
to gain information;
She demonstrated only
enough emotions
To prove she had them. - You're beginning
to appreciate my lack of sympathy?
- You said it may be more
than trauma, yet you question
Her involvement in the murders
her father committed?
- What I'm questioning
is her state of mind.
- I want will graham
to talk to her.
- Jack. Not yet.
- You are not will graham's
psychiatrist, dr. Bloom.
Dr. Lecter is.
- Garrett Jacob Hobbs--
The, uh, minnesota shrike,
abducted and murdered
Eight girls
over an eight-month period.
Each of them had the same
hair color, same eye color,
Same age, same height,
same weight
As his daughter Abigail.
There was a ninth victim
Who also fit
Abigail Hobbs's profile,
But Garrett Jacob Hobbs
didn't murder her.
The killer who did
wanted us to know
He wasn't the minnesota shrike.
He was better
than that.
He is an intelligent psychopath.
He is a sadist.
He will never kill
like this again.
So how do we catch him?
- Giving a lecture
on Hobbs's copycat?
- Well, we need every good mind
we can get on this.
- This copycat is
an avid reader
Of Freddie Lounds
and tattlecrime.com.
He had intimate knowledge
Of Garrett Jacob Hobbs's
murders, motives, patterns--
Enough to recreate them
and, arguably,
Elevate them to art.
How intimately did he know
Garrett Jacob Hobbs?
Did he appreciate him
From afar, or did he engage him?
Did he ingratiate himself
into Hobbs's life?
Did Hobbs know
his copycat
As he was known?
Before Garrett Jacob Hobbs
murdered his wife
And attempted to do
the same to his daughter,
He received an untraceable call.
I believe
The as-yet
unidentified caller
Was our copycat killer.
- So you're not a doctor,
A nurse, or a psychiatrist.
- I'm a journalist.
I want to tell the truth.
Your truth.
Sometimes that involves
some deception,
But know this:
I will never lie to you.
- Sounds like something
a liar would say.
- If you tell me what you know,
I can help you
fill in the blanks.
- How about you tell me
what you know.
- Your dad was
the minnesota shrike.
Your mother wasn't the first
person your father killed.
He killed
eight girls.
Eight girls that looked--
- Just like me.
- Yes.
- Why do they call him
the shrike?
- It's a bird that
impales its prey,
Harvests the organs
to eat later.
He was very sick.
- Does that mean I'm sick too?
- You'll be fighting
that perception.
Perception is
the most important thing
In your life right now.
- I don't care what anybody thinks.
- You'd better
start caring, Abigail.
What you remember,
what you tell everyone,
Is going to define
the rest of your life.
Let me help you.
- How did they catch him?
- A man named will graham.
Works for the fbi but isn't fbi.
He catches insane men
because he can think like them.
Because he is insane.
- Would you excuse us, please?
I'm special agent Will Graham.
- By special agent he means not really an agent.
He didn't get past
the screening process.
Too unstable.
- I really must insist you leave the room.
- If you want to talk--
- Abigail,
This is dr. Lecter.
Do you remember us?
- I remember you.
You killed my dad.
- You've been in bed
for days, Abigail.
Why don't we
have a walk?
- I'm sorry we couldn't
save your mother.
We did everything we could
but she was already gone. - I know.
I saw him kill her.
He was loving right up
until the second he wasn't.
Kept telling me
he was sorry,
To just hold still.
He was gonna
make it all go away.
- There was plenty wrong
with your father, Abigail,
But there's nothing
wrong with you.
You say he was loving.
I believe it.
That's what you
brought out in him.
- It's not all
I brought out in him.
I'm gonna be messed up.
Aren't I?
I'm worried about nightmares.
- We'll help you
with the nightmares.
- There's no such thing
As getting used
to what you experienced.
It bothers me
a lot.
I worry about nightmares too.
- So killing somebody,
Even if you have to do it,
It feels that bad?
- It's the ugliest thing
in the world.
- I wanna go home.
- Special agent Graham.
I never formally
introduced myself.
I'm freddie lounds. - Are you trying to
salvage this joke from the mouth of madness?
- Please. Let me apologize
for my behavior in there.
It was sloppy and misguided
And hurtful.
- Miss Lounds.
Now is not the time.
- Look, you and I may have
our own reasons for being here,
But I also think we both
genuinely care about what happens
To Abigail Hobbs.
- You told her I was insane.
- I can undo that.
- You help Abigail see me as
more than her father's killer,
And I help you
With online ad sales?
- I can undo what I said.
I can also make it a lot worse.
- Miss Lounds...
It's not very smart
to piss off a guy
Who thinks about
killing people for a living.
- "it isn't very smart
to piss off a guy
Who thinks about killing
people for a living."
You know what else
isn't very smart?
You were there with him.
And you let those words
come out of his mouth.
- I trust will to speak
for himself.
- Evidently
you shouldn't.
- I'm just happy the story
wasn't about Abigail Hobbs.
- Well, then it's a victory.
(sighing)
So, Abigail Hobbs
wants to go home.
Let's take her home.
- What Abigail wants
and what she needs
Are different things. Taking her out
of a controlled environment would be reckless.
- You said she was practical.
- That could just mean
She has a dissociative disorder.
- You take her home,
She may experience intense
emotions, respond aggressively,
Or re-enact some aspect of the
traumatic event without even realizing it.
- Where do you weigh in
on this, doctor?
- Dr. Bloom is right.
But there is a scenario where revisiting
the trauma event could help Abigail heal
And actually
prevent denial.
- Then we have a difference
of opinion. Therefore,
I am going to choose
the opinion
That best serves
my agenda.
I need to know
If you're right about the copycat, will.
- We have no way
Of knowing what's waiting
for her when she goes home.
- Thanks again
for meeting with me.
I know this hasn't
been easy for you.
- Oh yeah? How
would you know?
- I've been writing
about Garrett Jacob Hobbs.
I've spoken to the relatives
of some of his other victims.
- Hobbs is dead.
He deserved a lot worse.
Him and his whole family.
- There must be some
small comfort knowing
That justice was served.
- Comfort?
My sister was impaled on a severed
stag head, cut down the middle.
He pulled out her lungs
while she was still breathing.
There's no comfort in that.
- I'm sorry. I am.
But you have to try not
to remember her that way.
- What do you
want from me?
- I just thought
you should know Abigail Hobbs
Came out of her coma.
- Is this where my mom died?
- Yes.
- I was sort of expecting
a body outline in chalk or tape.
- They only do that
if you're still alive
and taken to the hospital before
they finish the crime scene.
- Goodbye, mom.
- If you ever wanna go,
You just have to say so and we'll go.
- Go where?
The hospital?
- For now.
- Who turned all
the pictures around?
- Crime scene cleaners
will do that.
- They did a really good job.
Is that where all my blood was?
- Yes.
- You do this a lot?
Go places and think
about killing?
- Too often.
- So you pretended to be my dad.
- And people
like your dad.
- What did it feel like?
To be him?
- It feels... Like...
I'm talking to his shadow
suspended on dust.
- No wonder you have nightmares.
- The attacks on you
and your mother
Were different.
They were desperate.
Your dad knew he was
out of time. Somebody
Told him we were coming.
- The man on the phone?
- It was a blocked call.
Did you recognize his voice?
- I had never heard it before.
- Was there anybody new
in your father's life?
Someone you met or
someone he talked about?
- Abigail, he may
have been contacted
By another killer.
A copycat.
- Someone who's still out there?
- Yeah.
- Can you catch
somebody who's crazy?
- Folie a deux.
- What?
- It's a french
psychiatric term.
Madness shared by two.
- See?
- One cannot be delusional
If the belief in question is
accepted as ordinary
By others in that person's
culture or subculture.
Or family.
- My dad didn't seem delusional.
He was a perfectionist.
- Your dad left
hardly any evidence.
- Is that why
you let me come home?
To find evidence?
- It was one of many
considerations.
- Are we gonna
re-enact the crime?
You be my dad, you be my mom,
And you be the man
on the phone.
- Abigail, we wanted you
to come home
To help you leave
home behind.
- You're not gonna find
any of those girls, you know.
- What makes you say that?
- He would honor every part of them.
He used to make
Plumbing putty out of elk's bones.
Whatever bones are left
Of those girls are probably
holding pipes together.
- Where did he make this putty?
- At the cabin.
I can show you tomorrow.
- Abigail, there's
someone here.
- Hey, Abigail.
So, uh, does that hurt?
- Sometimes.
- Everybody on the block
was on the news.
And everyone at school.
Such whores.
- Did you talk to the news?
- No. No!
My mom doesn't want me talking
to you, much less the news.
- Since when do you
listen to her?
- Well, clearly I don't.
I'm talking to you right now.
Everybody thinks
you did it, you know?
- Do you think I did it?
- I don't think
you're the type.
Then again, I didn't
think your father
Was the murder-suicide type.
Although I guess the hunting
could have been a clue.
- Mine or his?
- Both, now that
you mention it.
I don't think
you did it.
- I do.
- This is private property.
- You were the bait, right?
That's how it worked? You lure
them back to daddy for dinner?
How'd you trap
my sister?
Did you chat her up?
- Hey! Piss off!
- Did you help your old man
cut out my sister's lungs
While she was still using--
(spitting)
- He said he was
somebody's brother.
- Marissa! Come home.
- No...
- Come home!
- Can you stop being
such a bitch?
See you later.
- Bye.
- He's gone.
You've never
seen him before?
- No.
- Let's get back to the hotel.
We'll go to the cabin tomorrow.
- We should
report this, yes?
- Yes.
I'm sorry, okay?
This will all stop.
Please. I'm gonna
make it all go away.
(alarm beeping)
- He cleaned everything.
He said he was
afraid of germs,
But I guess he was just afraid
of getting caught.
- No one else ever came
here with your dad...
Except you.
- He made everything
by himself.
Glue, butter...
He sold the pelts
on ebay or in town.
He made pillows.
No parts went to waste.
Otherwise it was murder.
He was feeding them to us.
Wasn't he?
- It's very likely.
- Before
he cut my throat,
He told me he killed those girls
so he wouldn't have to kill me.
- You're not responsible for
anything your father did, Abigail.
- If he would've just killed me,
None of those other girls
would be dead.
- We don't know that.
Your father--
- I need ert at the Hobbs cabin.
- Abigail--
(screaming)
- Do you think she knew the guy
down by the stream? - Somebody's brother.
- Not somebody.
Abigail said he asked
if she helped her dad
Take his sister's lungs
while she was alive.
- The young woman
on the stag head.
- Cassie boyle.
Had a brother,
nicholas.
But Garrett Jacob Hobbs
didn't kill
Cassie Boyle.
- I know.
Garrett Jacob Hobbs would've
honored every part of her.
- You brought Abigail Hobbs
Back to minnesota to find out
if she was involved
In her father's murders,
and another girl dies.
- Yep, scraped
his knuckle on her teeth.
There's foreign tissue
and what could be
Trace amounts of blood.
- You said that this copycat
Was an intelligent psychopath, Will.
That there would be no traceable motive,
No pattern. He wouldn't
kill again this way.
You said it.
- I may have been
wrong about that.
- Yes, because Garrett Jacob
Hobbs never struck his victims.
Why would the copycat do it?
- I think he was provoked.
Nicholas Boyle
murdered this girl
and his own sister.
- With or without Abigail Hobbs?
- Without.
- Well, do you think
that Abigail Hobbs
Knew nicholas or cassie boyle?
- No...
- You don't think
she knew them...
Or don't want to think
that she knew them?
- She said she didn't know them.
(Jack sighs.)
- Dr. Bloom says that Abigail
Has a penchant for, uh,
Manipulation. Is she
manipulating you, will?
- Agent Crawford.
- Look, he said he was wrong
about the copycat killer.
I want to know what else
he's wrong about.
- Whoever killed the girl
on the field killed this girl,
I'm right about that.
He knew exactly how
to mount the body.
Wound patterns are almost
identical to cassie boyle.
Same design, the same...
Humiliation.
- Abigail Hobbs
is not a killer.
But she could be
the target of one.
- I think it's time that Abigail
Hobbs left home permanently.
Doctor, would you be good
enough to collect Abigail
And all of her belongings
And escort her out
of Minnesota, please?
Not you, will.
I want you here.
- (journalists):
Abigail! Abigail!
- You killed my daughter!
- Abigail--
- Why did you come back here?
Why come back?
- Stay here. Stay here.
(woman sobbing)
- Abigail.
- Miss lounds.
You're on the wrong side
of the police line.
- I've been covering the Minnesota
shrike long before you got involved.
I wanna help you tell your story.
You need me now more than ever.
- I wanna talk to her.
- No you don't. Go inside.
- I'm not the only one lurking
about the Hobbs house peeking in windows.
You really should monitor those
police lines more carefully.
- Have you seen
a young man, mid-20s,
Ginger hair? Unwashed.
- I'll tell you if I saw him
If you tell me
why it's important.
(sobbing softly)
- None of her
is gonna go to waste.
(whimpering)
- I'm not gonna hurt you.
Okay? I just need you
to listen to me.
I didn't kill
that girl, okay?
I didn't kill her!
Wait!
Listen! I didn't--
- Abigail?
Abigail?
- She'll be all right.
Abigail.
Show me what happened.
- He was gonna kill me.
- Was he?
This isn't self-defense, Abigail.
You butchered him.
- I didn't...
- They will see
what you did
And they will see you
As an accessory
to the crimes of your father.
- I wasn't.
- I can help you,
If you ask me to.
At great risk to
my career and my life.
You have a choice.
You can tell them
you were defending yourself
When you gutted this man...
Or we can hide the body.
- Then I don't
remember anything.
Maybe a blur out of the corner
of my eye and--
And then a big fat cut to black.
- Well, Nicholas Boyle
attacked Abigail, you,
Struck dr. Lecter
in the back of the head.
- Well, where's Abigail?
- Lecter took her back to the hotel.
- She scratched nicholas boyle
on his way out the back door.
The blood on her hands matches
the tissue that we pulled
From marissa schurr's mouth.
- And then what, he--
he got away?
- We'll catch him
one way or another.
Where you going?
- I wanna go home.
- Hello, Abigail.
- How did you know it was me?
- Hospital called.
You climbed over the wall.
Where else were you to go?
Home is no longer an option.
Come down from there.
- I don't want to go to sleep.
- You can't anticipate
your dreams.
Can't block them,
can't repress.
- I didn't honor
any part of him,
So it's just murder,
isn't it?
- Most would argue
self-defense.
- Then why not
tell the truth?
- Most would argue.
There would still be those
Who would say you were
taking after your father.
- You're glad I killed him.
- What would be the alternative?
That he killed you?
- I don't know
if he was going to.
- No, you don't.
- You're the one
who called the house.
You talked to my dad before--
What did you
say to him?
- A simple conversation,
Ascertaining if he was
home for an interview.
Then why not tell the truth?
- I think you called the house
as a serial killer.
Just like my dad.
- I am nothing like your dad.
I made a mistake.
Something easily misconstrued.
Not unlike yourself.
I'll keep your secret.
- And I'll keep yours.
- No more climbing walls,
Abigail.