Previously on Hannibal...
I'm giving my life to death.
And now Death has followed you home.
I don't think I wanna do chemotherapy.
- Do I have any say in this?
- No.
I'm devoting a lot of time to this
mural, Will. I could use your help.
What was the cause of death
in the bailiff's murder? - Bullets.
- And in Will Graham's victims?
- Mutilation.
There are clearly two different killers
and two different cases.
Will claims someone else committed
the crimes he's accused of.
- He said that person was you.
- Perhaps he was half right.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Wrap the leader
around the tippet. Four,
five, six times.
Tuck the end
between the lines.
Tighten.
And... trim.
It's called a blood knot.
Your father taught you
how to hunt.
I'm going to
teach you how to fish.
Same thing, isn't it?
One you stalk,
the other you re?
One you catch,
the other you shoot.
What are you trying to catch?
The one who caught you.
The one that got away.
Catch a fish once
and it gets away, it's
a lot harder to catch again.
(chuckling)
Everybody thinks you're lying
about the one that got away.
That's why I have to catch him.
Last thing before
casting a line:
name the bait on your hook
after somebody you cherished.
To say goodbye?
If the person you name it
after cherished you,
as the superstition goes,
you will catch the fish.
Oh.
And what did you name it?
Abigail.
(creaking sound)
You were right.
Killer was in the mural.
Just where you said he'd be.
His name was James Gray.
We found his vehicle
outside the farm.
Enough DNA on the bed of his
truck for us to be confident
he's the Muralist. - You found as much
evidence on him as you did on me.
I'm glad you said it.
Who stitched him
into the mural?
We don't know.
He may have had a partner.
Another killer. Maybe
they had a suicide pact.
There was no partner.
This artist worked alone until he
was stitched into his own creation.
- No signs of a struggle.
- No.
So, this second killer,
whoever he is,
understood the Muralist
well enough
not just to find his canvas,
but well enough to convince him
- to be part of it.
- You have an idea who that might be?
- I do.
- Don't say, "Hannibal Lecter."
- I'm saying Hannibal Lecter.
- Didn't you stop ringing that bell?
I'm not asking you to believe anything you
can't prove. I'm just asking you to prove it.
- Hannibal Lecter has no reason-
- That is exactly right.
He has no discernible reason
other than
his own amusement and curiosity.
That's hard to prove.
There will be
a very clever detail
to find on James Gray.
He wouldn't be able
to resist it. Probably something
that was overlooked.
Something hidden.
I'll look for clever details.
But I'm not looking
for Hannibal.
Just as long as you're looking.
You look out there.
I'll look in here.
(bee buzzing)
(buzzing)
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
I'll give you the same deal
I gave Beverly Katz.
I know you know what it is.
You've been recording
our conversations.
Or are we pretending
you didn't?
What "this" are you
offering in exchange
- for my "that"?
- I'm quite the topic
of conversation
in psychiatric circles.
(chuckling)
I shared my diagnosis of you
on the witness stand.
Your personality disorders,
neuroses-- all forgeries.
Even if that were true,
I'd still be a psychopath
- of some interest.
- Mm.
Quite a manipulative
one at that.
Poor, confused, wounded bird
for Agent Crawford and
Doctors Lecter and Bloom.
And for me, well,
I get the psychopath's
triumvirate: charm,
focus, and ruthlessness.
The charm being
debateable, of course.
So, either I'm a psychopath
or I am delusional.
Or I'm right about Hannibal
Lecter. Aren't you curious
which one it is?
- Will you allow me to test you?
- Test me?
I'll take 'em all.
You will be the first
and last word in the mind
of Will Graham. God, you could
dine out on that for years.
What about Dr. Lecter?
Shouldn't you be
my one and only psychiatrist,
Dr. Chilton?
- Ideally.
- Well then,
as to your "that"
for my "this."
Do not discuss me or my therapy
with Hannibal Lecter.
Tell him that you've
decided I am no longer
any of his business.
I am now under
your exclusive care.
Lazarus had it good.
My social circle
doesn't include a friend
with power over death.
I suppose I should've
embraced Facebook
while I had the chance.
(chuckling)
I never should have
let Jack talk me
into taking chemo.
He's trying to
extend your life.
He's trying to extend
a quality of life
that's not worth the effort.
Jack's efforts or yours?
I'm vomiting my stomach lining.
On a good day, I sleep
fifteen to eighteen hours.
On a bad day, I don't sleep.
My best-case
scenario
is prolonged pain management.
Jack will help you manage.
He loves you, Bella.
When you are gone, he will feel
your silence like a draft.
My silence
is inevitable.
The war is over.
The cancer is
an occupying force.
I want to surrender.
While I still have my dignity.
- You are considering ending your life?
- Suicide seems
like a valid solution
to my problem.
How does that make you feel?
Alive.
How does it make you feel?
I've always found the idea
of death comforting.
The thought that my life
could end at any moment
frees me to fully appreciate
the beauty, and art,
and horror
of everything
this world has to offer.
A death benefit?
Upon taking his
own life, Socrates
offered a rooster to the god
of healing, Asclepius,
to pay his debt.
What debt might that be?
To Socrates, death
was not a defeat...
...but a cure.
Gentlemen...
Local police were supposed
to exterminate the bees
so we could work the crime scene.
Apparently, someone shut that down.
- I did. - He did.
- Jimmy?
Well, I love bees.
Did you know that the drone
is nature's most talented
suicidal swordsman?
When the drone
mates with the queen,
his ejaculation
is so explosive,
it's audible to the human ear.
All right.
How long has he been out here?
Ah, from de-comp, I'd estimate two weeks.
Which makes sense with how
much honey is being produced.
Do bees naturally hive
in human carcasses like this?
No. The victim was purposely
repurposed as a human apiary.
Purposely.
Somebody removed
the eyes and part
of the brain to
make room for the hive.
Zeller's out in the field, otherwise
I'd ask him to help me with this.
I was a surgeon and
a doctor, yes. Have you found
any evidence on
the Muralist's friend?
That's what I need your help with.
Might not have been a friend.
Might not have even
been an acquaintance.
Whoever killed him,
understood him.
So often you open your mouth
and I hear Will Graham's
words come out.
I have an arrangement
with Will.
He's agreed to consult
with me on cases,
if I keep investigating
the murders he's accused of.
I'm happy to hear that.
Will needs a champion
now more than ever.
He has you, doesn't he?
You think there's a chance he
could be innocent. I know you do.
I believe there is
a possibility.
I'm just relieved he's not saying
the killer is you anymore.
At least not to me.
Who does Will believe
killed the Muralist?
Doesn't know.
He thinks if
James Gray's killer
hid him in the mural, he may
have hid something else.
A signature?
What kind of killer
seeks to depict the unconscious,
instinctual striving of his victim
by sewing him into
a human mural?
It wasn't just for appearances.
You have to get to the truth
beneath the appearances.
Only by going deep beneath
the skin will you understand
the nature of this
killer's pathology.
Before I start
asking you questions,
I need some confidence that
you will be telling the truth
- when you answer.
- What's this?
A consent form.
You're agreeing
to a narcoanalytic
interview. You. Me.
And our old friend,
sodium amytal.
A little something
to loosen my tongue?
Something lawfully
used in the evaluation
of psychotic patients.
What would you use
to induce memory loss in a
patient, psychotic or otherwise?
The protein synthesis
that moves memories
from short-term to long-term
can be interrupted,
but that requires
tools and skills.
And a certain level
of unorthodoxy.
Does Hannibal Lecter possess
those tools and skills?
Dr. Lecter has indicated
to me that he is open
to the unorthodox when
it comes to treating patients.
I wonder how that
subject came up...
Sharing stories
of the unorthodox.
Sign here.
I want you to draw
a clock for me.
(muffled): Did Dr. Lecter
administer any drug therapies
during your sessions together?
Sedatives...
The strobe causes neurons
to fire en masse,
like striking many
piano keys at once.
The strobe causes neurons
to fire en masse,
like striking many...
The dissonance might foster
a change in your mind.
Is something wrong?
Will...?
He was inducing seizures.
He was encouraging them.
The blackouts.
The lost time.
It was strategic.
It was planned.
You would only see a seizure
response in a brain
afflicted with
photosensitive epilepsy.
Or afflicted by something
just as damaging.
Like encephalitis.
That would suggest a radically
unorthodox form of therapy.
Yes, it would.
Doctor Lecter.
I am so embarrassed.
You didn't get my message?
I canceled your appointment
with Will Graham.
Is everything all right?
I can explain.
Shall we?
Will is at a delicate
point in his therapy.
I don't want to confuse him
any more than he already is.
Confuse him?
Isn't it your opinion he's
an intelligent psychopath?
It was, but my opinion is evolving.
After administering a
narcoanalytic interview,
therapeutically vital
information has come to light.
- What sort of information?
- What Will Graham suffers from
may not be a single condition,
but a continuum
of illnesses, all with different
neurological mechanisms.
Some naturally occurring,
- others appear to have been induced.
- Induced?
Induced by whom?
Did you ever use any kind
of light stimulation
in your treatment?
Light stimulation is a
standard tool for neurotherapy.
Evidently, it was overloading
his visual cortex.
Creating seizures, time loss,
gaps in his memory.
Almost strategically, it seems.
You're suggesting
it was intentional?
All our conversations
about psychic driving.
You were so curious and eager
to hear what I had to say
- while saying very little yourself.
- I had very little to say.
I have been thinking
about the possibility
that you may have been psychic
driving Will Graham all along.
A bold accusation, Frederick.
You are not the only psychiatrist
accused of making a patient kill.
We have to stick together.
Last time I did this,
this isn't how I did this.
The young man at the dispensary
calls this "purple kush."
He says
all his cancer patients
love its "deep body stone."
(chuckling)
May I?
- Do you still get drug tested?
- Oh, come on, gimme that thing.
I'm supporting my wife.
I filled out my advadirect.
I added a DNR.
Oh, you are harshing
my buzz right now.
I read an article the other day
about magnetic hyperthermia.
It's looking promising
as a treatment
for lung cancer.
Come here.
I know what to expect
from lung cancer.
I am my mother's daughter,
and I watched her
go through exactly
- what I am going through now.
- I know.
Hey... I remember
sitting by her bed
when she woke up
in so much pain
that all she could do
was scream my name.
I didn't know how to help her.
So I did nothing.
There was nothing you could do.
And there will be a time
when there is nothing
you can do.
And I don't want you
to remember me
pleading with you
to make the pain go away.
Oh, I'm not going
to remember you that way.
First of all,
I'm going to remember you
walking along the quays
of Italy in the sunshine
with a trail of signori
behind you
shouting "bella,
bella, bella."
And I'm going to remember
that your hands...
that they smelled of thyme when
you came in from the garden.
And garlic and onions
every time you left the kitchen.
(laughing)
I'm going to remember you as
beautiful as you are right now.
Well, good.
Good.
Duncan Halloran,
fifty-two, divorced, bankrupt.
Reported missing
six months ago.
And what do we know
about his death?
Considering any post-mortem morphological
changes, this guy's white blood cell count
- was through the roof when he died.
- You're telling me
his killer was a fever
and/or a massive infection?
- Lock 'em both up.
- No family. No money.
No reason to live.
Alive, dead, or dying,
- who put him under the tree?
- It's possible
we're dealing with a highly motivated
religious individual here.
- Explain. - In Hinduism, honey is one of
the five elixirs of immortality.
In Christianity, the bee
is considered to be
an emblem of Christ; his
mildness and mercy on one side,
- his Old Testament justice on the other.
- OK. The orbital bone,
his sphenoid, um, behind where
the eyeballs would usually be,
there's tiny punctures.
Something long and sharp
was pushed in his brain.
Jack, this guy was lobotomized.
- How are you feeling today?
- Not well.
My arthritis is killing me.
I can't take much more of it.
A course of bee venom
therapy would soothe
the inflammation.
I can barely afford
this treatment.
That's a problem
for another day.
Now,
you just quiet your mind.
Just live in the present.
- You feel that?
- No.
Good.
You feel that?
- No.
- Good.
Feel that?
I can't feel anything.
Good.
Then you won't feel this...
(whimpering)
Mister, you're not supposed
to stare at the sun.
It'll hurt your eyes.
Multiple holes in this guy.
Over a dozen.
Both eye sockets.
The-the lesions have severed
most of the nerve tract
in the frontal lobe.
He's covered in bee stings
like he got swarmed.
Must be floating in apitoxin,
or he doesn't feel a thing.
Yeah, the not feeling anything has
got nothing to do with bee stings.
Welcome to the world
of the living dead.
There's a pattern.
- Hey.
- Hey...
- Look what the cat's dragged in.
- What are you looking at?
(both): A pattern.
See, some of the bee stings triggered
an allergic reaction, others didn't.
The inflamed bee stings
were all in line
with the body's meridian,
on acupuncture points.
The bee stings are
hiding the needle marks.
What did you say?
Uh, the bee stings are
hiding the needle marks?
Stitches are hiding stitches.
Only by going deep
beneath the skin
will you understand the nature
of this killer's pathology.
He took his kidney.
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
Tell me if he's real.
- I don't see anyone.
- No, he's right there.
- There's no one there. We're alone.
- You're lying.
You came here alone. Do you
remember coming alone?
- Please don't lie to me.
- Garrett Jacob Hobbs is dead.
- You killed him. You watched him die.
- What's happening to me?
Will. Will, you're having
an episode. I want you
to hand me over the gun.
Will, I want you
to hand me your...
Will...
He's had a mild seizure.
That... doesn't seem
to bother you.
I said it was mild.
Are you the man who claimed
to be the Chesapeake Ripper?
Why do you say "claimed"?
Because you're not.
You know you're not and
you don't know much more
about who you are beyond that.
Are you
the Ripper?
A terrible thing,
to have your identity
taken from you.
Whoever killed James Gray
didn't just take his leg.
Sutures hidden
beneath the stitching
that wove him into the mural. One
crime made to look like another.
Like the Copycat.
And...
the Chesapeake Ripper.
Now you're saying Hannibal
Lecter is the Chesapeake Ripper?
I'm saying also the Chesapeake Ripper.
Um...
were the kidneys
surgically removed?
- Yes.
- Dr. Lecter was a surgeon.
I know he was. I asked him to
consult on James Gray's autopsy.
You what?
If you invited him
with an actual agenda,
Hannibal would know it.
- He pointed me to the evidence.
- He pointed you
to an absence of evidence.
He's baiting a hook, Beverly.
He's toying with you.
Go to Jack. Tell him everything.
I can't bring this to Jack
until I can back it up.
Stay away
from Hannibal Lecter.
The Chesapeake Ripper
kept surgical trophies.
If Hannibal's the ripper, what's
he doing with his trophies?
(crows cawing)
He's eating them.
***
Yes.
I'm Special Agent
Jack Crawford with the FBI.
This is Agent Zeller
and Agent Price.
We'd like to speak with you about
two of your former patients.
Would you like to come in?
When was the last time you saw
Duncan Halloran or Lloyd Roat?
Whenever our last
appointments were.
- I can check in my calendar, if you want.
- Sure.
- Have you found them?
- Yes, we have.
Mr. Halloran is deceased.
And Mr. Roat
might as well be.
Whew...
- Poor Mr. Halloran...
- What were you treating him for?
That man trudged
from disease to disease.
He had severe combined
immunodeficiency.
Life didn't seem
to be going his way.
- Please.
- Thank you.
Hm...
I find that, uh,
people don't get their own way
because, um,
they often don't know themselves
where that way leads.
Mr. Halloran,
he couldn't envision
a dignified end of life.
So, it's much nicer to die,
well, for him,
to die in a meadow,
a head full of bees.
- Have you tried the honey?
- No.
I couldn't bring myself to
either. It seemed
too morbid.
So you left him in the field
- to die?
- I brought him
to the field to die.
I didn't kill him.
I quieted his mind
so that he could die in peace.
And Mr. Roat?
- You quieted his mind, too?
- Oh, him.
He suffered
crippling arthritis.
After he was quieted...
...I saw him walk pain-free
for the very first time
in his life.
I can't make pain go away,
but I can make it so that
it doesn't matter.
I-I protected them.
I protected these people
from hopelessness.
And that's beautiful.
Please come in.
It's a little unnerving,
not being able to walk
across the floor.
Nothing can be so unnerving
for someone strong
as being weak.
I was so weak
after chemotherapy,
Jack had to
physically pick me up.
It was the second time
he carried me
across the threshold.
I brought you something.
A gift?
Paying my debt.
Coq Gaulois.
For helping me understand
that death is not a defeat,
but a cure.
What have you taken, Bella?
My morphine.
Every bit of it.
I didn't want to die at home.
I didn't want Jack to find me.
I didn't want him
to make that call...
...to be in the room
with my body,
waiting...
for it to become
some ceremonial object
apart from him,
separate
from who I was,
someone he can only...
...hold in his mind.
You denied him his goodbye.
I denied him...
a painful goodbye.
And allowed myself
a peaceful one.
Tell Jack...
...I love him very much.
Yes.
Goodbye,
Dr. Lecter.
Goodbye, Bella.
Hey. Have you seen Jack?
Oh. No, no, no,
there was, uh,
some emergency with his wife.
Dr. Lecter called
- from the hospital, asked him to come down.
- Is Mrs. Crawford okay?
I don't know.
He didn't say.
So Hannibal's
at the hospital, too?
(moaning softly)
- Hi, baby.
- Hey.
I'm here.
What are you doing here?
I want to apologize.
I couldn't honor
what you asked of me.
I'm sorry.
(coughing)
Get out.
Gotcha.
(creaking)
Oh, my God.
(gunshots)
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player