Sync and corrections by elderman
Resync by n17t01 www.addic7ed.com
I don't care where he is.
Find him.
It's urgent.
Yes, I'll hold.
He's been locked up
for almost a year
and overnight they decide
to hold a trial
and pronounce a death sentence?
What did you expect?
Hasan blew up 129 civilians
in the marketplace in Ramadi.
I know what he did.
I also know he's got intel
about an imminent attack
on U.S. soil.
He's been dangling
this so-called attack
for the last three months.
Yeah.
And now he'll come clean
if we commute his sentence.
We don't dictate law
to the Iraqis anymore.
This is their jurisdiction.
And Hasan is their prisoner.
David...
Hold on a second.
He's Abu Nazir's
bomb maker, David.
Execute him now, and everything
he knows is gone forever.
It's over.
I'm on my way to the prison now.
At least petition JSOC.
- Have them appeal to the Iraqi Army.
- JSOC can't do anything either.
David, you're a CIA deputy
director... you can do this.
- I told you it's over.
- Please don't shut me down.
David, Senator Feldman's
looking for you.
- Tell him I'll be right there.
- David, please,
this is
my last chance with Hasan.
- Carrie, I have to go.
- David...
I'm hanging up.
Estes didn't go for it.
I knew he wouldn't.
Is that him?
Yes.
I'm not sure we can trust him.
Can he get me inside or not?
He says he can.
Now you have only two minutes.
Understand what I say...
two minutes.
Ibrahim...
I tried to get the
Agency to intervene,
but they couldn't do anything.
I'm sorry.
So I have nothing to say to you.
Ibrahim, you said
your family was in hiding,
afraid for their lives.
I can get them to Amman.
Tell me what you know,
and I will personally
guarantee their safety.
Why should I believe
you will do what you say?
We have to go.
You said two minutes.
The guards, they are coming.
I need more time.
You don't believe me?
Well, maybe I was wrong
to believe you.
You said you were
an important man.
You said you had information
about an attack by Abu Nazir.
- I have information.
- Prove it.
Because unless you do,
I won't protect your family.
Please, we're out of time!
My family!
You promised to protect them!
You're listening to "Jim
Dawkins in the Morning."
Wake up, Washington.
This is Dave sitting in
for Jim Dawkins.
We got a lot
on the topic today.
So why don't you get
your phones ready
and give us a call.
They say that Washingtonians
are apathetic and...
♪ ♪
Last night, at 2300 GMT,
one of our ground assets
produced a live lead
on an enemy operating base
in the Korengal Valley.
Nice of you to join us, Carrie.
How is it you are
the only analyst
in this section that can't
get to a briefing on time?
I wanted the whole
group to hear this.
Within the hour,
Delta Team was on site.
where they identified multiple
insurgents on our hit list.
Minutes later, two UH-60
Blackhawk gunships
lit the target with
over 8,000 rounds.
All 13 hostiles
were confirmed kills.
But, during the sweep,
one of the deltas found
something else...
a padlocked door
to an interior room.
I wanted you
to see for yourselves.
Get the fuck down!
Get him on his feet!
What did you say?
I'm an American.
Turns out he's one of ours.
Marine Sergeant Nicholas Brody.
MIA since early 2003
and presumed dead...
until now.
What happened to his partner?
Brody was a scout sniper.
They work in pairs.
Corporal Thomas Walker also
went missing that day.
According to Sergeant Brody,
Walker was killed
during their captivity.
But that shouldn't dampen
what is a major win
for the agency and for everyone
in this room.
You should all take a moment...
give yourselves a big hand.
Because of you, an American hero
is coming home.
Good job.
What were his exact
words, please?
An American prisoner of war
has been turned.
He said this in English?
Yes. He whispered it
into my ear
right before the
guards pulled me away.
And when he used
the expression "turned..."
He meant turned...
working for Abu Nazir.
Why am I just hearing
about this now?
Because until ten minutes ago,
I didn't know there were any P.O.W.'s
still alive in Iraq or Afghanistan.
So you're suggesting
that Abu Nazir...
You're suggesting
that Abu Nazir
planted intelligence in
his own safe house
just so we could recover
Sergeant Brody?
I realize it sounds
like a reach.
To say the least.
Why not just drop him
near a checkpoint
and make it look
like he escaped.
Why would you sacrifice
13 trained fighters?
Because Abu Nazir
is playing the long game.
This way, no one
suspects a thing.
Except you.
Yeah, except me.
Yeah.
And Sergeant Brody's due home
from Germany tomorrow morning,
which gives us
just under 22 hours.
To do what?
To authorize a
surveillance package.
To tap his phones,
wire his house,
follow him wherever he goes.
David will never sign off
on that and you know it.
Of course he won't.
The White House needs
a poster boy for the war,
and David just served
him up on a platter.
That's why I'm coming to you.
I'm not going over his
head, not on a hunch.
But if I'm right,
if he is a terrorist,
we need eyes and ears
on Brody from the minute
he steps off the plane.
- Never happen.
- But...
Out of the question.
Carrie...
All right, fine.
What do I have to do?
Prove that the safe house
leak was planted.
Or at least give me a reason
to doubt its authenticity.
I'm in the penalty box, Saul.
I'm 5,000 miles away
from my contacts.
I can't collect intelligence
from behind a desk.
Find a way.
No, don't look at me that way.
We're all fighting
the same enemy here.
We're ready for you,
Sergeant Brody.
Your debriefing.
I want to call my wife first.
Oh, I think that's mine.
Oh, no. Oh...
Don't get it. Don't.
It might be one of my kids.
Hello.
Jessica?
It's me. Brody.
Brody?
Come on, Jess, talk to me.
What do you want me to say?
Tell me that you're okay.
I'm not okay.
I'm a long way from okay.
Hey.
Mom!
Where's your sister?
I thought you were
at the movies with Jody.
Dana!
Is she in her room?
Mom...
Come with me. Dana?!
Mom, just wait a second.
Come on. I have some
incredible news for you guys.
Mom! Come on, Mom!
Dana!
Mom, don't go in there!
Mom, just...
Tried to stop her.
How come you're home so early?
Who is he?
Xander.
Xander...
you need to leave right now.
I'll text you later.
Xan, your jacket.
Why are you making such
a big deal out of this, Mom?
Gee, Dana, I don't know, it's
either the lying or the drugs.
You're supposed to be looking
after your brother.
Well, he didn't
burn down the house.
Why don't you just do what
you say you're gonna do
for a change? What?
Mom!
You said you had something
important to tell us.
Shit!
What, Ma?
Come here, you two.
Touchdown in about two hours.
You need anything?
No, I'm good. Thanks.
You'll have some time
with your family first.
Then you'll meet
the Vice President,
who'll introduce you to
every major media outlet
in the whole country.
The turnout is overwhelming
here at Andrews Air Force Base
where Sergeant Nicholas Brody
is scheduled to land
in just under two hours.
Now a White House spokesman
confirms
that the Vice President
will be on hand.
Do you even remember him?
Not really.
As we reported, Sergeant Brody
is one of two Marines
who went missing in action
eight years ago,
during a mission into
Iraq, near the Syrian border.
A former Marine Scout sniper,
Sergeant Brody was operating
in hostile territory
when his spotter...
Hi, Brody.
The soldiers
were then separated...
You coming or not, Mom?
'Cause I don't think it'd
appropriate if we were late.
Yeah, let me just get my coat.
Are you really wearing
that dress?
But after the announcement
that Sergeant Brody,
in fact, survived
the eight-year ordeal and was
greeted by a wave of enthusiasm
from an American public
eager to greet a true hero.
More details on
Sergeant Brody's captivity
are expected to come out
over the coming days,
but a military spokesman...
You look pretty, Mom.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Start in the living room.
I got 30 minutes.
And good to see
you, too, Carrie.
Who the fuck is he?!
Relax, it's all good.
It's my brother Max.
Max, say hi to the client.
Hi.
What happened
to Nick and Eddie?
Out of your price range.
I told you, for a grand a day,
it's gonna be bare bones.
Hey, you got
a bad feeling about this?
You want to roll this thing up
before we get started,
you just say the word.
Eyes and ears in every room.
Then it's back to my place
to set up the monitors.
No way you could delay
the ceremony?
Not without looking
like a complete asshole.
He's in the head now
puking his guts out.
I thought the Army docs
did a complete psych eval.
They did.
So what's the problem?
I don't know, David.
Maybe eight years at the bottom
of a hole had something
to do with it.
I have the Vice President
arriving as we speak.
And I need him smiling and
waving like a hero,
like it's the fucking
Macy's Day Parade.
The President asked me
to thank you personally.
I have to think the short list
for the directorship
just got a lot shorter.
Well, I appreciate
the consideration, sir.
Not that I'm pushing for it.
Sure you are.
Hi, Dad.
Dana.
How was your trip?
Look at how beautiful you are.
Chris.
Pleased to meet you.
Hug him, Chris.
Where's Mom?
When?
Four years ago.
Sergeant Brody,
the Vice President's here.
Sergeant Brody.
It's an honor.
Thank you, sir.
You okay?
Yeah.
Good morning, Marines.
Good morning, sir!
I said, "Good morning, Marines."
Stand at ease.
Sergeant Brody, on behalf
of the President
of the United States and
a grateful nation,
it is my privilege to welcome
you home!
Oorah!
Sergeant Nicholas Brody.
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
I'm not really too good
at making speeches.
My wife does most of the talking
in the family.
Even though
I can't mention 'em by name,
I want to thank the Special
Forces team that saved my life.
And thanks
to all of you out there
for your prayers
and your good wishes.
It made all the difference.
Most of all,
I want to say...
I want to say
thank you to my family
for their strength
in my absence...
and for their undying faith
this day would come.
I'm a lucky man.
Guy's got game.
How long before you're set up?
The feed will be live
by the time
Sergeant Brody
gets back to his house.
More details on
Sergeant Brody's captivity
are expected to come out.
So, uh, you and Carrie,
how long you guys
known each other?
Long enough.
'Cause I'd kind of feel
a lot better
if I had a clear picture
about who we're dealing with.
We are breaking, like,
12 federal laws.
You would, would you?
A clearer picture?
Why don't you shut the fuck up
and get back to work, okay?
Hey...
I'm sorry, um... let's just say
that she's a little intense.
Yeah.
What's that?
It's what she hides
in her aspirin bottle
instead of aspirin.
I have one of my migraines
coming on, so...
Let me see that.
What do you think it is?
I don't know.
I'm driving.
Are you sure
that's a good idea?
Jesus, Mom, just let him drive.
Okay, I guess.
Marine!
Mike?
Welcome back.
Thanks, man.
How you holding up?
You look good.
It's great to be home.
It's great to have you home.
This is for real?
You stayed in?
Military intelligence.
I know, right?
Me, of all people, huh?
And Megan? How's she?
Long gone, buddy.
She divorced me between
my second and third tours.
Ah.
Look, I hate to bring this
up, but Langley wants to
schedule a follow-up to
your debrief in Germany.
- They asked me to arrange it.
- When?
- Tomorrow.
- Tomorrow?!
I know. I said the
same thing, but...
this guy Estes, he wants it
done sooner than later.
He just got here.
It's okay, Jess.
I'd rather just
get it over with.
Well, I'll send
a car in the morning.
Good.
And when you're up for it...
I'm taking you to the Greeks
for some steak and beer, buddy,
'cause we got a lot of lost
time to start making up for.
Huh?
Yeah. God, it's good
to see you, buddy.
You, too.
Look.
We're famous.
You said you'd be ready
by the time they got home.
It's just a minor glitch,
give me a few minutes.
You painted the house.
Mike's brother did it.
He's a contractor.
He gave us a really great rate.
What do you think of the color?
I like it.
Come on.
I'll show you
what we did inside.
How's it feel to be back?
Can we get a group shot
with the yellow ribbon?
What do you think?
Sure.
Come on, come on.
Yeah. If you could just line up
in front of the tree, yeah.
Family shot.
That's fantastic.
Big smile.
I'm having trouble collecting
that intel. I need you to get me
into Sergeant Brody's debrief
tomorrow morning.
And what good
would come of that?
I'm a trained interrogator.
I'll ask him a few questions,
poke around his story a little.
principals only.
David's all about punishing me.
And not just for what
happened in Baghdad.
- Do you blame him?
- No, but...
this shouldn't be personal;
I belong in that room.
Will you behave yourself?
Carrie?
Sorry.
Uh, yeah.
I need you to promise.
You will raise
no eyebrows in there.
You will break no china.
I promise.
Good.
Then you can have your face
time with Sergeant Brody.
Thank you, Saul.
Yep.
Oh, Christ.
Well?
Hello, Big Brother.
So when do you want
me back tomorrow?
Carrie.
I need to be in the office
by 9:00, so get here at 8:00.
Okay.
Hello?
Who was that?
Oh, Jesus, you scared me.
Nobody. They hung up.
How was your shower?
God, you look beautiful.
How about a glass of wine?
I opened a bottle.
Oh, I see what this is now.
Dimming the lights,
plying me with liquor.
Is it that obvious?
Kind of.
I gotta say, I like you in
that nightgown, though.
My mother wears a nightgown.
This is a negligee.
How about that wine,
what do you say?
Sure.
The tag is still...
Is that okay?
Yeah.
Jess...
Hmm?
Oh, my...
Hey.
What they did to you...
Hey. Hey...
Baby...
Oh, Jess...
Oh, God...
Hey.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
I'm so sorry.
Let's sit down here.
It's over.
It's over now, baby.
I'm home.
Okay.
I'm home now, baby.
Okay. Oh, baby.
Oh, God...
It hurts...
What time is it?
Quarter after 8:00.
The debrief!
I'm late!
- Shit!
- Want a donut?
Two calls came in;
both hang-ups.
Yeah?
One last night, one this morning.
Both times the wife answered;
both times there was no one
on the other end of the line.
Did a number pop up on a tracer?
No, and the calls were blocked.
Is there any way that...
No, not without a subpoena.
Look, Virgil,
if somebody's trying
to make contact with Brody,
it'll only happen once.
And when it does,
we'll be there.
All right?
It's all good. Relax.
All right.
I've got to get dressed.
Many of the men and women
in this room are involved
in the operation which resulted
in your rescue, so we take
an extra measure of pride
in welcoming you.
Thank you, sir.
Now, we've all
read your debrief
from Germany, so
today we just have
a few more questions...
clarifications, really...
that might help us in our
ongoing fight against Al Qaeda.
- I understand.
- Good.
Good. We'll, uh, start
with Stuart Strickland,
lead analyst in
our Iraq section.
Sergeant Brody,
it's a pleasure.
A few weeks after your capture,
Special Forces conducted
a direct action mission against
a former police HQ in Garma...
According to your debrief,
most of your incarceration
was spent at a secret military
facility outside Damascus.
What landmarks
or structural details can you
give us to help pinpoint...?
Eight months you were
smuggled overland
to an enemy operating base in
Afghanistan.
Now, after so many years,
what prompted...?
Sergeant Brody, my name
is Carrie Mathison.
I served as a case officer
in Iraq.
Your picture was on
our MIA wall.
I saw it every day
for five years.
It's good to meet you in person.
Thank you, ma'am.
I'm sorry we were unable
to find you sooner.
I appreciate that.
I'd like to start
with the first few days
of your captivity
if you don't mind.
Not at all.
How soon after you were taken
did the interrogations begin?
Pretty much right away.
What did they want to know?
Anything I could tell 'em
about U.S. ground operations,
supply routes, communication
codes, rules of engagement.
When you were debriefed
in Germany,
you said you gave up
no such information.
My SERE training was excellent.
And Corporal Walker?
Ma'am?
Did he give anything up?
We were never interrogated
together, so I don't know.
But still you must have
wondered, especially
after you learned of his death.
I'm assuming
there's a point
to all this, Carrie?
There is, sir.
As you know, the first 72 hours
after a soldier's capture
are critical.
What he knows can be
used by the enemy
during that period to
devastating effect.
The point is Sergeant Brody
stopped being a source
of actionable intelligence
fairly quickly,
and yet he was kept
alive for eight more years.
I'd like to ask him
if he knows why.
I often wondered that myself.
Who was your interrogator?
An Al Qaeda commander.
His name was Zayadi.
Zayadi?
That's what he told me
his name was, anyway.
Was this him?
No.
But you know who this man is.
Of course.
Every Marine in country
was briefed
on high-value targets.
Did you ever meet him?
Abu Nazir?
Was he ever present during
any of your interrogations?
No.
Look again.
Sergeant Brody?
No, I never met him.
What-what... what about Walker?
Did he ever mention Abu Nazir?
No.
You sure?
Carrie, how many times
does the man have
to answer the question?
It's just, I'm just
a little surprised, sir.
Abu Nazir was in charge
of coordinating attacks
against coalition forces
at the time.
No one had more
reason to sit down with the only
two American P.O.W.'s
in his custody.
Well, apparently, he didn't.
Is there anything else, Carrie?
No, sir, that's it.
Thank you, Sergeant Brody.
Thank you.
Moving on, Sergeant Brody,
I'd like to turn your attention
to anything you may have
witnessed
or overheard when in captivity.
Remember Mrs. Base?
The math teacher?
Yeah.
Yeah, she was, like, my
least-favorite teacher of all time.
She's so annoying.
Hey, can you guys
come in here a second?
Hey, I need help
getting ready for tonight.
What's tonight?
Some of your father's buddies
from Bravo Company are coming
over for a barbecue.
There's a bag of corn
that needs to be shucked,
and the grill needs
to be cleaned.
I'll do the corn.
So, do I have to be here?
Why is everything always
a problem with you?
I was just asking a question.
I know things haven't
been easy between you and me.
But we all have to find a way
to be there
for each other now, okay?
Yeah, okay.
Clean the grill.
Hello?
Hey, Jess.
Hey. How did it go?
I'm actually still here
at Langley.
I'm stuck in this debrief,
and it's taking a little
longer than I expected.
How much longer?
Oh, only an hour or two maybe.
Well, don't forget,
everybody's coming at 5:00.
Sure. I won't be late.
Okay. Bye, honey.
Sergeant Brody
you're a man who's endured
a terrible ordeal.
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
Anything?
As a matter of fact, yeah.
Brody just lied to his wife.
- Tell me.
- Max is tailing his town car.
Brody just said
he was still at Langley,
but he told his driver to
drop him off at Bluemont Park.
This is it.
He's making contact.
All right, I'll meet you there.
Where's-Where's Bluemont Park?
Saul?
Hey. Late for a
meeting off campus.
How many boards
can one man sit on?
You kissed Carrie Mathison
into my debrief this morning.
I'm curious if that was
her request or yours.
Hers. Frankly, I'm surprised
you didn't assign her yourself,
since she's the only one in the
section who's ever been to Iraq.
It's not her resume
I have a problem with.
It's her temperament.
What happened?
She turned a routine follow-up
into a cross-examination.
Kept trying to connect
Brody to Abu Nazir.
It's always Nazir with her.
I won't deny
she can be a little obsessive
on the subject.
Is there something
I should know, Saul?
Not that I'm aware of.
Because the last time
I heard her like this,
she bribed her way
into an Iraqi prison,
caused an international crisis.
I appreciate your concern.
Carrie has learned her lesson.
And we both know
how good she is.
What did I tell you
when I agreed
to give her one more chance?
You said only if I agreed
to do the babysitting.
I said it would end badly.
For both of you.
You've got a big blind spot
where she's concerned.
Trust me.
I did, too.
Now my wife lives in Palm Beach,
and I only see my kids
twice a year.
Did you fix the audio?
Well, we'll know soon enough.
I set up a directional mic
near the band shell.
Max, switch
to channel three.
Somebody's approaching Brody
from 1:00...
a female, dark red coat.
I didn't think
you'd be able to make it.
I don't understand why
you had to go through Mike.
Why didn't you just
call me yourself?
I did. Twice.
Are you recording this?
But your wife answered.
She didn't give me
any messages.
Because I hung up.
She hates me, Brody.
Hates you? Why?
Because I got remarried.
Jessica reacted like
it was a personal insult.
Like I was publicly
giving up hope that you
and Tom were still alive.
What the...?
Who the hell is she?
Helen Walker. It's the wife
of the other missing Marine.
Ah, well, then,
she's not Brody's contact.
Just keep listening.
The Pentagon said
you both were dead.
And now they're refusing
to give me any information
about what happened to Tom.
What do you want to know?
How he died.
He's gone.
Does it really matter
how it happened?
It does to me.
He was beaten to death.
Were you there?
No.
Thank you for telling me.
I'm going home.
Want to be there
in time for this barbecue.
Hold on a second.
Max, will you give us a minute?
Max, step out of the van.
I didn't think that this was
any of my business.
Now I'm thinking that it is.
Clozapine?
I'm sorry.
Was I supposed to say something?
Just tell me I'm not out here
risking federal prison
on behalf of a crazy person.
I am crazy.
It's not funny.
If anybody at the Agency
finds out about this...
I've got a mood disorder, okay?
I looked it up, Carrie.
Clozapine's an anti-psychotic.
I'm dealing with it.
I've-I've been dealing with it
since I was 22.
- Does Saul know?
- God, no.
No. Nobody does.
Don't act so shocked.
I mean, it can't come
as a complete surprise.
You know I love you, Carrie,
but I got to be honest.
None of this is making me feel
any better.
What are you saying?
That I'm making this shit up?
Well, maybe I am; you know,
maybe it is all in my head,
but you're in it now, Virgil,
up to your fucking neck,
and so is your weird
little brother,
so don't even think
about bailing on me.
You think for one minute
you get away with this?
I thought that once
I had some proof...
Do you have any?
Anything?
Even suggesting that Sergeant
Brody's what you think he is?
No.
Then get a lawyer.
'Cause you're gonna need
one when you report
to the IG first thing
in the morning.
- Saul, please...
- There isn't anything to say.
I-I'm just making sure
we don't get hit again.
Well, I'm glad someone's
looking out for the country, Carrie.
I'm serious...
I missed something once before;
I won't... I can't
let that happen again.
It was ten years ago.
Everyone missed
something that day.
Yeah, everyone's not me.
I understand that.
I doubt a grand jury will.
Come on, you recruited me, Saul.
You trained me.
You put me in the field.
Tell me what I can do
to make this right between us.
What the fuck are you doing?
Good-bye, Carrie.
Aw, fuck!
Shit. Shit.
♪ ♪
You know, I'm
shaking his hand...
he's the vice president...
and I suddenly realize...
I don't even know
the guy's name.
Hey.
Hi.
Geez, you don't call,
you don't write...
We have to talk.
'Cause you can't
keep ducking me.
I'm not ducking you.
I'm just trying to deal
with the situation.
Yeah, well,
you're not the only one.
Look...
I understand you want
to do the right thing
and I support you, but, Jess...
three days ago we were
about to tell your kids.
We were talking about
moving in together.
Mike,
please.
♪ ♪
Hey, you want me to forget it?
You know, all you
got to do is tell me
that it wasn't great between us.
♪
♪ (indistinct
chatter continues)
He's my husband, Mike.
♪ ♪
They're gonna burn.
The burgers.
Oh.
Right.
Here.
So, Mike's been a big
help to your mom, huh?
He comes around
whenever she needs him.
You like him?
Yeah, he's cool.
There you go.
One's for Mom.
Thanks.
Ow!
I'm just saying that I think
that somebody somewhere is
looking at him right now and thinking
congressman or senator or...
You know?
Can I ask you a
personal question?
Don't you want to get
a couple more drinks in me first?
You're married?
No.
But you wear a ring.
Oh, weeds out the guys
looking for a relationship.
What?
Uh, I... I don't know,
I guess I've never
heard it put so bluntly before.
I just find it a lot easier
not to screw things up
with people I don't know.
Come on, you can't
be all that bad.
What if I told you I betrayed
my only true friend
in the world today,
just played him for a fool,
put his 35-year
career at risk?
I would say that in this town
you're in good company.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
Another, please.
Coming right up.
These guys are pretty good.
You want to grab a table?
I'd rather just get out of here.
Okay. Where should we go?
I'm done making the decisions.
You're in charge now.
Wow.
Okay, I like it.
Are you coming?
Hey, Carrie, are you okay?
♪ ♪
What am I looking at here?
His right hand.
He's just nervous.
No. No. Look again.
It's a pattern that repeats,
like a musical phrase.
There.
That's hardly definitive.
No.
Just... wait.
This is him outside his house.
And here he is at
Andrews Air Force Base.
Okay,
do you... do you see?
It happens
whenever he's on camera,
whenever he knows the world
is watching... it's the same
sequence over and over again.
A code of some kind.
He's making contact, Saul.
He's sending a message
to somebody... a handler,
a sleeper cell, somebody.
We should explore this further.
Let's get the
crypto guys on it.
Pittman's team is
the best... plus,
he knows how to be discreet.
I'll get his number.
So am I still going to jail?
Not just yet.
What do you want to know?
How he died.
Were you there?
No.
- Did you ever meet him?
- Abu Nazir?
Was he ever present during
any of your interrogations?
Again.
No, I never met him.
Harder.
Shh. Shh.
Sync and corrections by elderman
Resync by n17t01 www.addic7ed.com