Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
PRESIDENT REAGAN: Air and naval
forces of the United States
launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
REPORTER: Pan Am Flight 103 crashed
into the the town of Lockerbie.
REAGAN: He has sanctioned
acts of terror
in Africa, Europe,
the Middle East.
PRESIDENT GEORGE H.W. BUSH: This will not stand,
this aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
REAGAN: This relentless
pursuit of terror.
PRESIDENT GEORGE W. BUSH:
We will make no distinction...
REPORTER:
The USS Cole was attacked
while refueling in
the port of Aden.
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable
and cowardly act.
The next song
we're going to play for you
is one of the good old
favorites.
Until something stops him.
WOMAN: I'm just making sure
we don't get hit again.
MAN: That plane crashed
into the World Trade Center.
Thousands of people running.
We must and we will remain
vigilant at home and abroad.
(speaking Arabic)
SAUL:
What the fuck are you doing?
God!
CARRIE: Fuck! I missed
something once before.
I won't...
I can't let that happen again.
SAUL:
It was ten years ago.
Everyone missed something
that day.
CARRIE:
Everyone's not me.
Previously on Homeland:
BRODY: I appreciate you
looking out for Jessica.
Like you did while I was gone.
You were my friend! You...
Carrie here.
It's me.
Where are you?
I'm taking some time,
from home.
CARRIE:
I know I have oatmeal,
but no Yorkshire Gold out here
in the sticks. Sorry.
How do you know
the tea I drink?
Did you spy on me?
You are a spy, right?
You're telling me the fucking CIA
thinks I'm working for al-Qaeda?
I think you're working
for al-Qaeda.
We have a deal with Aileen.
What did she tell you?
They were just told to buy the
house, go about their business
till a visitor arrived.
Which he did on Monday.
She's sitting with a sketch
artist right now.
Ask me anything.
Why did they kill
Walker and not you?
I killed him.
SAUL: Galvez, you up there?
Affirmative.
Face the airport, Galvez.
We're looking for
direct targets.
GALVEZ:
Reserve M-1.
SAUL: That's a landing pad
for Marine 1.
Oh, shit.
A mile is well within
a sniper's range.
An expert sniper.
Saul.
We were wrong about Brody.
A P.O.W. was turned,
but it wasn't him.
Aileen just I.D.'d Tom Walker.
He's alive.
He's the terrorist.
Yo.
Homeless vet here.
Hey, I fought your war.
Iraq-- ring a bell?
Hey, come on, man.
I'm hungry.
Ma'am, ma'am?
Ma'am?
Nah.
Thank you. God bless you.
God bless the little children.
Thank you, little man.
All right, all right.
Yo.
Hungry here.
ESTES:
Is this the man you saw?
Your father?
Is this your office?
Yeah, yeah, this is my office.
I thought you were a spy.
I guess, in a--
in a way.
How can you spy on anyone
sitting in here?
Lucas, Lucas, come on.
Just... What did we agree?
That everything
had to be secret.
Right, and what else?
You get to ask
your questions first.
(clicking tongue)
Why'd you do that?
Touch your nose?
HELEN: He told me he'd seen
his father at school.
Watching him through
the chain link.
It never occurred to me
it could actually be true.
Tom was dead.
That's what they told me.
I know it's a lot to deal with.
You think?
For years I pray Tom's alive.
Now you tell me he is, but he's
turned into some kind of monster?
I didn't say that.
Yes, you did.
"Brainwashed." That was
the word you used.
Planning an attack
on his own country.
That's what we believe.
So I don't know whether
I should be celebrating
or putting my son and
I into witness protection.
What we need to do is find him
before anything happens.
You can help with that.
How could he be alive
all these years and not call?
When you say he's changed,
that's the only reason
I believe you.
ESTES:
Carrie?
Will you send in
Mrs. Walker, please?
He needs your help in there.
Do you think you can do that?
In Germany you said Walker
died in the middle of the night.
He was killed, yes.
Beaten to death?
I didn't see it.
I heard it.
But it was pretty clear.
Then they made you bury him?
Yeah, outside the compound.
Just like I said in my original
debrief and a hundred times since.
So you want to tell me
what this is all about?
I'm just reconfirming.
Oh, that's why they told me to
drop everything and rush in here.
Well, his wife--
widow-- she's trying
to close the file.
Just trying to oblige.
Like I said,
mostly we were kept apart.
All I know for sure
is he's dead.
Thanks.
I got what I need.
Thanks very much.
I didn't say anything.
Oh, so it's just a coincidence
that I've been dragged in here
to go over Tom Walker's death just two
days after I told you I killed him?
I didn't tell them what you
said. I would never do that.
Then why am I here?
I can't say.
Oh, sure, of course not.
I can't.
You know, for somebody
who lies all the time,
I'd think you'd be better at it.
Brody...
Oh, please, just stop.
I'm sorry.
Fucking me to get information,
is that part
of the job description?
Or do you get a promotion
for showing initiative?
What was that about?
Nothing.
He's mad about having to answer
the same questions over and over.
Okay.
He is. What?
I think I got a lead
on Tom Walker. Interested?
Come on.
They called me back to Langley.
To answer more questions
about Tom again.
You don't have to explain
where you were.
Jess,
you have every right
to be mad at me.
I know I've been impossible.
And I know I can't just vanish for
two days without hurting you all.
After eight years,
what's two more days?
What's that supposed to mean?
You don't even care?
Because I do.
(sighs)
Brody, I hung on for six years.
Six years after they told
me you were dead.
Six years after a Marine
came to the door
and said they were going
to start paying death benefits.
I waited for you
because I wanted so much
for you to be alive.
Then I screwed up.
I didn't wait long enough.
I screwed up.
But I can't keep
paying for that.
You don't have to.
(sobbing) I can't.
Damn it.
(sniffles)
Chris will be home soon.
It's not your fault.
None of it is.
That's what I'm
trying to tell you.
And I don't want
everything to fall apart.
Remember what you
said about Walker
when we found out he was
watching his son?
You said his family
was his Achilles heel.
That's what got me thinking about this.
About what, exactly?
His son spots him at school.
I thought maybe he'd try some
other form of contact.
Well, I think he did.
Okay, press "Enter."
It's right there.
Okay...
Phone records?
Helen Walker's phone records.
Galvez got 'em for me.
Turns out there's something
very interesting about them.
Look at the time stamps.
8:10, 8:08, 8:14, 8:11.
All on weekdays.
Made from various
disposable cell phones.
S-So wait, Walker's been
talking to his wife?
No. That's the point.
At 8:00 a.m. she takes
the kid to school.
The calls come in
when she's not there.
Listen.
What is it?
(phone ringing on speaker)
Just listen.
RECORDING: Hey, this is Lucas.
And Helen.
LUCAS: Please leave a message
after the tone,
with your name and address,
and the time you called,
and the date,
and why you called,
and for who, and when...
HELEN:
And we'll call you back.
LUCAS:
Depending on your answers.
His Achilles heel.
He calls just to
hear their voices.
(door opens)
Who does?
You can say;
he's cleared.
This is Special Agent Hall,
our FBI liaison on
the Walker task force.
That phone message.
It's Walker's wife Helen
and his son Lucas.
He calls when he knows
they won't be there. Why?
Well, like Saul said,
just to hear their voices
on the answering machine.
To feel like he still belongs.
This is how we find Walker.
We get Helen to
pick up one morning.
She draws him out
while we track the GPS.
Well, how is her state of mind?
Think she can handle it?
I can get her there.
HALL: That's your plan?
You wait for him to call
and then cross your fingers
that the wife doesn't
sink this whole mess
by saying something
she shouldn't?
I mean, we have
a critical situation here.
A Marine sniper
turned by Abu Nazir,
on U.S. soil, targeting his own country.
CARRIE: Yeah.
That's what we told you.
Agent Hall has
a suggestion how to proceed.
I was just telling
the Assistant Director
exactly how we tracked
down Whitey Bulger.
Right. You put ads on TV.
We took the lead.
We enlisted the public.
What I'm saying is
there's things to do
besides sitting here,
waiting for him to call us.
Like you did with Whitey Bulger?
Exactly.
Who it took you 20 years to find?
Okay. So, uh,
we all know each other.
Walker's out there,
we need to find him fast.
Assess what our
approach should be,
I'd like a recommendation
on my desk in two hours.
Now, Agent Hall...
(phone ringing)
Somebody gonna get that?
How about you?
I'm not getting it,
I'm winning. DANA: Not anymore.
Watch this.
DANA: Whoa! Well, I'm out.
I'll get it.
Where are all these aces coming from?
I don't know.
DANA:
I'm good at this game.
Hello?
Mrs. Gaines.
All right... Elizabeth.
Uh-huh.
Yes, of course.
Who's Mrs. Gaines?
You know. That lady at church
with the chauffeur.
What's a chauffeur again?
Like, one of those little dogs?
I swear to God, you're like
a half idiot, half moron.
Dana.
Well, seriously.
I'll ask.
She says she invited us
to a party tomorrow night.
Oh, she did. I forgot
to get back to her.
I'm supposed to tell you
we're gonna look back on it
as the party of the year.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
Do you want to go?
We don't have to.
DANA:
Are you guys joking?
Elizabeth Gaines promises
the party of the year,
and you're actually thinking
about not going?
Well, I'm going if you're not.
Okay.
Uh, we'd love to.
Thank you.
Wow.
Thank you very much.
She's sending a car.
Around 7:00.
A car?
Dad, when something
good happens,
you just gotta
learn to say yes.
I've never heard
you say anything
remotely nice about Elizabeth.
How come we suddenly have to
go to one of her parties?
'Cause the alternative is
sitting here watching you pack.
I have to.
No, you don't.
I leave the day after tomorrow.
You don't have to leave,
that's my point.
All your friends will be there.
I know.
You can explain to them.
The necessity of this
precipitous departure.
Saul... 'Cause I can't,
for the life of me,
after 25 years together?
I don't understand.
Is this how you're going to be?
Because I can't take
a whole evening of it.
I'm going to be this way
whether we go out or not.
The difference is at Elizabeth's
they'll be serving champagne.
(doorbell rings) Okay. We go.
For old times' sake.
But my flight does
leave the next morning.
Right.
And I'm going to be on it.
Right, right, right, right.
I heard you.
What?
Are you okay?
I'm a little busy, actually.
Can I come in?
Estes put me in charge
of the task force.
Congratulations.
Yeah, to you.
It was on your recommendation.
And because of the phone idea,
which was also yours
but somehow became mine when
you handed it to me today.
(sighs)
This can't wait?
No.
Saul, you look out for me.
You always have...
and...
You saw me arguing with
Brody earlier today.
I wasn't honest
with you about that.
Yeah.
I kind of got that.
When the surveillance on
Brody was shut down...
I contacted him.
Personally.
(whispering):
How personally?
At a support group first.
And then we saw each other.
A few times.
Look, I was chasing
the wrong guy.
"Chasing," good word for it.
Well, it's...
it's moot, now.
It's over.
It should never have happened.
Do you get that?
Yeah, I do.
Why else would I be here?
And like I said, it's over.
You okay?
Yeah, I'll survive.
Well, with any luck Tom Walker
calls his wife tomorrow morning,
we track him down and
we're all heroes by noon.
(scoffs)
Come on.
Get some sleep.
See you tomorrow.
(cell phone ringing)
Saul. We're good here.
The son's just
leaving for school.
Helen Walker?
She seems okay.
I was about to give her
a last-minute pep talk.
Great. We're good to go then.
You sound jazzed.
Better than last night, anyway.
I was weaned on
inter-agency noncooperation.
Nothing makes me happier than
seeing the FBI stand around
with their dicks in their hands,
watching us work.
Lovely.
They're ready to
trace the call.
If it's even him.
It will be.
When he calls,
you need to engage him.
Keep him talking.
So you can find him.
So we can help him.
Is that what everyone on
this task force is saying,
"let's help Tom Walker"?
Helen, it's important
you understand.
He hasn't done anything
wrong, not yet.
We're all working
to keep it that way.
(phone rings)
Okay, we're a little early here.
Are you set?
Talk to me. What the hell
sort of trace is that?
Wild routing through
a series of numbers.
Two continents so far.
Okay, just hit Mumbai.
She needs to pick up
before it goes to voicemail.
Helen.
(phone rings)
Helen, you need to get that.
Hello?
WOMAN:
Hi. This is Diane.
Do you need your carpets professionally steam-cleaned?
Okay, cut this, please.
DIANE: Well, we have a special
offer just for you.
Right now you can get
up to five rooms
professi...
Cut it.
Thank you.
Reset, please.
(sobbing)
There, see?
You can do it.
I can't. I don't even
know what to say.
He misses you.
And Lucas.
That's why he calls.
You need to show him you
feel the same way. How?
By saying I gave up,
got remarried? No.
By saying you've
told Lucas about him,
you've shown him pictures,
enough that he actually
recognized him.
You've kept him alive
in your son's thoughts.
When Tom calls...
tell him that.
(phone ringing)
Hello?
(click)
(dial tone buzzes)
Fuck. He hung up.
I don't see any GPS data.
Tell me we have something.
Signal originated at cell towers
in northeast D.C.
Call was most likely made
within a mile of there.
So what do we have on
street cams in the area?
Ivy City, coverage is sketchy.
Well, let's see it, come on.
Where's facial recognition?
There you go.
Again.
Chris. What are you doing?
I don't want to miss the car.
It's a hired driver,
he'll come to the door.
It's not like he's trying
to avoid detection.
Have you noticed?
What?
They're not fighting.
CHRIS:
He's here.
Mom! Dad!
The driver's here!
Sweet! Come on,
check it out!
So. How do we look?
Swear to God,
I must be adopted.
(laughs)
You look beautiful.
You can stop staring now.
I'm not.
Yes, you are.
I can feel it.
So do you, by the way.
You look handsome.
Who's gonna tell me that when
you're halfway around the world?
We're chasing this guy at work.
20 of us from Langley
plus the FBI.
He's got this fatal flaw,
this weakness
we're trying to exploit.
Carrie calls it
his "Achilles heel."
What is it?
He loves his wife.
♪ Let someone start
believing in you ♪
♪ Let him hold out his hand ♪
♪ Let him touch you... ♪
Hi, there.
♪ And watch what happens ♪
There she is.
(indistinct conversations)
Oh, will you excuse me?
Sure. Okay.
Saul, Mira.
Good to see you two
together, finally.
It must be great to have
her back.
I hope she never leaves.
He's even crankier than usual
when you're gone.
Do us a favor,
stay put this year.
Is that Vivian?
Excuse me.
Well...
did I accidentally hit a nerve?
Accidentally?
I doubt it.
Well, I may have heard rumors.
Oh, my God! Look at them.
Excuse me.
Don't you look lovely.
Thank you.
Thank you for sending the car.
You didn't have to.
Oh, well, I wanted to be sure
you actually made
an appearance.
Saul?
Do you know Saul?
Yes. Yes, we've met.
A couple times.
This is my wife Jessica.
Saul Berenson.
Hi.
The bar's through there.
Grab a drink and
I'll introduce you around.
Thank you.
Thanks.
♪ ♪
Elizabeth...
you have that look.
Well, they are perfect,
aren't they?
SAUL:
For what? What are you up to?
You've been poking around
about Brody
ever since he became the
poster child for D.O.D.
You have some plan
in the works for him.
Oh, I have a plan for
everyone, you know that.
You're grooming him.
For what exactly?
By the end of the evening
you just might find out.
(sighs)
All tucked in...
finally.
I've never heard so many
reasons not to go to bed.
Oh, he's not even asleep yet.
Matt's up there reading
to him right now.
He seems very devoted
to your son, Matt does.
You were lucky to find him.
Yeah, I was, very.
And despite everything,
being married to Tom,
that was lucky, too.
I mean having him in my life,
those years before he left.
What about you?
Me?
Who's in your life?
Oh, I met somebody.
But I don't think
it's gonna work out.
BRODY: So that's what
we're tasked with, my squad,
to safeguard this,
this artwork,
I guess you'd call it.
It's in the one
presidential palace
that's still held by the enemy.
So we shoot our way
into the palace,
we engage multiple targets
down this long hall.
We finally get into the
room where this is,
this-this national treasure
we've risked our lives for,
this solid gold bust
of Saddam...
and somebody's already replaced
it with a Mr. Potato Head.
(all laugh)
Will you excuse me, gentlemen,
for one second?
Sure.
Thank you.
Would you excuse me?
Okay, I have to ask.
I know what you're gonna say.
So I'm not imagining.
Everyone's...
being really nice to us, yes.
It's weird. And that guy...
Head of the Democratic
National Committee.
His wife practically jumped me.
She said, "I want you
to think of me..."
"...of me as
your new best friend"?
Exactly.
What's going on?
I don't know.
(chuckles)
Want to get some air?
Yes.
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking about
all the things
that happen in people's lives...
that pull them together
or split them apart.
The million little events,
coincidences...
the outside forces.
Mira leaves tomorrow, right?
I've been there myself, Saul.
Three times.
I know what it looks like,
what it feels like.
If you ever need
to talk to somebody,
believe it or not,
I'm a good listener.
You know, you were asking what
Brody's being groomed for.
You're about to find out.
Make yourself useful.
Get the Brodys to the library.
REPORTER (on TV): Capitol Hill is
calculating the political fallout
following the press conference
by Eighth District Congressman
Richard Johnson
caught in
a sexting scandal, sending nude
and seminude pictures
of himself
to a number of
Congressional interns,
charges he vehemently denies.
This is a setup, a persecution.
The facts will show these
accusations
to be completely without merit.
My wife and I are gonna get
through this together.
And no, I have absolutely no
intention of deserting
my office or the voters
who put me there.
REPORTER: The Congressman pledged
to disprove the allegations
and serve out his term.
House Minority Leader
Ellen Randall expressed
disappointment
at the news and has called
for an Ethics Committee
investigation to determine
whether any other violation...
He'll be gone in two days.
I have an idea who
might replace him.
The impact of the scandal
on Johnson's status
as Chairman of the House
Armed Services Committee.
The Congressman has been
a fierce opponent
of the administration's efforts
to allocate more funding
for unmanned surveillance
and drone strikes in
the Middle East.
(chuckles)
"Dick Johnson?" Really?
That's his name.
Well, he should think
about changing it
if he's gonna be doing
stuff like that!
You're drunk.
Not as drunk as I bet Dick
Johnson is right now!
(both laugh)
You saw how everyone
was looking at you, right?
They were looking at you.
This was a... really nice
date, Sergeant Brody.
You showed me
a really good time.
Dick Johnson.
(chuckles)
Wow. My feet are killing me.
Oh, shh!
(TV playing)
How was it?
Fancy.
You guys said you'd be
in bed by 11:00.
It's Ice Age, Mom.
I think I missed this one.
Not one. You missed,
like, three.
What's wrong with the elephant?
It's a woolly mammoth, Dad.
Shh!
(sighs) Here. Move over.
I'm coming in.
(groans)
(sighs) Your arm okay?
Hmm...
Mmm, popcorn.
I'll have some of that.
Mmm.
(phone rings)
Hello?
Tom, is that you?
Tom?
Lucas said he thought
he saw you
at his school.
Holy shit!
(phone buzzes)
Hey, Carrie, we're live.
You sure?
Yeah.
I didn't hear it ring.
Notify the FBI team on the
ground, then patch me in.
Where's Helen?
I don't know.
Saul, we're on. Get up.
I am, Carrie. I'm up.
No GPS data.
Phone must have it blocked.
Well, get past it so I'm not
just guessing here.
Okay, I'm on it.
You don't have to say anything.
I know you're listening.
I can feel you there.
Okay, I think we're there.
Got it.
Tac One,
immediate left onto
New York Avenue.
Proceed five blocks, then left.
(tires squeal)
And I need you to know
that I never gave up on you,
I never lost hope.
But Lucas,
he was getting so big...
And a boy needs a father,
that's what you always said.
And it... it wasn't enough,
me raising him on my own...
not if he was to have a future.
Our son.
But I never stopped
loving you...
never.
Not for one second.
(voice breaking):
And when Lucas said he thought
he'd seen you
that day at his school,
my heart was so glad.
Just the thought of it
was a miracle.
And I don't care
why you're back, I don't.
Just that you are.
TOM:
Helen.
(gasps)
Oh, baby, I've done
a horrible thing.
No, Helen, no. Don't! Don't!
They're tracing this call!
You got to get out of there!
You hear me?!
Get out now!
(tires squealing)
Patch me into the tac team.
GALVEZ:
Okay, you're connected.
Do not lose the target!
He's not the target!
He's my husband!
(tires squealing)
Okay, what's your position?
Okie Street pushing east. He's
moving towards the rail yard.
Negative. That position
would be too exposed.
We've got a sighting.
No, he'll stay
where there's cover.
(groans)
Hello?
Galvez, what just happened?
I'm not sure.
I think Tac One is down.
Where?
What is his position?
Mount Olivet Street.
Olivet.
Okay, they're on him.
Following.
Target in sight.
No.
Wait.
What do you mean?
They need to flank him
on the next street.
Contain him, but stay back.
Galvez, tell me you copy.
It's too late. They're in.
He's running!
Gun!
(gunfire)
(clamoring)
FBI! Do not move!
Show me your hands!
Show me your hands now!
FBI! Do not move!
Do not move!
(sighs)
(crowd clamoring)
OFFICER: Folks,
I need you to stay back.
(angry clamoring)
OFFICER: Stay back, all of you.
Behind the barricade.
(angry clamoring continues)
Anyone care to tell
me what happened?
The tac team followed
Walker here.
Two casualties.
Local Muslims here
for morning prayer.
We cleared the building,
including the Imam.
I think I saw him outside.
Looked very unhappy.
Walker assaulted
our team leader.
Took his weapon.
Operating theory is
that he fired first.
That's very much in dispute.
Where's Walker?
SAUL:
We're looking.
ESTES:
Meaning you have no idea.
CARRIE: We were right on top of him.
We'll find him again.
ESTES:
It better be soon.
This is a nightmare.
I couldn't agree more.
Suggestions?
The way I see it,
we're down to one option.
We go public about Walker.
Appeal for help finding him.
And what about
what happened here?
Call him a terrorist.
What happened here won't matter much.
Saul?
(sighs)
I'll draft the language.
Let's regroup at Langley.
The sooner we get this
done, the better.
(conversing indistinctly)
(buzzing)
Who is it?
It's okay.
Go back to sleep.
What are you doing here?
There's something
you need to know.
Not at 6:00 in the morning.
Tom Walker is alive.
You're lying.
No.
It's not possible.
It's true.
I killed him with my own
hands, just like I told you.
No. Abu Nazir made
you think you did.
There's a manhunt on
for Walker.
He's somewhere in the area.
We're going public with the
information in a few hours.
I thought you deserved
to hear it first.
I wanted to tell you
at Langley, but I couldn't.
It was still classified.
But I need you to know that I did not
betray your confidence to anyone.
I would never do that.
I knew for a fact an American
P.O.W. Was turned.
I didn't know Walker was still
alive any more than you did.
Don't hate me because
I thought it was you.
I don't hate you.
You just did what you had to.
Just did your job.
No, it wasn't just my job.
(door opening)
Is she...?
CIA.
(sighs)
SAUL:
Mira, I'm so sorry.
We had a severe meltdown.
Two innocents were killed.
Muslims waiting
for morning prayers.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
It's okay.
No, it's not okay.
I said I'd be here to make breakfast,
take you to the airport.
I'm already late, Saul.
I'm here now. I'm here.
It's better I take a cab.
You know how far it is
from here to Delhi?
7,503 miles.
Well, we're still
going to talk.
Sure.
I'll text you.
(sighs)
Please don't do this.
When I woke up this morning,
Saul, you were gone,
and it hit me that there hasn't
been one day since I've been home
that you were there at night
and then you were still
there the next morning.
And I couldn't even remember
when was the last time
you were home
for 12 straight hours.
And I don't think
you could remember either.
It's my weakness.
(sniffles)
My Achilles heel.
Every time they'd
call me, I'd go.
I'm gonna miss my plane.
(engine starts)
(sighs)
(stifled sob)
The first news reports
about Walker
hit the air less
than five hours ago.
We've already had
nearly 2,000 sightings.
All of them probably nothing.
If I'm Walker I'm burrowing
into my hole right now.
Carrie?
We're going to have tips
a mile deep by morning.
It'll be tough to wade through.
We'll need to prioritize.
I had a kind of epiphany today.
About Walker?
I wish.
No, about me.
I'm going to be alone
my whole life, aren't I?
♪ ♪
(alarm warning beeping)
(beeping stops)
(mechanical voice):
Fault, zone two.
(newscast plays indistinctly)
WOMAN: a war hero,
and now he's at the top
of the FBI's Most Wanted List.
MAN: Could this be just an
extreme case of PTSD,
or is Walker a member
of al-Qaeda?
WOMAN:
This isn't some troubled vet.
The FBI called Walker
a credible threat
with ties to subversive
elements.
MAN: Right here in D.
C.? That's correct.
Walker?
Are you crazy?
The entire country is
looking for you.
You can't be here.
You people told
me Walker was dead.
(shouting)
(groaning)
(yells)
My friend.
(screaming) You told
me I killed him.
You made me believe.
I don't know!
(gagging)
Really, really!
You have to talk to Abu Nazir!
I'm through talking with Nazir,
and you can tell him that.
(gasps)
Tell him it's over.
(wheezing)
(panting)
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com