PRESIDENT REAGAN: Air and naval forces
of the United States
launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
REPORTER: Pan Am Flight 103 crashed
into the the town of Lockerbie.
REAGAN:
...savage acts of terror in
Africa, Europe,
the Middle East.
GEORGE H.W. BUSH: This will not stand, this
aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
REAGAN:
This relentless pursuit of terror.
We will make no distinction.
REPORTER:
The USS Cole was attacked
while refueling in
the port of Aden.
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable
and cowardly act.
The next song
we're going to play for you
is one of the good old
favorites.
Until something shocks him...
WOMAN: I'm just making sure
we don't get hit again.
MAN: That plane crashed
into the World Trade Center.
Thousands of people running.
We must and we will remain
vigilant at home and abroad.
(speaking Arabic)
SAUL:
What the fuck are you doing?
God!
CARRIE: Fuck! I missed
something once before.
I won't...
I can't let that happen again.
SAUL:
It was ten years ago.
Everyone missed something
that day.
CARRIE:
Everyone's not me.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Homeland:
I got a mood disorder, okay?
I looked it up, Carrie.
Clozapine's an antipsychotic.
Only seven this time?
Raiding my samples cupboard
not only enables you,
it jeopardizes my license.
So... seven pills.
The terrorists are
still out there.
We need Brody in the public eye
reminding America
that this is far from over.
And smile for the cameras.
Look at him. He's been blogged
and tweeted about
and solicited by every
national talk show.
During the debrief, Carrie
mentions Abu Nazir's name
out of the blue.
Three days later,
one of her assets reports
the first Nazir sighting in over
seven years.
Maybe it's coincidence.
Or maybe there's something
she's just not telling us.
This intelligence
your asset gave up
her life to acquire,
do not squander it
by continuing to invade
the constitutionally protected
privacy of the Brody family.
You need to take down
that surveillance.
We're on to the next case.
Raqim Faisel.
FAISEL:
He followed me to this house.
AILEEN: Darling, I promise no one
knows we're living here.
I still think we should leave.
Our instructions were
to sit tight.
You knew this would not be easy.
I can't help but feel
I'm missing something.
You're missing him.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Hey, I know you.
I'm not supposed to be here.
Hey, look, I'm not going back
in if it means
you can't go back in.
That's not necessary.
Maybe we can hold our own
private meeting out here.
How's that sound?
It's tempting.
(grunts)
(chanting in Arabic)
(Brody's chanting continues)
(jet engine whining)
(whining gets louder)
(doorbell rings)
(baseball game playing on TV)
FRANK:
Run, you fat fuck, run!
Christ, you call
yourself a ball player?
He's safe, you fuckwit!
Geez, you freak.
COMMENTATOR:
A double and a single in the fourth.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you're wrong.
Why don't you just man up
and admit it, asshole!
That's right, you jerkoff,
I'm talking about you!
You're a goddamn disgrace!
Unfucking believable!
The only team in baseball has
to pinch run their leadoff man.
How long you been
standing there?
What? I can't hear you.
Oh, well, yeah. Oh, yeah.
There. Hey.
Hey. I rang the bell,
like five times, Dad.
Hey, is Maggie home?
No, she had to go deal
with some patient crisis
at the hospital
Hey, you hungry, huh?
She say how long she'd be?
I can make you a sandwich.
You want a sandwich?
I got, we got turkey,
lettuce...
(phone rings)
Shit, I gotta get this.
Uh, yeah, turkey's great.
Uh, hold on a second.
Hello.
Hey, Danny.
What?
The one surviving terrorist
from the compound in Afghanistan
where we rescued Brody.
Scooped him up in some
shitshack in IBD.
Clean lift. Nothing broken,
nothing spilt.
Okay, I'll be there
in 30 minutes.
(sighs)
Oh! Sweetie!
(chuckles)
Welcome.
Hi. You okay?
No, happy to see you is all.
Yeah?
Over here.
(Frank sighs and
clears his throat)
Educated guess says you, uh...
you need this to go.
Sorry, Dad.
(steam hissing)
(sighs)
Oh. Oh, you must think I'm ready
for the glue factory, Carrie.
Unplugging the iron like that.
Come on.
I'm just trying to be safe.
Did you take your meds
this morning, Dad?
I did. Thank you for asking.
Bad enough I've got your sister
up my ass 24/7.
Now you, too?
And just so you know,
those pills are killing me.
No they're not, Dad.
Sometimes you just feel like
you're spinning out
of control a little
when they bring you
up instead of down.
That happens to you, too?
It's a good time
to avoid household appliances
in my experience.
I was distracted,
I was excited to see you is all.
(sighs)
Okay, message received
and understood.
I wish I could stay and help you
out with the chores.
Yeah, right.
Well, you enjoy.
Drive safe.
And...
Fuck the C.I.A.
SAUL:
So, how are your parents?
MIRA: Wonderful. They seem to
get busier and busier.
We need to get them
over here more.
Too much work in
Mumbai for that.
That's what they would say.
Maybe they ought to think
about handing the slums project
off to somebody else now.
What have you lost?
Ticket for the parking.
WOMAN (over P.A.):
Will standby passengers...
It'll be in the car,
where you always leave it.
(phone ringing)
Oh. That didn't take long.
I love you so.
I tell you that already?
Go on, answer it.
I know you have to.
Hello? Saul Berenson.
He wants everyone here ASAP.
No, no, no, on the secure link.
Get me Captain Mike Faber
at the Pentagon.
GALVEZ: Has been alerted
and is in-bound.
I'm gonna get a cab.
Oh, and Estes wants everyone
to clear their schedules...
Mira, wait. Wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Um... no.
I-I know what that look
means, Saul, and I'm not.
I'm not angry, I'm really not.
And I hope I see you later.
Saul?
Yeah, yeah, I'm still here.
All right,
before the briefing starts,
there's a report
you need to read
from the Pakistan phase
of the interrogation.
I'll be right over.
Afzal Hamid.
34 years old, Syrian.
According to our friends
in Pakistani Intelligence,
a mid-level member
of the Islamic People's
Liberation Army.
Abu Nazir's group.
Which means he most likely has
knowledge of Nazir's plans
to attack us here
in Fortress America.
Including money trail from the
Hawala shop-- where it went,
what it's being used for.
ESTES: Which is exactly why
you and Carrie
will interrogate him.
With the help of Sergeant Brody.
Excuse me. Sergeant Brody?
Yes, Carrie, Sergeant Brody,
who is in a unique position
to establish a baseline
on Hamid. Right or wrong?
Right.
Now, the interview
itself will take place
at a designated safe house,
yet to be determined.
Brody absolutely
can't be there.
He will be there, Carrie.
That ship has sailed.
Then we might as well
just hand our playbook
straight to Abu Nazir.
Well, the alternative
might be worse.
Nothing is worse than Brody
witnessing this interrogation.
The blowback will be profound.
Assuming we do what
you want then-- that is,
share your suspicions
about Sergeant Brody--
what do you think
will happen then?
Well, it might force David
into a decision.
A decision based on what?
How many times must we
have this discussion?
There's no evidence linking
Brody to Abu Nazir.
This is a different
discussion, Saul.
This is about
operational security.
(sighs)
Okay, Carrie.
March up to his
office right now.
Tell him he's been duped.
Tell him Sergeant Brody's
location in Afghanistan
was intentionally leaked
by Nazir.
Tell him the story
of his American hero
has a surprise twist.
See what he does then.
My guess-- you're
packing your cubicle,
looking for a job in
the private sector.
Don't we have a moral obligation
to say something?
Our obligation is to stop
the next attack on America.
Which you won't be a part of
if you keep pursuing this.
Has it occurred to you
at the very least
we'll be able to observe Brody
at close quarters
in a high stress environment
which we can control.
Yeah, it's occurred to me, Saul.
Has it occurred to you
if we do our jobs
and break Afzal Hamid,
he just might give up
the whole plot,
including Sergeant Brody?
Well, that's a big if, Saul.
You're screwing up my rug.
Either David Estes makes the
weather, Carrie, or we do.
Your choice.
(rhythmic breathing)
This can't be good.
Jess said I'd find you here.
It's urgent.
Langley needs to see you.
Langley?
So you better haul ass.
Shit, shower, shave, be ready
sometime in the next 40 minutes
when they come to get you.
What do they want?
Didn't say.
Eyes only classified.
You couldn't have
just called me?
They told me not to.
No open line phone calls.
Jesus.
Yeah, no shit.
You went by my house already?
Figured I'd stay out
of Jessica's hair.
You figured right.
Is that it?
Can't tell me anything else?
That's all I know
right now, Brody.
If I knew anything else,
I'd tell you.
Yeah.
What did Mike want?
The CIA wanted to see me.
About what?
I don't know.
(sighs, pants)
Going to take a shower.
They'll be here any second now.
Hey. Are you okay?
You know what, Jess?
Can you just stop
asking me that
every two minutes? I'm fine.
Okay. Okay.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...
No, you're right. I get it.
(door opens)
CHRIS:
Hey, Dad.
Mom said you wanted to come
watch my karate tomorrow.
She did?
He's getting his blue belt.
If I pass the test.
So can you come?
Sure. Wouldn't miss it
for the world.
(shackles clinking)
(engine starts)
North. So not Langley.
No blindfold or anything?
We trust you.
Sir, we're five minutes out.
Copy that.
♪ ♪
Estes, we're up. We're online.
Sergeant Brody,
Carrie Mathison.
We met at the debrief
a few weeks ago.
Yes. Uh, good...
good to see you.
Thanks so much for coming.
How are you settling
back in with your family?
Yeah.
Um, can we get you
anything-- a coffee,
or soda or water--
before we get started?
Get started with what?
Have a seat.
Do you know this man?
Motherfucking shit.
(zipping)
Yeah, I know him.
He was my guard.
Visual recognition confirmed.
Do you remember his name?
They called him Affie.
CARRIE: His full
name is Afzal Hamid.
He was the sole survivor
of the attack
on the safe house
where you were rescued.
(urinating)
(urinating stops)
(zipping)
Who's he?
My colleague.
As-Salamu alaykum.
(speaking Arabic)
What's he doing?
He's waiting to see
if Hamid will say
something first.
This is the first stages
of an interrogation.
Not exactly.
Pakistani Intelligence
held him for three days
before they turned him over.
Did he talk?
I'm afraid
I can't tell you that.
In fact, I can't share
any operational details
with you at all.
Then why am I here?
CARRIE:
Two reasons: one, to confirm
his identity, which
you've just done,
and two, to provide
us with information
we can use to unsettle him.
To prove we have
complete control.
To demonstrate our omnipotence.
Are you comfortable with that?
Yeah, I think so.
Okay, good.
Are you ready to begin?
One question.
Go ahead.
Will he be tortured?
We don't do that here.
What is it you think
he knows about?
Like I said, I can't...
Divulge operational details.
Got it.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, I'm ready.
You can put this
on now, please.
Tap the mic twice so my
colleague knows we're ready.
Do you speak English?
Please.
Does he?
Did he ever speak
English to you?
They all spoke some English.
This is for my friends
in Guantanamo.
(screaming)
SAUL:
We know you speak English.
Therefore, I will continue
to address you in English.
Are you a religious man?
Okay, this part needs to move
a little faster.
Are you good with that?
They all prayed.
They're extremely devout.
Of course you are.
SAUL:
This soldier
was your prisoner.
When did you first meet him?
Damascus.
We know you didn't meet him
until Damascus--
that's when
the interrogations began,
didn't they?
And you were part
of those interrogations,
weren't you?
Yeah, he was.
For how long
was Sergeant Brody interrogated?
Days?
Months?
Years.
It went on for years,
didn't it?
What did you do
to Sergeant Brody, Afzal?
If you have a detail
we could use.
He beat me with a stick
wrapped in barbed wire,
and he pissed on me.
You beat him
with barbed wire
and urinated on him.
So you're a religious man
and a torturer.
What are you, Catholic?
You think your wife and sons
are still alive?
There, you see that?
That's exactly what
we were going for?
He was convinced
we already know
the answers to our questions.
Now he thinks
we know if his family is alive--
information he wants.
SAUL:
Let's back up, shall we?
Five days ago, you're safely
hidden away in Islamabad.
Or so you think.
I mean, why else have
your family with you.
Then suddenly
in the dead of night,
you disappear without a trace.
It's not just your
poor wife and children
who are wondering
where you are.
One man in particular
is beginning to worry.
Abu Nazir.
Who, as we all know,
is not your average
Islamist terrorist
bent on bringing down
Western civilization.
No, this man has
a certain style,
a certain...
...artistry.
Let's take the case of
Yasser Akram, for example.
Lifted by our British friends
from a villa in Lebanon
in August 2006.
Within days of his capture,
his only brother...
a good and holy man,
is killed in a car bomb.
The Yemeni police had
to ship what was left of him
in a small plastic bag
to a lab in Dubai
just to identify him.
Not to mention
what was done to...
his poor parents...
to his wives...
and most disturbingly,
to his children.
We can protect
your family, Afzal--
up to eight individuals.
But we don't have much time--
Abu Nazir is not a patient man.
You can come in now, Joelle.
(door opens)
When you're ready to talk to us,
write down their names
and addresses.
If you love your kids,
like I love mine...
I would hurry.
(door opens)
(door closes)
(Carrie sighs)
Now what?
Now we wait for him
to pick up that crayon.
When the interrogator said
that he could protect his...
We already have his wife and
children out of harm's way.
You can go home now;
thank you for your help.
We've got it from here.
Hey, guys?
Hey, would you just
let me in the room with him,
just for a couple of minutes?
I just want to look
the prick in the eye,
let him know that
the tables are turned.
You know I can't do that.
I wish I could, but I can't.
You do see that, don't you?
Sure.
Look, go home,
forget about today,
forget about all this--
and, of course,
it goes without saying...
Don't tell anybody.
Hey, but if you do find yourself
needing to talk to someone,
um...
Anytime,
24/7.
Good-bye, Sergeant Brody;
you've been a big help today.
ESTES:
Hey, Carrie?
Hey.
Excellent work,
both you and Saul.
Doesn't get
any better than that.
Let me know Thank you, David.
the minute Hamid makes a move,
one way or the other.
I will.
Well?
When you turned over
that picture of Abu Nazir,
he stopped breathing
for a few seconds.
I know he's hiding something from us,
I know it.
Shit!
What?
Well, now's the time
we really could use that
surveillance on his house.
Don't go there, Carrie.
Be patient.
All right, I'll take the doom watch.
You go be with Mira.
I'll call you if
anything happens tonight.
Pace yourself.
Come on, asshole,
pick up the damn crayon.
JESSICA:
Brody.
Sorry, I didn't mean
to startle you.
Hey, where you been?
You cut your hair.
(laughs)
What do you think?
Nice.
You always liked it short.
No, I like it. Really.
You did something for me by
going to that support group,
so I thought I'd do
something for you.
Tea?
Thanks.
(groans)
What are you doing out here?
Nothing. Just
enjoying the quiet.
Rough day?
What was it about, anyway?
I'm not really supposed
to talk about it, Jess.
Not even a little?
I can't.
I'm sorry.
How's your tea?
Good.
Yorkshire Gold.
Your favorite.
It's perfect.
(clears throat)
Thanks.
(loud heavy metal playing)
(heavy metal stops)
(exhales quietly)
(loud heavy metal playing)
(loud heavy metal continues)
(heavy metal stops)
(loud heavy metal playing)
(filling cup)
(heavy metal stops)
(exhales)
(groans softly)
(fan whirring)
(loud heavy metal playing)
(water sploshes)
(exhales)
(fan whirring)
(loud heavy metal playing)
(heavy metal stops)
Saul...
looks like he's getting ready.
Eight names--
four in Islamabad, three in Lahore,
one in Larkana.
That's gonna take some doing.
First we need
a show of faith from you.
Do you understand
what that means?
I don't know anything.
You know I don't.
That is how we operate--
for exactly this reason.
Say good-bye to your family.
An e-mail address in Pakistan.
Whose e-mail?
I don't know.
I swear to you.
Now you promise...
my family...
my children.
What do you send to
this e-mail address?
I forward ones sent to me
from someone else.
Who?
Was the location of the compound where
you were holding Sergeant Brody
deliberately leaked to us so we would find him?
Carrie. Carrie.
Did Abu Nazir ever
meet Sergeant Brody?
(chair creaks)
First...
my family.
Then we talk.
We'll be back.
Come on in.
Thank you for meeting me, sir.
You know, when I told you
my door was always open,
Sergeant Brody, I meant it.
Good timing--
it appears
our friend in the safe house
is getting ready to do business.
No friend of mine, sir.
Uh, no, no. 'Course not.
What can I do for you, Sergeant?
I believe I've earned a moment
face-to-face
with my torturer, sir.
Yeah, I, uh... I heard.
And I've got to tell you
that Carrie was correct.
She doesn't have
the authorization
to let you in there with Hamid.
Do you?
As much as I'd like to...
Sir, can I stop you there,
save you the trouble?
Please.
Nobody respects your
operational concerns
more than I do.
I did not come here to tell you
that I can get Hamid talking
any quicker than
your own experts can.
But yesterday, I did exactly
as was asked of me,
hard as it was just to sit there
and watch us dance around
his rights,
after what he did to me
for eight years.
Now you're telling me
he's ready to talk.
I think that means
I've earned the right
to at least look him in the eye,
and tell him
that he didn't beat me,
he doesn't get to win...
Sergeant Brody...
Sir, I haven't finished,
if you don't mind.
This is really important to me.
I need to do right
by my wife and my kids,
and I need to be fully able,
both physically and mentally,
to honor my duties
as a Marine and as a man.
But first, I got to close
the door on this chapter
of my life.
That's all I ask, sir.
Please don't rob me of the
opportunity to do that.
For my own sanity,
if nothing else.
Sergeant, would you, uh,
would you wait outside
for a second?
Lorraine, will you
get me the DCI.
Yes, sir. Right away.
Let's, uh...
Let's go close that door,
Sergeant.
We sent a phantom e-mail
to the one Hamid gave you.
Whoever it is
will never actually
receive the e-mail
or know that it was sent.
So far, it's bounced
off of a server in Rio,
where it went through
a re-encryption
filtering protocol,
then to Johannesburg--
same drill--
then to Thailand,
then Finland, and now,
nearly an hour later,
your guess is as...
(computer chimes)
I'd say you owe me dinner,
Carrie.
Possibly even sex.
Holy fuck.
I wouldn't go that far.
(sighs):
Jesus Christ.
The 14th man gave up
an e-mail address we just traced
to the Engineering Department
at Bryden University.
Faisel? Are you
fucking kidding me?
The professor we
tailed then cleared?
Correct. Everybody stop
what you're doing.
Only thing I need you
to do right now
is find this man: Raqim Faisel.
Faisel hasn't been
at the university all day.
And he's not home, either.
What home address
you got for him?
An apartment in Truxton Circle.
(sighs)
(dialing)
Virgil, I need you to look for
something at Bryden University.
Yeah, today. Right now.
(door opens)
(door closes)
You beat me.
You humiliated me.
You killed my friend.
But you did not break me.
You should've killed me
when you had the chance.
But now, here we are.
I'm a sergeant in the United
States Marine Corps, shit-bird.
How did you think
this would end?
Hey! Hey, come on!
(grunting)
Calm down!
Calm down.
(Brody panting)
Thank you, sir.
Means a lot.
(Hamid speaking Arabic)
VIRGIL:
Fact is,
these eggheads
and whatnot may be
smarter than all of us
put together in this room.
But what I learned
over the years,
when it comes to safety
in the workplace,
you would not believe some of
the violations that I've seen.
Can't you come back when
Dr. Faisel is actually here?
I'm not comfortable letting
people in his office
when he's not present.
We understand, ma'am.
Um, look, uh,
if we damaged anything,
I can put in the paperwork
to pay for it.
Maybe we can help you
with one or two of
the violations in here.
Excuse me?
Are-Are you
suggesting...
No, he's not.
Not on my watch.
Just do the paperwork,
numb nuts.
(phone ringing)
Yes, we have a few
potential violations
we'd like to report.
That could be Dr.
Faisel calling now.
Hey.
Hello.
Know where this address is?
Hello?
Right next to
the fucking airport.
Hey.
See that new belt he's wearing?
Yeah.
Blue.
Impressive.
I'm sorry I missed it.
I wish I'd been there, son.
I got caught up at a meeting.
It's okay.
Mike took me.
Yeah, I see that.
MIKE: Ice cream?
No, I'm good, thanks.
Have some.
We're celebrating.
Anyway, I should hit the road.
Did your mom ask Uncle Mike
to take you to karate?
MIKE:
It's no big deal.
I've been taking him
for the last, uh, three years.
CHRIS:
Four.
I started when I was eight.
MIKE: Right. And look
at you now.
A blue belt.
Pretty damn awesome, huh?
Right, Brody?
You bet.
What meeting?
I can't talk about it.
Your son did awesome today.
You should be proud.
Didn't you say you
were leaving, Mike?
See you later, bud, okay?
Later, gator.
(door opens, closes)
Got any sprinkles?
CARRIE: He led us right past this house
just this last Tuesday.
VIRGIL: Which probably means
he knew we were tailing him.
Should've had us do it.
MAX:
Dead quiet in there.
Not a squeak.
Maybe they're taking a nap.
Sometimes, I swear to God,
he's my own brother,
and I don't know
if he's part moron
or just acting like
it to piss me off.
(cell phone ringing)
What's going on, Saul?
SAUL:
He's dead, Carrie.
Hamid's dead.
Suicide.
Jesus Christ, no.
Wha-- How?
When?
Carrie, what happened?
Minutes ago.
I just got here.
Body's still warm.
How the hell is that possible?
Razor blade fragment,
left wrist.
What? Where did he get that?
H-He must have had
it on his person.
We missed it.
Saul, he had to have
gone through
at least a dozen
full body searches.
The fragment is tiny.
He could have had it
concealed in a cavity
or under his skin
in scar tissue.
Or somebody passed it to him.
Passed him what?
Carrie...
Admit it's possible, Saul,
because we're sitting on
Dr. Faisel's
house right now,
and there's no sign
of him anywhere.
What's your point?
My point is, whoever gave
Hamid the razor blade
could have warned
the professor, too.
A fucking razor blade?
I want authorization to go in.
Estes wants us
to watch and wait.
Damn it, Saul, there's no time!
If Faisel is on the run,
we need to know now.
You have my authorization.
Move in.
Alpha team, go.
Bravo, cover the back.
Charlie team, stand by.
Here we go.
MAN: House is empty.
He must have left in a hurry.
Looks like for good.
Did you hear that, Saul?
Saul?
(speaking Hebrew)
(Saul continues speaking Hebrew)
(door closes)
(footsteps approaching)
I'm so sorry.
(exhales)
I know what you're gonna
say, and you're right.
All I can say is this is not how
I planned your first days back.
You must still be
jet-lagged.
Why are you still up?
You should be in bed.
I know that look.
You been waiting up for me.
What's wrong?
Saul, darling,
you know what's wrong-- you just more
or less said so in a nutshell yours...
Wait, wait. Please
not do this right now.
Do you mind?
It's been a very, um...
complicated day.
Your life is a very
You must...
be aware, Saul,
this last month in
India with my family
I've been doing
a lot of thinking.
Soul searching.
We discussed this
before you left.
I can start scaling back,
maybe even get reassigned,
spend more time at home.
Just listen.
I actually realize now
it's not right or fair
to ask you to do less.
So what I need--
me, Mira--
is to make my life
not just about you.
You know,
you said yesterday
that my parents
should pass
the Mumbai slums project
onto someone else.
Not to you. I didn't mean to you.
Our life is here, Mira.
Our life is
wherever you get sent--
Amman, Beirut, London, Aden--
often at a moment's notice,
and I need more than that.
I need to make my life...
I need to make my life
about my passion.
I need to put my
roots down somewhere
that matter to me, Saul.
(doorbell rings)
Do I get any sort of say in all this?
Are you gonna get that?
Mira.
How was your trip?
Welcome home.
Uh, um, it was wonderful.
It was an inspiring time.
How are you...
Carrie?
I'm so sorry, I really
didn't mean to intrude.
However...
It's really important that I talk to you.
It's, uh, so lovely to see you,
but I didn't sleep
on the plane,
so I'm completely
sideways. Forgive me.
We'll catch up soon.
That'd be great.
Good night.
Don't say I didn't warn you this whole
thing would blow up in our faces.
SAUL:
What the hell?
Who let Brody in
that room with him?
Who do you think, Saul?
Jesus fucking Christ.
Yep, I had pretty much
the same response.
(sighs) Brody must
have identified
that camera blind spot while
watching the interrogation.
SAUL:
Just so you know,
the working theory
is that Hamid smuggled
the razor blade inside
the soul of his shoe.
Bullshit! I mean, not only did Brody
contrive to get himself in the room,
he orchestrated Hamid's suicide
and he warned Dr. Faisel.
And we-- you and I--
let it happen.
(low grunt)
Enough on the sidelines,
enough in the shadows--
we need to take this up the chain
before we're counting bodies
and trying to spin yet another
monumental intelligence screw-up.
Don't think I'm
not considering it.
Well, how about doing
something about it?
Because nothing's
changed, Carrie.
Wh-Wh... What do you
mean, nothing's changed?
I don't see Brody giving
Hamid a damn thing, do you?
Not a razor blade,
not a goddamn summer cold.
Good! You know?
Get angry!
I'm over your whole
detached routine.
(whispers):
You're out of line.
This is my home. Get out...
I'm going to Estes
with or without your approval.
Take some boxes with you,
'cause you're gonna need 'em
when you clean out your desk.
What happened to the Saul Berenson
that trekked the Karakoram,
did three months in
a Malaysian prison
stared down Uday Hussein
at the height of his power?
When did you become
such a pussy, Saul?
(whispers):
I think you should leave now.
With pleasure.
You know what?
You can keep that.
Fuck this shit!
(door opens)
(door slams)
(panting quietly)
(panting)
(crickets chirping)
Carrie.
(crying): I'm sorry, Maggie.
I didn't know where else to go.
Oh, God, what happened?
I think I just quit my job.
MAGGIE:
What? Don't be silly.
No, I'm serious.
I'm done. I'm done!
I've had it up to here.
All right, just stop. Stop.
Stop.
You were so right,
you were so fuckin' right
- when you told me that my job would kill me
one day. - Just take a deep breath.
Calm down, 'kay, Carrie?
Carrie, just calm down, okay?
Does Saul know about any of this?
Saul?
No, S-Saul is part
of the problem.
But you said he
always had your back.
Well, I'm on my own now,
that's for damn sure.
Do you really want
to know the truth?
I've been on my own for a while now.
Stop.
We both know you're not
quitting anything, okay?
It's just the heat
of the moment,
it's not you, okay?
That's not who you really
are-- I know you. So...
this is what's gonna happen.
You're sleeping here
tonight, okay?
My guest room's
already made up.
The girls are gonna be over the
moon to see you in the morning.
Yeah.
(laughs): 'Kay?
Listen, I don't care if
the world's about to end,
okay, you're gonna stay here
for as long as it takes
for you to get
your head straight.
'Kay?
Promise me that you'll
sleep in in the morning.
I'll try.
Hey, thank you.
Aunt Carrie?
Hey.
What's wrong?
Nothing, sweetheart.
Did something happen?
We heard you and Mom talking.
No, girls, really, I'm fine.
Why don't you girls
get back to bed
and let Aunt Carrie
get some rest, okay?
Can we sleep in here?
Yeah. Please?
(laughs)
You sure?
I'm positive.
Come on in.
MAGGIE:
Get in there.
I'm sleeping right here.
(speaks indistinctly)
Okay.
Sweet dreams, guys.
(laughs)
Mwa!
Hey, no, stay there.
Stay there.
(exhales)
You know, I meant it when I said
I wouldn't miss your karate.
I screwed up.
I'm sorry.
Can you forgive me?
I'm proud of you.
You're a blue belt now.
You got it done,
like I knew you would.
You know why?
'Cause you're my son.
What are we praying for?
Since I was four,
me and Mom prayed
every night...
that you were alive...
that you'd come home one day.
And now?
That you're gonna be okay.
♪ ♪
Auntie Carrie?
(whispering):
Shh... Close your eyes.
Close your eyes.
What are you doing?
(sighs) Nothing, Pumpkin.
I just can't sleep.
Are you worried
about the bad guys?
What bad guys, Josie?
You know, the ones
who blow people up.
Are you worried?
A little.
Yeah. Me, too.
I have an idea.
Come live with us.
We'll protect you.
No, honey.
You know what?
That's my job.
Okay.
Go to sleep.
♪ ♪
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com