Air and naval
forces of the United States
launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
Pan Am Flight 103 crashed
into the town of Lockerbie.
He has sanctioned acts
of terror in Africa...
This will not stand, this
aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
His relentless
pursuit of terror.
We will make no distinction...
The USS Cole was
attacked while refueling in...
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable
and cowardly act.
The next song
we're going to play for you
is one of the good old
favorites.
Until something stops him...
I'm just making sure
we don't get hit again.
That plane crashed
into the World Trade Center.
Thousands of people running...
We must... and we will
remain vigilant.
What the fuck are you doing?
Fuck! I missed
something once before.
I won't... I can't
let that happen again.
It was ten years ago.
Everyone missed something
that day.
Yeah, everyone's not me.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Homeland...
An American prisoner of
war has been turned.
Hello?
Jessica? It's me. Brody.
We need eyes and ears
on Brody from the minute
he steps off that plane.
Wait, there's no camera in the
garage? And now he's placing
a bag containing God knows
what in our blind spot?!
Three days ago, we were
about to tell your kids.
He's my husband, Mike.
I know this is hard, but that's his
job now-- to be a public figure.
You know, Mom,
it'd be a lot less funny
if you weren't fucking
his good friend Mike.
We need Brody in the public eye,
reminding America that
this is far from over.
How has the homecoming been?
It's been great...
for all of us.
Five days ago, on Prince Farid's
yacht, the prince's majordomo
announces that the prince
has a surprise visitor.
Abu Nazir.
His Highness has a
special favor to ask,
a job he wants you to do.
She was DOA at Providence.
Apparently, they had her wearing
some crown jewel type necklace
that's vanished.
Maybe Abu Nazir really
went on that boat
to talk to someone
in the prince's entourage.
You're looking for a money
transfer, right?
Jewelry is the easiest way
to move wealth.
Four hundred.
Where did the money go?
Could be anywhere.
Congratulations.
I hope you'll be happy here.
For us, it's perfect.
♪ ♪
Service A's today, Marine.
Shirt first.
Green pants.
Khaki tie.
You left it on the back
of the bathroom door.
Hey, Jess, have you seen my tie?
In the bathroom,
behind the door.
And smile for the cameras.
What can I tell you
that you don't already know?
Not much.
But here goes.
This is what I learned
over there.
Friendly fire isn't.
In an ambush,
shoot for the knees.
Never lie.
Never leave a man behind.
And if you pick it,
it will not heal.
Good luck in your deployment.
Remember your training.
God bless you
and God bless America.
Look at him.
Ever since that Lawrence
O'Donnell interview,
it's been like this
wherever he goes.
He's been blogged and tweeted
about, offered book deals,
been solicited
by every national talk show.
The vice president tells me
you had a hand in convincing
Sergeant Brody to go
public with his story.
The vice president didn't send
his chief political operative
here to thank me
for delivering Brody.
You're right.
I came to find out how closely
the public image
matches the man.
Now, for someone who's been
through what he's been through,
Sergeant Brody seems remarkably
composed.
Are you asking me
if he's emotionally stable?
Is he?
I'm not a psychiatrist.
But you ordered his psych
evaluation in Germany,
which I'm sure you reviewed.
So, if we looked under the hood,
what would we find?
Well, we weren't exactly vetting
him for national office.
That is why you're
here, isn't it?
In the most preliminary sense.
Then again, if his psychological
profile checks out,
and his politics are correct,
why not?
I sure know a lot of folks
who would open their checkbooks
to him right now.
Sorry to interrupt, sir,
but Saul Berenson is outside.
Tell him I'll be right out.
I'm sorry, Ms. Gaines,
but I need to take this.
My colleague has never learned
how to take no for an answer.
The vice president remembers
well your conversation
regarding directorship.
Any information
you could give us
on Sergeant Brody would
be much appreciated.
How much longer is he gonna be?
He'll be right with you.
Did you tell him I have an
operational protocol for him
to sign off on?
Sir, right now, he's in a meeting with...
Lizzie.
Saul.
We'll see ourselves out.
Nice to meet you.
Major.
So, tell me what's so important
that it couldn't wait.
Abu Nazir, David, remember him?
Two horns, long tail,
a strong scent of sulfur?
I think we found out how
he's financing his attack.
This is a photograph
of the prince's chief aide,
Latif Bin Walid,
taken nine hours after Lynn Reed
was killed.
And the necklace she was wearing
that the police reported
as stolen...
we believe it was
in this package.
You're saying that was the money
transfer we've been looking for?
It's a working theory.
Hard to believe Latif
would park a half a million
dollars in some Laundromat.
Not when that Laundromat's
doubling as a hawala broker.
Hundreds of millions move
through these informal networks
every day.
And because they're based on
an honor code,
there are no records,
which makes
financial transactions
nearly impossible to track.
Yeah, but hawala systems are
typically used to transfer funds
across borders, internationally,
not as dead drops.
What you're suggesting is pretty
unorthodox, isn't it?
Abu Nazir is always unorthodox.
That's why he's still out there.
Our friends at the Bureau
have ongoing surveillance
of the five known hawala
operations in the metro area.
That's where we got this photo
of Latif at the Laundromat.
Since then, 51 customers have
come and gone.
One of them may have the
necklace or its cash equivalent.
One of them may have the money
that Abu Nazir is using
to fund an attack
on American soil.
Why not just ask the guy
who runs the place which one
came for the necklace?
Same reason we're not
extraditing Latif.
Arrests at this time would be
of negative value.
We don't want to spook Abu Nazir
before we know how many others
he's activated.
Lynn Reed was killed
three weeks ago.
That means we're three weeks
behind the bad guys.
Which is why we need to
initiate an operation immediately.
Work up files
on all these people.
Do it.
All right, you heard him.
Let's start putting everybody
through facial recognition,
cross-referencing with INS, DMV,
every database we've got.
And once that happens, we'll split into
five two- person teams and run them down.
That means background checks,
limited surveillance,
selective face time with
family, friends, employers.
Hey, can I talk to you
for a minute?
The FISA warrant
expires tomorrow.
If you're asking me to
try and extend it, don't.
At least hear me out.
I had to drag a skeleton from
Judge Turner's closet
to get you those four
weeks in the first place.
I know what you did.
And you still haven't produced
a single lead connecting Sergeant Brody
to this or any plot against America.
That doesn't mean I'm wrong.
It just means he may be
laying low for awhile.
Turned and trained,
but a sleeper.
You're arguing against
yourself, Carrie.
We can't watch him
indefinitely, and you know it.
But, Saul...
Listen to me.
Listen carefully.
This intelligence your asset
gave up her life to acquire--
do not squander it
by continuing to invade
the constitutionally-protected
privacy of the Brody family.
It's not an either/or
proposition.
The money we're tracking
is connected to Brody.
I just haven't found out how.
If you're right, the money will
eventually lead back to him.
But until then, you need to
take down that surveillance.
First chance you get, you will
remove the cameras and microphones
from Sergeant Brody's house,
and cover your tracks.
Are we clear?
I'm just saying,
they were a bunch of kids.
They're Marines, and they were
looking at you like a rock star.
Not because I was
a POW for eight years.
Because my face has been
plastered all over TV
for the last three weeks.
Whatever the reason, your visit
meant a lot to them, Brody.
Well, I'll take
your word for it.
Good. I'll see you tomorrow.
All right.
Hey, you hungry?
I think we have steaks on the grill tonight.
Thanks, I'm good.
I'm just gonna grab
something on the way home.
You sure you don't want to come in?
Yeah.
Why not?
Mikey, all I'm saying is,
for the last two weeks,
you've hardly come by once.
I've been driving your
ass around every day.
I figured you'd be
sick of me by now.
See? That's exactly
what I'm talking about.
Every time I invite you
into the house,
you make up
some lame-ass excuse.
If I didn't know
any better, I'd...
think you were avoiding us.
Hey, I just figured... I thought
I'd give you some space.
I mean, let you be alone
with your family
without me getting in the way.
Well, I appreciate that, Mike.
You looking out for the family.
And for Jessica.
Like you did while I was gone.
You'd have done the same for me.
You know what?
I'm not sure I would have.
Ah, I'll see you
tomorrow, Mike.
All right.
What's so interesting?
There, in the woods.
See the antlers?
It's
an eight-point buck.
It's beautiful.
Yeah, until he tramples
those tulips you planted.
How'd it go with the recruits?
Great.
Good.
Yeah.
When's dinner?
Whenever you want.
Okay, well, we need
some more propane.
Don't worry, honey,
probably just had a bad day.
Forget it, doesn't matter.
Come on, let's go wash up.
Are the kids asleep?
Well, then,
what are you waiting for?
♪ ♪
Yo, wild man.
Cut that shit out,
you're gonna miss the war.
♪ ♪
Come on, tuck in your shirt.
Dana-- she's waiting
in the car.
Did you see the flowers?
I did.
I told you.
I'll put out some soap flakes.
Soap flakes?
Yeah,
the deer think they're
smelling people.
If that doesn't work,
we can build a fence.
Build a fence--
there's an idea.
Maybe Mike could do it;
He's pretty handy.
Carrie?
Are you ready?
Come on, we don't have all day.
They're only gonna be in church
for, like, an hour and a half.
Rolling up this operation
is a fucking mistake.
You don't agree?
It's not like we have a choice.
Saul said that he would
have my head on a stick
and parade it out in front
of the inspector general.
Yeah, but what do you think?
I mean, you've been watching
Brody as long as I have.
You must have an opinion.
Look, we've been on him
for a month and
we've come up empty.
W-What about Max?
What does Max think?
He thinks the wife
is hot, okay?
Come on.
♪ All people ♪
♪ That on Earth do dwell ♪
♪ Sing to the Lord ♪
♪ With cheerful voice ♪
♪ Him serve with fear ♪
♪ His praise forth tell ♪
♪ Come ye before Him ♪
♪ And rejoice ♪
♪ The Lord ♪
♪ Ye know, is God ♪
♪ Indeed ♪
♪ Without our aid ♪
♪ He did us make ♪
♪ We are His folk ♪
♪ He doth us feed ♪
♪ And for His sheep ♪
♪ He doth us ♪
♪ Take ♪
♪ The Lord, ye know ♪
♪ Is God indeed ♪
♪ His mercy is ♪
♪ For ever sure ♪
♪ We are his folk ♪
♪ He doth us feed ♪
♪ To Father, Son ♪
♪ And Holy Ghost ♪
♪ The God Whom Heaven ♪
♪ And Earth adore ♪
♪ From men and from ♪
♪ The angel host ♪
♪ Be praise ♪
♪ And glory ♪
♪ Evermore. ♪
♪ Amen. ♪
I have been looking
all over for you.
Just a second.
We're done here,
it's time to go.
You ready?
There's one camera left.
Thought I'd let you do
the honors.
Hey.
That was a beautiful service.
Yes, sir, it was.
Sergeant, this is
Elizabeth Gaines.
She is one of the vice
president's closest advisors.
It's an honor to meet you,
Sergeant Brody.
This happened yesterday?
When I dropped him off.
What did he say exactly?
He asked why I haven't been
coming around the house.
I told him
I didn't want to intrude.
Think Dana said something?
No. Well, maybe we should
just go ahead and tell him ourselves.
What we should have done is
tell him right away
when he first got back.
Now it's turned
into this big lie.
Your story has inspired
a nation in need of inspiration.
Well,
I'm not so sure about that.
I asked Major Foster
to introduce us because
there's something I'd like
to discuss with you.
May I take you
to lunch next week?
Yes, ma'am.
Don't drive yourself crazy.
I just think that
maybe we should try
to find a way for us all
to be together again without
feeling so damn awkward.
We're having some people
over tomorrow night.
Good, good, I'll be there.
Hey.
We've barely spoken
in three weeks.
I'm kind of, kind of
worried about you.
I'm fine.
Tell me.
It's just...
he's so...
What?
Nothing.
Jessica, I want to know.
Work permit expires
at the end of November.
Lives with two roommates
in Tenleytown.
Single mother back in Jakarta.
So she's sending money home,
which explains her visit
to the hawala broker.
Personal references
all check out,
and I called up
her supervisor at Exotech.
Mm-hmm. Diligent, super bright,
star of his
I.T. department.
All right, moving on.
Where's Carrie?
Oh, she should be here soon.
She said she was running late.
She say why?
No, sir.
How well do you know her?
I like to think we're friends.
I understand she's
a bit of a folk hero
to some of you analysts.
Well, we've all read
the cables, sir,
heard the stories.
With you it's more
than that, isn't it?
You want to do what she does.
It's no secret I've
put in for Operations.
Three years in a row.
You know, you don't look
like a Galvez.
I take after my mother, sir.
She's Lebanese.
And your father?
Guatemalan.
They met at the DMV.
My mom refused to take off
her headscarf for the photo,
my dad was the guy
taking the pictures.
America.
Yes, sir.
Your file says
you're fluent in Arabic.
And Spanish, sir.
You know, there might
be something opening up
in the Cairo station.
My recommendation would
carry weight... which
brings us back to
Carrie Mathison.
I didn't put you
with her by accident.
I don't understand.
During a debrief,
Carrie mentions
Abu Nazir's name
out of the blue.
Three days later,
one of her assets reports
the first Nazir sighting
in over seven years.
Maybe it's coincidence.
Or maybe there's something
she's just not telling us.
You want a taste of Operations?
Find out if she's running
something on the side.
Sir...
I'm not sure I-I'm
comfortable with...
Spying?
I'm making sure there are
no loose cannons
rolling around on my deck,
because if there are,
I need to tie them down.
Hey, Carrie.
David, hi.
Sorry I'm late.
What was that all about?
Uh, he wanted
to review the, uh, Jalbani file
before he cleared it.
So we're onto the next case.
Raqim Faisel,
Assistant Professor
at Bryden University.
That woman you were talking to
at church today-- who is she?
Oh, she works for
the vice president.
Works for him how?
Some kind of advisor.
What did she want?
She wants to have
lunch with me.
Why?
No idea.
I invited Mike over
tomorrow night.
He knows most of the people
who are coming, so...
No. It's a
great idea, Jess.
The more the merrier.
Better go check on Chris,
make sure he's doing
his homework.
Yeah?
What happened to you?
- You just disappeared.
- I had some personal stuff
to take care of.
Yeah.
Well, uh, okay, listen.
I just, uh, finished running
background on Faisel.
Listen to this.
Three trips to Lahore
in the last 18 months.
For what purpose?
Unclear.
I put in a call
to Pakistani intelligence.
Oh, I don't trust those fuckers.
Make some appointments
at the university,
find out what you can.
And tomorrow,
you and I will spend
some quality time
with our professor.
You know, it's customary
to wait for someone to say,
"Come in"
before you actually come in.
You didn't say anything
to your father, did you?
About what?
No, I didn't.
'Cause if you did...
Ma, I didn't say a word.
Jesus, it's like the Spanish
Inquisition around here.
I believe you, okay?
What are you doing, Ma?
I'm sitting on your bed.
Well, yeah, I can see that.
Is that a crime?
No, not exactly.
What then?
Is something wrong?
No.
Are you guys gonna get
a divorce?
No.
We're not getting divorced.
'Cause if you are, I just
want you to know
that I'm cool with it.
I just think you guys should do
whatever's best for you.
Dana,
no one's getting a divorce,
okay?
Okay.
You should probably
tell Chris that, 'cause he's,
like, totally certain
you and dad are gonna
ruin his life or something.
Rumor or fact?
What, me and Estes?
Why are you so interested
all of a sudden?
I don't know. I keep hearing
you guys had a thing once.
Is it any of your business?
We had a moment.
Misguided. Ancient
history now.
What?
I was on the wrong side
of that bet.
Why? Does it seem
so unlikely?
Kind of.
Well, he was the smartest guy
in the Near East
Division by a mile.
It's not that. It's just,
I don't see a lot of love lost
between you two.
It didn't end well.
Does it ever?
Uh...
That's our guy.
I thought you said
he lived in Truxton Circle.
He does.
Not headed there now.
Hello?
Where is he?
It's after 4:00.
He should be on his way here.
Tell him the traffic's bad
on the beltway.
What did you say?
He should use
an alternate route.
Tell him now.
Guy hasn't broken
the speed limit once.
Does that make him more
or less suspicious?
Makes him boring as shit.
We tailed him all afternoon.
After class, he drove
to a Moroccan restaurant
near the airport,
where he dined alone.
Second team's outside
his apartment now.
His briefcase looked full,
so, my guess is,
he's in for the night.
What's he an assistant
professor of?
Mechanical engineering.
Tenure track.
Generally liked.
Published, peer reviewed.
Muslim?
Yeah, but not a Koran thumper.
Worships at Kalid Muhammud.
What about those
three trips to Pakistan?
Lecturing at the University
of Lahore. It all checks out.
He was delivering
a series of papers
on alternative
energy applications.
All right. Then see what second
team comes up with tonight.
If nothing, move on.
Hey, uh, whose
birthday is it again?
I think it's Mitchell's.
I'm gonna go buy him a drink.
Sure. How about you?
You want another?
Uh, no. I should go.
Stay and visit.
Visit?
Why not?
Why are you being nice to me?
Do I need a reason?
Not unless you want me
to believe a word you're saying.
All right.
Okay.
It occurs to me that
I've been holding on to the idea
of being angry at you,
rather than actually
being angry at you.
Just so we're clear, are
we talking about Baghdad,
or what happened pre-Baghdad?
Both.
Did you just get diagnosed with
cancer, or something, David?
You see? It's a
habit for you, too.
Neither of us can get past it.
Past what exactly?
Our
period of distrusting
each other.
Well, that could have
been pretty much any time,
couldn't it?
I don't know about that.
Well, if I never said
it, I'll say it now.
I'm sorry, David.
Just so I'm clear,
are we talking about Baghdad,
or what happened pre-Baghdad?
Both.
Both. But mostly pre.
I can't believe I chased you
up to New York like that.
No, I never should have
left in the first place.
You deserved an explanation.
I don't know. I might
have run away from me, too.
If I had known your marriage
would break up, David...
No, no.
The truth is, it was
probably over anyway.
How is Victoria?
Remarried.
To a nice Jewish guy
from Fort Lauderdale, a doctor.
She and the kids
converted last year.
You're kidding me? Victoria?
Well...
mazel tov.
He's short.
So, how's it been?
It's been tough, I won't lie.
Well, at least he's home.
Joanie's husband
is still over there,
and she only gets
to talk to him once a month
on the SAT-phone
when he's back at Battalion.
Yeah.
How's the sex?
I know.
It's awful, right?
More like nonexistent.
Denis couldn't get it up
for almost a year. Really?
Oh, yeah. What about drugs,
like Viagra, or whatever?
No, the problem wasn't
between his legs. It's up...
Have I ever been
with an impotent man?
I don't think so.
Well, you haven't lived.
Mm. Ooh!
Oh, uh, looks like
they might be, uh...
Oh, there she is.
Hey, Jess.
Hi.
This is Demmie.
Demmie, Jessica.
Jessica, Demmie.
Debbie, nice to meet you.
It's Demmie with two M's.
Demmie.
Come in. Let me get you guys
something to drink.
Okay.
Where'd you find her?
It was short notice, all right?
So, where's Brody at anyway?
I don't know. I haven't
seen him for a little while.
I have no idea where he is.
Want me to find him?
That would be great.
Thanks. All right.
I'll be right back.
Brody?
So when are you going back
to work full-time?
This week, I think.
That'll be good.
Get you out of the house a little more.
Are you hungry?
I am starving...
Brody?!
Jesus fucking Christ.
Brody? What's going on?
Is everybody all right?
Looks like the soap flakes
didn't really work, Jess.
I killed the deer.
Give me the gun, Brody.
Back off, Mike.
Mom!
Go back inside, Chris.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Come on, Chris,
let's go inside.
It's gonna be okay.
You know what, Mike,
I can handle this.
Can you please
just tell everybody to go home.
No, I'm not leaving you alone.
Just go, please.
Do what she says, Mike.
Make sure Chris stays inside.
I don't want him
coming back out here.
Chris? Why?
What's the problem?
What do you think I'm gonna do?
I don't think you're
gonna do anything.
All right.
I'm gonna go get a shovel,
clean up this beast before
the flies get to it.
Goddamn it!
Don't walk away from me, Brody.
He was eating all your
flowers, for Christ's sake.
What's the big deal?
You fired a weapon!
In front of our friends,
in front of our son!
You want to believe
that's normal, go right ahead.
There's nothing wrong with me.
Is that right?
You barely sleep, you turn
your back on your friends,
you scare your children.
I mean, you won't even...
What? Say it.
You can't even fuck your wife!
We need help, Brody.
I see what this is.
Time for me to get my head
shrunk, go to psych services?
I don't give a shit
who you talk to,
as long as you talk to somebody.
What if I say no?
Then I can't do this anymore.
♪ ♪
There's no point
in imagining the worst.
I'm not imagining.
They followed me to this house.
They followed you
past this house.
Darling, I promise, no one
knows we're living here.
How can you be so sure?
Because if they did,
they'd be tearing
apart the living room,
not driving by outside.
No.
I still think we should leave.
Our instructions
were to sit tight.
In the meantime, we owe it
to ourselves not to panic.
You have a class to teach.
In less than an hour.
It's important that you do
exactly what you always do.
Go to work.
Hiyati.
We knew this would not be easy.
Who's next?
Sheik Eyad Hassoun.
He's a groundsman
for the Islamic House
on Constitution Avenue.
Any red flags?
It depends.
On what?
What you consider a red flag.
He was arrested 12 years
ago for refusing to leave
an unpermitted rally.
What was he protesting?
The presence of U.S.
Troops in Saudi Arabia.
All right, start with
his immigration status.
I'll be right back.
Any luck?
Not yet.
Keep laboring in the vineyards.
Something will turn up.
What I wouldn't give right now
for a little retail
intelligence.
Disenchanted imam,
an Islamist kid
halfway to the bomb belt.
A live source.
That would be nice.
Anything else
on your Christmas list?
Yeah.
Let me put Virgil and
Max back on Brody.
But this time, we
leave no footprint.
Just a light tail, two
12-hour shifts. No.
But we're following
all these other targets.
In case you hadn't noticed,
there's a lot of political heat
on the good sergeant.
Now more than ever,
we need to keep our distance.
I know it's hard.
I can't help but feel
I'm missing something.
You're missing him.
When you're on somebody
all the time, it's like that.
You know that
as well as anybody.
He's in your rearview
now, Carrie.
You're moving
in another direction.
Understood?
Yeah.
Hey.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Just watching the storm.
Oh, yeah?
Is it coming or going?
Hard to tell.
Coming, I think.
You want to join me?
I was just getting ready to go.
There's a, uh...
There's a veteran'
support group meeting
at the church tonight.
Okay.
Thought I'd...
Thought I'd drop in
and just try it out.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yeah, don't thank me yet.
I don't think
I'm gonna be able to stomach it
for more
than about five minutes.
Well, let's get you an umbrella,
just in case.
Stay away from the milk.
Spoiled.
Thanks.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey, no worries.
No worries.
Hey, I know you.
You were in the debrief at...
Please.
What?
It's just, I'm...
I... I'm not supposed
to be here.
Why not?
Okay, seats everybody.
Time to begin.
Hey!
Hey, wait.
Wait!
Look, I'm sorry.
I really had no idea
you were in this group.
I'm not. It's my first time.
Well, then, I'll leave you to it.
Hey, hold on.
Hold on a second.
What you say
your name was again?
Carrie. Carrie Mathison.
Look, I don't understand.
It's, uh... it's...
What's the problem?
It's totally fine
with me if you want to stay.
No, it's not that.
It's just, uh...
no one in there can know
what I do for a living.
I'm still an active
intelligence officer.
Your secret's safe with me.
Besides, I'm better
at spilling my guts
to total strangers anyway.
I hardly ever go
to the same meeting twice.
Sounds complicated.
You all right?
Are you?
Anyway, you should go back in.
They're getting started.
Hey, look, I'm not going back in
if it means you can't go in.
Please, really, that's...
That's not necessary.
Or maybe we could hold our own
private meeting out here?
How's that sound?
It's tempting.
Right?
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Where was it you said
you served again? Baghdad?
Yeah.
How come it's so hard
to talk about
with people who weren't there?
I have a better question.
How come it's so hard
to talk with anyone
who wasn't there
about anything at all?
Okay, now I really am going.
Don't leave me like this.
All alone...
in the rain!
You'll be fine.
Nobody expects you
to say anything
till the second
or third meeting anyway.
Well, that's assuming I get
to the second or third meeting.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com