Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
PRESIDENT REAGAN: Air and naval
forces of the United States
launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
REPORTER: Pan Am Flight 103 crashed
into the town of Lockerbie.
REAGAN: He has sanctioned
acts of terror
in Africa, Europe,
the Middle East.
PRESIDENT GEORGE H.W. BUSH: This will not stand,
this aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
REAGAN: This relentless
pursuit of terror.
PRESIDENT GEORGE W. BUSH:
We will make no distinction...
REPORTER:
The USS Cole was attacked
while refueling
in the port of Aden.
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable
and cowardly act.
The next samba
we're going to swing for you
is one of the good old
favorites.
Until something stops him.
WOMAN: I'm just making sure
we don't get hit again.
MAN: That plane crashed
into the World Trade Center.
Thousands of people running.
We must and we will remain
vigilant at home and abroad.
(speaking Arabic)
SAUL:
What the fuck are you doing?
God!
CARRIE: Fuck! I missed
something once before.
I won't... I can't
let that happen again.
SAUL:
It was ten years ago.
Everyone missed something
that day.
CARRIE:
Everyone's not me.
Previously on Homeland...
You're telling me
the fucking CIA
thinks I'm working for al-Qaeda?
I think you're working
for al-Qaeda.
We were wrong about Brody.
Wait!
I was-I was wrong.
This weekend, this time
that we spent together,
it was real.
Hey, Carrie, fuck you.
I pray every day that you never
lose sight of what
you committed to do
in Issa's name.
This is Issa, my son.
I want him to learn English.
"The house must be strong
to keep them safe."
That's truly excellent.
WALDEN: A drone missile hit and
destroyed part of a compound
in the mountains
of Northern Iraq.
The images being broadcast
of the bodies
of 83 dead children
allegedly killed in the strike,
we believe to be false,
created by the terrorists
for propaganda purposes.
The vice president--
the man most instrumental
in the drone attack
that killed young Issa--
is going to ask you to run
for political office.
Say yes. That will be a signal
to Nazir that you are
still committed to do this.
Aileen just ID'd Tom Walker.
He's the terrorist.
Tom was dead.
That's what they told me.
CARRIE:
What we need to do is find him
before anything happens.
ZAHIRA: Walker-- he meets
with a man to do business.
He drives a car
with the diplomatic plates.
SAUL: That's it on the left--
home of our Saudi diplomat.
What if Mr. Zahrani doesn't give
us anything anytime soon?
We'll figure out an elegant way
to lift and interrogate him.
(saxophone playing jazz riff)
SAUL: What do we know?
Very little, that's what.
But in our line of work,
sometimes very little
is just enough.
Take Mansoor Al Zahrani.
Mild-mannered second secretary
of the Saudi embassy.
Seen here going to work
three days ago.
We surveilled him 24/7.
We've listened to every phone
call he's made in the last week.
We pawed through
his professional life,
his financial life,
his personal life.
In short, we turned him upside
down and we shook real hard.
Two items of interest fell out.
Item one--
Al Zahrani's in debt to the
tune of about $750,000,
all due to investments even
I'd know better than to make.
Item two--
Al Zahrani's gay.
He's got three wives,
ten children.
He's a devout and
conscientious Muslim.
Yet, every Thursday
when everyone thinks
he's out jogging
in Rock Creek Park,
he's in fact, visiting this
bathhouse off Dupont Circle.
We managed to get inside during
his most recent visit.
As you can see,
he's a naughty boy.
I believe that item one and item
two will get us what we want,
which is for this son of a bitch
to tell where Tom Walker is
and what he and Abu Nazir
are plotting.
Most of Al Zahrani's debt
is carried
by a private equity bank
called Market Security.
As I said, we don't have much,
but we definitely
have something.
(jazz playing)
William Pritchard?
That's me.
Ah.
I'm Carrie Mathison.
You're really a spy?
Uh, an intelligence
officer actually.
This is very cool.
Can I tell my wife about this?
No.
Even cooler.
As I mentioned on the phone,
we're interested in
one of your clients--
Mansoor Al Zahrani.
Yeah, I pulled his file.
Makes dismal reading.
How'd you like
to cause him some pain?
I'd rather have the
money he owes us,
but short of that, pain
might be satisfying.
What can I do?
We'd like to borrow your bank.
You sure I can't tell my wife?
(vehicle doors closing)
(knocking on door)
(knocking)
Sergeant Brody?
Yes.
We need to check
your house, sir.
What the fuck?
We're Secret Service, sir.
(door opening)
Sergeant Brody,
sorry for the intrusion.
Everyone's a little on edge
because of your
sniper buddy I'm afraid.
I have to ask-- is Walker as
good a shot as they say he is?
Yes, he is.
Too bad for us.
(chuckles)
Clear the room.
I'm very impressed
with the way you've handled
coming back to the real world.
Thank you, sir.
Representative Richard Johnson--
mean anything to you?
I watch the news.
How would you feel about
running for his seat
in the upcoming
special election?
I would consider it a honor
to work with a man
who's actually fought
the war on terror.
Who's lived among the enemy,
and understands them.
What do you think?
You interested?
Yeah.
I'm interested.
Good news, good news.
I'd need to talk
to my wife first.
Is that a problem?
To be honest, it could be.
Well, we need her on board.
She's half the story.
War hero returns home
after eight years' imprisonment
to his beautiful, loving wife.
I'm sure you'll be able
to convince her.
(clicks tongue)
AGENT:
On the move.
(door closes)
Al Zahrani's got
diplomatic immunity.
That may not mean
much to you people,
but to us mere mortals in the State
Department, that's a serious issue.
We're not dragging him
to Tunisia.
We're not waterboarding.
We'll be very
polite and gentle.
I just want to ask him some
questions during his lunch hour.
The CIA's not even supposed to
be operating on American soil.
It's against your own charter.
This is the FBI's job.
SAUL: Al Zahrani's running a terrorist
cell out of the Saudi embassy.
He and Tom Walker are planning
an attack on the United States.
Fuck the charter.
He doesn't mean that.
Yes, I do.
You don't know if
this thing will work.
You grab the guy...
Entice.
You entice the guy
into the bank, and then what?
You got a couple
of hours maybe.
We figure two at the outside.
You have two measly hours
before the Saudi embassy
starts missing him.
What if he doesn't turn?
Being gay in Saudi Arabia is
like being the Antichrist here.
I'm aware of our cultural
differences with Saudi Arabia.
If Al Zahrani doesn't turn
and we blow the whistle on him,
he can look forward
to losing everything.
I mean everything.
I see no compelling reason not to do this.
Were you not listening?
I just gave you ten of them.
I'm going to the secretary
on this one, David.
And I will be appending all of my
objections right on the fucking order.
Append away.
Carrie, I want you to run
the interrogation.
Shouldn't it be Saul?
Al Zahrani will be thrown
if it's a woman.
Might give us some leverage.
David's right.
Everything we know
about Al Zahrani's in here.
Are you sure you're okay
with my doing this?
You're the right person
for the job.
Saul?
I'm fine.
Remember what you said to me way back about
getting the truth out of these guys?
What?
You're trying to find
what makes them human,
not what makes them terrorists.
Sounds like good advice.
Better get started.
Oh, Jesus. You scared me. Sorry.
Kids get to school okay?
Yeah, with the usual hysterics.
Chris is convinced he's the worst
athlete in the entire eighth grade,
and Dana's convinced
she's a lesbian,
'cause boys disgust her.
What's going on?
While you were gone,
I had a visitor.
Who?
Vice President
of the United States.
In our house?
It's a mess.
I doubt he noticed.
What did he want?
You remember
Congressman Johnson?
That poor bastard we saw
on the TV at Gaines' house?
He's resigning, and they
want me to run for his seat.
I knew it.
You said no, right?
Well, I said I'd talk
it over with you first.
You're actually considering it?
You can't be serious.
Well, what else am I gonna do?
Hell, stay in the Corps and
go back to Iraq? Brody,
we're just getting our
lives back on track.
We're just getting our
marriage back on track.
And you want to go into politics?
We'll never see you.
It'll be like you're
leaving us all over again.
I'll carve out plenty of time
for you and the kids.
No. Absolutely not.
You cannot do this.
I think I can make a difference.
Do you want our family to
be dragged through the mud
by every newspaper and cable
news channel in the country?
Because that's what's gonna
happen-- they're gonna dig
for dirt until they found it.
You don't know that.
Me and Mike.
You and that CIA lady
you fucked.
Don't be naive.
It'll all come out,
every last gory detail.
I got to go change.
I seem to have become
one of those women who takes her
kids to school in her pajamas.
VIRGIL:
Wives.
Three-- Zahra, Hala and Yasmeen.
He met Zahra when
they were both 15.
An arranged marriage,
of course.
He had his first
five children with her.
(groans) Um...
Farid, Suhail...
Gamila,
Huda and Wadiya.
How can someone
be 15 and married?
What could a
15-year-old
possibly know about the
intricacies of a relationship,
about taking care of a family?
More than you do?
Oh...
(phone ringing) (sighs)
Mathison.
Hey, it's me, Brody.
You there?
Yeah, I'm here.
I need to see you.
Why?
It's personal.
Well, when?
Now.
I-I can't.
How about tomorrow night?
What's wrong with tonight?
I'm working.
Yeah, she's working.
Who's that?
Uh, nobody.
It's a... a neighbor.
You sure you can't
make it tonight?
Yeah, I'm sure. Sorry.
Okay, tomorrow.
When and where?
We could go to that bar.
Why don't I just come
to your place?
Oh... Okay. Sure.
7:00?
I'll text you the address.
Okay, great.
See you then.
Hot date?
Hardly.
So you're texting
your address to a plumber?
It's none
of your fucking business
who I'm texting my address to.
So you think we have enough?
You think Al Zahrani will turn?
(sighs)
Well, you know as well as I do,
there's guys who roll over
and beg and mercy,
and then there's those other
guys who get all heroic,
and are willing to die
for the cause.
(sighs)
He's here.
Are you good?
Eye contact, please.
I'm good.
Good. It's good
that you're good.
Good is a good thing.
Carrie.
Eviscerate the motherfucker.
Hey.
They told me I might
find you in here.
Working on your jump shot?
Something like that.
How's the jaw?
Fine.
I'm sorry, dude.
I was way out of line.
No. I deserved it.
What do you want, Brody?
I'm telling you, man, this whole
coming home thing is tough.
I hear you. I'm either parading
around like a toy soldier
or doing the fucking laundry.
I need to be of service.
I need to do something
that matters.
I've been asked by Vice President
Walden to run for congress.
You fucking serious?
Yeah.
Jess doesn't want me to do it.
She's exercising her veto rights.
Why?
I think she's afraid
of being in the limelight.
You want to do it?
I got to do something.
Either that or I keep being
pulled back into fucking Iraq.
It's messing with my family.
I get these moods.
I'm no fun to be around.
Hey, Mikey, you and, uh...
you and Jessica...
you didn't do anything wrong.
And I can't blame you
for whatever happened.
You thought I was dead.
And I know you guys got close.
And I'm sure it's not easy for you
to say good-bye to each other.
And, um, this whole situation
is entirely fucked up.
Talk to Jessica.
Tell her how much
this means to me.
I got to get
my family back together.
And, um... she'll listen to you.
Thanks.
Hey, something else.
You took care of my kids.
I'll always be grateful.
PRITCHARD: Right this way.
We'll get it all sorted out.
Mansoor Al Zahrani, I'd
like to introduce you
to Eli Soodik and
Carol Sweetzer,
my top loan officers.
They'll lay out the details
of your debt restructuring.
I'll leave you to it.
I'm around if you need me.
CARRIE:
Security.
It's an unfortunate necessity
these days.
Security for what?
It's not like you're going
to hand me cash after all.
Please sit down.
Let's begin.
We have some questions
we'd like to ask you.
We don't have much time.
We need to get you back to your
embassy by the end of lunch hour.
You're not loan officers.
Who are you?
I would like to leave now.
I'm afraid we can't allow that.
You're CIA?
FBI?
Whoever you are,
you can't hold me.
I'm a Saudi diplomat.
I have diplomatic protection.
You know what,
I'm going to call my embassy
right now.
This is outrageous.
I will not allow it.
My ambassador will go
straight to the White House
and you will both
lose your jobs.
Why don't you take a look
at these photographs.
Then you can call
anyone you want.
Here.
I will not betray my country.
Of course not.
Sit down please.
You owe Market Security
$750,000.
Your salary at the Saudi embassy
is $170,000 a year.
You've sold all of your stocks
in the past three years.
You have no savings.
You have no other
real estate holdings.
Is that a fair summation?
Your point?
You're spending more than you make.
(chuckles)
Substantially.
Is that a crime?
No, not in and of itself,
but it is curious to note
that you are somehow meeting all
of your financial obligations.
What's in Geneva?
Cuckoo clocks.
Why have you traveled there
six times in the past year?
Business for my government.
Well, our friends
in Switzerland
inform us that on the morning
of last Saturday,
you had breakfast
at the Beau-Rivage Hotel
with a man named Faraz Sabbaq.
He handed you an envelope.
You then carried this envelope
to the Clariden Leu Bank
on Rue Francois-Versonnex.
20 minutes later you exited
the Clariden Leu Bank
without the envelope.
You should know that Swiss officials
had their eyes on Sabbaq,
and then you of course,
because he is a trusted
courier for Abu Nazir.
I don't know Abu Nazir.
Abu Nazir gives money to Sabbaq,
Sabbaq hands money to you,
you deposit the money
in a Swiss bank
and use it to pay your bills.
Why lose everything for a cause
you don't even believe in?
You're obviously not a zealot.
You don't believe in radical
Islam. You love the West.
No more questions.
I am done talking
to both of you.
Do you really want me to share
these photos with your wives,
your children, your parents,
your ambassador?
Go ahead.
Tell everyone you want.
Tell them all, I don't care.
I suck cock and I love it.
Yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy.
My wives already know.
They don't care.
They love me.
So fuck it, huh?
And fuck you.
Put me on CNN.
I'll admit to everything.
Now I would like to go
back to my embassy.
Sit the fuck down!
I'm not finished!
Oh, I think you are. Mr.
Al Zahrani, I'd like to remind you...
You love your children
very much, don't you?
Do you have a favorite?
No, of course not.
I think Janine
is your favorite.
She is a very remarkable
young woman,
but all of my children
are remarkable.
Not one of your other children
is a sophomore at Yale
majoring in
political philosophy.
Not one of your other children
was a National Merit Scholar.
has spent two full days with you
at the Phillips Gallery, happily looking
at your beloved Impressionists.
We would deport her.
And we would make sure that she
was not welcome in England,
or Germany, or France,
or Italy, or even
all-forgiving Scandinavia.
We would make sure that
she had no choice
but to go back to Saudi Arabia
and get fat
and wear a burkha for the
rest of her miserable life.
What do you do for Abu Nazir
in return for the money
he gives you?
What do you do for Abu Nazir
in return for
the money he give you?
I keep my ears open.
Tell him what the Saudi
government is thinking.
General information.
You met with Tom Walker
at least three times
at the Mount Olivet Mosque
last week, correct?
Yes.
Tom Walker is working
for Abu Nazir?
Yes.
Was he meant to shoot
the president
from the roof of a house
near Ronald Reagan Airport?
I don't know
anything about that.
Where is Tom Walker now?
He's lying low.
Where?
I don't know.
What's his current assignment?
When will you know?
When Abu Nazir decides
to tell me.
What the tradecraft for setting
a meeting with Walker?
(sighs)
I put my child's drawing
of a red heart
in the window of my living room.
When would the
meeting take place?
The next day at noon.
Where?
Farragut Square
by the fountain.
SAUL:
Mr. Al Zahrani,
I'd like you to go back
to your house now,
put that drawing in your window
tonight.
Tomorrow afternoon,
I'd like you to proceed
as you normally would
to meet Tom Walker.
Okay?
So I'm bait?
You're bait.
You're free to go now.
What happens to me
after all of this?
Go about your business,
live your life.
We say nothing
to Saudi intelligence
about your connections
to Abu Nazir,
you say nothing to Abu Nazir
about our little get-together.
You work for us now.
Welcome to the CIA.
Oh, damn it! Ow.
(doorbell ringing)
Mike.
Hello.
Hi. Come in.
No, it's better if
I stay out here.
Oh, okay.
How have you been?
Shitty.
Brody came to see me.
He did?
Apologized for slugging me.
He said he doesn't blame
either one of us for anything.
I mean, Christ,
he even thanked me
for taking care of the kids.
God.
I know.
He's trying, Jess,
he's really trying.
He told me about being
asked to run for congress.
Told me you were against it.
I'm just thinking
of the family.
What's best for the family.
Jess, right now, Brody's
a marine without a mission.
He's a lost man wandering
around in the fog.
This thing, really means
a lot to him.
He wants to be of service.
He wants to do this.
Let him.
He'll be a better father,
a better husband.
He put you up to this.
Yeah, he did.
So what?
He's right.
That's unbelievable.
He comes to you and now
here you are, on his behalf?
It's a little incestuous,
isn't it?
Why don't we all just
take off our clothes
and get in bed together?
Jess, come on.
I got to go.
(door opens)
(mellow jazz playing)
(doorbell ringing)
Hi there.
Hi.
Come on in.
Miles Davis.
Do you like jazz?
I don't know anything about it.
Here we go.
Oh, no thanks.
I really just came around
to ask you something.
I need you to be honest.
What?
Does anybody at the CIA know about
our weekend up at the cabin?
No.
You didn't tell anybody?
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Is there any way
they could find out?
Not unless I did tell them.
Which you wouldn't do.
Believe it or not,
I value my privacy.
Why the concern?
I've been asked to run
for political office.
Political office?
What are you talking about?
Vice President Walden wants me to
run for Congressman Johnson's seat.
Really? Wow.
Well, that's....
That's surprising.
I don't want to do it
if there's even a chance
the media would
find out about us.
I can't do that to Jessica.
I've been shitty
enough as it is,
and she deserves better.
And she's going to get it.
Jessica will never know.
Thanks.
I should get back home.
Yeah, I'm beat.
It's been a rough day.
You promise me this will
stay between us?
I promise.
Good-bye.
Good night.
♪ ♪
(sobs)
Off to work we go.
(engine starts)
VIRGIL: All right, we're
about 20 minutes out.
Excuse me.
Saul, any sign of Walker?
Nothing yet.
We got 15 of our people
in the square.
And Carrie's running point
down there.
Remember, everybody,
Walker is armed and dangerous.
We don't want a firefight.
We're here to nab him,
not spook him.
SAUL: Don't move until
Walker's in the grab zone.
Carrie?
I know the protocol, Saul.
This isn't my first polka.
SAUL:
Whit, how you doing?
Sniper One in position.
VIRGIL: We're passing
National Cathedral.
Traffic is loosening up.
We should be there any minute.
Any sign of Walker?
Quadrant report.
MAN:
North. No Walker.
MAN 2:
East. Nothing.
WOMAN:
West. Nothing.
South?
MAN 3:
South. Nothing.
Okay, we're here.
VIRGIL:
Al Zahrani's moving into
to Farragut Square,
southwest corner.
I got Al Zahrani.
Where the fuck is Walker?
CARRIE:
I'm looking.
CARRIE: Zahrani's
approaching the fountain.
Bait is set.
Ten o'clock.
Possible Walker.
He's... got a green watch cap.
Black fleece.
He's carrying a briefcase.
Target in range.
SAUL:
Whit, don't get trigger-happy.
You're just there
in case this whole thing
goes to shit.
Looks like he's headed
to the fountain all right.
Nobody makes a move
until Walker's in the grab zone.
CARRIE:
I can't see his face.
I need visual confirmation.
Finklestein, you're up front.
Go for a clear view.
FINKLESTEIN: Roger that.
CARRIE: Franklin, Patrelli,
approach him from the east.
FRANKLIN: 10-4.
PATRELLI: On it.
SAUL:
He's approaching Al Zahrani.
I want that positive ID now.
CARRIE:
Shit. Finklestein?
FINKLESTEIN:
I'm trying.
Franklin? Patrelli?
FRANKLIN:
It could be Walker.
It's hard to tell.
His head's down.
Patrelli?
PATRELLI:
Black male, six feet,
clean-shaven, athletic.
I can't tell.
He's carrying the briefcase
in his left hand.
So?
Walker's right-handed.
What about his watch?
Can anybody see his watch?
SAUL:
It's on his right wrist.
I don't like this, Saul.
Should I engage?
SAUL: Negative.
CARRIE: What's in the briefcase?
Saul, what's in
the fucking briefcase?
SAUL:
Wait for my command.
WHIT: Copy that. Shit.
Sorry. Pull back.
Pull back.
Get everyone out of here.
(buttons beeping)
CARRIE:
Everyone, get out of here!
(car alarms blaring)
(phones ringing)
Carrie!
Carrie.
Carrie?
(high-pitched ringing)
(no audio)
(ringing continues)
The explosion occurred
during the busy lunch hour
and killed five people,
wounded dozens,
and shut down the city Metro line.
(door opens and closes)
FBI special agents have joined
D.C. police in cordoning off
the area.
It was a suicide bomber--
a terrorist attack
right here in D.C.
We don't know that.
It's just unbelievable.
Hey.
Hey. Listen.
It's probably just
some crazy guy
who learned how to make a bomb
on the Internet.
Okay?
The most important thing
is not to panic.
Okay.
Where are the kids?
They're doing their homework.
Are they okay?
They're scared.
All right.
I'll go and talk to them.
Hey. Did you
think any more
about the, uh,
politics of it all?
Mike delivered your message.
And?
I told the kids
about the vice president
wanting you to run.
You told them?
We discussed how it
would affect our future,
that there would be
publicity and scrutiny
and gossip... (sighs)
but in the end, we all agreed
that we wanted you to do it.
Just to be clear,
are you saying yes?
Just promise me
I won't lose you again.
I promise.
Then yes.
It's a yes.
(rhythmic beeping)
(applause)
Thanks for coming out, folks.
(camera shutters clicking)
Dr. Steiner says
you're going to live.
All you got was a
really bad concussion.
No more head bashing
for a while.
Cut back on the drinking.
Otherwise, you're good to go.
Get some really good
drugs and a week's rest
before you head back
to the glue factory.
I'd love some good drugs
and a week's rest.
Lucky you.
In case you're wondering
about the bomber--
black guy with
the briefcase--
his name was Samuel Everett.
Homeless guy.
Walker met him at the shelter.
Must have paid him to
go meet Al Zahrani.
How did Walker know?
Who warned him?
Same person who slipped
Hamid a razor blade
so that he could
slash his wrists.
And the same person who warned
Raqim Faisel and Aileen Morgan
that we were onto their
safe house near the airport.
You were right.
Abu Nazir has someone
inside the U.S. government.
REPORTER (on TV): We take you
now live to the Capitol steps
where the vice president is set
to make his announcement.
Sergeant Brody is exactly
the kind of congressman we need.
His strength of character
is beyond question...
Turn it up.
And he is resolute
in the fight against terrorism,
which struck at the heart
of this nation's capitol
just yesterday.
He will be equally resolute
in the fight
against runaway spending
and profligate management
at the highest levels
of government.
(applause)
BRODY: It gives me great
pleasure and pride
to stand here today before you
having been given the generous
opportunity to serve.
You know, what I really came
to understand
lying in a dark hole
for eight years
in the Middle East
was that service
for your country
is the highest calling.
Sacred and profound.
(applause, cheering)
(turns TV off)
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com