Air and naval
forces of the United States
launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
Pan Am Flight 103 crashed
into the the town of Lockerbie.
George Herbert Walker Bush...
This will not stand,
this aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
- ...Trade Center.
- Without warning,
a bomb exploded
beneath the building.
The USS Cole was attacked...
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable
and cowardly act.
The next song
we're going to play for you
is one of the good old
favorites.
Until something shocks him...
I'm just making sure
we don't get hit again.
That plane crashed
into the World Trade Center.
Running up...
We must... we will be vigilant.
What the fuck are you doing?
God!
Fuck! I missed
something once before.
I won't...
I can't let that happen again.
It was ten years ago.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Homeland:
An American prisoner of war
has been turned.
Well, that's one interpretation,
but that's all it
is at the moment.
Jessica, it's me-- Brody.
If he is a terrorist,
we need eyes and ears
on Brody from the minute
he steps off that plane.
Out of the question.
The terrorists
are still out there.
We need Brody in the public eye
reminding America
that this is far from over.
What if he's not up
for it-- psychologically?
Just a couple questions
, Sergeant Brody.
You got ten seconds
to get off my property.
The...
The brass sent you over here
to turn me into
some fucking poster boy
for their bullshit war.
Abu Nazir?
Was he ever present
during any of your
interrogations?
No.
You are the only Agency asset
to have had eyes on Nazir
in seven years.
You know that they stone
women like me to death
if we get caught doing anything
that we're not supposed to?
I won't let anything
happen to you.
So Abu Nazir's resurfacing
just as Brody
has miraculously returned
home means nothing?
Dots are there, Carrie, but you
haven't connected them yet.
Wait, there's no
camera in the garage?
Jesus Christ, Virgil!
Allahu akbar.
Aamir.
Shh.
Stay there.
What are you doing?
Nothing, Aamir.
Just getting dressed.
Oh, it's beautiful, Aamir.
You're beautiful.
I'd like to swap
out this couch, please.
And the painting.
Something a little less Motel 6.
I'll do what I did for the
McCain 2009 interview.
Highest ratings ever.
You know, I missed that one.
I was out of the country.
Of course.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Carrie, would you get in here?
What is it?
It's a crew member
from the network.
They're about to move the couch
where we have a contact mic
mounted to the baseboard.
Holy mother of fuck.
Okay, wait a second.
Wait a second.
Can you...
you put that down?
And can we get
the painting back
on the wall, where it belongs?
We'll stick with Motel 6.
Just do it.
All right, I'm going to be late
for my briefing.
Let me know who wins.
Look, we're broadcasting
a special here in two days.
The homecoming
of an American hero.
I know what the audience wants.
You need to trust me.
No, I don't.
Okay. Keep the couch.
It's great. Let's just...
let's have you
take a seat right
there, please.
They back at it?
Looks like.
She has no idea who
she's dealing with.
I had no idea he had such, uh,
strong feelings
about home decor.
It's probably
the only thing to him
that seems the same.
I kept everything
exactly the same
the whole time he was gone.
Not everything.
I'm not going to
do this interview.
It's a complete joke.
They're trying to make us
into some perfect family.
You are the perfect family.
No, we're not.
Well, not you, maybe,
but the rest of them.
Your brother's a Boy Scout,
literally.
Your mother, she's got
this whole MILF thing going.
And your father--
I mean, Sergeant Brody,
he's a hero.
Yeah, he is.
So leave the rest
of us out of it.
Okay,
suggestion, if I may.
Do the interview, right?
But do something crazy.
Like what?
Light my hair on fire?
Wear a burka.
Every time the interviewer
asks a question,
tell him to go
shut the fuck up.
Mm-hmm.
Look, the whole country
will be watching, right?
And you can say
whatever you want.
Tell the truth.
The truth would be interesting.
Intelligence work
has led us to this man.
Prince Farid Bin Abbud,
also known to his friends
as Freddie.
We spent years chasing rumors
that the prince
funded terrorists.
But we've never had proof until
a meeting between the prince
and Abu Nazir was videotaped
by this woman.
Lynne Reed.
A CIA asset and member
of the prince's
personal retinue.
We're running a hooker?
If, by hooker,
you mean someone who's out there
risking her life
while we're sitting
around a conference table,
then yeah,
we are.
I just received word from her
that she successfully
downloaded
the prince's cell phone
onto an I-X chip.
I'll be retrieving it
first thing tomorrow.
Very good.
So, immediately after
his meeting with Abu Nazir,
the prince came here to DC.
We believe the purpose
of his visit
is to move funds
to one of Abu Nazir's people
here in the United States.
If we can flag the transfer,
we can follow the money
to Nazir's operative.
The prince is a global guy.
He lives on that phone
that Lynne Reed
just downloaded for us,
so... should be
a good place to start.
Questions.
You say you
believe the prince
is here for the purpose of
transferring funds. Why?
Like I said,
the timing of the trip--
following on the heels
of the prince's meeting
with Abu Nazir in Cypress.
My understanding is the prince
comes to the United States
every year about this time.
To top off his harem,
not to fund terrorism.
Saul.
What was that about?
It was a legitimate question.
So ask me offline.
Don't torpedo my briefing.
It was a question, Carrie,
not an act of war.
Abu Nazir's express goal
is an attack on our country.
It's his holy grail.
No one doubts that.
Well, half the reason
I think Abu Nazir
has something
in the works now is Brody,
and you know I can't
talk about that.
So let me see if
I understand this.
You think when
I ask you the same
exact question I'd ask
anyone else, that really,
I'm just giving
you a hard time?
Is that it?
Got a meeting to get to.
Dana.
Where were you?
With friends.
You missed the prep
for the interview.
Yeah, that was
kind of the point.
Hey.
Sorry.
Can I go?
No.
Sure.
I didn't mean to
confuse things.
So you know,
she's always like this.
It's not you.
You sure?
Ask her to do anything,
and the attitude
goes up like a wall.
I mean, she's obviously got
a secret life
going on out there.
Well, she's 16.
Only 16.
Well, I meant, didn't you have
a secret life when
you were that age?
Yeah, with you.
That was different.
You want me to try
talking to her?
Please.
Be my guest.
If I run into any trouble,
I'll send up a flare.
- I don't know.
- It's funny, though, isn't it?
You actually went swimming.
I thought that was the idea.
So what exactly are you
expecting to find on that?
These operations
need money, right?
You think it's
coming from Farid?
He's certainly
got enough of it.
So now we look for something
out of the ordinary
on the download you got us.
Electronic wire
with odd routing...
a meeting he takes
with someone new,
outside his usual circle...
a transfer of money...
I'll know it when I see it.
Are you sure about this,
about Farid being
part of an attack?
Pretty much, yeah.
Because I've been right
beside him for over a year
and all I've seen is a nice
guy with a few sexual quirks.
He gave me this amazing
necklace yesterday.
He didn't have to,
he doesn't owe me.
I swear, it actually
meant something to him.
I'm sure it did.
He's taking us all
clubbing tonight,
to show off the new girls.
That's what his
whole life is about.
Just having fun.
I know it must seem that way,
but the man you recorded
him with, Abu Nazir,
you know he's the real deal.
We never would have been able
to get this any other way.
You should feel really good
about what you've done.
Well, I have downloaded
his phone for you.
I'm done.
What about you?
Me? No.
I'm never done.
Shouldn't you be getting
ready for your interview?
They pushed it back
a couple hours.
Are you nervous?
No.
I was told Lawrence O'Donnell
gives everyone a hard time
except guys in uniform.
Chris! Dana!
Breakfast!
So you know--
Chris is all about
sugar in the morning,
usually Cocoa Pebbles.
Dana doesn't touch breakfast.
It's as if you're
trying to poison her.
So what were you two
talking about last night?
Huh?
I heard Dana laughing,
it was hard not to.
What was so funny?
Oh. It was this video
called YouTube.
Have you seen it?
The dog talking about food?
No, not that one.
I saw a cat that smokes.
It was really quite funny.
Hey. Want some?
No, thanks.
I'll take some.
Thank you.
Looks good.
Lack of porn is
a little surprising,
given the prince's reputation.
You know, at your briefing
yesterday, I didn't
mean anything,
calling your asset a hooker.
Want to make it up to me?
Find me evidence of
a money transfer.
Start with the encrypted files.
Really, it's important.
Saul.
I just picked up the
download from Lynne Reed.
Anything there?
Crypto's processing it now.
Hopefully we'll know
in a couple hours.
Good. I got a meeting to go to...
Meeting to go to, sure.
How long are you going
to keep doing this?
When are you going to
forgive me for screwing up?
I forgive you, Carrie.
No, you don't.
I really don't want to
get into this here.
I lied to you, it was
wrong, I understand that.
Do you?
Good.
Saul...
Everyone lies in this
business, I accept that.
But we all draw
a line somewhere,
and the two sides of that
line are "us" and "them."
And whatever we had, you and I,
whatever trust we built up
over a decade of
me protecting you,
teaching you everything I know,
you destroyed it
when you lied to me
and you treated me like "them,"
like every other schmuck
in this building.
Now, when you say
you understand,
is that what you mean?
What was it like, hearing
your liberators rolling in?
Well, they flew in.
Which I didn't
know at the time.
I was in a pretty deep bunker,
so I couldn't really
hear what was going on.
Then I heard
a massive firefight.
I knew there'd be casualties,
but at the moment the door
to my bunker blew in,
I still didn't know
which side had won.
Then a flashbang went off,
which blinded me.
And I just braced for the end.
It took a while to work out
what had really happened.
That you were free.
Yeah.
Sergeant Brody, your
commanders showed us
the results of your initial
medical exam.
Yes.
There's a section, "Scars and
Other Identifying Marks."
It goes on for
nearly two pages.
You were beaten.
No...
Yes.
Tortured.
That's right.
To what end?
What did they want from you?
They want you to lose faith.
Lose faith in your country,
which they say is the devil.
In your brother Marines, who
they say aren't coming for you
because you have
no military value.
In your wife,
who they say's got her arms
wrapped around someone else.
How do you resist that?
You can't.
Except by believing
that those people
they want you to renounce,
that they're keeping
the faith in you,
and you owe it to
them to do the same.
Semper fidelis.
Yeah.
Your father did his
interview this morning.
Good.
It is good, I think.
To talk about it.
To ten million people?
You think that's good?
Okay.
I get that you don't want to
do the interview with us.
I don't really think
anybody wants to hear
what it is I have to say.
Thank you for your order.
Please move forward
to the window.
Welcome to Gaucho Taco.
We'll be with you in a minute.
What's good here?
Well, it's 59 cent tacos, Mom.
I'm sure it's all delicious.
Look, Dana, I know
this is hard.
Your father was gone
for eight years.
And now he's back.
That's not it, Mom.
He's back and there's a
camera crew at our house,
when what we really
need is some privacy.
But that's his job now,
to be a public figure.
And it's our job to
be there for him.
We owe him that.
Dana, I do listen.
I know you think it's phony,
putting us up on stage,
and you're not wrong...
Well, Mom, it'd be a lot less
phony if you weren't fucking
his good friend Mike.
I'm not.
Oh, please, Mom.
With your black sleazy thongs
always drying in the bathroom,
and him coming over
to "help out."
Do you really think
I'm an idiot?
Dana, I thought he was dead.
We all did.
But he's not, Mom.
And he comes home,
to this devoted wife,
and everyone is in on
the secret except him.
Nice. Welcome home.
Dana!
Dana.
Your father can never
hear about any of this.
It would really hurt him.
Him, or you, Mom?
Him, both of us,
our entire family,
do you understand that?
Dana, I need you to promise.
Hi.
Hello.
This must be Jessica and Dana.
That's right, it's
my wife and my daughter.
I just stopped by to say hi
before the family
interview tomorrow.
Give us a chance
to get acquainted.
So...
Good we're all here.
You're late.
Yeah, sorry.
Where's Max?
He went home when the shift
ended, like I should have.
Please tell me
you found something.
Well, as a matter
of fact, I did.
Hello.
This must be Jessica and Dana.
Yes, my wife, my daughter.
I just stopped by to say hi
before the family
interview tomorrow.
Is that...?
Lawrence O'Donnell, I know.
Here, watch this.
You know that family interview
they're all getting ready for?
She knows.
Dana does. About us.
I mean, how?
We were so careful.
When you said you "had something,"
I thought you
meant something big.
Well, this is big.
No, I mean like a bomb.
Or a call from Abu Nazir.
I picked up the downlink
from Lynne Reed today,
and after all we went through,
there's nothing on it.
I need to find something here.
Hey, aren't you the one who's
always telling me to be patient?
I don't have time
to be patient.
I have three weeks left and
we're sitting around watching
this, whatever it is,
this reality show.
Hey, have you eaten?
I noticed there's some
spaghetti in the cupboard.
It's only ten years
past its expiration date.
I'm sure it won't kill us.
All right.
So what do we do?
Just wait for the prince?
That's right, you wait,
and you look beautiful,
and you try and enjoy yourself.
Think you can manage that?
I can certainly try.
Here's a question.
How do I get one of those?
Are you all right?
Yeah. Fine.
It's all yours.
Another bottle.
Easy. Pace yourself.
I know.
We have all night.
You have two years.
I'm not so sure about that one.
His Highness says
she reminds him of you
when you first started.
His Highness has
a special favor to ask.
A job he wants you to do.
A job?
He's meeting with a businessman
tomorrow-- a new acquaintance.
He'd like you to go
there tonight
and make the man feel welcome.
Make him feel welcome?
Aamir said that?
He said he wishes
to make a good impression.
Why didn't he tell
me that himself?
The prince can be
excruciatingly indirect
in making his wishes known--
but for that, he has me.
Is there a problem?
No.
No problem.
Good.
The driver's waiting.
I need to freshen up first.
Hurry.
Hey.
You awake?
Brody, a lot's happened
in eight years.
There's a lot we need
to talk about.
I just want you to know that,
when you're ready, so am I.
Do you hear me?
Mm-hmm.
I want to try again.
Got any tomatoes?
In the crisper.
Any from this century?
Uh, in the cupboard, there might
be a jar of something.
No.
Take yours off.
Please, take it off.
Let me.
No.
It's better if you don't.
Hello.
Hey, it's Lynne.
Lynne, where are you?
I'm out.
Uh, it's getting weird.
What do you mean?
Did you find anything
on that cell phone?
That transfer you were
talking about?
No, not yet.
I think I may have found it.
They just asked me
to go entertain
some new business acquaintance
that the prince is
meeting tomorrow. Who?
I don't know. It's somebody
he's trying to impress.
You sound worried.
Normally, we don't even
talk to any man
but the prince, and they want me
to go meet him now.
The backup--
they're going to be able
to follow me, right?
What?
The people protecting me--
where are they?
Yeah, they'll be right behind you.
Don't worry, we have your back.
Just keep your phone on.
We'll be able
to track you that way.
Okay.
Thank you.
Her protection?
Where's your van?
Lynne's about to meet the
prince's new business partner.
She's a welcome gift.
Carrie, what did you tell her?
You heard what I told her.
What was I supposed to say?
No, Estes didn't
give you a protection detail?
Now, come on,
we finally got a break.
I'm not seeing her phone.
Why isn't this working?
I don't know.
Just trace her.
Since when did they make
R Street a one-way?
Okay, we've got her.
Where's the map?
Just give it a second, will ya?
Okay.
All right, she's still
at the club.
Lynne Reed?
Where we going?
Hay Adams.
You been before?
Many times.
Careful.
Thank you.
Nice hotel. Very nice.
So how did you get hooked up
with these guys, may I ask?
Okay, I get it,
none of my business.
You're right.
It's just they paid cash,
substantial tip in advance.
I mean substantial.
Wouldn't mind being on
the permanent list is all.
Well, take care of me and I'll
put in a good word for you.
Thank you.
You're very kind.
Just leave me your card.
Which way are they going?
We're nearly there.
Which way are they going?!
They're not going anywhere.
She's not moving.
Where are they?
Behind the club.
Turn there.
You think that's a good idea?
Turn there!
Shit.
Carrie, Carrie, wait!
Carrie!
Carrie, there is nothing
to be done here, okay?
They made her.
Come on, we can't be seen.
Shit. Shit.
Shit.
Fuck.
Where's your father?
Don't know.
Where's Dana?
Don't know that either.
They drove off together
about a half hour ago.
If she doesn't
do the interview,
does that mean I don't
get to do it either?
I mean, it's not that I don't
appreciate all that she does.
It's just, you know,
there are some things
that I don't appreciate.
Yeah, so ignore them.
Yeah, but it's...
I mean it's stuff
that I don't think
anyone would appreciate.
I mean, it's stuff that I don't
think you would appreciate.
What are you looking for?
You'll see.
What are these?
Historical artifacts.
Look.
You and Mom.
Mm-hmm.
Each padlock put
here by couples
who thought they'd stay
together forever.
I wonder how many did.
Not many, I bet.
Why are you even
showing these to me?
Because it's never easy.
A lot of things can happen.
You know, when I went
over to Afghanistan,
you were in third grade.
Chris was about this size.
Your mom and I were almost
still like newlyweds.
That's what I took
over there with me.
You were in a play that year.
The Wackadoo Zoo.
Oh, you were so good.
I can't believe that
you remember that.
Honey, it's practically all
I thought about for eight years.
It kept me alive.
But now I'm back.
Now all those things that
kept me going, they've gone.
All the people have moved on,
things have changed.
And what's replaced it,
well, doesn't make
any sense to me.
Not yet, at least.
You know, I'm kind of struggling
for things to hold on to.
And your mom's struggling, too.
You should cut her some slack.
We both should.
Yeah.
So...
why are you even doing
this stupid interview then,
if things don't make sense?
I don't know.
Maybe just to keep the peace.
What are you going to say?
Well, I'm not going to lie.
But I'm not going to
tell the truth, either.
I'm not going to tell a
bunch of total strangers
what I just told you.
Hey.
Go ahead.
She was, um, DOA at Providence.
Two rounds,
point-blank.
Apparently, they
had her wearing
some crown jewel type necklace
that's, uh, vanished,
so local law enforcement
is saying
it's a robbery gone wrong.
That's good for us,
keeps us out of it.
You get anything off
the prince's cell finally?
Yeah, it fits.
Saudis must have
made her somehow,
decided to take her out.
I want to talk to Prince Farid.
DC police already did.
I've got the interview,
if you want to see.
You okay?
This guy is a Marine, right?
I thought they were
supposed to be on time.
Okay, that's good, Tim.
I like that there.
Keep that.
Come on, let's go
put on your nice clothes.
Hey.
You ready?
I'm gonna go change.
Mike.
Uh, uh... uh,
she was my employee.
Uh, for nearly two years.
And this necklace,
it was a present from you?
Yes.
To your employee?
I'm told it was worth
quite a lot of money.
She was worth a lot.
To me.
She was a beautiful soul.
She-She would never
hurt anybody.
So, wipe that look
off your face,
and you find out
who did this to her.
Find out!
It continues in that vein.
I need to talk to Farid.
Not possible.
If you don't trust me, you're
welcome to be in the room...
It's not gonna happen, Carrie.
They're at the airport by now,
heading back to the Gulf.
You let them leave?
If it makes a difference,
State Department made the call.
Said it wasn't worth
antagonizing the Saudis.
Yeah, you mean
she wasn't worth
antagonizing them.
It hurts to lose
an asset, Carrie.
I get that.
But she's gone.
And Abu Nazir
is still out there.
What we need now is a
new way to find him.
I'm sitting in the home of
Marine Sergeant Nicholas Brody,
his wife Jessica, and his
two children Chris and Dana.
A family that put a
yellow ribbon on the tree
for eight years
while Sergeant Brody was
presumed dead in Iraq,
when, in fact, he was being
held as a prisoner of war
under brutal conditions.
So, a lot of adjustments
to make, I'm sure.
How has the homecoming been?
Well...
It's been great.
For all of us.
It's been really, really great
to have him back.
And I hope it is for him, too.
Coming home.
Carrie Mathison.
Yeah, they called.
You police?
State Department.
Did anyone notify the family?
Yeah, they're here.
They are?
Yeah.
Drove all night
from Sandusky, Ohio.
Never been to DC before.
What did you tell them?
Nothing.
It's all hush-hush.
They're not idiots, though.
They know her so-called job was
traveling with a Saudi prince.
I don't think
there's any illusions
what he was paying her for.
She wasn't just some escort.
She worked for us.
She gave her life
for this country.
That's what I wanted to say.
That's what any human being
would say to these people,
that she was good, that we
owed it to her to protect her.
But I-I could not say that.
I couldn't say that because
it's a secret; I'm not allowed.
And I was thinking,
this is a fucked-up business.
This is
a fucked-up business,
and I...
Are you done?
No.
No, I'm just gonna keep
talking and talking,
so you can't say you have
some meeting to go to
or make up whatever other excuse
you're gonna make up,
so you don't have
to deal with me.
Carrie.
Everyone's left.
There's no meetings to go to.
She called me from the club...
ten minutes
before she was killed.
She asked if I had protection
on her, and I said yes.
What do you want me to say?
It matters?
It doesn't matter?
Don't worry, it'll all be fine?
Just say something.
Because when you cut me out,
I'm all alone out here
and I can't stand it.
They made your informant.
Killed her.
And I didn't stop them.
So, this transfer you had
everybody looking for...
Never happened.
And now they're gone.
But the prince was so
broken up about her--
really, really sad.
I-I can't believe he knew
they were going to kill her.
What made you think
he was even involved?
The video of him with Abu
Nazir that Lynne Reed shot.
Which was what exactly?
Their conversation was benign,
what little we could hear of it.
An exchange of pleasantries.
Nothing more.
Maybe Abu Nazir
really went on that boat
to talk to someone else.
Someone in the
prince's entourage.
Someone without his means?
If the prince
wants to fund something,
he's got the resources.
Not everbody does.
You're looking for
a money transfer, right?
Transfer of money
from a nomadic culture
that has always known
jewelry is the easiest way
to move wealth.
Tell me again about
the necklace she was wearing.
Five hundred thousand.
Three-fifty.
Four hundred.
Where did the money go?
Could be anywhere.
Congratulations.
Not many young couples
can manage
their first home all cash.
Thank you.
I hope you'll be happy here.
I'm, uh, I'm sure we will be.
They say you get used
to the noise.
We don't mind it.
I like being close
to the airport.
For us, it's perfect.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com