PRESIDENT REAGAN: Air and naval
forces of the United States
launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
REPORTER: Pan Am Flight 103 crashed
into the town of Lockerbie.
REAGAN: He has sanctioned
acts of terror
in Africa, Europe, the Middle East.
PRESIDENT GEORGE H.W. BUSH: This will not stand,
this aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
REAGAN: This relentless
pursuit of terror.
PRESIDENT GEORGE W. BUSH:
We will make no distinction...
REPORTER:
The USS Cole was attacked
while refueling in the port of Aden.
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable and cowardly act.
The next number
we're going to swing for you
is one of the good old favorites.
...until something stops him.
WOMAN: I'm just making sure
we don't get hit again.
MAN: That plane crashed
into the World Trade Center.
Thousands of people running.
We must and we will remain
vigilant at home and abroad.
(speaking Arabic)
SAUL:
What the fuck are you doing?
God!
CARRIE: Fuck! I missed
something once before.
I won't...
I can't let that happen again.
SAUL:
It was ten years ago.
Everyone missed something that day.
CARRIE:
Everyone's not me.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Homeland:
At 4:42 p.m. a drone missile
hit and destroyed part
of a compound in the mountains
of northern Iraq.
The images being broadcast
of the bodies
of 83 dead children allegedly
killed in the strike
we believe to be false,
created for propaganda purposes.
And they call us terrorists.
The Vice President,
the man most instrumental
in the drone attack,
is going to want to use you.
Get as close to him
as you possibly can.
Representative Richard Johnson
mean anything to you?
I watch the news.
How would you feel about running
for his seat in
the upcoming special election?
I'm interested.
A political office?
What are you talking about?
I don't want to do it if there's
even a chance
the media would find out about us.
SAUL:
Al Zahrani's running
a terrorist cell
out of the Saudi embassy.
He and Tom Walker are planning
an attack on the United States.
Who are you? You're CIA?
What's the tradecraft for
setting a meeting with Walker?
I put my child's drawing
of a red heart
in the window of my living room.
SAUL: I'd like you to go
back to your house now,
put that drawing in
your window tonight.
So, I'm bait?
It could be Walker.
It's hard to tell.
I can't see his face.
I need visual confirmation.
SAUL:
He's approaching Al Zahrani.
Saul, what's in
the fucking briefcase?!
Everyone, get out of here!
Carrie?
♪ ♪
(ball bearings rattling)
The President's a busy man, David.
He wants his helicopter ungrounded.
Not when we're seeing
increased chatter
with references to Marine One.
He's been briefed,
it doesn't faze him.
Well, tell him it should.
I did.
So?
So he's the leader
of the free world, David.
He doesn't enjoy looking like
some impotent asshole,
which is how this guy Walker's
making us all look.
He'll look even worse
if his helicopter gets
blown out of the sky.
Tell him that.
What have we got?
16 agencies.
You are kidding me.
Nope.
16 agencies had some awareness
of our operation to get Walker.
And that's just on
the intelligence side.
So how do I find the leak?
You can start by looking around you.
Goddamn it.
Sir.
Yeah?
The Vice President wants to see you.
He's here?
No, sir.
Succession protocol requires him
to be on lockdown
as long as the threat to the
President remains red.
He's in his bunker.
Where's Carrie?
Still in the hospital.
She's supposed
to be released in a few hours.
Good.
Tell her we need her here.
Yes, sir.
CARRIE:
Green. No, green.
I was specific about that,
and I don't see what the problem is.
(panting):
A green pen is what I want.
And blue is what is available.
Okay, green is important.
Green is necessary.
It doesn't make sense
if it isn't green,
and it's really
not an unreasonable request.
Carrie?
Saul, thank God!
My green pen is dry.
I asked four, five,
six times for a new one,
but there's no understanding.
They offered me blue,
they offered me black.
I mean, is green so hard?
Is green elusive?
I mean, my kingdom
for a fucking green pen!
She's yours?
Yes.
She should go to her room.
The doctor will be in.
Okay, I am laser-
focused on the green,
but there's more.
There's many, many, many, many more.
The thing is, Saul, that
Abu Nazir has methods
and patterns and priorities.
A single sniper?
No, no.
Abu Nazir doesn't do that.
He never has, he never will.
He goes big!
He explodes!
He maims en masse, we know that.
Slow down, slow down.
Facts... facts are facts,
and we have about a week, maybe less,
to figure out the real target,
not this single shot to the president,
spy-novel-101 bullshit.
Well, actually, that's
the working theory.
Well, it's wrong.
It's, it's incomplete.
Walker's not even critical!
He's just a part, a piece, a pixel.
A pawn of no importance.
There is a bigger, pernicious
Abu Nazir-worthy plot
out there,
and we have little time.
We have to code it,
collide it, collapse it, contain it.
Lie down, Carrie.
The doctor's coming.
Okay, the important thing now
is the green pen.
(breathing heavily)
(gasps)
Thank you.
Why Gettysburg?
You heard why.
He wants to spend time
with his family.
Yeah, but it has
to be in Pennsylvania?
I mean, it can't be here?
Can you just help, please?
Mom, I have plans tonight with Xander.
He already bought tickets.
(knocking)
(doorbell rings)
Actually, that's probably him.
He said he might come over.
Dad, I got it.
It's okay.
Hey, Sergeant B!
Hello.
Is it true you're
running for Congress?
Yeah.
Are you?
You 18?
No felonies?
No, none yet.
All right.
How are you?
Good.
Hey, Mrs. B!
Well, you obviously didn't tell Xander
we're leaving for a couple days.
It's a whole couple of days now?
JESSICA:
It's just overnight.
Xander, uh, why don't you tell them
about those tickets
that you already bought?
What-what tickets?
Dana, you're going.
You know, I could stay here by myself.
No, you can't.
You know, I could stay with her.
You're kidding, right?
Dana, we've already discussed this.
Come Monday, the campaign's
gonna take over,
you're not gonna see your father
for days at a time.
He just wants
to spend one last weekend
with the four of us.
I don't think it's too much to ask.
Okay, I give up. I'll go.
Mmm!
Yeah, I'll go.
Hi. Dr. Jeremy.
Where's Dr. Steiner?
Not here today.
You're the doctor?
(sighs) I've been waiting
a half an hour.
I'm sorry.
I mean, I got a real situation here.
I'm aware.
I spoke with Carrie earlier.
Well, then you can explain to me
what's going on.
As far as her injuries go,
Carrie is fine.
I already heard that.
I-I-I mean, um...
how she's acting.
I'm sorry. I have to speak
with Carrie privately.
I'd like to come.
She'll allow it.
Saul, there you are.
Hey, how you feeling, Carrie?
Is it time yet?
Are we going?
Going?
To work. We gotta hop-to.
We gotta haul ass to Langley.
They have to understand, Saul.
Nazir's movements in green after
a fallow yellow always creeping
towards purple are
methodical, meaningful
momentous and monstrous.
Okay, I'm gonna get you
a bit more Ativan
to settle you down.
I don't need to settle down!
Tell him!
Saul, tell him.
Carrie...
you're not yourself.
Of course I am!
No. I can't follow you.
You're talking very fast.
Your thoughts are running together.
All these ideas...
I-I... I can't understand.
Is there a doctor we should call?
My sister.
Honey, is this really necessary?
Complain to Ma, she's the one
that got it for me.
Really?
Careful, careful! I'm driving.
Jack me to Gettysburg,
and this is what you get.
Okay, here it is.
"Four score and seven years ago
our fathers brought forth on
"this continent a new nation,
conceived in liberty
and dedicated to the proposition
that all men are created equal."
What's four score?
Four times 20.
Lincoln means "87 years ago."
He's talking about the American
Revolution of 1776.
Why didn't he just say that?
You'll see when we get there.
How far are we now?
Three score miles.
(all chuckle)
Hey, come on.
Holy shit!
Dana! Really?
I'm sorry.
I just hadn't realized
Dad's scars were so faded.
I mean, you can barely see 'em now.
She'll be here, right?
I mean, she said she was on her way?
Maggie will come.
Maggie's reliable.
You can count on Maggie every time.
(chuckles)
Is she an especially slow driver?
Okay...
Huh?
This is red and blue,
it's not red or blue. Okay.
Maybe she got pulled over.
(mutters):
Shit...
Sleeping dogs here,
sleeping dogs there.
This whole box is dogs, really.
She can fix this, right?
She said she was bringing medication.
The question is what wakes them?
Is it a whisper, a crash,
a deep internal pain?
How about a glass of water?
(doorbell rings)
Hi.
She's manic?
I don't know, you tell me.
Hi, Carrie.
Hi, Maggie.
You look so professional.
So this isn't new?
No. She's bi-polar.
She's stable on her meds.
The explosion must have
sent her into a flight.
Why didn't she ever tell me?
She said no one at work could know.
Right.
So what do we do?
We'll up her Lithium.
We're giving her Clonazepam
to start leveling her out.
Carrie?
Is it essential, entirely?
Yeah, it is.
Here you go.
So that's it?
She'll be fine by what, morning?
No. It takes time. Days.
Maybe a week.
Oh, that long?
And someone needs to watch her
while she's evening out.
Full-time?
Or we put her in the psych ward.
Well, that would kill
her security clearance forever.
That's why I treat her.
Well...
I got to get back to work.
I can stay till 7:00.
Can you take the night shift?
Well, what do I have to do?
Just be with her.
Keep her out of trouble.
Okay. 7:00.
(elevator bell dings)
(door buzzes)
Welcome to my goddamn humble abode.
Want to tell me where we stand?
We've been coordinating security
with your secret service detail.
Well, I've been in here
for eight hours.
At present, the threat...
The threat is one fucking guy.
Marine sniper, sir, highly trained.
Do you see where I am?
Do you?
I'm underground cowering out of sight,
at a time when I need
to be highly visible.
I'm announcing my candidacy next week
for President of the United States.
You may need to push that back, sir.
I'm not going to push that back...
Sorry...
I am not going to push that back.
That date is set.
And I'm not going to do it from here.
Vote for the fucking cave dweller
just because you
can't locate Tom Walker.
Yes, sir.
So fix it.
Sir, there's something you should know.
What's that?
The C-4 used in the explosion--
we sourced it to a Saudi shipment.
Oh...
It was delivered last year
to Prince Sultan Air Base.
Part of a large arms
deal that came in...
Why do you do this?
What's that, sir?
Tell me things I don't want to hear.
We've got two Muslims
dead in a mosque,
an explosion in
the streets of D.C.
and Walker who the fuck knows where?
You want your portrait up on the
walls at Langley someday?
Focus on that. Find Walker.
Yes, sir.
And fire someone.
I don't care who.
CHRIS:
That's it?
BRODY:
Yep. That's it.
CHRIS:
Can we go now?
Only if you can tell
me what happened here.
Battle of Gettysburg.
Can you be more specific?
Four score and...
I didn't know I'd be tested.
Okay, we're in Pennsylvania, right?
Was that the South or the North?
God. North.
That's right.
General Lee had brought
the war to the North.
The South was winning.
The Northern forces were outnumbered,
and they were on the run.
Then they dug in there.
All along that ridge.
General Meade, the Northern general,
he drew a line out there
and he gave instructions to his troops
to defend it at all costs.
And that means with your life.
What happened?
They prayed.
Both sides did.
These were extremely religious people.
I meant what happened
with the fighting?
Well, imagine...
You're bone tired,
you're cut off from water.
The most crucial part of
the line that must be held
it's right up there.
You see up there, that little hill?
It's Little Round Top.
There are just 300 of you.
You're commanded by
a school teacher from Maine.
When suddenly, 2,000 enemy soldiers
come charging out of those trees,
screaming at the top of their lungs,
determined to cut you down.
Did they?
They charged twice.
And then a third time.
And that's when this teacher
from Maine--
Joshua Lawrence Chamberlain
was his name...
...asked his men
to do a very strange thing.
What?
He told them to stop shooting.
No guns, just bayonets.
And instead of shooting
they charged down the side of
that hill toward the enemy.
And it was so unexpected,
it was so crazy,
that the line was held that day.
All because of a school teacher
from Maine, who was willing
to do what was necessary
for a cause that he believed in.
Saul.
Where've you been?
You told me to get Carrie, remember?
Where is she?
Keeping her another day.
Perfect.
Hey, David.
She said something interesting.
Of course she did.
Sniper attack-- that doesn't
make sense for Abu Nazir.
It's not his methodology.
Well, maybe it is when he has a
military sniper working for him.
She thinks something bigger.
Marine One all over the wire.
New references to Marine Two.
The two leaders of the free world
aren't fancy enough targets for you?
She says it's a sideshow.
If she wants to get her ass in to work
I'll be happy to bat that around with her.
Right.
And it better be soon,
because the Vice President's
about to fire us all.
She just got blown up, David.
Might not be tomorrow.
Why, what's the problem?
Doctor's orders.
Dad.
Yeah?
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I was just thinking.
Where'd your mom go?
Gift shop with Chris.
I had no idea that you knew so much.
About Gettysburg?
About anything.
(chuckles)
I mean, I know
you're a Marine and all,
and I shouldn't be surprised.
Anyway, I get why
you wanted to come here.
Can you promise me something?
Yeah. What?
I have this feeling that things are
going to get pretty wild soon.
Geez, Dad, it's just a campaign.
Your mom's going to need you.
When I'm not around.
Promise me you'll watch out for her.
Promise me.
CHRIS:
Hey, look what we got.
Yeah, I promise.
You want one?
Oh, that's fantastic.
One for you.
That's great.
I don't get a general's hat?
I'm the boss around here, that's why.
You are.
Let's see you salute.
Hi-oh.
Corporal First Class.
How do you have no food in your house?
I eat out.
You eat Chinese take-out
and yogurt.
You ever hear of the four food groups?
Yes. But I won't recite them
because I'm resting my mind.
I know you hate this.
I have a lot of work to do.
You always say that.
No, no, something big is
happening. Something dangerous.
There's no time for rest.
I know you feel that.
But you'll need to trust
my judgment now.
You need rest, healthy meals,
patience.
Carrie! Carrie,
what are you doing?
Carrie!
(horn honking)
(tires squealing)
Carrie!
(car door opening and closing)
What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?!
Look at this.
You have to stay with me.
Isn't this amazing?
We're going home.
Somewhere down there, there's
a sliver of green
just-just taking its time.
This is-- this is how
everything works.
Carrie...
You wait, you lay low, and then...
Then you come to life.
Come on.
(panting)
So what do you want to eat, guys?
I don't know.
What do we got?
Should we try this place?
Oh, babe, you know what?
I forgot my toothbrush.
I'm going to go pick one up.
Okay.
All right? Will you get me
something to eat?
Will you get me a burger?
Chocolate shake?
Okay.
As-salaamu alaykum.
Wa alaykum assalaam wa ramat
allahi wa barakatuhu.
I don't have much time.
(clears throat)
Put your arm through here.
The explosive?
Not armed yet.
Listen now.
These must be tight.
Or the vest will show.
The switch is here.
Under this cover.
Wait until the last second
before you open it.
Some people get nervous.
You don't want your hand
on the switch until the end.
I read that part of the
blast goes upward.
Toward here.
Point of weakness.
So that the head is cleanly severed,
and normally found intact.
Everything else...
...isn't.
(speaking Arabic)
La ilaha illa Allah.
(train whistle blows)
DANA:
Where were you?
Huh?
What was that? That package?
Oh, that was just something for Mom.
What?
That was a present.
You get me something to eat?
Yeah. It's getting cold.
Okay.
Is something wrong?
No. Why?
You just sound weird.
Come on.
What'd you get, a burger?
Yeah.
Sweet potato fries.
I already put ketchup on it.
I can't put it in the milkshake now.
Get another one.
Chris...
CHRIS: Eat it.
You eat it.
I already, I...
Try it.
Hey, Dad, isn't this where we were?
Chris, did you steal all my fries?
Sorry. We were hungry.
Yeah.
Totally okay.
In there, up here.
That's us there, Little Round Top.
MAN:
Excuse me?
You're that soldier back from Iraq.
One of them.
You're the hero.
Running for office.
I'm no hero, sir.
Well, whatever you call it,
you're one tough motherfucker.
Man, what
you went through--
kind of puts things in perspective.
I'd vote for you.
Thank you, sir.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm waiting to hear
what you have to say.
I'm sure it's going to be good.
Hey, this is my son Jimmy.
Hey, Jimmy.
We run a construction
business locally.
To be honest...
Hi.
She's upstairs.
Took her meds already.
Good.
She was working.
There was an incident today.
What happened?
She almost got hit by a car.
She's okay.
She's fine.
But I had to give her
another sedative.
She really needs to rest.
Okay.
I'll go see her.
She's probably asleep already.
You don't have to.
I want to.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Saul.
Sorry I didn't say
good-bye this morning.
Did you see the papers?
Downstairs-- the work?
I did.
(sighs)
There's so much more to do.
I'm just so sleepy.
That's okay. Rest.
Maggie upped my meds.
I shouldn't have let her.
They're making me so drowsy.
(sighs)
Carrie?
I'm so sorry.
About all this.
I feel responsible in a way.
'Cause when you came back
from Baghdad, I knew.
I saw something had happened.
You were damaged.
I left it alone.
Other times when you were so...
out there, I guess I half knew.
Maybe hoping it was something else.
Anyway, I should have asked.
I should have asked
if you were really okay.
There's no time, Saul.
It's high purple.
♪ ♪
(murmurs)
I thought I heard you out here.
I need more ice.
Again?
It's free.
You glad we came?
Yeah.
The guy at the diner was funny.
Did you like Gettysburg?
Yeah, it was cool.
I wanted you to understand.
That the Civil War, all wars,
they turn everything upside down.
Everything and everyone.
I hope that you'll remember
Joshua Chamberlain when you get older.
And be brave, and daring,
and ready to fight
for what you believe in.
Dad...
What?
Do you mind if we talk
about this some other time?
It's kind of melting.
Tell your sister to go to bed soon.
Okay.
Good night.
I told Chris to get to bed.
(Chris and Dana arguing)
(laughing)
I'll give him a direct
order next time.
What?
Why the big smile?
Just happy to see you, that's all.
Yeah?
I really think this trip
was a great idea.
It's like something's changed.
Like we've turned this corner,
and everything doesn't have
to be so difficult anymore.
When I was watching you
at dinner with those people,
how much they need you.
I don't think they were
even from our district.
(laughing) I know.
But I could see it.
How you're this promise.
That things could be better.
I wish that I had never said
no to your running for office.
'Cause I see now what
a good thing it is.
Not just for other people...
for us, too.
Brody, I'm...
What?
...happy.
It's like you're finally home.
(whispers):
The kids are next door.
Shh, shh, shh...
(giggles)
(birds chirping in distance)
(chuckles)
You understand.
It's a timeline.
Yes! It's Abu Nazir's
activities.
Were you up all night?
More or less.
The fallow yellow.
He went quiet for months.
No videos, no meetings.
But then?
He came to life again with purpose.
More than ever.
But why the hibernation?
What happened?
Injury? Bad health?
Or loss.
Tragedy.
He was mourning during the yellow.
And then green was revenge.
It was a plan.
And now... the purple.
He's ready to see it through.
It's here.
We have to figure out what
happened right here.
I'll get the A team on it
this morning.
Galvez--
he can find anything.
That's a good idea.
(sighs)
What about me?
You relax.
I did hear you last night.
You did?
I've had this since college.
I wrote a 45-page manifesto
declaring I'd reinvented music.
(chuckles)
The professor I handed it to
escorted me to Student Health.
Ah.
(chuckles) I wasn't even in his class.
You didn't do anything, Saul.
I just came this way.
(knocking)
(door opens)
Dad wanted to be here.
You bet I did.
Hey, how's my girl, huh?
What is that?
It's her work.
That's goddamned glorious.
It should be in the National Galley.
Dad, this is Saul.
Hey. Frank Mathison.
I hear you look out for her.
Happily.
Sorry. Gotta run.
Oh, well...
You'll tell Galvez?
And you'll sit tight.
So?
I slept.
Hey.
Let's get you a square meal.
Yeah, yeah, come on.
I'll make you one
of my world-famous
sandwiches, huh?
(chuckling)
Morning!
Ha!
Serves you right.
You're supposed to be packing,
not unpacking.
What is it?
I told you, something for Mom.
Really? You got her
something at the drugstore?
Yeah, I did.
Really.
JESSICA:
You two ready?
Yeah. Shh.
Yeah, we're ready!
Thanks. All right.
You're supposed to help me with this.
Why?
To exercise your mind.
But not tax it.
I have to go to work.
No way.
I'm okay!
I may have a major situation
that I know how to fix.
I know how to stop it.
Feels good out there, doesn't it?
Like you're the Queen of the world.
Yes! Exactly!
But you're not, Carrie.
Okay, I just have to make a call.
To who?
There's this guy I know.
He's a POW.
He knows how to fill in
this blank, this-this gap
because he was there
at that exact time.
So tell Saul to call him.
No, it-it, it has to be me.
He only told me.
Your sister said no calls.
No, I have to, Dad.
Hey, look!
You're only one day out.
Hey, when I'm there,
I'm just like you.
You know, lots of gut feelings,
things that I have to do.
But there's good gut,
and then there's bad.
Yeah?
Well, sometimes I think I need
to empty my refrigerator
and set it on fire, you know?
That's what my gut says.
It's bad gut.
And if I wait a while,
I realize it.
No, this is right.
This is right, I know it.
No, Carrie, come on!
Hey, come on! Come on!
I got the corners together.
You can help me with the sides.
Carrie!
(door closes)
Ah, shit!
Oh, gee, I wonder who leaked our ETA.
Maybe he spent the entire
weekend here waiting for me.
Ever think about that?
It's good to be home.
What? Yeah.
Yeah, it is.
(cell phone rings)
Oh, it's already started.
Chris, help your mom with the bags.
Hello.
It's Carrie.
I know.
(panting):
Okay.
I'm calling you, not because of
me and not because of you.
I'm not calling to try to...
I-I... I'm just calling
about Abu Nazir.
What?
Let me be more clear.
Okay. We have been alerted
that something is coming.
Something is gonna happen imminently,
and it all has to do
with a certain period in Abu
Nazir's life, the fallow yellow
if you want to be precise.
I don't understand.
Okay, you were with him then.
You have insight.
You can identify the impetus,
the incident, the injury.
(sighs)
Something happened to him, a tragedy.
Carrie, are you okay?
You loved him! You told me
that you loved him,
so you must know.
Look, uh, would it help if we met?
Yes! Yeah, okay. Good.
Are you at Langley?
No, no, I'm home.
Stay there.
Okay.
XANDER:
What's that?
It's called Little Round Top.
It's this place where
this teacher from Maine
named Joshua Chamberlain
saved the Union.
I don't see what's so weird about it.
Well, it's not the weird part.
Okay, here it is.
Now it's just your dad.
I know.
So what's, what's weird about it?
He was just strange all weekend,
or at least it seemed like it to me.
I mean, he said everything
was fine, but look at this.
He just... stands there.
You're right.
That is totally weird.
(panting, mutters)
Okay.
(doorbell rings)
MAGGIE:
Who's that?
It's a friend.
David.
Sergeant Brody called me.
What?
He told me everything.
I-I don't know what you mean.
I think you do.
Come on. Let's go inside.
What?
Come on.
Ma'am, sir.
FRANK:
Excuse me.
He admitted to being complicit
in some kind of fling with you.
But illegal surveillance, Carrie?
The continuing harassment?
No! That-that is
a mischaracterization.
Your office at Langley's
being cleared as we speak.
These gentlemen are
here to do the same.
What? No! No!
Carrie, Carrie...
Are those classified documents?
Don't, don't, don't, don't!
No, David, that chart is
very important!
It is very meaningful!
What is wrong with her?
No, don't. Don't tell him.
David...
I am about to solve
this fucking thing!
Strip it.
No, no, no, no, no! Please, please!
MAGGIE: Carrie, no, come on.
We need to sit down right now.
Come with me. I'm serious!
- We're gonna sit down right... - Please, just
let me hold onto it for a little while...
ESTES: How long has she
been like this?
No! You don't... you don't know
what you're doing!
Carrie?
You don't know what you're doing!
We're just gonna...
No!
David, this isn't...!
(overlapping shouts)
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com