Sync and corrections
by n17t01 and bellows
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Homeland...
WALDEN: You want your
portrait up on the walls
of Langley someday?
Find Walker.
Walker's not even
critical.
He's just a part,
a piece, a pixel.
There is a bigger,
pernicious,
Abu Nazir-worthy plot
out there,
and we have
little time.
Carrie...
you're not yourself.
She's bipolar.
This explosion must have
sent her into a flight.
Carrie said something
interesting.
Sniper attack-- that doesn't
make sense for Abu Nazir.
It's not his methodology.
Well, maybe it
is when he has
a military sniper
working for him.
She thinks
something bigger.
MAN:
The switch is here.
Wait until the last second
before you open it.
BRODY: I read that part of the
blast goes upward
toward here--
point of weakness.
Hello.
I'm calling about Abu Nazir.
Something happened to him,
a tragedy.
You were with him then.
Y-You have insight.
Would it help if we met?
I'm home.
Stay there.
Sergeant Brody
called me.
He told me everything.
Your office at Langley's
being cleared as we speak.
I am about to solve
this fucking thing!
Strip it.
SAUL:
I'm so sorry.
I feel responsible in a way.
'Cause when you came back
from Baghdad, I knew.
You were damaged.
There's no time, Saul.
It's high purple.
My name is Nicholas Brody...
and I'm a sergeant in
the United States Marine Corps.
I have a wife...
and two kids...
who I love.
By the time you watch this,
you'll have read
a lot of things about me,
about what I've done,
and so I wanted
to explain myself.
So that you'll know the truth.
On May 19, 2003,
as part of a two-man sniper team
serving
in Operation Iraqi Freedom,
I was taken prisoner by forces
loyal to Saddam Hussein.
Those forces then sold me to an
al-Qaeda commander-- Abu Nazir,
who was operating
a terrorist cell
from across the Syrian border
where I was held captive
for more than eight years.
I was beaten...
I was tortured...
and I was subjected to
long periods of total isolation.
People will say I was broken,
I was brainwashed.
People will say that
I was turned into a terrorist,
taught to hate my country.
I love my country.
What I am is a marine,
like my father before me
and his father before him,
and as a marine,
I swore an oath to defend
the United States of America
against enemies
both foreign and domestic.
My action this day
is against
such domestic enemies--
the vice president and members
of his national security team,
who I know to be liars
and war criminals
responsible for atrocities they
were never held accountable for.
This is about justice
for 82 children...
whose deaths
were never acknowledged
and whose murder is a stain
on the soul of this nation.
Hi.
Any change?
Afraid not.
How worried
should we be?
Worried.
I haven't seen her like
this in a long time.
She's not eating,
she hasn't left her
room in three days.
What about the lithium?
I thought you said
that'd be kicking in by now.
It has kicked in.
This is the depression that
comes in the wake of the mania.
It's actually
much harder to treat.
Think some chicken soup
would help?
It might.
Elixir of the gods.
Can I go see her?
Of course.
Saul.
What does being on
administrative leave
mean exactly?
Well...
she's not going to face
any criminal charges,
thank God,
but we shouldn't kid
ourselves.
She's never going
to set foot in Langley again.
Hey, you.
Hey, Mr. Berenson.
(sniffs)
Remember when I used
to call you that?
What?
Mr. Berenson.
Yeah... a long-ass time ago.
Back when I could still piss
in a straight line.
How are you,
Carrie?
I've been better.
Don't worry,
I can't stay long.
(grunts)
Why don't you tell me
a story?
What kind of a story?
About a bad man
named Nazir
who took a break
from doing bad things,
only nobody
could figure out why.
You know I can't
talk about that.
(sighs)
I know, until my security
clearance is restored.
I know.
(sighs)
You need to concentrate
on getting better.
At least tell me that you're
still looking into it,
that you won't
give up.
You promise me that.
(whispering):
Promise.
(sighs deeply)
No, don't go.
Why did he do it?
Who?
Brody.
Why?
Do what?
Call Estes and...
rat me out like that.
Honestly, I can think
of a hundred reasons.
The man's running for
congress in case you forgot.
Think about it.
You're the last person he
needs in his life right now,
and vice versa.
(sobbing): But, Saul...
Listen to me.
This man has poisoned
your thoughts.
He has cost you
almost everything.
Forget him.
I can't, Saul, I can't.
My God.
You're in love with him.
♪ ♪
(locks door)
(sniffs)
(clanking quietly)
MAN:
It's number O-72.
B-15.
Good night, Isabelle.
(laughs)
Good night.
(engine starting)
(glass clinks)
I'm looking
at a lot
of distinguished
faces here tonight.
Yours,
Elizabeth.
The only reason
I'm here at all.
Thank you for convincing me
three years ago
to accept the nomination
for Vice President.
And yours, Richard.
You are the core
of what I'm confident will
be our next administration.
We've all been on a long,
difficult journey.
But tomorrow morning,
when I announce my candidacy,
we will throw down a gauntlet--
all of us here
in this room--
promising to put
America first again.
ALL:
"Hear! Hear!
(crowd chatter)
Good to see you, Walt.
(indistinct chatter)
Very nice.
You know, you're right.
It's a distinguished group.
Includes you, David.
It's a group worth protecting,
that's my point.
If you're asking me to call off
tomorrow, you know the answer.
I'm only suggesting
that we change the venue.
So I can announce a candidacy
from some hiding place?
(sighs)
You give them too much
credit, you know that?
Who's that, sir?
The enemy.
Guys like Walker.
He can do a lot
of damage.
To both of us.
Yes, he can.
But he's only one guy,
and you have the entire
Homeland Security apparatus
at your disposal.
For both our sakes,
take care of it.
And for God's sakes,
drink your champagne.
It's Billecart-Salmon.
Yes, sir.
(chuckles)
Oh, not again.
(sighing)
I'm sorry,
ma'am, but...
I know, I know.
Residents only.
What's it this time?
It's a major policy
address in the morning.
Vice President,
I think.
Oh, fucker.
Ma'am?
Serves me right
for buying two blocks
from the State Department.
Well, I'm sorry for
the inconvenience, Mrs. Sammler.
You have a
nice night.
Officers?
(gun clicks)
(gasps)
Okay, Mrs. Sammler.
Knock, knock.
Your night nurse is here.
I made spaghetti amatriciana.
You know, Carrie,
you're gonna to have
to eat sooner or later.
Damn it, Carrie.
You are starting to scare me.
Go... away.
I'm sorry, I
can't do that.
Your sister gave me
very strict orders.
So I'm going to sit here
with you until you fall asleep.
Okay?
Hmm. Smells good.
You sure you
don't want a bite?
JESSICA: Chris, can you get the
butter out of the fridge?
CHRIS:
Yeah.
So you're not coming
to my karate match?
BRODY:
Buddy,
I told you, I got this event
with the Vice President.
I'm sorry.
JESSICA: Chris, we talked
about this, right?
Your dad'll go
to the next one.
Right?
Right.
All right, dinner's ready.
Everybody, sit down.
(Jessica sighs)
(sighs) Whose turn
is it to say grace?
Mine.
Dad, do you know
how to do it?
I think I can fake it.
(laughs)
Dear God, bless
this food to thy use
and our lives to thy service.
And may you shine the light
of your love on this family...
hold them close...
and protect them always.
Amen.
CHRIS:
How did I do?
Not bad.
♪ ♪
NAZIR: The end of our
lives is preordained.
We are not created
for no reason.
We are only finding the path
we are meant to walk on.
So, purify your soul.
Forget about the physical world.
And take the time left to offer
good deeds and obedience.
(sighs)
Remember: all of life's
wasted time is behind you now.
And the way forward is clear.
You were looking at the battle
before you engaged in it,
and now you see it
with your own eyes.
(speaking Arabic)
Dad?
What are you doing?
What's going on?
How long have you been
standing there?
Dana?
Dad, you're scaring me.
Don't be scared.
Was that Arabic?
Yeah.
What does it mean?
It means, um...
I converted to Islam.
I didn't say anything to anyone,
because I didn't want
to upset you guys.
Well, then, it's a good thing
you didn't shoot a deer,
or step out on mom,
or beat the shit
out of Mike.
Okay, I deserved that.
Why do you wash your hands
and feet like that?
It's a ritual.
It's about purifying
your mind and body
before presenting yourself
to God.
Does Mom know anything
about any of this?
No.
She wouldn't get it...
at all.
Our little secret then?
Yeah.
MAN (over radio): These are the kind
of issues facing Vice President Walden
this morning as he prepares
to give his remarks.
The vice president will be
joined by staunch supporters
from virtually every corner
of the defense establishment,
including the Secretaries
of Defense and State
and the Joint Chiefs of Staff,
longtime advisor
Elizabeth Gaines.
The speech comes just days after
a bombing in downtown Washington
left five people dead
and it's clearly time to show...
in the next phase
of the war on terror.
Yet, the exact nature of
those measures remain unclear.
At the CIA,
Walden was widely credited
with developing closer ties
with the armed forces,
taking
a more militarized approach
to intelligence gathering,
and the elimination
of insurgents.
Under Walden's leadership,
the use of drone strikes...
Virgil?
became a key strategy
in the CIA's fight...
Virgil, where are my pills?
I need them!
Vice President Walden has met
with political resistance...
Virgil? Is anyone there?
VIRGIL: Carrie? (Gasps)
I'm right here.
Here. Here.
(panting)
(newscaster continues
indistinctly)
I need to get out of here.
Good. Uh, great.
We'll go for a walk, huh?
I want to go for a drive.
What are you doing here?
You're supposed to be
at the State Department.
I need your help
with something first.
(sighs)
What is that?
There's an 11-month gap
in Abu Nazir's activities.
Started around
two years ago.
He goes silent
like he fell off the
face of the earth.
Theory is,
there might have been some event
that precipitated this,
something that hit him
personally,
took him out of action
for a while.
And whose theory is that?
Just look at this.
It's all redacted.
What the hell
am I looking at?
I think it's a drone strike.
Why's that?
This reference
number here.
How'd you find this?
Grid search.
Cross-referenced with
Abu Nazir's likely locations
around the time
in question...
and I got
hundreds of hits.
None like this.
Can I ask
why you were even doing that?
I told you,
there's a gap.
This gap-- is it related
to that wall of garbage
we found in Carrie's apartment?
It was a time line, David.
It was classified
material, Saul,
improperly removed
from this office,
assembled by a crazy woman
into a crazy collage,
and I don't even want to know
about your involvement in it.
Well, ask me.
I'll tell you.
I said
I don't even want to know.
I need you too much right now
to have you land in custody.
I, I need you to do your job.
I think I am.
You're not.
The vice president is hosting a
highly visible conference today.
I asked you to be our man
on the ground there.
Go do it.
This is good.
Excellent--
I can't feel my hands.
We ought to sic him
on Tom Walker.
Okay, let's go.
This is good.
We're going
to be late.
Sure you don't
want to come?
Well, I want to.
Then do.
Come on, guys, we settled
this already.
(panting)
Next time.
Sure.
Hey, come on.
(laughter)
(exclaims)
Come on, Bruce Lee, you're
going to miss your bout.
You got everything?
Yeah.
Jess.
We're gonna be late.
I'll see you later.
(panting)
The turn's right up here.
Just going
for a little drive, huh?
We're driving, aren't we?
Yeah.
Great.
You want to tell me what
the hell we're doing here?
Getting some fresh air.
No, I'm serious,
Carrie, I have
a van full of equipment,
a lot of it not exactly legal.
So why are we here?
Carrie.
In a few hours,
the vice president
is expected to announce
he's a candidate for President.
Okay.
Up ahead in that building
he'll be surrounded
by his entire team.
I said why are we here?
Half the government
is going to be in one spot
and we've got a terrorist
on the loose.
And you think
this is the target.
I think it's worth considering.
(sighs)
Okay, Carrie, look,
first of all,
we don't have a terrorist
on the loose.
We don't have anything.
You see these guys?
They have a terrorist
on the loose
and it's their job
to do something about it.
It's my job.
Not anymore it's not.
It'll always be my job.
Don't you get that?
Look around,
Carrie.
There is security
up the wazoo here.
They are on it.
We are not needed.
No, all those guys?
They're thinking
it's a single sniper.
Because that's what it is.
No, it's not.
It doesn't make sense.
Virgil, I...
I know I'm not wanted.
I know it's just us
in this stupid van,
but I'm the same person
I've always been
and I need you
to be on my side now.
I need you to say yes.
Okay.
OFFICER: Come on, you got
to back it out. Let's go.
Sorry.
Made a wrong turn.
Find a place
to park
this thing.
(rustling)
(sighs deeply)
(breathing heavily)
(door rattling)
Just a minute.
The door's locked.
I'm getting dressed.
Dad, I really don't think you
should go to this thing today.
This thing...
is being hosted
by the vice president.
So?
So...
he's counting on me.
Ah.
To be there.
Well, all they're saying on TV
is how intense the security is.
Most since the inauguration--
that's what they're saying.
Well, that's all taken care of.
We have nothing to worry about.
I guess.
Dad.
What?
Have you noticed
how awkward it is,
having this conversation
through the door?
(vehicle stops)
I think I heard
my car arrive.
(clears throat)
You let 'em know I'll be
a couple minutes?
Seeing you praying
like that last night,
I think it kind of
freaked me out.
Apparently.
As if it's not enough that Tom Walker
is running around
out there with a gun.
You're safe.
Don't worry.
It's not me that
I'm worried about.
I'll be fine.
Two minutes.
I still think
that you should stay here.
Be good.
Sergeant Brody.
(door closes)
Who are you?
Kandarian.
Secret Service.
I've been assigned
to you for the day.
(car door closes)
Let's go.
(engine starts)
(siren wailing)
Saul Berenson found
a redacted document
that points to the mission.
I thought
that paper trail was burned.
You and me both.
What was he even looking for?
He was just fishing
for some action
that might have caused Abu Nazir
to drop out of sight
around that time.
Based on what?
Some theory
he has
that the current situation
is blowback.
You tell him
it doesn't matter
why terrorists do what they do.
I have.
He's a security expert, he's not
a fucking social worker.
I know, I told him to drop it.
Don't tell him;
Make it happen.
This cannot get out.
Right?
Operation wasn't
above my security clearance;
It was off the books,
or it was taken off
after the fact.
Yeah, well, you're right.
The reference number implies
a drone strike.
So there's got to be all kinds
of supporting
documentation, yes?
That's the weird thing--
there's not.
You check flight plans?
Yeah.
What about ops tapes?
I went down and checked
the vault myself.
The only thing that exists is
this redacted document you found
on the grid search.
It probably wasn't even supposed
to be there.
Obviously.
I'm stuck here
like some school
crossing guard
just so Estes can feel
like his ass is covered.
You want me to initiate
an official request
for information?
I have a feeling
that's the last thing
we want to do.
I could reach out
to some drone pilots.
(metal detector
beeping) OFFICER: Sir.
Sorry.
No, let's not raise flags.
I'll follow up on it myself.
(sighs)
So what are we
looking for exactly?
Exactly I don't know.
It's not one thing,
Virgil, it's everything.
All the Defense
leaders will be here--
at least two dozen
high-value targets.
Yeah, so?
So a single sniper is not
gonna take them all out.
So you focus on the
highest value target.
But why here
with all the security?
That's exactly
what I've been saying.
You attack here if you're
planning to take them all out.
A group of people
who are almost never
in the same place
at the same time.
GAINES: I'd really rather
talk about this conference
and our need to rededicate
our efforts to the war
on terror.
REPORTER:
Is that a course
that the vice president would
pursue as commander in chief?
GAINES: He'll be here shortly;
you can ask him yourself.
But the fact is, we are not
comfortable with a war...
(indistinct radio transmission)
We're on the wrong side
of the barrier, Virgil.
I agree.
Now, come on.
Let's go home.
Carrie, you are working
yourself up for nothing.
I wouldn't call a possible
terrorist attack nothing.
Shh!
You can't say
stuff like that.
Not here.
Don't worry,
everything's fine.
Is that what you want to hear?
(helicopter flying nearby)
It's a bit excessive, isn't it,
all this security?
(knocking on window)
Windows open, please.
IDs?
Sergeant Brody.
Sure.
Sorry about the
inconvenience.
(bangs on car)
Good to go!
Brody?
What's he doing here?
Uh, do me a favor;
Don't ask him.
I'm standing here
because of him.
I lost my job because of him.
Carrie, we really
should go now.
Carrie!
Goddamn it, Carrie.
Nervous?
Well...
I'll be standing
in there with...
two cabinet secretaries,
couple of joint chiefs,
head of Defense Intelligence.
I'm just a platoon sergeant.
GAINES:
You'll get used to it.
He's here.
Sergeant Brody.
Sir.
Congratulations.
Thank you, sir.
Ms. Gaines,
nice to see you again.
GAINES:
And you.
Mr. Vice President.
Thanks for coming out.
Thank you
for having me, sir.
(crowd screaming)
(clamoring)
(gunshot)
(frantic shouting)
Shit.
(gunshot)
(metal detectors beeping)
VIRGIL: We have to
get out of here.
Come on! Come on!
(beeping continue)
(whimpering)
Oh!
Oh, ah...
Thank you.
You're welcome.
(exhales)
Nicholas Brody.
Richard Halstead,
I'm...
Secretary of Defense.
Believe me,
I know who you are.
(sighs)
What a fuck up.
(breathes heavily)
Where's the vice president?
Who knows?
Where's the
vice president?!
He's all right.
He's just right behind us.
(phone rings)
Berenson.
It's me, Saul.
Uh, I-I got to call you back.
No!
Carrie, we've got a situation.
I-I-I know, I'm here.
Saul, you have to listen to me.
What do you mean, you're here?
I saw the whole thing;
The woman that was hit,
Elizabeth Gaines,
she is not the target.
Vice president was the target.
Walker missed.
Walker would not have missed
once, never mind three times!
This is...
this is just stage one.
The real attack
has not come yet.
What real attack?
What are you talking about?
Following an
assassination attempt,
they'll sequester
the high value targets,
that's protocol.
Right now, they're putting
the vice president and his team
out of sight,
in a single, small space.
They're supposed to be safe
there, but they're not.
They're vulnerable.
How?
Brody.
Brody?
For Christ's sake,
Carrie, not this again.
Forget about before;
This is now.
I saw him-- Brody.
They hustled him right through
the metal detectors
along with the vice president.
You even realize
what you're saying?
Yes!
He's planning on taking
them all out.
That is what's coming!
We've been hearing chatter
for days now,
Marine One, Marine Two.
I-I-It's not the
President's helicopter.
It's actual marines--
Brody and Walker.
They are Marine One
and Marine Two.
They're working together,
they must be.
Saul, you hear me?
Yeah, I do.
That's why Brody ratted me out,
'cause I was getting too close.
God, it finally all makes sense.
Yeah, sure.
Saul, you got
to get me in there.
There's a CT Officer
named Benton.
I-I-I know him.
I'll send him out for you.
Thanks. Hurry.
Yeah, bye.
There's a woman outside
the building, one of ours.
She's unstable, and you
need to contain her.
Her name's
Carrie Mathison.
WALDEN: I'm not getting stuck
down here for a day and a half.
SANDERS:
That won't happen, sir.
WALDEN: I won't run and
hide, you understand?
SANDERS: No one's asking
that, just a little caution.
WALDEN:
Get your hands off me.
SANDERS:
My apologies.
WALDEN:
Fuck your caution.
One of my closest
friends just got shot.
All right, I understand.
May I have your
attention please.
SANDERS: We've initiated a full
lockdown protocol for your protection.
That means this door
will now remain closed
until one of two things happen.
One, the sniper's
apprehended, or, two,
we establish to our satisfaction
that he's left the vicinity,
and it's safe to leave the room.
WALDEN:
And you believe this?
You fucking believe this?
SANDERS: You're safe, sir.
That's the priority.
Safe from what?!
We look like a
bunch of idiots.
Well, you're
my advisers.
How about some advice?
How about some fucking advice?
How do we spin this?
NAZIR: There is nothing
left to think about.
Clench your teeth.
Say the holy words.
Remember Issa.
WALDEN:
Well?
(click)
(breathes heavily)
(click, click)
HALSTED: I advise we
wait, like the man said.
There a men's room here?
There better be.
SANDERS:
This way.
Where is he?
There's no time.
VIRGIL:
Wait.
Oh, there he is.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
I said wait.
VIRGIL:
What's with all the backup?
Damn you, Saul.
Virgil, am I crazy?
Look, you know you are.
No, I mean about Brody.
Just tell me if I am.
(sighs)
Virgil, I need to know!
I don't know, okay?
But I trust you.
I need your keys.
Where are you going?
You don't want to know.
All right, go.
I'll run interference.
Ben!
Hey which one
of you guys is Benton?
Are you Benton?
Which one of you is Benton?
(panting)
(engine starts)
(low, indistinct conversations)
(speaks indistinctly)
(clears throat)
Any word out there?
No.
Well, they said
this could happen.
You okay? You look
a little peaked.
Well, not a fan of being
locked up, I guess.
You've reenergized him,
you know.
Sir?
Walden.
He sees you as a living,
breathing vindication
of everything
he's ever done.
He's got big plans for you.
Wouldn't you know it,
no paper towels.
Another fuck up.
(panting)
(whispers):
Oh, come on.
(panting)
(music playing quietly)
massive search for the sniper
is now underway
in the area between E Street
(vehicle approaching)
and Independence Avenue
all the way from
the Potomac to 17th...
(knocking)
I'm coming!
No one is going in or out.
Eyewitnesses say the vice
president and his supporters...
My God.
(loud knocking)
Oh, my God. Yeah?
What?
What are you doing here?
You're Dana, right?
Yeah.
I'm Carrie Mathison.
I know who you are.
It's about your dad.
Was he hit?
No.
I saw on the TV... No.
I-I know. I was there.
I saw it happen.
He wasn't shot.
But, Dana, I need your help.
Can I come inside?
(Carrie panting)
You heard about
Tom Walker?
Yeah.
How he was turned against us?
Yeah. Did he shoot those people?
Yes.
Dana, listen to me.
Your dad told me that you are
the one who understands him,
who he listens to.
And this is very hard to say,
but your dad
is working with Tom Walker.
They're working together.
They are carrying out an attack right now.
What are you talking about?
He is with the vice president
and other innocent people.
He is going to kill them
if we don't
stop them.
Okay, you have to call him
and just talk him down.
All right?
This will get you to
the Secret Service.
That'll connect you.
(soft gasp)
We don't have much time.
You can do
this, Dana.
(dialing)
Okay.
Hi. Um, I'm at 3319 Chapman,
and it's... it's emergency.
There's...
there's an insane woman...
No! No! Dana!
Get out!
Dana, please.
Get back inside!
Get out of my house!
Dana, please,
get back inside.
Get out! Please!
DANA:
Get out of my house!
Dana!
You must have noticed.
Leave me alone!
Something strange, him acting off.
No, you're off!
Just call him and make sure.
Something is
wrong with you!
God! Why are you even here?!
I told you!
So that we can stop him.
Who's that with Dana?
Stay in the car.
Leave me alone.
Mom...
What's going on?
She-she came here
and she says that Dad
is working with Tom Walker!
Get in the house.
Call the police, right now.
I already did.
Dana? Dana, please.
Please call him.
Get away from her!
Jessica, listen...
What are you doing
telling some crazy story to my daughter?
No, it's not crazy.
(panting)
He has intentions to kill the
vice president and his staff.
You have to believe me.
It's not too late to stop him. Believe you?
I told Dana she
needs to call him...
You fucked my husband.
And now you need to call him.
He tells you
to get lost,
(siren wailing)
and-and now you're...
making up all
those crazy shit.
No, you're not
listening to me.
Of course I'm not
listening to you.
Please, just call him.
You really don't want this happening.
Are we okay here?
No, we're not okay.
Okay, please.
You don't understand
what's going on, any of you!
Ma'am...
Okay, the world is about to end,
and we're
standing around talking!
Ma'am, come with us. No!
Get... get off of me!
Come with us! Come on!
Get off of me!
Do not move!
Stay down!
Stay... stay there.
(handcuffs clicking)
(Jessica speaking indistinctly)
(panting)
(quietly):
Ow!
Shit.
(continues panting)
(door opens)
You okay in there?
Yeah, fine.
We found the shooter's weapon
abandoned in an apartment
a block away.
It shouldn't be
too much longer,
we'll have you all out of there.
Great.
(toilet flushing)
(panting)
You sure you're okay?
I'm feeling a little
sick, actually.
If you need a doctor or anything?
No. No, thanks.
That won't be necessary.
(chuckles)
(low, indistinct conversations)
(panting quietly)
Sergeant Brody.
I got a call for you,
from your daughter.
She says
it's an emergency.
Dana?
(crying):
Dad... where are you?
Dana, I got to call you back.
No, Dad, no.
There was... there was
this crazy woman at our house,
the one that... that,
you know, you were with,
and... she was saying
all these things about you,
and I just...
I had to hear your voice.
Dad?
(panting)
(sniffles)
Dad?
Yeah.
Yeah, but, Dana, I...
Dad, she said that you were
working with Tom Walker,
that-that you're a terrorist.
I'm not.
I know, Dad, I know.
Of course you're not.
I-I wouldn't have believed her,
because you would never do
anything like that, ever. Ever.
I didn't believe her at all.
Dana, I'm here
with a group of people.
Look, I've got to go.
No, Dad, don't.
We're just, uh,
we're in a holding area,
and, um, you know,
they're about to let us out.
So you're coming home?
Sure.
Tell me that.
(panting):
Yeah, I'm coming home.
No, Dad, don't say it like that.
Dad...
promise me.
You have to promise me
that you're coming home, Dad.
(sniffles)
Dad?
(inhales)
Dad, you have to promise me.
I need you.
You know that.
(crying quietly)
I'm coming home, Dana.
I promise.
(exhale)
Okay.
Thank you.
SANDERS:
Copy.
All right,
we're clear.
We're clear.
Nick...
you look like shit.
Come on.
What a
fuckin' day.
Our thoughts and prayers
go out to her family...
as does this pledge:
Her murder will
not go unpunished.
For this reason...
I stand before you today
to officially announce
my intention to run for
President of the United States,
and to rededicate myself
and this nation...
JESSICA:
Yes, of course. Yes. Anytime.
That was the police.
They want to know if
we want to press charges.
WALDEN:
...fear.
Brody, are you
listening to me?
What did you tell them?
That I would talk to you.
I'll take care of it.
This woman is sick.
There's something
seriously wrong
with this woman.
So whatever you decide...
I don't want to ever hear
her name in this house again.
I said I'll take care of it!
(Walden continues)
Good.
I'm gonna go see if
Dana's doing better.
(applause over TV)
Saul.
Mr. Vice President.
Give us, uh,
five minutes?
Let's make it ten,
be on the safe side.
Ten.
How's Mira? Oh, great. Thanks.
No doubt you and David Estes
have already huddled about this mess?
What are you playing at, Saul?
I called it fuck the terrorists.
I remember where you are.
I know exactly where I am, sir.
Are we on the same side?
Because your tone suggests otherwise.
Trying to find out about
what happened yesterday,
why.
Trying to stop it from happening again.
And you think this redacted
file will help you to do that?
I can't let anyone see that until
I see what's under all those black lines.
Trust me Saul, this is nothing but a turd
let it lie.
You're my boss for 3 and a half years,
did I ever once let anything lie?
I'm saying this would
be a good time to start.
I don't agree.
Here's another thing you
might remember about me,
I'm a sentimentalist,
I like to hold on to things.
For old time sake.
If I ever told the american people
these interrogation tapes
had been destroyed
I was mistaken.
Coercion, cruelty,
all right, torture.
Makes for a very unhappy viewing.
You gave the orders William,
I gave the orders.
You're blackmailing me.
You'll stay with us.
The girls have fixed up the room for you,
They'll have you on the flowers.
They are very excited.
Thank you, Maggie.
I told them that you need to
rest but not, you know, why exactly.
Carrie?
Did you know he was here?
Carrie, what are you doing?
There are criminal charges pending,
you shouldn't talk to him.
I have to.
Brody, I am...
You broke into my house.
You terrified my daughter.
She's 16 years old, by the way, sixteen.
I'm sorry.
They asked me what I wanted
to do about it, the police did.
What did you tell them?
Nothing yet.
That'll depend on you.
For the last time, Carrie,
I am not what you think I am.
I'm sorry.
You keep saying that, it is not enough.
I know about your condition,
David Estes told me.
Carrie, you need to get some help.
I am.
And you need to stay away from me.
And from my family.
You set up surveillance,
you watched me,
you pushed your way into my life,
- and for what?
- Okay.
Fun?
It's crazy what you did.
- You understand...
- I said okay.
What does that mean?
I understand.
I'll stay away from you,
you have my word.
Goodbye Brody.
Goodbye Carrie.
Home now?
To the hospital.
Oh, fuck.
It's Abu Nazir in the target area.
- We believe...
- You sure wanna see this?
What you've been hiding from me?
Yeah, I do.
80% certain he was here.
A ground assault is preferable
in terms of collateral damage.
But impossible in the time frame.
That's a school sir.
Don't cloud the issue.
If Abu Nazir is taking
refuge among children
he is putting them at risk, not us.
So, we agree?
Good to go.
It's our joint opinion the
potential collateral damage
falls within current *matrix* parameters.
And, uh...
Someone actually came up
with that language.
That was 2 years ago,
you reported to me at that time
and you said nothing.
Because you would have stopped it.
Yeah, none of this would have happened.
No dead children,
no cover up, no Carrie Mathison
drawn out of the agency...
Keep her out of this.
You know what I think,
when she got a lead on Nazir,
first one in over seven years,
wasn't it worth mentioning
this strong string?
Even in private to me.
Or is your career on the
coat tails of the vice president?
Trump national security.
Really, I'm fascinated to know.
The world changed, Saul.
Right under your nose.
Answer the damn question.
I am.
We're about projecting
American power now,
degrading Al-Qaeda militarily.
You wanna play soft ball spy games,
go join the germans or the french.
I am this fucking close
to picking up the phone,
and calling the New York Times.
No, you're not.
You know why?
Because telling the world
we killed 82 kids on purpose,
would endanger every one of your
case officers in the field.
Not to mention every American
soldier on the ground.
You would, essentially,
be handling the enemy
the biggest recruitment
tool since Abu Ghraib.
I gotta say I am impressed.
You've got the balls to show up.
I'm impressed you're alive.
Care to explain?
We all went to the same place, Nick,
I just got out of there a lot quicker.
Now, you wanna tell me
what happened yesterday?
I don't answer to you, Tom!
And I didn't come in here to make excuses.
What the fuck happened?
I came here because you
got a direct line to Nazir.
Fuck Nazir!
My vest malfunctioned, okay?
Bullshit!
You fucking panicked!
Tom?
Maybe what happened yesterday
was a good thing.
What if I had detonated that vest?
What would be different?
Ask yourself that.
Today, they would've just replaced
Walden with somebody else.
So the fuck what?
So, that means I'm close
to the next president of
the United States, Tom.
That puts me in a unique position.
Nazir? You listened to
this garbage, Nazir?
I'm listening.
What do you want me to do?
Put Nicholas on the phone.
Nazir?
Is it true what you say?
Yes,
I hit the switch but nothing happened.
I meant about the vice-president.
Yes, it's true.
At the very least,
I'd be able to influence
policy at the highest levels.
Why kill a man when you can kill an idea?
That's what I'm thinking.
Nazir, are you still there?
I want to believe what you say,
but to help me believe
I need a demonstration
of your commitment.
Name it.
You did it once or at least
you were told you did, uh?
There is a wild card in this new play.
You understand what I'm saying?
Nicholas?
Yeah, I understand.
Then say goodbye.
Tell Walker I need to
speak to him privately.
(arab speaking)
Wants to talk to you.
It's done.
(arab speaking)
You got a million calls
while you were out.
Presidency office and
vice president's office, too.
You okay?
Yeah, better.
And, Jess, I'm sorry
that I shouted at you before.
It's okay.
I'm surprised you're
keeping it together at all.
Thank you.
- For what?
- Everything.
Excuse me, sir?
Excuse me, sir!
I'm sorry sir, this is locked ward.
I've got my pass here somewhere.
Here, for preop.
It's across the hall on the right.
- What did you say? Thank you.
- On the right, second door.
Just a little sting.
- How are you feeling, honey?
- Fine.
Take that thing out of her arm.
- Saul. - Sir...
- Out of my way.
This is fucking barbaric.
I won't allow it.
- Jim!
- I'm getting you out of here.
Saul, stop.
Just listen to me.
This was...
I wanna do this thing.
- What? - It was my decision,
I told them to go ahead.
Your decision?
Have a shock treatment?
It's not cuckoo's nest, Saul.
They use ultra brief impulses now.
It's called electrocomplusive therapy.
I don't care what is called.
They still attached electrodes
to your skull, don't they?
Still jilting into a seizure?
I need to do something.
I can't take this anymore.
Yes, you can.
You're the strongest person I know.
So pass.
No, it won't pass.
It's only getting worse...
Carrie, please, there's
alternatives to this.
You don't have to let them
fuck with your brain.
My brain's already fucked.
Yeah? It is a brain
I happen to love.
Is everything okay,
Ms. Mathison?
- Everything's fine, thanks, yes, really.
- You sure?
What about the side effects?
Memory loss...
That is only short time.
It's usually temporary.
A lot was happening that I
kinda like to forget anyway.
That's not even remotely funny.
Saul, I made up my mind.
I'm grateful for the
concern but I just...
I can't live like this any more.
It needs to stop.
Yeah.
Well...
You shouldn't feel all bad.
I mean...
It hasn't been an
unmitigated disaster.
You were wrong about Brody.
And you were right about Nazir.
You're telling me the yellow,
his period of dormancy?
Yes.
He was in mourning.
His son died in a drone
strike in northern Iraq.
Which son?
Youngest, 10 years old.
Along with 82 of his
Madrasi classmates.
Apparently the vice
president gave the order.
How on Earth did I miss that?
You didn't.
Record's been wiped white clean.
Expunged.
Like it never happened.
Wow.
Thanks for telling me.
You deserved to know.
So, Saul, is there any change that
I can appeal on my termination?
No.
Dad!
What you're doing up here?
Came up to fix the leak in the skyline.
Is it beer?
That came later.
Never knew it had views.
The *** back yard, nice.
Do you mind if I join you?
No, of course not.
You're ready?
This is the anesthetic
I was telling you about.
I want you to start counting
backwards from 100.
100...
99...
98...
97...
96...
95...
Issa.
Issa, no!
Issa...
Issa, Nazir's son
Brody knew him.
Saul, don't let me
fucking forget...
What did she say?
Nothing, it's the anesthetic,
everyone does it.
She's asleep.
OK, we're ready.
Paddles on...
Sync and corrections
by n17t01 and bellows
www.addic7ed.com