PRESIDENT REAGAN: Air and naval forces
of the United States
launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
REPORTER: Pan Am Flight 103 crashed
into the the town of Lockerbie.
REAGAN:
...savage acts of terror in
Africa, Europe,
the Middle East.
GEORGE H.W. BUSH: This will not stand, this
aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
REAGAN:
This relentless pursuit of terror.
We will make no distinction.
REPORTER:
The USS Cole was attacked
while refueling in
the port of Aden.
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable
and cowardly act.
The next song
we're going to play for you
is one of the good old
favorites.
...until something stops him.
WOMAN: I'm just making sure
we don't get hit again.
MAN: That plane crashed
into the World Trade Center.
Thousands of people running.
We must and we will remain
vigilant at home and abroad.
(speaking Arabic)
SAUL:
What the fuck are you doing?
God!
CARRIE: Fuck! I missed
something once before.
I won't...
I can't let that happen again.
SAUL:
It was ten years ago.
Everyone missed something
that day.
CARRIE:
Everyone's not me.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Homeland:
How has the homecoming been?
It's been great.
For all of us.
BRODY: I appreciate you
looking out for Jessica,
like you did while I was gone.
What do you want to know?
How he died.
BRODY:
He's gone.
Does it really matter
how it happened?
It does to me.
We're onto the next case.
Raqim Faisel.
What did you say?
MAN: He should use an alternate
route. Tell him now.
ESTES:
See what second team
comes up with tonight.
If nothing, move on.
What?
The one surviving terrorist
from the compound
in Afghanistan
where we rescued Brody.
Scooped him up in
some shit shack in IBD.
ESTES:
Afzal Hamid.
You and Carrie
will interrogate him,
with the help
of Sergeant Brody.
CARRIE:
Do you know this man?
He was my guard.
What can I do for you, Sergeant?
I believe I've earned
a moment face-to-face
with my torturer, sir.
14th man gave up
an e-mail address we just traced
to the Engineering Department
at Bryden University.
Professor we tailed then cleared?
Correct.
Find this man.
Raqim Faisel.
What's going on, Saul?
Hamid's dead.
Suicide.
How the hell is that possible?
Razor blade fragment.
Left wrist.
What? Where did he get that?
SAUL:
What the hell?
Not only did Brody contrive
to get himself in the room,
he orchestrated Hamid's suicide
and he warned Dr. Faisel.
And we-- you and I--
let it happen.
I think you should leave now.
With pleasure.
Know what, you can keep that.
Fuck this shit!
(video winding)
BRODY:
How did you think this...
(video winding)
(grunting)
Come on!
(video winding)
(grunting)
Come on!
(sighs)
(video winding)
(grunting)
MAN:
Calm down!
Calm down. Calm down.
SHOOTER: How is such a massive
fuck-up even possible?
Please, explain that to me.
Sorry I'm late.
ESTES: Hamid probably brought
the razor blade with him.
The heel of one of his
shoes was peeled back.
It's also conceivable that
he found the razor blade
somewhere in the safe house.
One of our sweepers
might have missed it.
There is another possibility.
Someone on our side
could have given it to him.
ESTES:
Th-That's a stretch.
CARRIE:
Why?
ESTES: You actually think
someone on the SEAL team
gave Hamid a piece
of broken razor blade?
Or maybe you think
I did it, or Saul.
I certainly don't
think you did it.
I'm just saying, we
should polygraph
everyone who came into
contact with Hamid.
Ask each one of them directly
about the razor blade.
I've written up a list.
We're talking about 11 people,
including the SEAL team
that brought him here.
She's right.
We can't rule out
the possibility
of a mole.
What if Raqim Faisel
was warned by the same person
who gave Hamid the razor blade?
SHOOTER:
Faisel?
The guy that bought the house
by the airport?
You want to connect him to this?
He disappeared
just as we moved in.
Coincidence?
Or did he know we were coming?
Oh, good Christ.
Look, if nothing more,
let's cover our asses.
11 polygraph tests.
What's the big deal?
I'll go first.
Take care of the polygraphs.
(door closes)
Don't you ever do
that to me again!
You disagree with me, fine,
but make it a sidebar!
Well, you heard
what the man said.
Set up the polygraphs!
And get me Faisel!
Yes, sir.
What a surprise.
Sergeant Brody's on this list.
Well, it's not my fault
Estes let him in
the room with Hamid.
Expected to find
your resignation
on my desk this morning.
I had a much better
idea, don't you think?
I should forget
the things you said?
Yes, please.
He's right, you know.
You embarrassed him in there.
Who gives a shit?
Saul, we're gonna get Brody.
He'll never pass
the polygraph test.
We'll see.
I'll bet you
everything I've got.
Everything. Including
my Monk's Dream,
signed by Thelonious himself.
I prefer Coltrane.
Not so fussy.
Okay, uh, here.
So, uh, the tables
will go right here,
the chairs around the tables,
and then just
throughout the yard, okay?
All right.
Yeah, okay.
JESSICA:
Damn it you two.
The memorial
is in a half an hour.
You're supposed to be ready.
Get dressed.
DANA: Ma, this little creep
keeps hogging the bathroom!
Chris, let your sister
use the bathroom, please!
(door closes)
You okay?
Not exactly looking forward
to seeing Helen Walker.
Kind of got on my high horse
when she remarried.
Why?
I was waiting for you
to come home.
I guess I figured
she could do the same.
I had no right.
Do you know
what you're going to say?
At the service?
No.
Well, just be honest.
I'm sure everything's
gonna be fine.
We should hurry.
(sighs)
Here.
You look very handsome,
Sergeant Brody.
MAN: Is your name
Carrie Mathison?
Last time I checked.
Yes or no, please.
Yes.
Do you work for
the Central Intelligence Agency?
Yes.
Regarding the questions
you'll be asked today,
do you intend
to tell the truth?
Yes.
Are you married?
No.
Have you ever been married?
Do you have children?
No.
Did you ever commit
a minor traffic violation?
Yes.
Are you now in Mississippi?
No.
Have you ever revealed
any classified information
to anyone without
proper security clearance?
No.
Have you ever taken
any illegal drugs?
Yes.
Have you taken
any illegal drugs
since joining
the Central Intelligence Agency?
No.
Did you pass a razor blade
to Afzal Hamid?
No.
Okay.
Here we go.
All ready, sir?
Um, is your name David Estes?
Yes.
Do you work for the Central
Intelligence Agency?
Yes.
Are you married?
You know, I was married,
but I cheated on her,
so that kind of soured things.
Is that a no?
No.
No. Okay.
Uh, do you have children?
Yes.
Not that they're talking to me.
Did you pass a razor blade
to Afzal Hamid?
No.
Find anything?
Eight million fingerprints,
a man's belt from Macy's--
size 32--
couple of takeout
food containers
from a local
Chinese restaurant.
Condoms.
Condoms? What else?
A six-pack of diet Coke
in the refrigerator.
That's it?
Interview the neighbors?
In progress.
Her?
GALVEZ:
Not yet.
(sighs)
I apologize for all
the commotion, ma'am.
We'll be out of your hair soon.
Oh, this is very exciting.
(chuckles)
It's not often we get
a murderer living
in the neighborhood.
Murderer?
That's what Marilyn
across the street said--
a cold-blooded murderer
raped and strangled
some poor girl
over in Fairfax County.
Whew! Lock your doors tight tonight.
Oh, I will.
Mr. Jawdal moved in
about, uh...
three weeks ago?
That's right.
Anything you can tell me
about him?
He was very quiet and polite.
They pretty much
kept to themselves.
They?
He and his wife.
- What happened? - I don't know. Someone must
have found out about the house.
How?
I don't know.
Where are we going?
Someplace safe.
Says who?
This is nuts.
There's no one there.
Yeah? How do you know?
I know. Relax, okay?
We're fine.
Fine?
Are you kidding me?
We're not fine.
We're fucked!
(sighs)
Raqim?
What?
I'm sorry I dragged
you into this.
You didn't drag me into it.
Okay?
I dragged myself into it.
I am a victim of
your fabulousness.
Are you saying I'm fabulous?
Yes, I am.
You are so full of shit.
WOMAN: I asked all of you
here today to help me
say good-bye
to my former husband,
Tom Walker.
This has been a...
(laughs):
very difficult...
eight years.
And now finally we can...
give Tom the farewell
he deserves.
Tom, uh, always said
that Nick Brody
was his closest friend.
And Nick was with Tom
when he died.
Nick.
(blows landing, grunting)
Tom Walker was a good man.
A true Marine...
and the best shot
I ever encountered, bar n...
Sorry.
Tom was the opposite
of pretentious,
whatever that is.
Humble?
He just wanted to get the job
done and get back to his family.
(sniffles)
Staff Sergeant Calhoun?
CALHOUN:
Present!
BRODY:
Private First Class
Fernandez?
Present!
Private First Class Wakefield?
Present.
Captain Faber?
Present!
Private First Class Green?
Present.
Corporal Walker?
Corporal Thomas Walker?
Corporal Thomas...
Patrick...
Walker.
(sighs)
Good service.
Yeah, it was really good.
Will you excuse me?
I'll be back in a minute, all right?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Okay? All right.
CARRIE:
Sergeant Brody?
Yeah?
Hey. That must
have been hard.
Yeah.
Hey, I hate to do
this right now,
but my bosses
kind of insist.
We need you to come out to
Langley to take a polygraph.
Why?
I'm afraid that's classified.
Can you come out today?
Is this to do with Hamid?
I can't say.
I'm sorry.
Well, I got to go
back to the reception.
They're having it at my house.
Oh, um...
how about tomorrow?
10:00 a.m.?
Okay.
Faisel's got a woman with him--
maybe a girlfriend,
maybe a wife,
maybe just a cohort.
She's Caucasian,
mid-20s,
blond hair, blue/green eyes,
depending who you talk to.
Caucasian?
Yep.
What do we know about her?
Nothing.
We lifted a bunch
of fingerprints
from the house--
we're hoping at least
one of them will be hers and that we'll
be able to I.D. her.
Hey, can we change gears
for a second?
When this is all over,
I'd like to go
back to the field.
I thought you were
done with the field.
Mira's been offered a job
heading up
the Red Cross in India,
and Ed Welles retires
in a few months,
so, you know, I thought...
You thought
you'd end
your illustrious career
as the New Delhi Station Chief.
Who said anything about
ending my illustrious career?
I'll take it up
to the seventh floor.
Thanks.
Sir.
Yeah?
Faisel's license plate.
Toll booth on I-70
caught it.
Where on I-70?
20 miles west of Baltimore.
SAUL: When?
WOMAN: Five hours ago.
Well, if they stayed on I-70,
they should be somewhere
around Columbus, Ohio, by now.
Alert the Ohio State Police.
We also
have a photo
of Faisel and the girl
SAUL: Run her face through the databases.
Also see if
that fancy new face-recognition
software gets us anything.
Also try and match her face to anyone
who popped up because of fingerprints.
Raqim?
We're here.
This is it?
You sure?
This is where they
said we'd be safe.
FAISEL: They said
they'd meet us here?
They said to sit tight
and they'd contact us.
(insects chittering)
Wait! Don't open the door.
FAISEL: What?
- Why? Why? - Don't open the door. Close
that, close that gently.
Gently.
Get back in the car.
(engine starts)
(tires screech)
(panting) Oh, fuck,
oh, fuck, oh, fuck.
We're okay.
Oh, fuck. You keep saying that!
Because it's true!
You sure there was a bomb?
I could see the trigger--
pressure-released.
Open the door and boom-- very
simple and very effective.
What? How do you
know this shit?
They... they-they
trained me.
They trained you?!
You never told me that!
Does it matter?
Yes, it does matter!
We are supposed to be
in a relationship!
honest with each other!
We should turn ourselves in.
And spend the rest of our
lives being interrogated
in some offshore
torture chamber?
We haven't actually
broken any law.
They can't hold us forever.
Tell that to the guys in Guantanamo.
(panting)
We got to get rid of this car.
(exhales)
MEN (rapping): * I'm not dealing with
another fuckin' politic *
♪ I'm like a skillet bubblin'
until it filters up ♪
♪ I'm about to kill it,
I can feel it ♪
♪ Building up, blow this
buildin' up, I've been ♪
♪ Sealed enough,
my cup runneth over ♪
♪ I done filled it up,
the pen explodes and busts ♪
♪ Ink spills my guts, you think
all I do is stand here... ♪
(rap continues in distance)
Helen?
Yes?
I'm so sorry.
Oh, thank you.
No.
I'm sorry I was
such a bitch to you
when you decided to marry Matt.
Oh, Jessica, you were just
holding on to
Brody, that's all.
You didn't want to let him go.
And see?
You were right.
Here he is.
♪ ...Hear my voice
till you're sick of it ♪
♪ You ain't gonna
have a choice ♪
♪ If I gotta scream
until I have half a lung ♪
♪ If I have half a chance,
I'll grab it ♪
♪ Rabbit run!
(laughter, whooping)
(chatter, laughter)
(laughter)
(indistinct chatter)
Hey, hey, to Tom Walker.
ALL:
To Tom Walker.
What went on over there, Nick?
How'd you and Walker get hit?
Well...
(clears throat)
...we were dug in.
You know, uh, next thing I know,
we're taking fire
from all sides and, uh...
and we ate dirt and prayed.
They were waiting for you.
Somebody screwed up.
Somebody always screws up.
Rear echelon motherfuckers.
Mm-hmm.
You are so full of shit, Brody.
Lauder, shut the fuck up.
No, no,
I think it's important
to state for the record,
in case anybody's wondering,
which they're not...
but hey,
the record's
the record--
Brody is full of shit.
Right up to his
fucking eyeballs.
It's always good sharing
a beer with you, Lauder.
Exactly when did Wild Man Brody
become a dick-
sucking war hero,
trotted out by the brass
so all the fucking
morons in this country
could have something
to feel good about,
so they'd stop asking:
What's the point,
what the fuck are we even
doing in Iraq and Afghanistan?
And when did you,
who once told me
you just wanted
to come back in one piece,
become the Boy Scout poster
boy for fucking recruitment,
suckering another
couple thousand boys
from fucking Indiana
and the Bronx to go out and get
their fucking legs blown off?
What happened to you?
Here's my question:
how come Walker died
and you came back alive?
What's that about?
Huh, what's that about?
Luck, Lauder,
that's what
it's all about--
good luck and bad luck.
I'm glad you brought up
the subject of luck.
Mike, you got anything
to say about that, you being
an expert on luck and all?
You're such an asshole.
Can I be honest?
I'll be honest.
Why not?
We're all compadres, right,
brothers in arms
and all that crap?
While you were away,
there's not a man here
who didn't want to bend
your wife over the sink
and fuck her up the ass.
You son of a bitch.
(punching)
Come on, come on.
(grunting)
You were my friend.
(panting)
Brody.
Fuck.
(tires screeching)
Meet Aileen Margaret Morgan.
28 years old, brown hair,
sometimes dyed blondish,
blue eyes, five-
five, 110 pounds.
This photo was
taken six years ago
when she was arrested
protesting outside
a G-8 meeting in Edinburgh.
The one to the right
was taken six months ago for
her current driver's license.
Somehow she made the journey
from Connecticut schoolgirl
to terrorist's girlfriend
involved in a plot
against America.
How?
Why?
Dig into her history.
Where did she grow up,
where did she go to school,
who were her friends, where
and when did she meet Faisel?
All of it.
Anything more about the car?
I want every cop
on the eastern seaboard
looking for that damn thing.
Sir?
Yeah.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but it's...
What?
Spit it out, spit it out.
It's time, sir.
Anybody know what
he's talking about?
I think it's time
for your polygraph.
Polygraph?
I don't have time
for a fucking polygraph.
It's all right, Saul,
you'll be fine.
If anything comes up,
I'll come and get you.
You're not gonna miss
anything important.
Please help me out here.
This is how we're
going to get Brody.
Look for any contacts overseas,
especially in the Middle East.
School, exchange programs,
graduate school,
kibbutz, anything.
This is
the polygraph room, sir.
Oh, is that right?
Hello, Larry.
Hello, Saul.
How's everything?
Oh, just peachy.
Okay.
Would you hold that for me?
Thank you.
Could you hold this
for me right here?
Born December 25, 1983,
Houston, Texas.
Father is Owen Robert Morgan,
mother is
Abigail Sarah Lifeliter.
RAKOR vice president.
He ever work in
the Middle East?
Saudi Arabia, 1991 to '96.
Looks like he's a pretty big
deal in the oil business.
Okay, so we've got
a rich American girl
living in Saudi
Arabia for five years
between the ages
of eight and 13.
When did Faisel leave Saudi
Arabia to study in the States?
1995.
So they overlapped
by four years.
(sighs)
What happened, Aileen?
What did you see?
Is your name Saul Berenson?
For Christ's sake.
(sighs) Yes.
Saul, calm down.
We've been through this before.
Take a deep breath,
think of something pleasant.
Okay?
Okay.
Uh, do you live
at 413 Circle Drive,
Washington, D.C.?
Yes.
There we go.
Much better.
Do you work for the
Central Intelligence Agency?
Yes.
Is your office
on the fifth floor?
Yes.
Are you planning
on telling the truth today
about Afzal Hamid
and the razor blade?
Yes.
Did you pass Afzal Hamid
a razor blade?
No.
Saul.
You got to relax
or we'll be here all night.
I can't be here all night.
We've got an emergency
going on out there.
The real world will not wait
for these bureau-
fucking-cratic idiocies.
(sighs)
We'll finish it tomorrow.
Saul.
(door slams)
Where'd she go after Princeton?
Jordan-- the Peace Corps.
How long?
Two years.
Do any traveling
while she was there?
Uh, Egypt, Lebanon--
oh, here we go--
SaArabia, March 22
to March 30, 2004.
Any overlaps with Faisel?
March 26 to 27, 2004.
Faisel visits his grandmother.
Aileen Morgan and Raqim
Faisel met somewhere
between 1991 and 1996
in Saudi Arabia.
They reacquainted themselves
there March 26 to 27,
also in Saudi Arabia.
They were childhood friends.
That was fast.
I got to go back,
finish tomorrow.
I figured you might
need me out here.
(sighs)
A naive, weak-willed American
rich girl falls madly in love
with a Saudi engineer
who happens to be a terrorist.
Sacrifices all to be with him
and help fulfill his mission,
whatever the fuck that is.
Sound convincing?
Why hasn't she cracked
at least a little bit,
called her parents,
run away, something?
Things are getting
pretty hairy for an amateur.
Maybe we've got it backwards.
Maybe she's the one
driving this.
She's the terrorist?
(phone rings)
Carrie here.
It's me--
Brody.
Yeah, y-y-you gave me
your number.
Should I hang up?
What's wrong?
(sighs)
I can't do the polygraph
tomorrow.
Why not?
I just can't, I'm a mess.
I've had the worst fucking day.
I could tell them my name
and it would sound like a lie.
Where are you?
♪
(clears throat)
♪ And I just don't need you
♪ Hangin' 'round
♪ Take your advice,
your so-called wisdom... ♪
Oh, you didn't have to come.
Uh, I'll have
whatever he's having.
Bourbon, straight bourbon.
Okay.
What's the difference,
I always wondered.
Straight's been aged for two
years in charred oak barrels.
Ugh, still tastes
like gasoline to me.
(both chuckle)
What happened to your hand?
I decked my best friend.
Ouch.
Hurts like a motherfucker,
excuse my French.
Uh, I was talking
about your friend.
Don't--
he's an asshole.
Want to tell me about it?
You ever been married
by any chance?
Nope.
Why not?
It just hasn't felt right
quite yet.
Or as important
as what I do for a living.
Plus the guy I was seeing
when I left for Iraq decided
I wasn't worth the wait.
Nice.
Eh, I can't say I really blame him.
I mean...
(laughs)
...it's not like I was
Little Miss Faithful over there.
(chuckles)
Hey, if you don't slow down,
I'm never gonna be
able to catch up.
How come, when I met you
at the safe house the other day,
you pretended like we hadn't
bumped into each other
at the, uh, support group?
Oh, that.
Yeah, that.
You mean aside from the fact
that I'm not supposed
to get help from counselors
outside the agency?
Is there another reason?
I don't know.
Standing there
that night in the rain.
I figured, who else had to know?
What?
(laughs)
I like it when
life is like that.
Like what, wet?
Heightened somehow.
When I was a girl, my friends
and I used to play chicken
with the train on the tracks
near our house,
and no one could ever beat me,
not even the boys.
(clicks tongue)
(sighs)
(slurring):
I can't stand the Wizards.
What kind of name is that anyway
for a basketball team--
the Wizards?
What are they, like,
magicians in hoods?
(both laughing)
Redskins?
(gasps)
I love the Redskins.
Me, too.
No, I grew up on the Redskins.
My father thought
he was a Redskin.
He used to take me to games
in the freezing cold.
One time we wore sleeping bags.
(laughs)
We climbed in, we zipped 'em up.
All you could see was our eyes.
You have great eyes.
Thank you.
Kind of secretive.
Ah, comes with the job.
Secretive eyes--
it's a requirement,
Yeah?
Really.
Oh, Jesus, we drank too much.
Yeah, we did.
Oh, I hope I don't puke.
You're gonna puke?
No.
You all right?
I'm half Irish.
The Irish don't puke?
(laughing): Nah, only when we have
to salute the British.
(both laughing)
(laughter)
This is me.
Want to know
what it's all about?
The polygraph?
I thought that was classified.
It is.
Hamid's dead.
Someone slipped him
a razorblade in the safe house.
Slit his wrists.
So...
(moaning)
(both panting)
(Carrie moaning)
(moaning)
(both moan)
(both panting)
♪ Will I ever catch a break?
♪ That's when I remember
♪ He's the one
I have to fake 'cause I got... ♪
Any more secrets
you want to share, huh?
What else don't I know?
Can't hear the song.
How can you just sit there
listening to wailing cowboys
when our lives
are falling apart?
I need to relax. I can't think
straight if I don't relax.
No, what we need
is a fucking plan.
What if we went to Mexico?
No. We should turn ourselves in.
No.
Yes, we can ask for
protective custody.
I'd rather die.
♪ Don't sweat
the little things... ♪
Yeah? Well, you're going to.
(sighs)
I got to pee.
♪ And pulled out a .45
♪ Well, that's when
people started to scramble ♪
♪ I saw a child in the front
(sighs)
♪ Without thought,
I told the children ♪
♪ As the stranger fired
his gun ♪
♪ And I thought, Lord,
I thank you... ♪
(dog barking)
(gunfire)
(gasps)
(panting)
(silverware clinking)
You're awake.
Jet lag, I guess.
I got some good news.
Hmm. Do you want some tea?
Tea? Sure.
Thanks.
Oh.
I've put in
for the New Delhi station.
Ed Welles retires
in a few months.
I believe
I've got Estes' backing.
Take the new job.
I can come with you.
I don't want you
to come with me.
What?
I want to go alone.
I need to go alone.
Why?
I just do.
For how long?
I-I don't know.
A week?
I don't know.
A month?
What?
I don't know.
(sighs)
New job?
Just a ploy?
Your way
of letting me down gently?
Saul...
we're like good friends
sharing a house.
You do the dishes,
I water the garden.
You are watching football,
I watch cooking shows.
You play golf, I do yoga.
Sounds perfect.
Come on. We're late.
Come on.
Have a good day at school,
sugar bunny.
Right.
JESSICA:
Dana.
(car doors close)
(car engine starts)
LARRY:
Did you go to college?
SAUL:
Yes.
LARRY: Did you major
in Political Science?
SAUL:
Yes.
Have you ever sold secrets
to an agent of another country?
SAUL:
No.
LARRY:
Are you married?
No, not really.
LARRY:
Yes or no?
I don't know, Larry.
Okay?
Maybe yes, maybe no.
Technically?
Technically, yes.
LARRY:
Did you give
Afzal Hamid a razorblade?
No.
That's it.
You're free.
Oh.
I hope I never see you again.
Oh, you will.
Thanks, buddy.
(sighs)
Trouble at home.
It'll blow over.
Brody next?
Brody's next.
Assuming he shows up.
This is it, Saul.
Finally.
Let's hope.
LARRY: Come on in,
Sergeant Brody.
Just stand over here.
This won't take long.
Can you just, uh,
take your jacket off?
You can put it on
the chair there.
(sniffles)
SAUL:
Oh...
(sighs)
(exhales)
LARRY:
Okay.
Now, just relax
and answer all the questions
honestly, yes or no.
All set?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Is your name Nicholas Brody?
Yes.
Are you a member
of the U.S. Marine Corps?
Yes.
Do you intend
to tell the truth here today?
Yes.
Have you ever sold secrets
to a foreign government?
No.
LARRY: Have you
ever been arrested?
BRODY: Yes.
I borrowed my dad's Pontiac one time.
I was 15 years old.
Have you ever been
arrested for a felony?
No.
Have you ever killed a man?
Yes.
Did you pass Afzal Hamid
a razorblade?
No.
Do you live at
3319 West Chapman Street?
BRODY:
Yes.
LARRY: Are you
sometimes called Nick?
BRODY:
Yes.
LARRY: Is Boston the
capital of Massachusetts?
BRODY:
Yes.
LARRY: Do you know Afzal Hamid?
BRODY:
Yes.
LARRY: Did you
meet him in Syria?
Yes.
Did you slip him a razorblade?
No.
Ask him again.
Did you slip
Afzal Hamid a razorblade?
No.
Ask him if he's ever been
unfaithful to his wife.
Go on, ask him.
LARRY: Have you ever been
unfaithful to your wife?
No.
Okay, Larry, wrap it up.
Thank you, Sergeant Brody.
That it?
We all done?
LARRY:
We're all done.
He's lying.
He passed the polygraph.
Same one you and I take
and flub every time.
Or at least I do.
(sighs)
It's... It's over.
Man is clean.
Saul...
You can't deny the facts--
what we just
witnessed--
just 'cause you find
them inconvenient.
(sighs)
So...
now we know
that Sergeant Brody's
been faithful to his wife.
Question:
Why do we care?
What was that all about?
(sighs)
Get in.
(car door bell dings)
(tires squeal)
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com