Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
PRESIDENT REAGAN: Air and naval
forces of the United States
launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
REPORTER: Pan Am Flight 103 crashed
into the the town of Lockerbie.
REAGAN:
George Herbert Walker Bush...
GEORGE BUSH, SR.: This will not stand,
this aggression against Kuwait.
REPORTER:
The USS Cole was attacked...
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable
and cowardly act.
The next song we're gonna play
for you is one
of the good ol' favorites.
Until something shocks him...
WOMAN: I'm just making sure
we don't get hit again.
MAN: That plane crashed into
the World Trade Center.
REPORTER:
Running up...
We must, we will be vigilant.
(speaking Arabic)
God!
CARRIE: Fuck! I missed
something once before.
I won't... I can't let
that happen again.
SAUL:
It was ten years ago.
- Everyone misses something.
- Everyone is not me.
Previously on Homeland...
What were his exact words?
"An American prisoner of war
has been turned."
I'm an American.
CARRIE:
If he is a terrorist,
we need eyes and ears
on Brody from the minute
he steps off that plane.
Out of the question.
How long before you're set up?
The feed will be live
by the time Sergeant Brody
gets back to his house.
VIRGIL:
Hello, Big Brother.
Ready for you, Sergeant
Brody, your debriefing.
I want to call my wife first.
Jessica, it's me.
Pleased to meet you.
Hug him, Chris.
(crowd cheering)
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
I want to say thank you
to my family
for their strength
in my absence.
Three days ago, we were
about to tell your kids.
He's my husband, Mike.
Abu Nazir? Was he present during
any of your interrogations?
No.
I didn't think that this was
any of my business.
Now I'm thinking that it is.
Just tell me
I'm not out here
risking federal prison
on behalf of a crazy person.
You know, maybe it is
all in my head,
but you're in it now, Virgil,
up to your fucking neck!
You think for one minute
you get away with this?
I thought that once
I had some proof...
Do you have any?
You've been suggesting
that Sergeant Brody's
what you think he is.
No.
Then get a lawyer.
I missed something once before,
I won't... I can't let
that happen again!
It was ten years ago.
Everyone missed
something that day.
It's a pattern.
Okay, do you see?
He's making contact, Saul.
He's sending
a message to somebody.
A handler,
a sleeper cell, somebody.
So am I still going to jail?
Not just yet.
(softly):
♪ From the halls of Montezuma ♪
♪ To the shores of Tripoli ♪
(panting)
(man speaks Arabic)
(shouts in Arabic)
♪ First to fight for
right and country ♪
♪ And to keep our honor clean ♪
(shouts in Arabic)
♪ We are proud to bear
the title ♪
(shouts in Arabic)
♪ Of United States Marine. ♪
(Brody shouts, gasps
over monitor)
(panting)
Hey.
You want some coffee?
Dana, Chris, come on!
We're gonna be late!
CHRIS:
Coming!
First day at work and they're
gonna make me late.
You want some eggs before I go?
Hey.
Hey, slow down.
CHRIS: Mom, I can't
find my socks!
Sausage, I think
we have sausage.
Happened again, didn't it?
Look in the dryer!
Dana, can you please help him?
Yeah.
Around 4:00 a.m. this morning.
You were yelling something
that sounded like Arabic
over and over.
You grabbed my arm really hard.
You wouldn't let go.
(gasping)
Jesus.
Show me.
CHRIS:
Hey, Mom, Dad.
They're still out there.
Do they stay out
there all night,
even when we're sleeping?
(reporters clamoring)
You forgot to flush again,
you little douche.
Dana, language.
(phone rings)
"Douche" is not a bad word.
Don't answer that!
Hello?
CBS News.
Third time this week.
Tell 'em I'm not here.
He says he's not here.
Hey, I thought
you didn't want to be late.
I know, maybe I should take
another day off.
Hey, all those years
on my own, Jess, I think I can
handle one more day.
All right? Go on.
Get out of here.
All right, come on, you guys.
(snaps fingers) Come on,
come on, come on, come on.
(door opens,
reporters clamoring)
(siren blips, whoops)
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Hello!
Hello?!
(reporters clamoring outside)
MAN:
There he is!
Brody, how does it feel
to be free?
Is it true
you're gonna reenlist?
Are you going to reenlist?
Would you ever go back
out there, Sergeant?
How does it feel
to be home again, sir?
Sir, are you going to reenlist?
(phone rings)
(sighs)
(ringing continues)
I've been going over
Brody's finger tapping
with the crypto team,
and I hate to say it, Saul,
but there's little, if any,
repeat pattern combination.
Not even a quadratic basis
to work with here.
I'll keep trying as long as
you need, but there's nothing
definitive one way
or the other yet.
Keep looking.
I want to leave no
stone unturned on this.
We'll talk later.
(wry laugh)
What do you think?
Oh, definitely an original...
by one of the preeminent
Dutch painters of his time.
Relatively recent acquisition,
if I'm not mistaken.
By an artist who,
as it turns out,
was not only Dutch
but also Jewish.
In a club with
no Jewish members.
That was your point, wasn't it?
How do you take it?
(sighs)
Your Honor, I'm not
asking for anything
that hasn't been granted
many thousands of times over
in the last ten years.
A surveillance warrant
on an unspecified subject
on American soil-- if this
were a standard request,
you'd go through standard
procedure, Saul.
In this case, I don't have time
for a government lawyer
to petition the court.
So you're asking me to issue
a FISA warrant directly to...
What is it exactly do you do
at Langley these days?
Among other things,
pay house calls
to those I'd prefer
not to have to...
strong arm?
Disturb.
Are you ever gonna let me off
your hook, Saul?
Well...
We both know you're far too fine
a judge for that, Geoffrey.
Can we at least act like
this is about the law
rather than a brief moment
of weakness in my past?
This is absolutely about
the law, Your Honor.
Hmm.
Shit.
(sighs)
(turns faucet on and off)
CARRIE:
Hey, Maggie, it's me.
Sorry I haven't called
in a while; I been slammed.
Um, thought I'll come see
you guys for a night,
if that's good with you.
Uh... call me back.
Let me know.
Thanks. Bye.
(footfalls) (gasps)
(sighs)
I've got a doorbell, you know?
Well, you think you still have
a right to privacy
with all this?
My God, look at this place.
It's broken--
the doorbell.
What's that?
This gives you four weeks.
You got a warrant?
A FISA warrant?
We're legal now?
Legal-ish, but far
from official,
and certainly
not Estes-proof.
Be very careful not to mistake
this for a stamp of approval,
or sanction from me
for you to wage some
sort of personal war.
Eyes on Brody makes
complete sense.
It's exactly what you'd have
done in my shoes, Saul.
No, it is not.
You lied to me
about it, Carrie.
Then right here in this room,
when I called you on it...
I know what I did.
And I know it was wrong...
and insulting.
Insulting...
and barely scratches
the surface of what that was.
Four weeks, Carrie.
Not a second longer.
I want to show you something.
He has nightmares.
Where he repeatedly begs
someone to kill him, in Arabic.
He's too ashamed or scared
or both to face the press
outside his house or take calls
from the TV news,
so what does he do?
He finds shelter in the
corner of the bedroom,
where he hasn't moved
in over five hours.
All of which makes
complete sense
after eight years of captivity.
But what if it's
more than that?
(sighs)
If-if Brody had really
been turned, as you say,
you know what he'd more
likely be doing by now?
Talking to the press
outside his house,
doing TV interviews,
playing the hero card
for every penny it's worth.
Maybe it's not that simple
for him.
Get some sleep, Carrie.
No one said becoming a terrorist
was easy, Saul.
If you'd been taken prisoner,
tortured for God knows how long
and somehow,
finally been turned,
then, one day, you come home,
and suddenly it's real, it's on!
Well, that's one interpretation.
But that's all it is
at the moment.
Clean your apartment.
And eat some real food.
(door opens)
(door closes)
(sirens wailing in distance)
LYNNE:
Raised in Colorado Springs,
attended BYU,
interests,
finance, travel, men.
Stacey Moore,
this is Latif Bin Walid,
Majordomo for his Highness,
Prince Farid.
Please continue.
Would you say you're outgoing,
or more the quiet type, Stacey?
I'd say more outgoing.
Definitely social.
I like to party,
if that's what you mean.
Do you drink?
I'm not a drinker, per se,
if that's what you mean.
(sighs) Stacey...
You are interviewing for a job
that pays, in two years,
more than most people
in this country earn in 20.
If you're successful
in this interview,
you'll be required to appear
self-possessed, confident,
modest and reticent
all at the same time.
So, stop asking what I mean.
Think and answer for yourself.
Do you enjoy anal sex?
Excuse me?
How about other women?
Sure.
Both.
Have you ever dated
any famous men?
That's none of your business.
You need to wax that, sweetie.
Hair down there's not an option
for His Highness.
Very nice.
You're through
the final interview.
We'll contact you
within the next week.
Congratulations,
and you can get dressed now.
(phone beeps on)
Who are you calling?
My aesthetician.
I, too, need a wax
before the prince gets in.
Feel free to book the
appointment for me, if you like.
Music.
Mm-hmm. On hold.
Kenny G.
Welcome to America.
Gimme.
Would you mind selecting the
next girl to come in, please?
Come on, pick up, pick up.
Hi. This is Lynne Reed.
Two E's.
I was referred by one
of her clients, Carrie.
Yes, that's her.
I need to book a Brazilian wax
for noon tomorrow.
Right. No-- that's the only time
I can do it.
Okay, noon it is.
We'll see you then.
(keypad beeping)
(phone ringing)
Hello.
Carrie, it's Yvonne Marshall.
I'm the duty officer tonight.
Hi, Yvonne. What is it?
You have an asset
in from the cold.
Booked a treatment tomorrow
at the Yara Spa in Georgetown.
Lynne Reed?
That's right. She used your
first name as a reference
and made a noon appointment.
Noon?
Ar-Are you sure she said noon?
That was the only time
she could make it.
(sighs)
Okay. Thanks, Yvonne.
(phone beeps off)
(door opens over monitor)
(door closes)
Hi.
Mm. How was school?
Okay.
Is Dad here?
Don't know.
JESSICA: If you want to help, you
can start unpacking those for me.
Hey.
How was your day?
Great.
FOSTER: Oh. Hope
you don't mind, Mike.
We helped ourselves
to some of your hooch.
Thought we would
stop by for a...
for a situation report
on Sergeant Brody.
(sighs)
Situation report
on Brody is this:
He's been back three days,
and it's gonna take a little
more time until he's willing
to come out of his shell,
let alone his house.
The man represents a significant
victory in the war on terror,
thanks to our friends
at the CIA.
I'm putting aside
for the moment
that Sergeant Brody
owes them his life.
These are the facts:
Bin Laden's dead...
and America thinks,
or wants to think,
that this war is
drawing to an end.
Politicians are pushing for a
wholesale withdrawal
from Afghanistan.
But as we all know, Captain,
the terrorists
are still out there--
after blood.
We need Brody in the public eye,
reminding America
that this is far from over.
What if he's not up for it...
psychologically?
Fuck it.
Drive on.
Isn't that what
you Marines say?
In combat, where we also shit
in Saran Wrap and shoot to kill.
You want Brody to do that, too?
Don't take that tone
with me, Captain.
Career pencil-pusher, with
his brown nose in my scotch
saying, "Fuck it, drive on."
You're a captain in the
United States Marines.
You mean to tell me you can't
give a sergeant a direct order?
Is that what you want me
to report up the chain?
Look, Mike, I get it.
You and Brody are
friends, right?
By the way,
how's his wife Jennifer doing?
Jessica.
If not for us, Brody should
at least do it for her.
For the kids.
And I'm sure you're
more than familiar
with their current
financial problems.
DOD's offering a very generous
reenlistment package,
plus a promotion,
that could pull his family
out of the shitter.
(puts glass down)
Give your friend
the correct advice, Captain.
Make it happen.
(puts glass down)
(door opens)
(indistinct conversation)
(video game gunfire
and explosion sound effects)
Where does Mom
keep the pancake mix?
The what...?
You're toast, asswipe.
BRODY:
Found it.
Hey, Dad...
What's it like to kill somebody?
(sighs)
Can I help you?
Yeah, just a couple
questions, Sergeant Brody.
Nick. Can I call you Nick?
You got ten seconds
to get off my property.
I'm Alan Quick, channel 10,
and technically, I'm standing
on a public easement.
Five seconds.
Oh, come on, Nick.
Hey, how about we start
with an easy one?
Tell me, how are your kids
doing with all of the--
(blow lands, Alan groaning)
(gagging)
(Alan gasping over monitor)
(wheezing, gasping)
(Alan coughing)
(panting)
(Alan groaning and gasping)
(birds chirping)
Fuck.
Fuck!
Max, he's heading
through the woods out back.
Uh, less than a minute ago.
I need you to hurry round
to Mansfield Road.
It's about 400 yards north.
Okay. Call me back
when you find him.
(sizzling)
Shit.
Who left this pan on the stove?
(steam hissing)
Chris!
Where's Dad?
♪ ♪
(door opens)
You know, the whole
reason I left the Company
and went freelance was
so I could have a life.
You're becoming my wife's
least favorite person.
I've got incoming HUMINT
I got to go deal with.
Who is it?
Someone I recruited
in Bahrain a few years ago.
Professional girlfriend
of a Saudi prince.
What's she got?
We'll find out soon enough.
(sighs)
You got anything to eat?
Um... yeah.
There's a yogurt in the fridge.
(water trickling)
Lynne, how are you?
Okay, fine, I guess.
W-What are you doing
here in D.C.?
Prescreening more girls
for the prince's harem.
He gets in tomorrow.
12:00 noon appointment.
What's the code red?
So, there I am,
five days ago, in Cypress
on Prince Farid Bin Abbud's
yacht...
(panting)
when the Prince's Majordomo,
Latif Bin Walid,
announces that the prince
has a surprise visitor.
So, this surprise visitor,
who was he?
You know that they stone
women like me to death
if we get caught doing anything
that we're not supposed to?
(sighs)
(men speaking Arabic)
Abu Nazir.
I was this far from him.
I really don't want to do this
anymore, and I mean it, Carrie.
I feel like I can't
even breathe now.
They're gonna
suspect something.
Lynne, all you have to do now
is keep your eyes and ears open
for the remainder of
your contract with the prince.
That's what you said when
you recruited me in Bahrain,
but I never thought that
I would get eight feet
from the most dangerous
terrorist in the world.
You are the only agency asset
to have had eyes on Nazir
in seven years.
Asset?
I am just some girl
from Sandusky, Ohio,
who you talked into
helping out her country.
And I won't let
anything happen to you.
Don't quit on me now, please.
You can't.
Don't think I don't
appreciate what it took
for you to do this, Lynne.
(over phone):
Saul Berenson.
Alert the group, Saul.
Inform Estes.
This is a game-changer.
Can't be more specific?
I don't want to talk
on an open line.
Source protection?
It's way past
source protection, Saul.
I've got a visual confirm
on the Sandman.
What?
CARRIE: You heard me.
Actual eyes on.
How far away are you?
20 minutes.
I'll assemble the group.
What are you doing here?
Have to talk to Brody.
Hey, bud.
What's up?
My dad beat the crap
out of somebody.
Dana, I asked you to please
watch TV with Chris for a while.
She went to her room.
Beat the crap out of who?
Can you please go watch TV
for a little while?
I need to talk to Uncle Mike.
Can you do that for me?
Yeah.
Okay.
Come in.
What's going on?
Why aren't the kids at school?
You don't know? Isn't
that why you're here?
No. What?
Are you okay?
Brody hit a reporter and then
he took off into the woods.
Chris saw the whole thing.
Take a breath, Jess.
Come here.
Well, hello, Mrs. Brody.
MIKE:
When was this?
JESSICA:
About an hour ago, maybe more.
Why didn't you call me
right away, Jess?
What the hell is that?
He has nightmares.
Brody did that?
Or flashbacks,
whatever you call them.
I have to make it work
with Brody. I have to.
This is where he tells you
everything's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay, Jess.
JESSICA:
Is it really?
Do you honestly think so?
Ugh.
That's disgusting, Carrie.
This is the first
confirmed sighting
of Abu Nazir in seven years.
And very much to your credit.
Nobody's arguing with that.
But it's not enough
to authorize a task force.
I'm not asking for that.
All I need is a few more bodies
on Sergeant Brody.
(sighs) Look, the
circle's small.
We keep it that way
till you have more than
just a theory
linking Brody and Abu Nazir.
So Abu Nazir's
resurfacing just as
Brody has miraculously
returned home means nothing?
It's just a coincidence?
The dots are there, Carrie, but
you haven't connected them yet.
Saul, I understand that
you're still furious with me,
but give me
something here, please.
(sighs)
I'm not telling you to stop.
I'm telling you to slow down.
The FISA warrant--
that gives you four weeks.
Use it.
Carefully, methodically.
Look, like it or not, you work
for Deputy Director David Estes,
who has career stakes in Brody,
whom he and his department
brought home to great fanfare.
Want to challenge that,
better be damn sure you get
all your ducks in a row first.
(sighs)
(phone beeps on)
Where is he now?
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know?
He can't have gone far.
Listen to me, if Brody has
one 15-second meeting
with one contact,
that's all it'll take.
I'm not gonna miss that.
Find him and find him fast.
Call me back.
ESTES:
...last 14 days of
air traffic data
from all airports--
commercial, cargo.
And the banks.
All new patterns and numerical
transactions of any amounts.
Please. Thank you.
Let me be the first to say,
Carrie, outstanding work.
All other files on your
desk go on the back burner,
as of right now.
I want your girl on this prince
Farid like white on rice.
Mike.
First thing you get her to do
is upload the data
on his BlackBerry.
She's scared out of her mind.
Thank you.
I need to be able
to guarantee her protection.
Backup.
Would a four-man
fire team do it?
Great.
For an escort you
recruited in Bahrain?
Don't be a prick, David.
You know damn well if we
put a Quick Reaction Team
on the girl in this
short time frame,
we have no idea of
knowing who's watching.
If Abu Nazir even smells we're
onto the prince, he'll vanish.
Into thin air, again.
It's the QRT's job
not to be detected.
You're saying
you can't trust those guys
to protect an asset in danger?
It's my job to make the
tough calls, Carrie.
The answer is no.
Your job is to
control your asset.
She needs backup,
you're it. Get it done.
Yes, sir.
(P.A. beeps)
WOMAN (over P.A.):
Will someone in Lighting
please pick up line three?
Lighting, line three, please?
(cell phone ringing)
Please let this be good news.
He's looking at everything.
Lumber, nails, screws,
electrical wiring,
power tools, you name it.
Is he taking notes or anything?
Whatever he's doing, looks like
he's doing it all in his head.
Okay, he's on the move.
I'll, uh, I'll call you back.
What?
JESSICA: I guess we
might as well eat.
Is Dad still AWOL?
MIKE: Oh, he'll be back,
don't you worry.
Hey.
Any new developments?
I'm telling you,
this guy's got to be wishing
that Brody doesn't come back
so he can keep doing the wife.
She thought
breaking up was easy.
Any popcorn in there?
Well, as a matter
of fact, we have...
pretzels.
I love-a da pretzels.
Uncle Mike,
since you're a captain
and Dad's only a sergeant, does
that make you the boss of him?
Smells delicious.
CHRIS: Don't sergeants have
to salute to the captain
and call him sir?
It's Irish stew!
Dad's favorite.
Right, Mom?
Is Dad in trouble?
Trouble? No, no.
Like I told you earlier, bud,
that reporter out there,
he's the one
who should be in trouble,
all right?
Wait, there's no
camera in the garage?
Uh, you know, on this budget,
I had to prioritize.
And now he's placing a bag
containing God knows
what in our blind spot?
Jesus Christ, Virgil!
Guys think about playing
a couple rounds of cards?
Yeah.
Huh?
Where's the sound?
Not that you deserve it, but...
(typing)
Thank you.
JESSICA: Where have you been?
Sorry.
I was out walking.
All day?
Didn't know that
wasn't allowed.
Please don't do that.
You know, the past eight years
haven't exactly been
a picnic for me
and the kids, either.
One way or another,
we've all changed.
We just have to find
a way to start over.
You punched a reporter.
Oh, he'll live.
In front of Chris.
He'll live, too.
That's it?
"He'll live?"
Dinner smells good.
Go on.
I lost.
There's no hand.
Oh.
Hey, guys.
What are you playing?
Hearts.
Hearts? Watch out
for this guy, kids.
Back in the day, he used to
double his paycheck
playing this game.
Hearts, which the Marines
call "Hunt the Cunt."
Dana!
Maybe the daughter
is the terrorist.
DANA: Don't blame me, Mom,
blame the Marines.
Fuck you, Virgil.
Right, and good night
to you, too.
Mom's Irish stew?
Should we say grace?
We say grace now?
When we have things
we're especially thankful
for, right, guys?
Can I do it, please?
JESSICA:
Go ahead, sweetie.
Dear God, thank you for
bringing my dad back.
Please make him a captain, too,
just like Mike.
(sighs)
What about the food, Chris?
Oh, yeah, and, uh,
thanks for the food.
MIKE:
Amen.
No.
You sure?
Cuban.
You always come over
here in uniform?
"Once a Marine,
always a Marine."
Does it start
something like that?
Look, I'm not gonna
bullshit you.
You can't keep
doing this, Brody.
BRODY:
Doing what?
MIKE: Come on, you know
it's a fuckin' win-win.
You talk to the press.
You take that call
from CBS News, I mean,
do an interview--
Whoa, whoa, stop
right there, Mike.
There gonna
give you a promotion.
I mean, Hollywood's gonna do
a fuckin' movie about you.
In the process,
you get to provide
for Jess and the kids.
BRODY:
I said stop!
The brass sent you over here
to turn me into some
fuckin' poster boy
for their bullshit war.
You know what?
You can go right back there
and tell 'em the days
that I take orders from
the United State military
or the government, are over.
Done.
You know what I
really need, Mike?
I need the last
eight years back...
where I get to take care
of my wife and kids...
where I don't get asked
to go over there
and fight their fucking war...
or I'm not taken prisoner.
Not left out there to rot.
Never tortured--
none of it.
Can you do that for me?
Or is it too much to ask?
BRODY:
There's the door.
Uncle Mike.
(sighs)
There are times when you have
to stand up for yourself...
and what you believe in.
I wish you hadn't seen
what you saw today,
but you did, and I'm sorry.
You gonna be okay?
(toothbrush whirrs, sports
broadcast on TV, over monitor)
ANNOUNCER:
That's what happens sometimes
when you have some success
against a great
offensive player.
(broadcast continues
indistinctly)
ANNOUNCER: Gets the ball,
puts up another three...
(crowd cheering on TV)
ANNOUNCER:
He's gone!
I'll tell you, they are having
an amazing season.
ANNOUNCER 2:
Back up by eight now.
Roberts has got
half the points.
He's got 15 of the 32.
He just keeps missing...
Everyone just wants
to thank you for your service.
Your sacrifice.
Maybe they want to thank all
of us-- you, me and the kids.
Fine.
One day, you're gonna want
to talk about all this.
Broadcast continues,
indistinctly)
♪ ♪
Take His Highness upstairs
to settle him in.
How long until his
next appointment?
Long enough.
Uh, yeah.
No, I read the article
in the Journal--
it's fantastic.
No, I'll call you
soon, we can--
(gasps)
Oh! Wow! I...
Are you fucking kidding me?
I am so sorry.
That was an accident.
Don't worry, sir.
Accidents happen.
Here, let me get that.
No need. Please.
May I at least
pay for the dry cleaning?
Thank you. No need.
Go wash it off.
You have less
than three minutes.
I'll wait here.
You're not gonna
believe what happened.
I-I spilled tea on this
girl's blouse and it's...
Jesus!
Under the sponge
of this compact,
there's a plug-in device
that'll fit into
the prince's Blackberry.
It'll need 45 seconds
to upload all his data.
And let's suppose that
I get that far...?
You call the spa again and you
hand it off to me in person.
What if the device doesn't fit?
It will.
You said before that you would
never let anything happen to me.
And I meant it.
There's a team
protecting you 24/7.
Where are they?
Aside from the man who
spilled tea on you just now,
who you won't see again,
they're right under your nose.
But if you can see them,
or know who they are,
that's a problem.
I need your compact.
♪ ♪
RUBY & JOSIE:
Auntie Carrie!
Hi!
Aw... Oh! Wow!
That is the best welcome
I've ever had from anyone.
How are you two?
You forgot
Ruby's birthday, silly.
It was really awesome.
This man brought
snakes and lizards
and turtles and everything.
A snake ate a rat.
Ugh!
I missed that? Damn!
I forgot your birthday.
I'm sorry, Ruby.
Oh, but there...
is this.
(laughs)
I told you, Ruby.
You thought I'd forget something
as important as that?
I was working
last Saturday, honey.
If I could've come, I would've.
I promise.
Mom! Mom! Look what Aunt Carrie
got Ruby for her birthday!
Wow, that is so cool!
Did you say thank you?
Thank you.
You're welcome, honey.
Okay, now, you two monkeys.
Come on in
and finish your homework.
You can see Aunt Carrie
when you're done.
That's impressive!
I beat them.
Don't tell the neighbors.
Come on in.
Staying for dinner?
I can't. I'd--
--love to, but you're
slammed as usual.
Maggie...
No, don't.
You don't have to explain.
(sighs)
We worry about you, Dad and I.
Yeah.
How's he doing?
Considering he has the
same illness you have...
Well, now he's under my roof,
he goes for regular therapy and
treatment-- that's the deal.
So, um... he's good.
Are you finished?
Come on, Maggie, ease up a bit.
Just once, give me a break.
Only seven this time?
Raiding my samples cupboard
not only enables you,
it jeopardizes my license,
so, uh... seven pills.
And we talk again in
a week, not a month.
Or you could just
deal with the problem
like any normal person would
and go see a psychiatrist.
I keep telling you
to work where I work.
You can't disclose your illness
or they'll pull
your security clearance.
I understand, Carrie.
I'm really good
at what I do, Maggie.
And I'm not just a quack.
Dad'll be pissed he missed you.
Where is he?
Bill took the day off.
They went golfing.
You said you were
coming tonight.
It's not even 6:00 yet.
Next time.
Okay.
I'll go say good-bye
to the girls.
Hello?
Please answer.
(door creaks, chains rattle)
♪ ♪
(switch clicks)
Shit, Virgil!
♪ ♪
(remote clicks, door rattles)
(men praying quietly in Arabic)
(men praying,
chanting in Arabic)
(prayers, chanting continue)
Allahu akbar.
(praying in Arabic)
(clears throat)
Couldn't sleep?
I was cleaning out the garage.
Oh... hey, I fixed the door.
(door shuts)
(reporters clamoring)
(clamoring)
You people ready?
Is it true you're gonna enlist?
Would you ever go back to Iraq?
Saul...
turn on your TV.
It's happening,
exactly what you said.
He's out there playing
the hero card.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com