PRESIDENT REAGAN: Air and naval
forces of the United States
launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
REPORTER: Pan Am Flight 103 crashed
into the the town of Lockerbie.
REAGAN: He has sanctioned
acts of terror
in Africa, Europe,
the Middle East.
PRESIDENT GEORGE H.W. BUSH: This will not stand,
this aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
REAGAN: This relentless
pursuit of terror.
PRESIDENT GEORGE W. BUSH:
We will make no distinction...
REPORTER:
The USS Cole was attacked
while refueling in
the port of Aden.
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable
and cowardly act.
The next song
we're going to play for you
is one of the good old
favorites.
Until something stops him.
WOMAN: I'm just making sure
we don't get hit again.
MAN: That plane crashed
into the World Trade Center.
Thousands of people running.
We must and we will remain
vigilant at home and abroad.
(Speaking Arabic)
SAUL:
What the fuck are you doing?
God!
CARRIE: Fuck! I missed
something once before.
I won't... I can't
let that happen again.
SAUL:
It was ten years ago.
Everyone missed something
that day.
CARRIE:
Everyone's not me.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Previously on Homeland...
You still haven't produced
a single lead
connecting Sergeant Brody
to any plot against America.
You need to take down
that surveillance.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey, I know you.
We're on to the next case.
Find this man, Raqim Faisel.
He followed me to this house.
No one knows
we're living here.
I still think we should leave.
Someone must have found out
about the house.
How? I don't know.
Where are we going?
Someplace safe.
We should turn ourselves in.
No!
Three days ago you were
about to tell your kids.
I mean, we were talking
about moving in together.
He's my husband, Mike.
You were my friend!
(grunting)
Hey, if you don't
slow down, I'm never
gonna be able to catch up.
(both moaning)
MAN: Have you ever been
unfaithful to your wife? No.
He's lying.
He passed the polygraph.
Get in.
(tires squeal)
(car door shuts)
(baby fussing)
Help you?
Ticket to Mexico.
Lot of cities in Mexico.
Tampico? Leon?
The next bus to Mexico,
whatever that is.
(baby crying)
Beaumont to Monterrey.
Transfer in Nuevo Laredo...
Sounds like a winner.
So, why am I here?
I don't know.
You just got in my car.
Well, I couldn't have gotten in
if you didn't stop for me.
True.
So, did I pass?
The polygraph? Yeah.
Flying colors.
So you won't be hauling
me in again next week?
Not that I know of.
I'm taking some time...
from home.
From Jess.
Is that right?
She was fucking someone.
I'm sorry.
So what exactly are we doing?
Well, I'd like a drink.
Or three.
All right, swanky
or hole-in-the-wall?
I don't like the word
"hole" anymore.
Right.
But I do like a good dive.
The more I drink,
the worse I play.
That's not happening to you.
I know.
Pissed off all my college
boyfriends, too.
All of them?
Both of them.
Fuck me.
Two out of three?
Buy me another, you're on.
Cuervo?
Tequila Revolucion, silver,
no lime.
You like your clear liquors.
What's up, chief?
You want a ride?
I got one.
What, Opie over there?
"88," huh?
Yeah, it's my jersey number
from high school.
Or code for HH.
Eighth letter of the alphabet.
"Heil Hitler."
You're not just a pretty face,
are you?
You guys are White Nation, huh?
That's cool.
It's Aryan pride, baby.
So what's the plan?
Like, world domination?
Yeah, that's right.
Any time soon?
You wanna hear about it?
You can come outside.
We got a van.
Hell, yeah.
I love sucking Nazi dick.
You know, I don't like people
fucking with me.
Well, who does?
Who does like people
fucking with them?
Hey, is there a problem?
Yeah, the problem is
this mouthy bitch.
Hey, look, are we okay here?
Huh?
So is there, like,
a supremacist fist bump?
What are you, a fucking moron?
Bitch!
Oh, God! Get those fuckers!
Oh, shit!
You fucking lunatic!
(Carrie laughs)
I gotta unlock it.
Open it! Okay, get in.
It's open.
Fuck you, bitch!
Here they come. Go!
(men yelling indistinctly)
(laughs)
You are a dangerous
fucking drunk.
Thanks.
It's not a compliment!
My hand!
(laughing)
Okay, okay, where now?
I have a cabin...
or my family does.
I've been meaning to get there.
Sounds like the stars
have aligned.
I-95. Hit it!
(Brody laughing)
Final touches, hon.
All smooth. There.
You're done.
Dana, you're up.
So, I'm thinking layers.
Like, maybe really cut it
to my shoulders or something.
Okay.
Where's Dad?
He's taking the weekend away.
Why?
Dana...
He knows about you and Mike.
Yeah.
Jesus, Ma.
Dana, I thought I was a widow.
Our situation was very unusual.
Yeah, so you
gave up on him and went whoring
out with his best friend.
You cannot talk
to me like that!
And now, Mom,
it's royally fucked up!
Enough with the language
and the attitude!
Or what?
Or you're grounded.
Yeah, right.
Starting right now!
The whole weekend, you're home.
I got a line on
our runaway terrorist.
The one whose boyfriend
got iced in the motel?
She stole a car outside
of Columbus last night.
Just turned up
in Beaumont, Texas.
Woman fitting
her description bought
a one-way bus ticket, cash.
Due to cross the border
late tonight.
We believe Nazir's people
killed her boyfriend Faisel,
and I think she'll
give them up.
Texas agents can
intercept the bus.
I want to go.
You want to go to Mexico?
Bring her back myself.
One-on-one.
You can talk to her here.
Put her in a room with a bunch
of suits, she'll go silent.
David, I get this girl.
I've spent the last three days
figuring her out.
I can get her to talk.
FBI's gotta escort you.
Fine, as long as they keep
their fucking distance.
David...
trust me.
Wow, I like it.
Yeah, it's old school.
No A.C.,
build your own fire, like that.
(grunts)
Yeah, it's perfect.
Where is the fucking key?
(phone rings)
Hello.
Maggie, it's me.
Hi.
Um, hey, just curious,
which rock do we keep
the cabin key under?
You're at the cabin?
Uh, no, I'm home.
Just wondering about the key.
Carrie, what's going on?
Uh, nothing. Nothing at all.
You were supposed to come over
tonight and get your meds.
Uh, Monday.
Gonna do that Monday.
You don't have a pill
for tomorrow or Sunday.
No, I have one left.
I'm fine.
You sound drunk.
(snorts) Drunk?
(laughs)
I am, actually, at the cabin
With who?
Uh, no, I'm all alone.
I'm meditating.
Okay, well, look,
take your pill tomorrow
and then come over Sunday night.
No skipping.
Okay, promise.
Okay.
Uh, so, the key?
It's in the old stove.
(gasps) Right! Stupid.
I remember.
Okay, um, thanks.
Hey, look, I'm at the open house
at the girls' school, but...
Oh, great. Have fun.
I'll drop everything and
leave if you're in trouble.
Okay, I'll see you Sunday.
Okay.
Everything okay?
Yeah. Wait.
Wait here.
(key jingles)
(keys jangling)
(sighs)
What you looking at?
A star.
Wait an hour.
You'll see thousands.
I just need one.
I'd ask you what you
were wishing for, but...
What?
How would I know if you
were telling the truth?
Oh, the polygraph.
"Have you been faithful
to your wife, Sergeant Brody?"
(chuckling)
"Yes, I have."
(both laugh)
And hours before,
I was climbing all over you.
Did you learn that over there?
The climbing?
No.
How to beat the box.
Well, I had to lie
sometimes to save my life.
Maybe I became an expert.
How'd you resist cooperating?
I mean, you're in a hole.
They're beating you.
Carrie, I don't want
to talk about it.
Sorry.
(clears throat)
You're a pretty good
drinking buddy.
(laughing): I got a little
carried away with the Nazis.
(chuckles)
Well, I figure we're safe here.
Yeah, unless my sister
sends in the dogs.
I've been thinking about you.
Yeah?
And last night.
Mmm.
Parking lot sex.
Classy.
Can we graduate to cabin sex?
Ow.
BRODY:
Okay.
(grunts, laughs)
(Speaking spanish)
Last stop, Nuevo Laredo.
♪ ♪
(Speaking Spanish)
Hands up! Hands up!
(In Spanish)- To the ground! To the ground!
- Come here! To the gound!
(Speaking Spanish) Easy, easy..
(Speaking Spanish)
Here! Here! Slowly!
Easy, easy, easy.
Hi, Aileen.
Who are you?
Your ride.
(Speaking Spanish)
How did you get out of the truck?
Unless you prefer
the Federales.
(Speaking Spanish)
Let's go, gringuita.
Yes, we have company.
In case you try to bolt,
the Feds are there.
Of course, I told them
you weren't dumb
enough to do that.
So we're headed to
McLean, Virginia.
Should take us 30 hours.
I got what they call a
heavy foot, so maybe 25.
And then I turn you over.
To the FBI.
Who, frankly, are
chomping on the bit
to put you away, Aileen.
See, they frown on terrorists.
And, in particular, privileged
wealthy American terrorists.
I'm looking forward
to the drive, actually.
I've had some upheaval at home.
Could use some peace, quiet.
You're obliging me with
that, so thank you.
I'll just say this.
We could talk things
out, you and I.
Come to an understanding.
But once we
get to D.C.,
the Feds step in and I move on.
And how you're treated
and what you're
charged with--
All that--
It's quite out of my hands.
So... food
for thought.
(sighs)
(Brody sighs)
(groans)
Morning.
God, it's so nice down here.
Yeah.
(sighs)
I overdid it last night.
Me, too.
No more booze today. No.
(grunts)
(sighs)
Look...
I know.
This was crazy.
I should call home.
Yeah.
I should go home, actually.
Sure. Okay.
We can head back.
I love the water.
Mm.
There's actually a really
beautiful waterfall out there.
My sister and I
would hike to it
every day in the summer,
take our compasses
and notebooks,
play Lewis and Clark.
(sighs)
SAUL: Not only did your
cohorts turn on you
and blow away your boyfriend...
Faisel was your
boyfriend, right?
Not only that.
Now they're after you.
You're as safe as
you've been in two days
riding with me.
What was the plan, Aileen?
Why'd you buy that house
under the flight path?
Tell me that.
And tell me who's out
there working on Plan B.
Then I can help you.
Bullshit.
Huh.
She speaks.
(speaks Arabic)
Must have learned
Arabic growing up.
Riyadh, right?
I know those compounds.
Rich oilmen and their families,
blocking out the world
with those great walls,
living like desert kings.
The pools, the gardens.
Never mind the desperate
people outside the walls.
The guest workers...
limping along the road.
Kids with no shoes, shirts.
Kids like Faisel.
You met there, right?
As kids?
He was 13; you were 15?
Somehow, between
you being shuttled
to that fancy American school
and him laboring each
day for $1.10 a week,
you and Faisel
found each other.
He had a horse.
We'd ride.
Did you love him then,
or did that come later?
You don't know me.
BRODY: So were you
Lewis or Clark?
CARRIE:
Oh, had to be Lewis.
Why?
I like the name Meriwether.
(laughs)
So you were an adventurer
even as a kid?
Yeah, I never really fantasized
about New York or
a corner office.
It was always, like,
Nepal or Uganda.
How long were you in Baghdad?
A couple
three-year stints.
What happened out there?
What didn't happen?
What sent you
to that support group?
I lost someone.
My translator.
Were you with him?
Uh, he was protecting me.
Trying.
But this mob just got crazy.
And they hung him from a bridge.
I was...
pinned down.
I couldn't...
Yeah.
It's hard to find people
to talk to about it.
How about your wife?
It's like she doesn't know
who I actually am now.
Well, maybe it just takes time.
I...
I can't be with her.
No?
No, I just...
(clears throat)
I just can't.
But I can with you.
(chuckling):
Well, we were drinking heavily.
No, but it's
different with you.
It's, uh...
(clears throat)
I don't know. It's free.
As in, I don't charge?
(laughs)
As in, it's the first time
since I've been back
that... well, I found
some fucking peace.
Yeah.
Me, too, actually.
And that's pretty rare for me.
So...
Are we gonna try this sober?
Uh, waterfall's just up here.
MADDIE:
Concentration.
Okay, so your word must begin
with the last letter
of the word before it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, let's go.
Okay.
(chanting): Concentration,
concentration is the game.
Keep the rhythm,
keep the rhythm just the same.
Subject.
Boys' names.
Xander.
Raphael.
Liam.
Mike.
(coughs)
Drink!
For the tenth time.
You suck at this game.
(chuckles)
All right!
Come on, come on.
(chanting): Concentration,
concentration is the game...
All right, forget
this, forget this.
Let's go out. Yeah?
No, I'm grounded.
Your mom's working all day.
She'll never know.
No!
Hey.
Whoa, whoa.
Wild thing, slow down.
JEFF:
Let's go to the quarry.
Yeah.
Yes.
No, guys, just let me...
Get some more beer.
(gasps)
Oh, my God.
You okay? Fuck.
I didn't feel anything.
Come here.
One of you get a towel for her
right fucking now.
MADDIE:
Oh, my God.
30 miles to Memphis.
You been to Graceland?
No?
You got to go
once in your life.
See the Jungle Room.
Stay at the Heartbreak Hotel.
My dad thought Elvis
was the devil.
Hoover thought he was
a national security threat.
Like minds.
SAUL: We've been
in touch with him.
Your dad.
I haven't.
I know.
Six long years.
Thank you.
Fries?
No.
He's worried about you.
He's worried about
what their friends will think.
That their good little
Princeton girl was shacked up
with a poor brown Saudi,
and planning to give
their beloved U.S.
the "fuck you" it deserves.
Do you realize
how serious this is?
You could end up
with the death penalty.
What do you care?
Why are you here, anyway?
The FBI could've delivered me.
That would have been
standard, right?
I thought
we'd understand each other.
Why?
You were isolated growing up.
Right?
Well, there was
the compound community.
If you like immoral businessmen.
So you went outside the walls.
Found Faisel.
And then it was okay.
There was something good there.
But then my father
saw us one day.
Riding that horse.
His princess cavorting
with a local brown boy.
Aileen?
Is Faisel the reason you were
shipped off to boarding school?
What do you know about it?
More than nothing.
I married a brown girl.
You should eat.
ETA: 12 hours.
Think about
what you want, Aileen.
(door closes)
(keys jingling)
Hey.
I'm sorry.
We were there forever.
Is everything okay?
19 stitches.
Jesus.
Good night, guys.
Do you need help, hon?
No.
You okay?
I don't know.
(sighs)
Everything's just so...
Fucked up?
Complicated.
Yeah.
Dana's like a surly stranger
in my house.
I don't even know
where she went.
How did she go from my adorable,
loving baby to that?
Were you adorable and loving
when you were 16, Jess?
You and Brody having it out.
And now he's gone,
I have no idea where.
Chris is still aces.
(chuckles softly)
I just want things
to be simple again.
Hey.
I miss you.
CHRIS (in distance):
Mom?
Coming, sweetie.
Chris wants you.
I heard.
Thanks for watching him, and
thanks for fixing the door.
No problem.
Does it hurt?
Yeah.
How about... you?
I think we all need to give
peace a chance around here.
You know what would
help with that?
If you stayed away from us.
There's no place for my dad
when you're here, Mike.
(quiet jazz music playing)
Hungry?
Thirsty.
Me, too.
We're not doing that.
No. No.
(clears throat)
Sorry.
(laughs)
No, I am, I am.
Jesus.
I feel like
a terrified teenager.
I know, I know.
Well, shit, I'm just gonna,
I'm just gonna ask.
Will you go to the prom with me?
Do I get a corsage?
Wrist or pin-on?
Actually, I'll take a nosegay.
I-I don't even know
what that is.
It's a kind of bouquet
from medieval times.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Pre-shower, pre-soap,
they would carry them around
to mask the unpleasant smells
of the time.
To keep their,
their "nose gay."
I know these things.
(both laugh)
Are you still thirsty?
Not at all.
(thunder rumbles)
(both panting)
Do you want to stop?
No, I want to just live here.
For a second.
(moaning)
Issa?
(gasps)
Issa, where are you,
goddamn it?!
Hey, hey, hey, it's okay.
It's okay.
(gasping)
It's okay, you're with me.
Issa, no!
You're with me.
What happened?
You're safe.
You're not there.
Everything's fine.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
Where are we?
Calliope, Indiana.
I grew up here.
There were four
Jewish families.
My dad was the local druggist.
The nearest synagogue
was three hours away.
So we'd come here.
You're religious?
My parents were.
Commerce brought 'em here,
even though the community
didn't want us.
And they gave me strict orders
not to assimilate.
You can't be on
the baseball team.
They start the game
with a Christian prayer.
You can't sing Christmas carols.
When the other kids
stand to sing,
you sit at your desk
with your hands folded.
Respectful.
But silent.
Being a dutiful son, I did
precisely as they asked.
Happily?
What do you think?
I was a kid.
I just wanted to play ball,
I wanted to be in the pageant.
I'd gladly say their prayers,
sing the songs.
I just wanted to not be alone.
Man, I hated this place.
It was the reason
I was different...
strange...
isolated.
They fuck you up.
Yeah.
We got to get going.
The agents await.
I don't know what
happened to you, Aileen.
I don't know how you went
from one more angry teenage girl
to joining
the fucking jihadists.
And if your issues are
truly geopolitical--
Then I can't help you.
I think you wound up here
because you fell
in love with a boy.
And he's gone now.
Oh, that's a heartbreaker.
I want to get you
through this as best I can.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
So, I know I have oatmeal--
Maybe frozen O.J.,
but no Yorkshire Gold out
here in the sticks, sorry.
BRODY:
What?
Ugh-- Knowing my dad, we're
probably looking at Folgers.
And I'm not kidding.
How do you know the tea I drink?
I don't know.
You probably had it at Langley.
I'm gonna go get some wood.
I'll be right back.
So what's the trouble at home?
Nothing much.
Just the love of my life
walking out my door.
For good?
I hope not.
'Cause I can't imagine
being that lost.
What happened to his body?
Raqim?
It's probably in
an Ohio morgue.
He'd want a Muslim burial.
Well, if no one claims him,
he'll be buried
in a potter's field.
(phone ringing)
Estes.
David, it's me.
We have a deal with Aileen.
She talked?
We need someone
up on the roof of that house
under the flight path now.
What did she tell you?
She doesn't have the full story.
They were just told
to buy the house,
go about their business
till a visitor arrived.
Which he did on Monday.
She get a name?
No.
But he was American.
She's sitting with
a sketch artist right now.
Guy didn't say a word,
went right to the roof.
He spent over an hour up there.
Doing what?
That's what we got
to figure out.
All right,
we'll get Galvez up on the roof
right away.
Hi.
I didn't drink tea at Langley.
What?
Yorkshire Gold.
That wasn't just a lucky guess.
Well, why does that matter?
Were you watching me?
I don't know what you mean.
I mean did you spy on me?
You are a spy, right?
Brody...
That's why we ran
into each other
at the support group, isn't it?
Why you slipped me your number
in case I ever
need to ask anything?
No, you're wrong, Brody...
Don't fucking lie
to me, Carrie!
It was my job.
It is my job.
Oh, so you're still spying.
I'm working.
I'm always working.
On what suspicion?
Tell me, goddamn it!
Shit.
You looking for this?
Abu Nazir's bomb maker told me
an American prisoner
of war had been turned.
And he was coming home,
to carry out an attack.
And you believed this?
He told me minutes
before he was executed.
So?
So he was my prisoner.
I interrogated him for months.
He was cooperating at the end.
There was no reason
for him to lie.
You think I'm that P.O.W.?
There's no one else
it could be.
You're telling me
the fucking CIA
thinks I'm working for al-Qaeda?
I think you're working
of al-Qaeda.
(scoffs)
(exhales sharply)
What about the gun, Carrie?
Bears? Intruders?
We just keep it in the cabin.
Mm. Plus, you never know
when a terrorist
might darken your door.
I never said terrorist--
I said turned.
If that were true,
if any of this were true,
wouldn't I just kill
you right now?
Not if you're playing
the long game.
(clearing throat)
Ask me anything.
What?
There's the gun.
Hold it to my fucking head
and ask me anything
you want to know.
I'll show you how wrong you are.
Afzal Hamid.
What about him?
Did you slip him a razor
blade at the safe house?
How could I do that?
Answer the question.
No. But I wish I had.
And I hope he bled slowly,
and died in a lot of pain.
Who's Issa?
Where did you hear that name?
Who is he?
He was my guard.
He was nice to me.
What goes on in your garage?
My garage?
You said ask anything.
I take the trash bins
in and out.
Fix a bicycle sometimes.
Why do you go there
so late at night,
so early in the morning?
To pray.
What is that?
What? Nothing.
No, it's not nothing.
It's a habit.
When I don't have
my prayer beads.
You're a Muslim?
Yeah.
You live in despair
for eight years,
you might turn to religion, too.
And the King James Bible
was not available.
Why did they kill
Walker and not you?
You asked me that in the debrief.
Yeah, and you were evasive.
It doesn't matter.
I'll decide that.
You don't need to know.
I need to know everything.
I killed him.
Okay?
They told me to
beat him to death
or be killed myself.
(sighs)
And so I did it.
And I vowed to never tell
another living soul.
Who told you to kill him?
Abu Nazir.
So you did meet him.
Yes.
You lied to us about meeting
one of the leaders of al-Qaeda?
That's right.
You want to explain that?
I was embarrassed.
Ashamed.
Why?
Because he offered me comfort,
and I took it.
And became his follower?
A soldier in his jihad?
No.
No. Jesus, don't you understand
anything I'm telling you?
I'm not made of that stuff.
I'm no hero.
I had nothing to give.
I was broken, living
in the dark, for years,
and a man walked in...
and he was kind to me.
(breathing tightly)
And I loved him.
(cell phone ringing)
GALVEZ: Hello?
SAUL (on phone):
Galvez, you up there?
Affirmative.
I've searched every square inch.
No weapons, no tools, nothing.
Okay, so what's this guy
doing up there for an hour?
GALVEZ: Well, it's pristine,
I'll tell you that.
Would have expected some
bird shit and whatnot.
SAUL:
He cleaned his workspace.
GALVEZ:
I guess.
Okay.
Face the airport, Galvez.
We're looking for direct
line of sight targets.
Now, what do you see?
GALVEZ: There's a bunch
of airport hotels.
Uh... a control tower
maybe half a mile out.
And how about further?
You got binoculars?
Yeah.
Okay, Terminal B
is about a mile away.
Air France, hanger 30.
And what is that?
It's small.
Has a helipad out front.
Any signage?
Uh... "Reserve M-1."
Marine One.
That's a landing pad
for Marine One.
Oh, shit.
A mile is well within
a sniper's range.
An expert sniper.
SAUL:
An American military sniper.
David.
Send me
Sergeant Brody's picture.
Brody? Why?
So Aileen can look at it.
So we done here?
Well, you have an
answer for everything.
But you still don't believe me.
I know an American
P.O.W. was turned.
It has to be you.
(sighs) (phone vibrating)
I'm leaving.
No.
We're not finished.
Yeah, we're finished.
If you want to arrest me,
you can come to my house.
No! Brody!
Or maybe you want
to shoot me, now.
(vibrating)
Brody!
Saul...
We were wrong about Brody.
What... what do you mean?
SAUL:
A P.O.W. was turned.
But it wasn't him.
I, I... I don't understand.
Aileen just I.D.'d Tom Walker.
The other soldier
captured with Brody.
Tom Walker died.
No.
He's alive.
He's the terrorist.
Shit.
Brody!
Wait!
I, I was wrong.
I made a terrible mistake.
Don't you think I
don't already know that?
I'm sorry. I am so sorry.
This weekend, this time
that we spent together,
it was real.
The parts that...
that we both...
The important parts.
Hey, Carrie.
Fuck you.
(stifled sobbing)
♪ ♪
(inhales sharply, sobs quietly)
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com