Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
PRESIDENT REAGAN: Air and naval
forces of the United States
launched a series of strikes
against terrorist facilities...
REPORTER: Pan Am Flight 103 crashed
into the town of Lockerbie.
REAGAN: He has sanctioned
acts of terror
in Africa, Europe,
the Middle East.
PRESIDENT GEORGE H.W. BUSH: This will not stand,
this aggression against, uh, Kuwait.
REAGAN: This relentless
pursuit of terror.
PRESIDENT GEORGE W. BUSH:
We will make no distinction...
REPORTER:
The USS Cole was attacked
while refueling in
the port of Aden.
This was an act of terrorism.
It was a despicable
and cowardly act.
The next samba
we're going to swing for you
is one of the good old
favorites.
Until something stops him.
WOMAN: I'm just making sure
we don't get hit again.
MAN: That plane crashed
into the World Trade Center.
Thousands of people running.
We must and we will remain
vigilant at home and abroad.
(speaking Arabic)
SAUL:
What the fuck are you doing?
God!
CARRIE: Fuck! I missed
something once before.
I won't... I can't
let that happen again.
SAUL:
It was ten years ago.
Everyone missed something
that day.
CARRIE:
Everyone's not me.
Previously, on Homeland...
You're telling me
the fucking CIA
thinks I'm working for Al Qaeda?
I think you're working
for Al Qaeda.
BRODY: Ask me anything.
What goes on in your garage?
Why do you go there
so late at night,
so early in the morning?
To pray.
You're a Muslim?
Why did they kill
Walker and not you?
I killed him.
CARRIE:
Who told you to kill him?
BRODY: Abu Nazir.
So you did meet him.
BRODY:
Yes. If you want to arrest me,
you can come to my house.
No! Brody!
We were wrong about Brody.
A POW was turned.
It wasn't him.
Aileen just I.D.'d Tom Walker.
Tom Walker died!
No.
He's the terrorist.
HELEN:
Tom was dead.
That's what they told me.
What we need to do is find him
before anything happens.
Oh, baby, I've done
a horrible thing.
No, Helen, no. Don't. Don't!
They're tracing this call.
You've got to get out of there!
(tires squealing)
Gun!
CARRIE: The tac team
followed Walker here.
Two casualties.
Local Muslims here
for morning prayer.
TV NEWSWOMAN: Congressman Richard
Johnson, caught in a sexting scandal
sending nude and semi-nude
pictures of himself
to a number of
congressional interns.
He'll be gone in two days.
I have an idea
who might replace him.
Are you crazy?
You people told me
Walker was dead.
I-I don't...
My friend!
(screams)
You told me I killed him!
You made me believe!
I don't know!
You have to talk to Abu Nazir!
(grunting)
I'm through talking with Nazir.
Tell him it's over.
(mellow country music
playing quietly)
(dialing)
(vacuum humming loudly,
phone vibrating)
Hey, Jess. It's me.
I'm in the store.
What's... I think
it says Vitamin Water?
What is that,
some kind of medicine?
If you get this
in the next few minutes,
will you call me back? Thanks.
(vacuum stops)
You finish your homework?
I just can't believe that Tom
Walker is really actually alive.
I know.
It seems crazy.
What's Dad say?
So far, not a whole lot.
Well, have you even asked him?
Yes, Dana, of course
I've asked him.
He can't believe it.
He says there's got
to be some mistake.
It's not the first time the
FBI have gotten it wrong.
Yeah, but what
if they're right?
Two Marines are captured
and one comes back a terrorist?
Dad must be going
out of his mind.
Did you find everything
you're looking for today, sir?
Yes, thank you.
You're welcome.
Just one thing.
Yeah.
What does that say?
Vitamin Water.
What is that?
It's-It's good. It's
like flavored water.
Would you like me to get
someone to find it for you?
What flavor?
I don't know, what you got?
Um...
Hey, you're that Marine
war hero guy, right?
(cell phone ringing)
(grunts)
(car alarm wailing)
(cell phone continues ringing)
(groans)
(grunts)
(panting)
(speaks Arabic)
(groans)
(panting)
(speaks Arabic)
IMAM: We have nothing to do
but pray for our brothers,
that they were going
to heaven for God.
And the FBI said that
they were fired at first.
Which is a lie.
(crowd murmuring)
The truth is,
they shot and killed
two innocent people
in a house of worship.
Without provocation.
REPORTER: What about the man
they were chasing-- Tom Walker?
What do you know about him?
All any of us know is that a
stranger ran through our mosque
being chased by FBI agents
while we were gathering
for morning prayers.
REPORTER: Have you been told the names
of the agents who fired the shots?
IMAM:
No, we're still awaiting
a full investigation.
We don't know anything yet.
(crowd clamoring)
IMAM:
No, sir.
We do not condone hate.
Or violence.
HALL:
Ms. Mathison.
Special Agent Hall.
I asked to meet
the SWAT team commander,
the man who was on
the ground for this.
And you got me.
His boss.
How can I help?
Would you mind taking
your shoes off, please?
What are we doing
here, exactly?
Everything we can
to catch Walker.
You're aware there's an
FBI manhunt up and running.
All 56 field offices,
canceled leave...
The reason why I asked to meet
the actual SWAT commander
is because I need him
to walk me through exactly
what happened here.
Which he already did with me.
So, Walker comes in from the
alley, through this door here.
And we already know
he was armed,
because he stole a gun
from one of your men.
And?
Did Walker open fire first?
Yes. Yet the imam is
standing out there,
telling the world that's a lie.
The imam?
It's his word against mine.
He also says that neither he nor
any of his flock know Walker.
Which is not true.
Do you want to know why?
Please.
Walk with me.
He hauls ass down these stairs
to a service corridor
that goes left to
a janitor's storage room,
or right, doubling back
underneath the building
to a bilko door on Raum Street,
all the way on the east
side of the building.
Son of a bitch goes right.
He knew exactly where
the fuck he was going.
You following me
on this so far?
He knows this mosque.
Correct.
And probably a lot of people
that come here, too.
Assalamo alliakum.
Wa 'aliakum-as-salam.
Imam, let me begin by saying
how deeply sorry I am
for your loss.
Losses.
Plural.
There were two dead.
Imam, my name is
Carrie Mathison.
Another government official
here to suggest that if
we weren't all guilty,
one way or another,
none of this would
have happened.
Right?
I'm also well aware of your
good work in this neighborhood,
beyond just here in the mosque.
Then you should know
how violated we all feel.
I do. Yes.
I have seven eyewitnesses,
including myself,
who saw what happened.
Please forgive me, but my job
right now, my only job,
is to catch this man Walker
as soon as possible.
He did not fire a single
shot at the agents.
He was moving too fast,
trying to get away from them.
Either Walker was very lucky to
get away as quickly as he did,
or he knew this mosque
well enough
to use it as an escape route.
I have families to comfort.
I have funerals to arrange.
I have a community who believes
they will never get justice
for what happened.
If you do know Walker,
or anything about him,
or anyone who might...
whatever you tell us,
no matter how small,
would be in total confidence.
And yet you offer me
nothing in return.
What do you mean by that?
Specifically.
Just so I'm clear.
Two families will
get no justice,
unless the FBI tells the truth
about how they killed
two innocent people
who were doing
nothing but pray.
In other words,
you do know something.
Good-bye, Ms. Mathison.
Mr. Galvez.
He knows Walker.
You saw that, right?
I'm not crazy?
You're not crazy.
(sighs)
I don't give a shit
what it takes,
that imam is going to talk to me.
What it takes?
He wants a full FBI mea culpa.
Good luck with that.
(kettle whistling)
It's not medicine,
it's a drink.
Dana likes the "Revive" flavor,
and Chris likes
the "Energy" one.
And Dana's been asking
a lot about Tom Walker.
It's all over the Internet, and
I don't really have any answers,
so if you can come home
as soon as you can...
Oh, um, I told Chris that
I would take him to a movie
if he got all his
homework done today.
He specifically asked if
you would come, too, so...
just... call me back. Okay?
♪ ♪
(panting)
(gasps)
This is your new home now.
Come.
(water running)
♪ ♪
(door opens)
This is Issa, my son.
Assalamo Alliakum.
Issa...
(speaks Arabic)
Issa.
I want him to learn English,
fluently.
You will live here with him
as long as it takes.
(door opens)
(door closes)
I have no clue how to do this.
I'm not a teacher.
(doorbells jingle)
We have a problem.
(chuckles):
Hey.
What, are you stalking me now?
How'd you find me here?
They spent years training me.
Ah. So, what's
the problem?
The imam.
He'll calm down
in a day or two.
I don't have a day or two.
He says your men fired first.
I know what he's saying.
He has seven eyewitnesses,
including himself,
saying Walker didn't shoot,
or even raise a weapon at them.
And?
I believe he's withholding
information about Walker.
You people have rubber hoses,
don't you?
He's a good man
caught in a bad situation.
He runs a mosque
that a terrorist suspect used
as an escape route.
He wants justice for the men
who were killed,
for which I think he'll tell me
what he knows about Walker.
Justice?
W... What does that mean?
(sighs)
Well, for one thing it means
compensation for the families.
Look, if one of
your men made a mistake,
you need to come clean.
Let me ask you something.
You ever been in a firefight?
Yes.
Okay.
So, my men follow
an armed terrorist suspect,
based off intel
provided by you people,
at zero dark-thirty
into a fucking building
that they don't even
know is a mosque.
In seconds, a member of the team
thinks he has a clear shot
at bringing down a terrorist,
and he takes it.
Accidentally,
he drops two civilians
in the crossfire.
Shit happens.
But if you think
that I or the bureau
are gonna let the CIA come in
and throw any of my guys
under the bus,
you're fucking high.
Hey. Hey, Issa,
come closer.
Don't be afraid.
Come on.
Want to play?
Hey. Hey, you know
how to do this?
Can you do this? Yeah?
Want to learn?
Yeah?
Look. Soccer ball.
It's a soccer ball.
Soccer.
Can you say that? Soccer.
Soccer...
Hey.
Hey, Issa.
Hey, wait.
HALL (recorded): Accidentally, he drops
two civilians in the crossfire.
Shit happens.
But if you think that I
or the bureau are gonna let
the CIA come in and throw
any of my guys under the bus,
you're fucking high.
You're really fucking
something, Carrie.
I got to hand it to you.
There is no bridge
you won't burn,
no earth you won't scorch.
When it comes
to catching Walker,
or any terrorist suspect,
for that matter, damn straight.
You recorded a senior
FBI agent who thought
he was talking off the record
to someone on the same side,
so you could leverage the
FBI into admitting a mistake.
Are you really prepared
to sacrifice the very agency
that, with all their manpower,
is the best chance
we have to get Walker?
They accidentally shot
and killed two people.
Now, I get that it's not easy,
or even ideal,
but we need to convince them
to just make a statement
taking responsibility.
For what?
The hope that this imam
will give you information
that you don't even know he has?
No disrespect,
David, but I think
I've been
in the field long enough
to know a source
when I see one.
You will not,
I repeat, not,
do anything to
sabotage the FBI manhunt
for Walker.
That is a direct order.
What's happened here?
I was showing him a trick
with the ball.
And I, uh,
I knocked over some glasses.
(panting)
What the hell...
are you doing, Carrie?
What? Nothing.
The last I checked,
this was my office.
Just needed somewhere private
to calm down.
Somewhere private?
Okay, so I was hoping you'd
be here. Where have you been?
I just heard about the imam
and the FBI.
Estes is right.
That imam knows Walker.
I fucking know it, 100%.
You think the Imam's bad?
No. No, that's
the problem.
He's practically a saint.
I've got nothing on him.
I've got zero leverage.
You're 100% sure he's not bad?
Pretty much.
So?
Maybe you're approaching
the problem
the wrong way around.
(man singing in Arabic
in distance)
(praying in Arabic)
Allahu Akbar.
CROWD (chanting):
We want justice!
(clamoring)
So what are we doing here?
I think they call
it a Hail Mary.
(knocks)
As-salaam alaikum.
Wa 'alaikum-as-salam.
My name is Carrie.
I know who you are.
May I come in?
I need to speak
with your husband.
Please, have some tea.
I'm sorry, this isn't easy.
I understand.
Imam, I've done my research.
I know of your work
in the community--
the woman's refuge you
run with Father Rose
from St. Agnes'
down the street.
I have no doubt you and
I want the same thing.
Which is a better world.
And a better America.
If there's another terrorist
attack, this country
is primed to turn on itself.
You and I both know we're
halfway there already.
But if an attack happens
that can be traced
back to information
that you chose to withhold when
you were given the chance...
the mosque,
this community that you
worked so hard to build...
they'll put a match to it all.
Our only hope--
and it's a good one--
is that people like us
put our heads together
and help each other.
Now, I need to find Tom Walker.
Will you help me?
I pray what you say
about another attack
on America is wrong.
But you're right.
It takes more than just prayer.
We have to help each other.
Action speaks
louder than words,
yet so far you've done
nothing but talk.
What were you expecting?
It's very simple: the truth.
Two people
were tragically caught
between a terrorist suspect
and those whose job it is
to stop more
attacks on America.
That is the truth.
I know you know Walker.
Please.
If I say I have no information,
I have no information.
I'm sorry.
In case you reconsider.
Thank you for the tea.
Assalamo Alliakum.
Fi Amaan Allah.
CROWD (chanting):
We want justice!
How'd it go?
The FBI better fucking find
Walker-- that's all I can say.
♪ ♪
"A man wants to build
a home for his wife.
"He loves his wife.
The house must be strong
to keep them safe."
Issa, that is amazing.
To be able to do
that this quickly?
That's truly excellent.
(sighs)
Sometimes, I swear to God,
people are
their own worst enemy.
SAUL (over phone):
Yeah, tell me about it.
What are you doing, Saul?
Y-You sound kind of...
What do we know about Walker?
We know he's a sniper.
Snipers are trained
to go to ground,
either in plain sight
or, as is the case here,
that doesn't work,
they blend into the wild.
I think the other word
for that is "disappear."
(phone beeps)
Hold on a second.
Hello.
Carrie, this is Zahira.
Can you meet me in 15 minutes?
Yeah, of course.
MAN:
Hey there.
Whoa, whoa, I come in peace.
My bad, I didn't mean
to sneak up on you like that.
Don't worry about it.
May I?
Sure.
That sure is some work
of art you got there.
What is that,
some sort of limited,
made to measure edition?
Something like that.
Nice.
What you hunting?
Office supplies.
(chuckles)
What you got there?
Marlin 336
with the Vari-X.
Yeah, gets the job done.
Oh, it'll get her done.
(both chuckling)
It sure is
a beautiful day for it.
You, uh, you have yourself
a good one.
Want to see this
thing in action?
Just about got it
in the sweet spot.
Sure, sure,
w-why not?
I didn't get your name.
It's, uh, Dan.
N-Name's Dan.
Good talking to you, Dan.
Good luck out there.
Right, y-you, too.
Hello, Zahira.
When you came to our home,
you knew it was not permitted
for you to be alone
with my husband.
Two pairs of ears
to hear what you had to
say being better than one.
Maybe.
I love my husband, Carrie.
He is a good man.
I don't doubt it.
I understand what you
said about this country--
the knife edge it's on.
Please, I need your word that
you will not say anything
to anyone about our meeting.
You have it.
This man Walker-- over
the last few weeks,
he has come to the mosque
maybe eight or nine times.
Every time, he meets with a man
who does not come to
the mosque to pray.
Just to do business.
Do you know the name
of this man?
All I know is,
he drives a car with
the diplomatic plates.
Which country?
S-Saudi Arabia.
Thank you.
(breathing heavily)
(gasps)
Bad dream?
Yeah, yeah, it was.
(panting)
Hey, what you got there?
Hey, this is beautiful, Issa.
This is really great.
Thank you.
(sighs)
What is this? What's going on?
(groans softly)
(sighs)
(tapping)
Nicholas?
Can you hear me, Nicholas?
Nicholas.
Yeah, I can hear you.
You're angry.
How the fuck
do you think I feel?
You're also in shock.
Which is why you told our friend
in Washington to tell me
that it's all over.
I've been living
the last eight years
thinking I killed Tom Walker.
Which I now find out
is not true.
Which means everything I did--
everything...
Is the peace you found
in Islam a false peace?
Everything I believed in.
You believed
in Allah's forgiveness
and, through Allah's mercy,
in yourself.
It was all a trick!
It was based on a lie!
I did not let you actually
kill your friend.
Isn't that good news?
What is Walker doing?
Helping.
That's all you need to know.
You remember the new
beginning you were given?
Yes, I remember.
Issa.
You trusted me with Issa.
Why?
Why not trust a man
who would rather die
than give information
to his enemy?
You got your enemy
to teach your own son.
No, we only began as enemies,
because that's what
the others told us to be.
Are we enemies now?
Have you forgotten?
BOTH: Buy me some peanuts
and Cracker Jack
I don't care if I never...
BOTH:
...get back
I want to...
BOTH:
Root, root, root for the
home team...
Finish it.
Come on, brat.
You're almost done.
Let me root, root, root
for the home team
If they don't win, it's a shame
For it's one, two,
three strikes, you're out
at the old ball game.
♪ ...ball game. ♪
You air brat.
You are a brat.
And you're gonna be late
for school. Get out of here.
(sighs)
Hey, are you forgetting
something?
Score a goal today.
(explosion)
Issa?!
(speaks Arabic)
(mumbling in Arabic)
Issa?!
(woman shouting
in Arabic, crying)
Issa?!
Issa?
Issa? Issa?
(sobbing):
Issa...
Issa.
Issa!
♪ ♪
(speaking Arabic softly)
(both praying in Arabic)
NAZIR:
I pray every day
that you never lose sight of
what you committed
to do in Issa's name.
I never wanted or planned
any of this.
It was your choice
doing what you are doing
after what happened that day.
But... in the end,
you are... a soldier,
as you say.
And you will either stay true
to that and do what
you feel is right...
or you will not.
Alamdulilla.
Nazir? Nazir?!
Nazir said that you would
remember this
from two years ago.
At 4:42 p.m. local time, a drone
missile hit and destroyed
part of a compound 120 miles
northeast of Mosul
in the mountains
of Northern Iraq
from which Abu Nazir,
the leader of the IPLA,
is believed
to have been operating.
The images being broadcast on
some news outlets
around the world of the bodies
of 83 dead children
allegedly killed in the strike,
we believe to be false,
created by the terrorists
for propaganda purposes.
And they call us terrorists.
Make no mistake, that in
the planning of these missions,
all that can be done is done
to protect the innocent,
in particular, the precious
lives of children,
while we keep our promise
to hunt down the terrorists
who continue to plot against...
(turns off TV)
As you already know,
that man there,
the Vice President,
the former Director of the CIA,
and the man most instrumental
in the drone attack
that killed young Issa,
as he prepares to become
President,
he's going to want to use you,
to be seen with you,
his American hero,
more and more.
Let him.
We also believe
that he's going to ask you
to run for political office.
Say yes.
This will be a signal
to Abu Nazir
that you are committed still
to doing this.
Ah, Jesus.
(gunshot)
The doctor says you should
take these with food.
Go out the back way.
Take a right.
Your car is across the street.
The groceries are inside.
(engine starts, country music
playing over radio)
♪ So glad he never made the
choice that he'd always regret ♪
♪ And the tougher things got,
the tougher that he stayed... ♪
(grunts softly)
SAUL That's it on the left,
home of our Saudi diplomat.
CARRIE:
Diplomatic fucking immunity.
Just like "Klaus" in '03.
That was the Swiss
embassy in Caracas,
and we nearly
let Klaus slip away.
I'm not losing this guy, Saul.
For now, we wait and see
if Mr. Zahrani does anything
or goes anywhere
that will help us
get to Walker.
You live for this shit.
So I've been told.
What if Mr. Zahrani doesn't
give us anything anytime soon?
We figure out an elegant way
to lift and interrogate him.
(groans softly)
I'm not gonna ask you
where you've been all day.
I know you have a lot on your
mind, and a lot to process,
and I'm in danger of sounding
like a broken record.
Oh, my God, what happened?!
I got mugged.
What do you mean, mugged?
As in, attacked and robbed.
Are you all right?
Did you call the cops?
What good are the cops
gonna do?
By the time I came round,
the fuckers that did this
were long gone.
Where did this happen?
Grocery store parking lot.
Three of the bastards.
I-I'm fine.
I'm fine.
I went to the, uh...
I went to the emergency room.
Why didn't you call me?
They got my phone.
I didn't want to worry you
and the kids.
Seriously, it's no big deal.
Are you hurt?
Ah, a couple broken ribs.
It... Hey, hey.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
All right?
Fuck, Brody, you should've
called the cops.
I really don't need
the attention right now.
What else did they take?
Oh, a few bucks, my pride.
You're all right,
that's what's important.
Mm-hmm.
You know what
the worst part of it is?
I really wanted
to spend the day
with you and the kids.
I want us to spend
more time together...
as a family.
That sounds so good.
(sighs)
Eight years out there,
I come back,
I get mugged outside
the grocery store.
It's unbelievable.
(both chuckle)
America's a violent country.
What can I tell you?
Oh...
(groans) I'm sorry.
Oh, and guess what.
What?
There's a message on
the voicemail...
from the Vice President's
office.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com