This is Russo. Please leave a message.
He's not answering my calls.
It's over, and he must know it.
You don't think there's
any way he can recover?
The Republicans will play that interview
on every radio and television station
from now until November 5th.
I sympathize with the kid, but this
was my concern from the beginning.
And I should've listened to you, sir.
I thought he could handle the pressure.
Okay. So he withdraws.
We need to replace him.
You have any ideas?
With less than two months to go?
If the President hadn't shut
me out of the early discussions,
I could've come up with some good options,
but I don't know anyone who's got
the name recognition and donor base
to start a campaign from
scratch just seven weeks out.
Let me think.
Everything hinges on
the next few minutes...
all my months of planning,
every move I've made.
- There is one person.
- Who?
You, Mr. Vice President.
If you ran to reclaim your seat,
I think you'd win by a landslide.
Resign the vice presidency.
Only if you win.
Walker needs me for 2016.
Are you entirely certain he's
gonna keep you on the ticket?
I mean, it's no secret
the two of you don't exactly get along.
What has he said?
Oh, you're putting me in a very
awkward position, Mr. Vice President.
Has he been bad-mouthing me?
Well, the exact phrase he
used was "pain in the ass."
That fucker.
He's got no idea how to lead,
no sense of respect.
- Oh, is this his idea?
- No.
- His way of getting rid of me?
- No. It struck me yesterday,
and I just thought it was worth suggesting.
But, no, I haven't
discussed this with anyone.
And you shouldn't.
People don't leave the White
House to become a governor.
May I ask you a personal question, sir?
Do you want to be the Vice President?
Peter said that when you were
out on that campaign trail,
you had so much enthusiasm and energy
that he thought you maybe
missed being the Governor.
I do miss it.
Then why not go back?
You could be the hero of this election
and secure Pennsylvania
for the Democrats in 2016.
Garrett would never go along
with something like this,
even if he hates my guts.
It would make him look weak,
like he's lost control
of the administration.
Not if it was a mutual decision.
Look, let me talk to Garrett.
I won't mention that we've spoken.
I suppose there's no harm in
finding out what he thinks.
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
- Slogans for 400.
- "1976. He's making us proud again."
- D.J.
- Who is Carter.
- No. John.
- Who is Ford.
- Peter?
- Slogans for 600.
- "1888. Grandfather's hat fits Ben."
- Peter, are you here?
- Claudia.
- Who is Benjamin Harrison.
- Yes.
- Presidential slogans for 800.
- "1900... "
- On the train ride down,
I almost called the police
to have them break in
and make sure you hadn't hurt yourself.
I'm not gonna even ask you what
happened. It doesn't matter right now.
- "1964. In your heart, you know he's right."
- What matters right now...
- what matters...
- Who is Goldwater.
- Claudia
Barry Goldwater. Yes.
Oh, come on. Hey, I'm watching that.
What matters is the 50 reporters
in front of your building
and the 150 campaign staffers who
don't know if they still have a job.
It's over.
I know.
So, tell them to go away.
What, are you just gonna hole yourself
up in here and hope it all goes away?
Yeah, that's pretty much the plan.
Well, I won't let you.
Hey, put that down. Hey.
- Hey, put that down!
- Peter...
We need to put out a statement.
Call me when you're prepared to do that.
I'll be at the headquarters in Philly.
I was scared that I was starting to feel
too much for you.
I think that's why I ended it.
And you have no room for fear?
No. Being afraid doesn't
accomplish anything.
That's not true. When I'm overseas,
rational fear... disease or violence...
that sort of fear keeps you alive.
Back here, God,
I find myself afraid of things
that I can't name or point to.
It's like, uh, how little am I seeing?
Or have I wasted this day or this moment?
Yeah, I think that sometimes...
whether my life will add up.
Francis would roll his eyes
if he heard me talking like this.
Does he know where you are?
No, he doesn't.
If he's looking for you,
that's where you are.
Over there.
Before you met Frank.
Alone.
Curious.
Absorbing everything.
You have no idea what I
was like when I was a girl.
Did he ever know that side of you?
He wasn't interested in that girl.
And neither was I.
What were you interested in?
Being more than an observer.
You wanted to be seen.
Not just seen.
I wanted to be significant.
There's no historical precedent.
Aaron Burr ran for Governor,
Calhoun for the Senate.
200 years ago. One shot a man in a
duel, the other believed in slavery.
Is that really the sort of
company we wanna share, Frank?
Mr. President, we stand losing
control of an important swing state,
our majority in the house, and quite
possibly your second term in office.
Preventing all of that may
require unconventional measures.
It would look like I'm pushing him out.
Or worse... that he's
abandoning the administration.
You make a joint statement.
You say he won't resign unless he wins.
If he loses, he stays on as Vice President.
No one could accuse either of
you of disloyalty to the other.
- Did Jim come to you with this?
- No. It's entirely my idea.
I wouldn't dream of speaking to the Vice
President without passing it by you first.
I think he'd take it as an affront,
like I'm trying to get rid of him.
Honestly, sir, I think he might be
more interested than you imagine.
- Why is that?
- Well, I hesitate to bring this up,
but when he was campaigning for Russo,
he spoke quite freely about you, sir.
Mm-hmm. Tell me.
Of course, I'm getting
this secondhand from Peter,
but the gist of it is that...
that you lack entirely in leadership,
and that you have no sense of respect.
And he wants more responsibility.
And how do I give him that when he shows
absolutely no discretion, no discipline?
Well, that is entirely my point. Now, look,
I take full responsibility
for backing Russo,
but there could be a
silver lining in all this.
You could accomplish two goals:
Secure Pennsylvania for the Democrats
and find an honorable
way to replace Matthews.
What do you think?
I think it is a very big decision,
and we do not want to make it impulsively.
I agree. I'd like to put
some more thought into it.
Well, that is very prudent,
sir. Just bear in mind,
seven weeks out, that every day counts.
- Hi, sir.
- How much is it?
Oh, I got your receipt right here.
No, no, no. It was... it was just $40.
Yeah. Don't tell anyone, all right?
No. I... I never say
anything about our tenants.
- The press still outside?
- Yeah.
I told them you weren't
here, like you said.
Most of them left. There's
still, you know, a few, though.
If I wanted to leave, is there a
place I could do it without being seen?
Yeah. The freight elevator
down to the garage.
- I could call you a cab or...
- All right. Thanks. I'll let you know.
Mr. Russo, uh...
sir, it's none of my business,
but, uh, my Uncle... he fell
off the wagon a few times.
When he did, the best thing for
him was just not to be alone.
I'll give you this money back,
I'll take that bag off your hands,
come in here, keep you company...
I appreciate it. I'll let
you know if I change my mind.
Sit down.
Where's Claire?
Not here.
So what is this, tying up loose ends?
I wouldn't presume.
People like you can't be neatly tied up.
But I thought perhaps we could start...
It's very tasteful.
This is the dress she wore to the gala.
I believe so.
It is.
I recognize it.
Go back into the bedroom.
I'm amazed how well you got her in focus.
What should we call her?
Why does she need a name?
I never photograph anyone
without knowing their name.
You didn't take the photograph. I did.
I think we should call her Claire.
She doesn't even look like me.
Not even a younger version.
Why do you keep saying that?
Not her features, her expression.
Hey, we should mount it. You
can hang her in your house.
Would Francis object?
Can we please not discuss Francis?
You brought him up in the park.
I know I did, and I shouldn't have.
So we have to pretend he doesn't exist?
I thought we could talk about anything.
He is a presence here. You must admit that.
When you walked through the door yesterday,
he walked right in with you.
It's just me, nobody else.
You keep telling yourself
that, it might come true.
How do you think she'd feel
if she knew I was wearing this?
I don't know.
You don't think she'd be upset?
She'd probably say you
look very beautiful in it.
It's like steel.
You should put it back.
I think I'll keep it.
I'll buy you one of
your own, if you'd like.
No. I want this one.
She came into my bedroom.
She should know I came into hers.
Is your bed always so perfectly made?
It's a habit I formed at military school.
What side of the bed does she sleep on?
That side.
She can keep it.
Fits her better anyway.
Listen, Zoe...
Whatever just happened upstairs,
whatever these past six months have been,
can we agree that it is time to simplify?
What does simple look like?
We maintain our professional arrangement,
as you suggested, which I will honor.
You still trust me?
What choice do I have?
You didn't hurt me
or discard me like you said you would.
I'm glad I didn't have to.
Yes, we'll agree to simplify.
Good.
Sorry I'm a few minutes late, Frank.
Please, have a seat.
I have a pretty good idea why
you asked for this meeting.
- Have you and the President had a chance to speak?
- We have.
- Is he leaning one way or another?
- He's torn.
- And what about you?
- I'm a little less torn.
My instincts tell me it's a mistake.
You wanna convince me otherwise?
Well, look, if your instincts tell you this
is not the way to go, I'm not about to...
Frank, I'm gonna ask you
two very direct questions,
and I would appreciate direct answers.
When you got my son into college,
were you anticipating a moment like this?
I don't follow.
Honestly, Frank?
Was I antici...
I would be happy to answer you
directly if I knew what you were asking.
All right. I will ask
you my second question.
Do you want the Vice
Presidency for yourself?
I would serve at the pleasure
of the President. That was his...
you proposed this idea so that
you can take Matthews' place.
- I did not say that.
- But it is what you want.
- What I want is in the...
- The President makes you v.P.,
he keeps you on the ticket in 2016,
and you use that as a
springboard to run in 2020.
Tell me that trajectory
has never entered your mind.
Well, Linda, I make a habit
of considering all trajectories
in any given situation.
But that's a practical
exercise, not a personal one.
So you refuse to admit it.
Admit it's what I want? That's irrelevant.
You're the one who asked
for this meeting, not me.
This meeting's about
trying to solve a problem,
not fulfill some personal ambition.
But if both could be
achieved, you wouldn't object.
I think this is a sound course of action
regardless of who the President
taps to replace Matthews.
I must gamble everything I have right now.
If I'm honest, she may use it against me.
If I'm not, she won't lift a finger.
I've used the same tactic myself.
Once someone is exposed,
they're at your mercy.
She wants to hear me say the words.
Yes.
I want to be the Vice President.
And, yes, I helped your
son get into college
in the hopes that you
would return the favor.
But I can't force you to do so, Linda.
But I also think that we
would make a formidable team.
Look what we've been able to accomplish
even when we've been
at odds with each other.
Now put your mind to what we
could accomplish if we weren't.
Thank you for taking the time, Linda.
I'll call you back. How'd it go?
She's holding her cards
very close to the chest.
- Any word from Peter?
- Nothing.
Christina said he wouldn't
leave the apartment.
But I called the doorman, and
he said that Peter was gone.
- Where?
- He doesn't know.
He needs to officially withdraw
to put pressure on Walker.
- I'm trying to track him down.
- Why'd you let him out of your sight in the first place?
I thought he was showering. He disappeared
when I was on the phone with you.
There was a plan here, Doug.
He explodes, he withdraws,
we put him back together,
and he quietly goes away.
Russo has made no public appearances
since allegations that he was inebriated
during a radio interview on WZPZ
Pittsburgh yesterday morning.
Sources among the Democratic
leadership have suggested
that the party is currently
considering options to replace Russo.
Meanwhile, Republican
candidate Jack swofford's lead
has jumped to a 24-point margin,
according to an overnight
CNN poll of registered voters.
The swofford campaign is also reporting
a sharp spike in contributions...
nearly half a million
dollars in the last 20...
I saw that this morning.
Francis got Peter to run.
Do you know him well?
We weren't close.
Do you need to make calls? 'Cause
I can head into the other room.
I don't think so. Thanks.
Where are you going?
To the lab. I should've gone in today.
Adam.
- Adam...
- Just go. Go. Leave.
How long do you think this
can possibly go on for?
We have never spent more
than 48 hours together.
Maybe there's a reason for that.
A part of me still loves you.
Which part?
I can't be just a pit stop, Claire,
- or some sort of escape...
- Oh, come on. You're more than that.
- ... or a top-up on whatever Francis can't provide.
- Oh, fuck off!
He's my husband, Adam.
We've gone through more
than you could ever imagine.
I envy your free spirit,
and I'm attracted to it,
but not all of us have that luxury.
Which is what I find so
frustrating about you, Claire.
You... you had a choice.
You chose not to be free.
No. What I chose was a man I
could love for more than a week.
I shouldn't have said that. I...
At least you're being honest.
I can't live moment to
moment like you, Adam.
I have a history with Francis,
I have a future with him,
and it's bigger than a moment.
Then you should kill it...
whatever part of you still loves me.
If you can't,
I will.
- Adam...
- No.
- Hello?
- Hey. Hey, sweetie.
How's it going? I'm...
are you with your mom?
She's downstairs. You
want me to go get her?
No. No. I just wanted to call
and say, uh,
you know, hey to your...
uh, your brother and you.
Is he... is he there?
He's in his room, I think.
Okay. You wanna go get him?
Hold on.
He says he doesn't want to talk to you.
Wh... why not?
We've seen the news, dad.
There were all sorts of TV
cameras at our school yesterday.
Mom's making us stay home this week.
I want you to do something.
I want you to go to, uh,
your bedroom window and look out.
You see that black car?
- Yeah.
- That's me.
You shouldn't be here, dad.
Mom would be really angry.
Well, we don't need to tell her.
Right?
It'll just be... it'll just be, uh...
it'll just be our little secret.
Your voice sounds weird,
like it did on the radio.
You... you heard that?
I have a computer.
Uh,
I'm sorry.
I...
Sometimes your dad makes mistakes.
- I better go.
- No.
I don't like to hear your
voice when it's like this.
It makes me sad. Bye, dad.
Sarah, please...
Peter?
Christina.
Where are you?
I'm, uh...
Mm. I'm not...
I'm not... I'm not doing so well.
Where are you, Peter?
- I'm in my car.
- Are you driving?
No.
Tell me where you are.
I'm outside my kids' house.
- You mean Madeleine's?
- Yeah.
I need you to stay right there.
Okay, Peter?
You'll stay there?
Peter.
Peter, are you still there?
Hello?
I'd like to turn myself in.
For what?
A few months ago,
I was pulled over for drunk driving.
They let me go. I should've been convicted.
Well, if you were let go, sir,
we can't arrest you for it now.
Well, I drunk drove
here. Arrest me for that.
We can put you in a detox tank...
I wanna be formally arrested.
My name is congressman Peter Russo.
I was arrested in January
on Michigan Avenue.
Please have a seat, Congressman.
I gotta make a few phone calls.
- Have you found him?
- I'm in front of his ex-wife's house.
But Christina said he called from there.
- He's not there?
- No.
But his phone is. I found it by the curb.
So we have no way to contact him?
Not unless he reaches out to us.
This isn't good.
Want me to alert the authorities?
Let's give him a little longer.
- How long did it last?
- About six months.
- He was older.
- A lot?
Yeah.
Was he a journalist, or
did he work on the hill?
I'd rather not say.
All right.
He was someone I looked
up to... for a while.
Why did it end?
He has a wife.
We both knew it was gonna end eventually.
I mean, it was really...
it was fucked up.
The first night we spent together,
he told me he was gonna
hurt me and then discard me.
And when it ended,
I told him that he'd done neither.
But... it does hurt.
I won't hurt you.
Yeah, you can't promise me that.
Yes, I can.
- Has anyone else seen him?
- No.
He's in an interrogation room by himself.
I never should've got mixed
up with this fucking mess.
We're way behind regret time, Barney.
Just have your guys keep him out of sight.
I'll need a back exit.
- I got him. Thanks.
- Yeah.
Come on.
Hey, Peter.
Where's your car?
It's down the street.
I'll drive you home. You go back
to mine, have Meechum let you in.
- This way?
- Yeah.
What were you thinking, Peter?
I need to take
responsibility for my actions.
By getting yourself thrown in jail?
Real responsibility.
Like... like they talk
about in the meetings,
not the lies we told for the campaign.
What you just did was extremely reckless.
I don't care.
I'm making a statement tomorrow, Frank.
- About pulling out of the race?
- Mm-mm.
That's not enough. I...
I need to stop hiding.
Well, let's work together on the language.
I have to do it on my own.
It's gotta be my own words.
Look, Peter, this isn't just
about you anymore, all right?
- Let me help you.
- I don't want your help.
I didn't never ask your help
when you... I got arrested.
When did your help ever help me?
You can live your life the way you want to.
I'm done being told how to live mine.
Well, there has to be a
way to take responsibility
without shattering everything.
Are you at least willing
to have that discussion?
- Do you want me to come upstairs?
- No.
I know you're in a lot of pain, Peter.
But I don't want you to
feel any pain tonight.
Here. You can start fresh tomorrow.
Go ahead. I won't judge you.
Hell, I'll even join you.
Just relax.
You're home now.
Whatever it is you have to face tomorrow,
you don't have to face it now.
Right now it's just you and me.
The rest of the world doesn't matter.
Your children, Christina...
they will forgive you,
because you're loved, Peter.
Failed.
I failed myself.
I failed my family.
I failed the campaign.
No, you haven't, Peter.
May I?
You know, when Claire
and I were first married,
we talked about having children.
I told her flat out I didn't want any.
It was selfish but honest.
I didn't have a
particularly happy childhood.
I suspect you didn't either.
No.
You see, no person avoids pain.
And I just didn't think it was right
to bring a child in knowing that.
But now when I think back, I...
I realize that was cowardly.
I see you,
and I think, well, there's a brave man,
far braver than me.
I'm so tired.
When I... when I think about... when I...
You should close your eyes.
Let it all go.
We have all the time in the world.
Peter?
Peter.
I walked back.
Whatever happens in the next few hours,
whatever you hear,
we will never speak of it.
Sir...
I heard from Linda
about a half an hour ago.
The President wants to meet with you.
8:30.
About what?
I don't know.
Frank.
Now, when you brought up
this idea, I wasn't sold.
It struck me as both
desperate and careless.
But then Linda laid out all the pros,
and they clearly outweigh the cons.
I explained our reasoning to Jim and hoped
he wouldn't think I was off my rocker.
I did at first, but the President
made some very good arguments.
It's a bold move, Frank.
I'm very impressed.
Well, thank you, sir, for
being open to the idea.
And thank you, Mr. President,
for taking the risk.
We'll need to work this out step by step.
- The execution has to be perfect.
- Where are things with Russo?
- Any word from him yet?
- We're still trying to locate him.
- Well, is there any cause for worry?
- It's been two days.
I am a bit worried, I have to admit.
I mean, this must be an extremely
difficult moment for him.
We're hoping he'll reach out shortly.
Let's get our people on it.
I wanna know where he is.
Now, once he withdraws,
we have to move quickly.
We'll make a joint
statement, as you proposed.
It's a clear message, I think.
Pennsylvanians matter to us, and
we're not gonna let them down.
That's right. I'll say that Jim's an
invaluable asset to the White House,
but that I have great
admiration for the sacrifice
he's willing to make for
the people of his home state.
And you should not accept his
resignation until he's elected.
- That will show your continuing commitment to him.
- I think that's a good idea.
As long as I can devote myself
wholly to the campaign, I agree.
Now, should Jim win, we'll need to
nominate a Vice President immediately.
Linda, you're putting
together a list of names?
Yes. And you can begin the vetting process
as soon as you narrow down the choices.
I already have a short
list of top contenders.
- I want your input on that, Jim.
- More than happy.
Congressman?
We can use the existing infrastructure.
Are you okay with Nash Aarons?
I like Nash, but I'll want to
bring in some of my own people.
Well, that won't be a
problem. Nash is a team player.
And we can reallocate some of your
existing 2016 reelection funds...
Excuse me. Linda.
Peter Russo is dead.
Suicide.
He was found in his garage
with the car still running.
I'm so sorry, Frank.
- May I have a moment, sir?
- Of course.
I will get more information
and start drafting a statement.
Let's reschedule.
Whenever is best for Frank.
Congressman Peter Russo was found dead
early this morning in the parking garage...
- why didn't we break this?
- ... Of his apartment building in Washington D.C.
U.S. Secret Service Agents
discovered his body after reports
- ... that Russo had been missing since Saturday.
- Fuck!
His body was transferred
to the D.C. coroner's office
where an autopsy is expected to
confirm his death as a suicide.
A junior congressman from Philadelphia...
- Zoe.
- ... Russo was 36 years old...
- Look at this.
- ... And is survived by two children.
- I gotta get to the office.
- Russo was in the midst of a heated battle
for the governorship of Pennsylvania.
He was last heard publicly during
a morning political radio show
on Pittsburgh station WZPZ.
Now, during the interview, he slurred
his words, he sounded disoriented...
- Christina.
- ... Leading many to believe
- ... that he had relapsed...
- Can you get me a train back to D.C.?
Right here on this TV station
for all your late-breaking details
about this major news story:
The suicide of congressman Peter Russo.
I find it very difficult to express
everything that I'm feeling right now,
and I know Claire feels exactly the same.
Peter was very special to us.
A sort of magnetic presence
that electrified everyone he touched.