[Walker] The whole reason we
do these meetings, Frank,
is so I can get
accurate information from you.
I always said
it was going to be close.
Then why did every article
I read yesterday
say the leadership was
confident the bill would pass?
- Do you know Janine Skorsky?
- She used to be the Herald's
White House correspondent.
I remember Janine.
She wrote
an article for Slugline
reporting
a verified vote count.
Once the media got ahold of
that, it went everywhere.
I don't know where she got that number.
Maybe she made it up.
It doesn't matter
if she made it up.
The democrats seem divided. The
leadership looks incompetent.
But compared the the budget
and our education act,
why, this was
a minor bill, sir.
That happened to be
in the national spotlight,
which is what you wanted.
I got the count wrong.
It rarely happens,
but it happens.
What worries me is that
the White House's influence
isn't translating
into support on the hill.
Linda's involvement
had no effect?
[Francis] I wouldn't say
that that's the case, sir.
Did you sense any push-back, any
fallout from the education battle?
Sir, the truth is
I wasn't there.
I had to make a trip
to California
to meet the Provost of Stanford
for my son.
I told you about it last week.
It was my decision, sir.
I made a judgment call
that we could pass the bill
without her help.
But, look,
tight votes like this,
you can analyze them to death,
but at the end of the day,
we came up short.
That's my fault, no one else's.
Certainly not Linda's.
I shouldn't have gone.
The meeting didn't even work.
I thought you said
they were reconsidering.
No. I got an e-mail
this morning.
They decided not to overturn
the admissions decision.
Oh, Christ. I'm sorry, Linda.
Not a great day so far.
But I appreciate your covering
for me in there.
There may be a way to turn Linda's
bad luck into my good fortune.
But first I must deal
with treason within the ranks...
the two renegades
who voted against the bill.
I have zero tolerance
for betrayal,
which they will soon
indelibly learn.
Sync and correction by GeirDM
www.addic7ed.com
I know why you lost the vote.
[Chuckles]
Somebody got to Vanderburgh
and Abrams.
Remy Danton.
- Your wife.
- [Chuckles]
I've got contacts
on both their staffs.
There was a meeting
between the three of them.
I know. I arranged it.
- She told them to vote no.
- No, not true.
Sources on two different staffs
saying the exact same thing?
That makes no sense.
I'm not telling you
what makes sense,
I'm telling you facts.
This is a juicy story, Francis.
Carly will love it.
The majority whip's wife
stabs him in the back.
Be careful, Zoe.
I'm feeding you.
Now you have to feed me.
So give me something better.
[Francis] Are you going
to answer my question?
Did she or didn't she?
Tell me now, or so help me God,
I will make it
my mission in life
to not only
destroy your careers,
but to obliterate all hope
and happiness
that you manage to cling to.
- She said it would be okay...
- To backstab me?
To do what we thought
was right.
So she did tell you to vote no.
She said it wouldn't be the end
of the world if the bill failed.
Those were her exact words.
You discuss this with no one.
Is that understood?
Do you blame yourself
for not being
in Washington to
secure the votes?
A bill this size is a team effort.
There are a lot of sponsors.
- But you were the chief
sponsor and the bill manager.
- That's true.
So shouldn't you
have been in Washington?
I'm running for Governor.
I have a
commitment to the
people of my state.
Are you aware
that the swofford campaign
is putting out a new
commercial today that says,
quote, "if Peter Russo can't
follow through in congress",
can he follow through
with sobriety?"
That's all.
Thank you very much.
- Do you want to comment?
- Thanks, guys.
- Congressman!
- [Chattering]
All I said was what you always
say... to vote their conscience.
You encouraged them to defy me.
I met with them.
That's what you asked me...
no, that is not what you did.
I specifically told you I needed
them to vote yes on this bill.
There was no room
for interpretation.
It's a deliberate lie, so don't
try to sugarcoat it, Claire.
I needed Remy's help.
You wouldn't offer any.
Oh, wait.
You did this for Remy?
No. For myself. To get my
shipment out of Sudan.
He provided assistance.
In exchange
for defeating the bill.
No. In exchange
for not helping it succeed.
Which is the same goddamn thing.
Do you realize you have endangered
everything that we have
been working toward?
There was a timetable here,
Claire.
We needed strong momentum
right up until the last minute.
I can't operate based on plans
you haven't shared with me.
Then you should've
asked me first.
No, I'm not going to
ask for your blessing
on every decision
I make, Francis.
We make decisions together.
Yeah, well, it hasn't felt like that.
Not for the past six months.
I don't feel as though
I'm standing beside you.
Other people know, Claire.
This could become
a story about us.
- And that's something
you do not recover from.
- Who?
- That's something that
follows you for life.
- Who knows?
Zoe.
I thought you said
she could be trusted.
- What about our trust?
- You can't control her, can you, Francis?
She wouldn't have been a problem
if you hadn't lied.
No, she wouldn't
have been a problem
if you hadn't
dropped your pants.
And you come in here,
to my office, and berate me
when you're the one
who's exposed us?
Don't you try
to turn this around on me.
I fired half of my staff for us.
I have turned down
donations for us.
I drafted Peter's bill for us.
I diverted time and energy
away from my goals for us.
Okay, I don't wanna
have to say this,
but maybe you need to hear it.
C.W.I. Is important, yes,
but it doesn't come close to what
we are trying to accomplish.
You must see that!
I'm just being honest.
Then be honest about
how you've been using me
just like you use
everybody else.
That was never part
of the bargain.
Is it the hot flashes?
[Quietly] Get out.
Get out.
[Clears throat]
I'll see you back at the house.
[Phone chiming]
I'm on my way to the office.
- Let me call you when I get there.
- No, no. We need to talk now.
I know you're upset, Peter, but
that's not going to achieve anything.
I am more than upset, Frank.
Change your tone.
I'm in no mood.
- I don't give a fuck!
- Good-bye, Peter.
You hang up on me now,
you're not gonna appreciate
who I call next.
- Excuse me?
- I promised my people jobs.
You promised me
you could get this bill passed.
You failed on your promise.
I'm not gonna fail on mine.
So however you need to fix it,
you figure it out.
Otherwise,
I go public with Kapeniak
and the Kern editorial.
You need to cool
down and think very
carefully about
what you just said.
You don't understand. I'm not
afraid of you anymore, Frank.
- Then you're misguided.
- My past is out in the open.
You don't hold that
over my head anymore.
They don't know
everything, Peter.
You destroy me,
you destroy yourself.
Fix it.
[Clicks]
- What do you want me to do?
- We have to accelerate things.
Isn't it too early? It's almost two
full months into the election.
- That gives the White House
too much time to vet somebody.
- Peter's crossed the line.
We built up his confidence, and
now we're losing control of him.
Maybe he was just
blowing off steam.
No. He's determined.
We have to act now.
You have everything you need
on your end?
Give me a when and a where.
Some sort
of social setting's preferable.
- Anything else?
- I'll need cash.
About three grand.
It'll be in your top drawer
by tomorrow morning.
Sir...
Once we do this,
we're committed.
- Understood.
- I can't predict how he's gonna react.
Well, I won't be blackmailed.
[Knock on door]
Hello?
[Claire] Zoe Barnes?
Yeah. Who is it?
Claire Underwood.
Zoe?
I apologize for not buzzing.
Somebody was coming in the
building when I was downstairs,
- so I just figured...
- [Door closes]
[Men chattering,
shouting outside]
This is nice... fire escape.
Hey, could you please
not go through my things?
Oh, I'm sorry. Am I intruding?
Yeah, actually. You are.
Well, that makes it
a two-way street, I suppose.
Okay, if you...
if you came here to punish me...
Fine. I get it.
[Exhales]
Such a shame,
how naive you are.
- I'm not naive.
- No?
I've known everything
from the beginning, Zoe.
My husband and I
tell each other everything.
Don't you believe me?
Is there a spider I can trap?
I'm not here to punish you
or to tell you to stop.
I just thought I should open
those big bright eyes.
I think you should leave.
I think I should too.
Maybe you're not that naive.
A lesser woman
wouldn't have opened the door.
[Door opens]
Union station, please.
[Beeps]
[Line ringing]
This is Claire. I'm unavailable
to answer the phone,
but if you leave a message, I'll be
sure and get back to you shortly.
- Thank...
- [Beeps]
[Beeps]
[Line ringing]
- [Zoe] Hello?
- Zoe.
[Toilet flushes]
You don't have to tiptoe.
I thought you fell asleep.
No. Just thinking about work.
I don't have anything for you yet.
I will soon.
I know you will.
You can spend the night
if you want.
Early meetings.
Wouldn't have time to get home
and change.
- You seem distracted.
- I have a lot on my mind.
- Like what?
- [Beeping]
- Work, just like you.
- No Claire?
Or maybe she qualifies as work.
She didn't mention anything?
About...
I thought you didn't
keep things from each other.
Look, just say
what you want to say.
She came by here
a few hours ago.
We had a nice little talk.
Don't let me keep you.
You should go home,
get some rest.
- Tell Claire I said hi.
- [Door opens, closes]
Hey!
[Line ringing]
This is Claire.
I'm unavailable to answer...
- [yells]
- [Phone clatters]
The lights in the Whartons' house
will go on in a few moments.
They always get up
precisely at quarter to 7:00,
which is just the time that Claire
would be going for her run,
if she were here.
Rebellion on all fronts...
Claire, Zoe, Russo.
I must not lose my resolve.
I will march forward,
even if I have to do so...
Alone.
See? Told ya.
- Good morning.
- Ohh!
Hi, Frank.
- How are you?
- I'm good.
- Have you heard from Claire?
- Yeah, I got her message.
- How's she feeling?
- A lot better.
Good. She said she'd be gone
for the rest of the week.
- Is it the flu or something?
- Something like that.
I just came over to pick up
a few things from her office.
- I could've sent somebody over.
- Oh, no. It's no big deal.
In fact, I also came here
to ask you a favor.
You went to Stanford, correct?
- Valedictorian?
- Yeah.
- Do you know the provost?
- Warren Tynsdale.
He flies me out
to do fund-raising events.
Supposedly I'm the poster child
for alumni.
Making the world
a better place.
Well, that is good,
because this is important.
Linda vasquez,
the President's Chief of staff...
her son, Ruben, applied.
I'd love for you to get on
the phone with Tynsdale
and tell him
that they should accept him.
I don't know. I...
I've never recommended anyone.
All the better.
It'll carry more weight.
Can I meet Ruben first?
[Sighs] I would really
prefer that Linda not know.
In fact, it would be better
if both she and Ruben
believed he got in
on merit alone.
Will you please do this favor
for Claire and me?
And for the president.
Thank you.
More contrast.
We need to catch
the edge of his face.
Let's re-crop it. Bring it in a
quarter of an inch on the left.
[Doorbell rings]
Would you...
[Intercom buzzing]
Somebody named Claire?
Remy.
You hungry?
I don't eat pork.
When did that happen?
When we started lobbying
for the meatpacking industry.
[Laughing]
Freddy, half a rack for me,
and some Collard Greens
for my friend here.
I'm good. I already ate lunch.
Half a rack coming up.
I don't usually
do business here.
This is my little secret.
I'd love it
if we could keep it that way.
I don't think you have to worry
about me bringing clients by.
You seem tense, Remy.
I assume you're upset
about the watershed bill.
Not with you.
You were just doing your job.
But now I have to do mine.
I'd like to propose
a partnership.
I'm always open
to partnerships, Frank.
If Peter Russo were
a pro-natural gas candidate,
how valuable would that be
to Sancorp?
The watershed bill
was anti-drilling.
Peter's pro-employment,
not anti-drilling.
He just wants to bring
employment to his people,
and Sancorp
is building refineries.
Mostly on site.
Do you think they would be open
to considering Philadelphia?
I can talk with them,
but I can't make any promises.
Oh, I don't want any promises.
Just engage with Russo.
You know, give him a glimmer
of good fortune.
Aw, Frank, here you go.
Come on. Smell that.
You sure you don't want to
reconsider your stance on pork?
- Brain food, brother.
- [Francis chuckling]
- I love it.
- [Stamper] 850.
You can afford that?
Yeah. Yeah, I think so.
First and last month
are taken care of.
So is the security deposit.
That's to buy some furniture.
I'll pay you back. I promise.
It's not necessary.
But I do need you to do
one thing for me.
- I come across as a hypocrite.
- [Francis] You need jobs.
Do you really care
how you deliver them?
First, I advocate for more
regulation for the watershed,
then I cozy up
to the drilling interests?
Yeah, but natural gas
is the future, Peter.
This is an industry
that could bring 100,000 jobs
into your state
over the next decade.
I agree with Peter.
It seems like flip-flopping.
Sancorp's lobbying efforts is
why we lost the watershed bill.
But they can also be
a very powerful ally.
[Christina]
Our message is a "fresh start."
This makes you look
like business as usual.
This is politics.
There are seized opportunities
and missed opportunities.
Seize this one, Peter.
Sancorp can commit to building
new refineries in Philly?
Sancorp will commit
to discussing it with you.
- I need more than that.
- Look, you asked me to fix a problem.
I've come to you in less than
24 hours with a solution.
Can you meet me halfway?
What would be the first step?
All right.
You remember Remy Danton?
- Oh, come on. He led the charge
against the watershed bill.
- I know. That's not the point.
One of his other big clients is
the McNeally cancer institute.
They're having
a big gala tonight...
a cocktail party...
for their donors.
Remy will be there.
We have events in Haverford
and Gladwyne...
yeah, well,
this is more important.
You also have a radio interview
tomorrow morning
with a local Pittsburgh station?
- Yes.
- All right.
Meet with Remy tonight.
And if it goes well
and if you're comfortable,
tomorrow morning on the radio, you
support their drilling efforts.
And Remy has assured me
if you do that,
he can push Sancorp
in the right direction.
Cancel the events tomorrow.
Head back to Philly,
do some damage control.
- I'll see you tomorrow afternoon.
- Peter...
please.
Okay.
I'm gonna go make some calls.
[Door opens, closes]
Peter, have you mentioned anything
to her about Kapeniak or...
No. I haven't mentioned it
to anybody.
All right. Stamper will
come by in the morning
and brief you
on the talking points.
[Door opens, closes]
[Claire]
When did you take this?
[Adam] Oh, it was about
7:00 in the morning.
The sun had just come up.
You were asleep... right here.
The light was perfect.
I had no choice.
I always slept so well
in this apartment.
- How long are you in town for?
- [Sighs]
I don't know.
I haven't decided.
You have no luggage.
It smells the same.
Feels the same.
- ♪♪ [Soft jazz]
- [Chatter, laughter]
[Peter] I think Sancorp
is missing out,
not having a significant
presence in Philadelphia.
There are advantages to centralizing
in a major urban center.
But the disadvantages are
commercial real estate prices,
city taxes,
building a pipeline.
It's all very costly.
So they'd have to
reduce costs elsewhere.
- Significantly.
- How can I help with that?
Statewide permitted-use zoning.
No more conditional zoning.
The municipalities
are slowing down development.
That's the state legislature.
You come out in support
of permitted use,
and you get elected Governor.
That'll put pressure
on the legislature.
Sancorp is very interested in having
a powerful friend in Harrisburg.
My opponent's pro-drilling.
Your opponent isn't asking
for refineries in Philadelphia.
We prefer friends
we can count on.
Have your clients listen to WZPZ
tomorrow at a quarter to 8:00.
It's a Pittsburgh station.
It's been a pleasure,
Congressman.
I look forward
to talking again soon.
♪
♪ [Continues]
You got a light?
This is a cancer research event.
I know. I helped organize it.
- You work for the institute?
- No. The hotel.
And they let you smoke here?
No. The manager would kill me.
Well, at least
it got you talking.
[Chuckles]
Are you having a good night?
You look happy.
Uh, I am. I am.
I'm having a great night.
- Why?
- I just got some very good news.
We should celebrate.
What are you drinking?
You know,
I was just leaving, actually.
You haven't even asked
my name yet.
- I apologize, but I have to go.
- It's Rachel.
I'm not trying to be rude, but
I got a big meeting tomorrow.
Then don't be rude.
Just stay a few more minutes
and keep me
from having to mingle.
My date ditched me.
So if you abandon
me now, that would be very rude.
These heels are killing me.
- Feel that. Feel that blister.
- Hey, I...
I have a girlfriend.
I'd be surprised if you didn't.
- Why'd your date ditch you?
- Mmm. Very scandalous.
Mmm, what happened?
Clink glasses with me.
[Clink]
Wow.
Ooh. [Belches]
[Both laugh]
I'm petite,
but I can hold my liquor.
Obviously.
When I do get drunk, though...
[Chuckles]
What then?
I get undressed.
What about you?
What are you like
when you get drunk?
- It's not pretty.
- Pretty's overrated.
I like it when things
get a little bit ugly.
When I work late nights,
they let me stay at the hotel
so I don't have to drive home.
Um...
This one is yours.
Room 1121.
[Door opens]
[Footsteps]
[Door closes]
[Meechum] Sir?
In here.
You wanted to see me?
I need you to locate somebody.
Who?
My wife.
Do you have a way of doing that?
I do, sir.
I know a guy
in missing persons...
she's not missing. I just...
Don't know where she is
at the moment.
I trust him.
We can do this off the books.
Good.
I'll get on it right away.
[Door opens]
[Laughter]
[Adam]
Come on. Give us another one.
No. I'll tell you why.
Because my mother
always used to tell
me to smile more.
Always drove me crazy.
She'd say, "Claire",
"why have you that scowl
all the time?
You look so much more beautiful
when you smile."
It was never
a real conversation.
There was never, "oh, what do you
feel?" Or "what are you thinking?"
Just so long as
I looked beautiful and happy.
That's all she cared about.
So you want me to ask you
what you're thinking
and feeling?
All the time.
I actually do wanna know what
you're thinking and feeling.
- How sad am I?
- Okay, so tell me first.
- What?
- Tell me first.
- I think I'd better get dressed.
- What? Why?
Uh, because...
I've got friends coming over,
and as a host,
I should probably wear clothes.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Why do you do that?
- Well, you know.
- It's proper?
- Kind of.
Oh, fuck.
[Scoffs]
[Chattering]
[Beeps]
[Door closes]
Thought you might have bailed.
Sit down.
Vodka or whiskey?
Uh, you go ahead.
Come on. You can be a good
boy downstairs, not up here.
Seriously, I'm good.
Whiskey, I think.
- [Minibar door opens]
- [Bottles clinking]
[Door closes]
So what's your good news?
I wanna know
what we're celebrating.
Why did your, uh...
why did your date ditch you?
- I asked you first.
- I did, downstairs.
He works on the hill.
Some staffer or something.
I don't know.
I think he's a glorified gofer.
A friend set me up with him.
So I said he should come
tonight, keep me company.
But all he wanted to do
was schmooze.
So I brought him
into the women's bathroom,
told him he was being
an asshole.
He told me
I was being childish.
So I slapped him.
- [Laughs]
- You slapped him?
Yeah. Big red hand mark
right across his face.
I think he was embarrassed
to be seen by the Schmoozerati.
So he left.
And that is the last time
I go on a date
with a guy who wears
a flag pin to work.
I'm one of those guys
who wears a flag pin to work.
This isn't really a date,
is it?
I really shouldn't be here.
That's what makes it fun.
Tell me your good news. I wanna
know what we're toasting to.
Let's toast to you.
I'm your good news?
Okay, I'll toast to that.
Oh.
Hey.
What are you...
I didn't wanna wait
at the Herald.
I was gonna call you, but...
Can I stay
at your place tonight?
Uh, stay with me?
Well, just on your couch
for a night or two.
Uh, why?
I can't be in my apartment.
- Did something happen?
- No. I...
I'm sorry.
Zoe.
Come on.
[Francis]
What time is the interview?
Quarter to 8:00.
I'll be with him.
And where's Peter now?
Are you sure
you want the details?
Mm.
Just tell me, is it going well?
Hasn't been any updates.
But if it does go well,
you'll be ready?
I'm ready.
I've been ready. I'm ready.
- Anything else?
- We never played chess before, have we?
I don't know how.
You want me to teach you?
I should really get some rest.
Be fresh for the morning.
Yeah, another time.
1160, WZPZ, 7:45.
- Good night.
- [Door opens, closes]
I hate being kept in the dark.
Waiting.
Speculating.
Useless.
♪
♪ [Latin jazz]
[Laughter, chatter]
[Woman] Oh, come on!
- Let's dance.
- Whoo-hoo! Yeah.
It's not a big deal.
Come on, let's do it.
- Come on, let's do it.
- No.
No, please, I can't. Not now.
Come on.
This is really nice.
Do you want anything?
Water? Juice?
No, thanks. I'm good.
Uh, you can have the bed.
I'll sleep on the couch.
No. No.
It's fine.
Please, Lucas,
let me sleep on the couch.
I'll feel bad.
All right.
- Can I help?
- I got it.
[Sheet rustling]
So, you know,
we don't have to talk
if you don't want to.
But I haven't seen you
in, like,
six months.
Except for when I
drunkenly stalked you at your...
[Chuckles]
- Right.
- That was kind of adorable.
It was either psychotic or sad.
Not adorable.
- [Smoothing out sheet]
- Yes, it was.
Can you hand me that pillow?
So, why do you need
to get out of your apartment?
It just felt small.
Well, it can't
be smaller than my place.
No. I don't mean size.
I mean...
I felt trapped.
Like I was in a place
that I didn't actually live.
Does that make any sense?
I guess.
Okay.
There you go.
Um, anytime
you need to get up or...
um, I'll just set an alarm
on my phone.
All right.
Well, feel free to watch TV.
I can sleep through anything.
Hey, thank you, Lucas.
[Puffs]
[Groans]
Hey, that's the last of it.
Better make it count, then.
- Drink up.
- Mm.
[Laughing]
Mmm.
Do I look familiar to you?
Familiar?
No.
- My face? My body?
- No.
How about my voice?
Have we...
No.
No. I was just
wondering if you had a
thing for brunettes
with blue eyes.
- Hey, where you going? Come back here.
- I wanna see you better.
[Sighs]
Shit. The sun's up?
Has been for a while.
- Oh, fuck. What time is it?
- 7:15.
Fuck. I have an interview
in half an hour.
- Skip it.
- I can't. I gotta do it.
[Retching]
[Toilet flushes]
You can keep the room
till noon.
- [Phone ringing]
- [Sighs]
- [Grunts]
- [Beeps]
- Hello?
- [Stamper] I'm at your building.
The front desk keeps calling
up, but there's no answer.
- I'm not there.
- Then I'll come to you. Where are you?
I'm... I'm at
the Park Highmore hotel.
Are you okay? You sound drunk.
It was, uh... yeah. Yeah.
I'm... I'm all right.
- You have the interview.
- I know!
Have you been drinking, Peter?
Uh, what? No. Um, I just decided
to spend the night here.
What room are you in?
11, uh... 1121.
Stay there.
I'm coming right now.
Jesus, Peter. What happened?
You're drunk.
- I'm fine.
- I can smell it on you.
Okay, I had a drink or two.
It was nothing crazy.
We can't do this interview.
I'm sober. I can handle it.
You're slurring your words.
I'm good.
I think we should cancel.
I'm gonna do the interview.
Just give me the talking points.
Sorry.
Sorry. I...
It's all right.
The couch had a spring in it
or something, and my back...
no.
It's all right.
I don't mind.
[Keyboard clacking]
Sir, I heard from my friend.
Missing persons.
And?
- She's in New York.
- What hotel?
Not a hotel, sir.
So she's not alone.
No, sir.
Adam Galloway?
Yes, sir.
I have more information.
I don't need to know.
Turn on 1160 A.M.
[Man] He's running to fill
Jim Matthews' old post
as Governor of Pennsylvania.
Glad to have you with us, sir.
[Peter]
It's good to be here, Jim.
- [Man] It's mark.
- Sorry. Right. Mark.
That's okay, Congressman.
It happens all
the time this early
in the morning.
So, Congressman,
the watershed act.
Yes. Uh, I'm ashamed of the...
well, I'm not ashamed.
That's not the right, um...
I'm disappointed, um,
because, you know,
the water...
It's, um... it's... actually,
what I'd like to discuss is...
we all know that natural gas...
that it's... it's a growing...
uh, in our state...
it's a... it's a big part
of, um...
economically,
the way things are going.
And I'd like to say...
to announce...
in terms of, um... [Stammering]
Are you familiar
with drilling regulations...
permitted use
versus conditional use?
[Mark] Are we still talking
about the watershed?
[Peter]
No. Drilling. Natural gas.
[Mark] Sir, you supported
increased regulation.
[Peter] Well, no. I... i...
it may have looked that way,
but, uh,
in fact, to be clear,
I'm for less...
Regulation.
Yes, sir. In the watershed bill,
the language clearly stated...
it didn't pass.
Well, right.
That's what I'm asking about.
- What about it?
- Why it didn't pass.
I just said.
No, sir. I don't think you did.
It just didn't.
Sir, three days ago,
you predicted...
I'm talking about
fucking natural gas.
I'm sorry.
[Mark] Congressman, I have
to ask you a question,
and it may come across
as indelicate,
but are you drunk right now?
[Peter] What? No. No.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm just... I'm really tired,
you know?
I've been on the campaign trail
for a few weeks now,
and...
- [Mark] Congressman?
- [Dial tone]
Congressman? Congressman?
[Buzzes]
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have let you.
I'm fucked.
Okay. Listen. We sober you up.
We'll make some kind of
announcement as soon as possible.
There's nothing I can say.
We'll figure this out.
Come on.
You're gonna take a shower.
There you go. Come on.
[Vasquez on phone]
How bad is it?
It all depends on whether it gets
picked up by the mainstream press.
- Well, shall I fill in the president?
- No. Hold off on that.
I need to speak to Peter,
coordinate with his campaign.
You'll be the first call I make.
Frank, before you go,
I got an e-mail this morning.
Stanford reversed
their decision.
That's wonderful.
The Provo said Gillian Cole
reached out to him.
I googled her.
She works for Claire.
- Thank you.
- No reason to thank me.
Ruben was just ecstatic. I don't
know how I'm gonna repay you.
The fact that your son is happy
is more than enough.
- You'll keep me posted on Peter?
- You bet.
- Okay.
- [Beeps]
[Beeps]
[Line ringing]
Hey, boss.
- Are you still with him?
- Yeah.
- He's taking a shower.
- How're we looking?
Zoe Barnes posted
ten minutes ago.
It's already on
the New York times web site.
The kid is done.
Have Nancy set up a meeting
with the Vice President.
- Today if possible.
- Will do.
And keep an eye on Peter.
He's done his duty.
- Let's get him back on his feet.
- You got it.
- [Beeps]
- And now Jim Matthews comes to the fore,
though he doesn't know it yet.
He will find solace
in his beloved Pennsylvania,
though Peter Russo
will find solace nowhere.
It only takes ten seconds
to crush a man's ambitions.
I need to take care
that I protect mine.
[Shower running]
Peter.
Peter!
Peter?
Hey!
Sync and correction by GeirDM
www.addic7ed.com