Previously on House of Cards...
Put down the bag. Put down the bag
and place your hands on your head.
Stay right where you are.
Tusk isn't planning his next attack
even as we speak?
It's time we go on the offensive.
The casino. We go public
as soon as possible.
Feng has ties to Tusk.
Tusk has ties to the president.
I had nothing to do
with it, Raymond.
I can smell the horseshit
through the phone.
Mr. President, would you walk us
through your history with Raymond Tusk?
Everyone is fair game now,
including me.
- What can I do? - Come and visit me
when I'm in prison.
Two Chinese destroyers entered waters
within three miles of Yonaguni Island.
It could have to do
with shipping routes.
Or the trade war. They can't
pick on the big kids,
so they're picking
on the little one.
Almost every woman in the
House supports this bill.
And I can't be one of them.
If the bill goes to the floor
as is, I won't just bow out.
I'll actively fight it.
Has Claire said anything?
Just that things have
been a little rocky.
- We saw someone.
- You mean a therapist?
- Weren't you worried about exposure?
- I could put you in touch.
How can I help?
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
...a longstanding source...
Underwood will
speak before the committee
today regarding
the allegations...
While little is being released
to the public, the
vice president's statement...
The vice president just entered
the Department of Justice.
We're here with Ayla Sayyad,
whose
Wall Street Telegraph article
catalyzed the investigation.
Ayla.
The issue at stake is whether the
White House was in any way involved.
Was foreign money traded
for political favors?
Did it influence
diplomatic relations?
Just the act of laundering
Chinese contributions is illegal.
If it had a significant impact on
White House policy, that's
a far more serious crime.
You've met with Daniel Lanagin
on multiple occasions.
We were in the same room, yes,
on 11 occasions since 2003.
But we only spoke
on three of those occasions.
- Those instances are highlighted.
- What did you discuss?
These were fund-raisers.
I speak to dozens of people.
Usually about nothing at all.
I'm Southern, Ms. Dunbar.
My mother taught me that conversation
during mealtime is not only polite,
it aids the digestive process.
So you didn't speak to him about
the Adohi Tribe's contributions
- to any of these super PACS?
- Absolutely not.
I never discuss super PACs with
any supporters. We both know the law.
During one of these
polite conversations,
do you recall Mr. Lanagin
ever mentioning Xander Feng?
- I do not. - Does that name
mean anything to you?
Other than being plastered
all over the news?
In that regard, it means
as much as Kim Kardashian.
Then let me be more specific.
What knowledge do you have
of Mr. Feng's political
activities?
- Is this coming from
your husband, or is it...? - From me.
And it's not that I don't
support the bill anymore.
It's just the article.
We've promised
Matt an interview.
Maybe in a few weeks, once
the investigation has died down.
The New York Times
isn't going to wait for us.
They've already scheduled the cover
for October, based on our timing...
Then I can't be a part of it.
- It's the Galloway nonsense, isn't it?
- Claire, come on.
It's OK. You can say so.
We're friends.
- It doesn't help.
- You don't actually believe...
No.
But enough of the
country still does.
And Garrett needs every bit
of support he can get right now.
So there's no convincing you?
I'll help you as much
as I can, quietly.
There are rumors that you and Mr.
Feng served as back channels
- to the trade summit last May.
- Exactly. Rumors.
We have Feng
in the US during the summit.
If he was back-channeling,
and even if I were aware,
any form of diplomatic
communication is usually classified.
Have you ever discussed Feng
with the president?
Any major player in Beijing
is worthy of discussion.
- So that's a yes.
- It's a general comment.
Did you discuss him
during the energy crisis?
I assume you're alluding
to his refinery co-venture...
- Yes, with Raymond Tusk. - The refinery
was never part of our conversation.
We needed an immediate solution.
A refinery would've solved
nothing in the short term.
And it's my understanding
that deal fell through.
Correct. But Tusk
did receive a subsidy.
As did every other
nuclear energy provider.
But his connection with Feng,
then a subsidy on samarium...
Nobody made any profits off these
subsidies. At best they're breaking even.
In fact, Raymond
fought us on the issue.
Then let's back up to
the Port Jefferson Bridge.
I don't blame her.
It's a valid concern.
Tell him I won't engage on Galloway,
so there's no point in asking.
This is Matt Bai, we can't dictate
what he'll ask. And he will ask.
Then I'll just say I won't
answer tabloid questions.
It's a legitimate question,
how the scandal could affect the vote.
Look, I say you pull out too.
We scrap the whole piece.
Jackie's fighting us.
The leadership is noncommittal.
We need this article
to refocus attention.
But it'll hurt you, both your
personal image and the bill.
But if we cut the cord, we schedule
two interviews then we cancel,
won't Matt be furious?
The story will be about pulling out.
We're talking about
the lesser of two evils.
I don't want you to become
the target, to undo all...
Then what if it's not me at all?
- You said the First Lady wasn't...
- Not her. Someone else.
Was the bridge a trade-off
to prevent additional GOP funding?
As far as I know, the bridge
was a delivery on a promise
the president had made to the
voters. Are we finished here?
Almost.
How many members of Congress have you
interviewed, Ms. Dunbar? About 200?
- One hundred ninety-four.
- I want to be of help,
but I doubt I can offer any more
than the 194 that preceded me.
- I have gotten some useful testimony.
- From who?
- A high-ranking House member.
- In the leadership?
- I'm not at liberty to say.
- Bob Birch? Jackie Sharp?
This individual says he attended
a meeting, July 14th, in the Oval Office.
She said "he."
So it must have been Birch.
I'm sure Raymond had no trouble
buying him off.
You attended that meeting also.
- It appears so. - You recall the
subject of that meeting?
A wave of conservative attack
ads. We were being outspent.
It must have been quite
a shock when Lanagin's tribe
shifted contributions
to the other party,
when they hadn't given a single
dime to the Republicans before that.
It would've been a shock, but we didn't
know where the money was coming from.
- According to my source...
- Bob Birch.
My source says the estimate
was 25 million.
You said, and I quote:
"With this kind of influx,
you can be sure somebody
isn't playing by the rules."
Sounds like something I might say.
Bob has a better memory than me.
The money stopped just after the
Port Jefferson Bridge was approved.
Is there a theory here, or are you just
grasping at straws?
The bridge leads to Feng.
Feng gives me Lanagin and Tusk.
- Tusk and the President...
- Ms. Dunbar, you want to play
six degrees of separation,
you could throw in Jimmy Hoffa
and the pope.
How about one degree
of separation.
Douglas Stamper,
your chief of staff.
This is him at Lanagin's casino,
July 14th.
I used these to get a warrant
for flight records.
The next day, Mr. Stamper
was on a flight to Beijing.
Why was he at the casino?
And why was he in Beijing?
- I would like to speak to my client.
- Please.
I work hard.
I keep things simple.
I know what my priorities are.
But there's this... this person.
She's not even in my life, except on
the edges making things blurrier.
It doesn't tempt me to drink.
It's more like she...
More like she feels what it was
like when I was drinking.
When I couldn't get enough.
No matter how many drinks I had,
I wanted another.
I don't want to be with her.
I mean, I do.
But...
...it's more like
she's my daughter.
Or my mother.
I don't know, this is fucked up.
Take your time.
I should cut her off,
the way I did with booze.
That's all. I'm done.
- Thanks for sharing.
We'll need time before
responding to your questions.
- I can wait as long as necessary.
- It could take a while.
There are national security
matters at stake.
The vice president needs to
consult with his advisors.
National security?
Are you really going
- to play that card, Oliver?
- His answers could entail
classified material.
- When can we expect a response?
- I'll let you know.
- May we hold onto the screen cap?
- Be my guest.
- We'll be in touch soon, Ms. Dunbar.
- Mr. Vice President.
If you think you're insulated, don't.
Our investigation is much
bigger than Douglas Stamper.
- That's enough, Ms. Dunbar. - Thank you
for your time, Mr. Vice President.
Happy to cooperate.
From the lion's den
to a pack of wolves.
When you're fresh meat, kill
and throw them something fresher.
Hey, I'm Fitz.
Doug.
You know, you can isolate,
white-knuckle this shit if you want.
Or you can ask for help.
You got a sponsor?
No, it's been 14 years.
I'm good.
Number's on the back
if you change your mind.
I thought you had a driver.
I do, but I didn't want him
overhearing anything.
- You shouldn't even be near this state.
- I'm not really here.
Long layover on my way
to California.
I've got auditors, federal agents,
in my office going through every file,
every document, they're going
through my goddamn trash.
Just stick to the Fifth
if she subpoenas you.
How did they know to look for Stamper?
To search the tapes on that exact day?
- Don't jump to conclusions.
- You're throwing me under the bus.
Underwood's the roadkill,
not you.
They're going to fuck me.
They'll find a way.
You know that.
And if that's the case, you and
your family will be taken care of.
They're already
offering me a plea.
You haven't even
been charged yet.
- If I cooperate. - You'll do less time.
But your family will have nothing.
They'll still have nothing
when you get out.
You testify against Raymond
and he'll still walk,
because all they'll have is your word,
and that doesn't count for much right now.
You wouldn't be here
if he wasn't afraid.
I'm not here because he's afraid.
I'm here because you are.
And I want to make sure
you don't do anything stupid.
After repeated
conversations with Beijing,
they remain intractable
in their position.
This morning I gave orders
for a carrier group
to reposition near Okinawa.
This won't put our ships in direct
confrontation with the Chinese vessels,
but it will put them within
reach of air strikes.
I'll be informing the Chinese
ambassador later today.
We'll release a statement
in coordination with the Pentagon.
Sir, our stockpiles of samarium will only
last another two months at most.
- If we go this route...
- I've heard everyone's concerns,
and this is the decision
I've made. Any questions?
OK. Thank you.
Frank.
My deputy briefed me
on the latest.
How did it go?
We have a few follow-up
questions we have to address.
- Like what?
- Nothing major.
Just odds and ends,
a few details.
I was under the impression
this would be short and sweet.
So was I.
But she's very deliberate.
We need this over, Frank, at least as far
as the White House is concerned.
We can't be distracted.
Not with warships on the move.
I'm confident we're
in the homestretch.
You seem more concerned
than you're letting on.
- Oh, no. Not at all.
- You're fidgeting.
Oh...
It's my class ring.
I forget I...
- I buried it.
- You what?
I... It's a long story.
I've never seen you
this stressed before, Frank.
Well, I've never seen you
this tired before, sir.
You've got rings of your own,
dark ones.
They're getting worse,
aren't they?
You should take more naps
on those sofas in the Oval.
Naps don't cut it these days,
Frank. Not even a dent.
Lie after lie.
First to a prosecutor,
then to a president.
I feel exposed,
like the skin where
my ring used to be.
Even Achilles was only as strong
as his heel.
Where's Doug?
He's not answering his phone.
- He went to a meeting, sir.
- In the middle of the day?
I think he's on
his way back now.
I want him
back as soon as possible.
Sir, this arrived for you.
The watch you gave Remy
when he left for Glendon Hill.
I recognized it from
the quote on the back.
- Was there a message?
- No, just the watch.
- Let's find Doug.
- Right away, sir.
Forgive the plastic.
Luc Tuymans.
He's the real thing.
Well, I'll take your word.
It's not mine. None of it.
California.
You want to sell your house,
your Realtor decorates it.
Well, one room at least.
Where are you moving?
Oh, I have a little
ranch in Sonoma.
My wife's gone,
my kids won't talk to me,
but at least I'll
have my painting.
- You paint?
- No, and there's no ranch.
But the rest of it, the rest of it's true.
Cheers.
- I'm here about Jacqueline Sharp.
- Oh.
- We're thinking of hiring her.
- A lobbyist?
She could lose her re-elect.
Not a great time to be an incumbent.
I know you two were close.
So you're looking for what?
A recommendation?
We have the lowest turnover of any
shop on K Street. There's a reason.
What are you looking
for at Glendon Hill?
- A killer instinct.
- Well, she certainly has that.
Forgive me if I'm prying, but...
...did she have anything
to do with your...
Departure?
Jackie did what she had to do.
I'll never forgive her,
but I understand why she did it.
Did what exactly?
I paid cash for my ticket.
I was careful.
Clearly not enough.
Sir, the casino had cameras everywhere.
There was no way to avoid them.
But there had to have been
thousands of hours of footage.
- How they found that...
- I have to ask you a question, Doug.
And I'm sorry, but I need you
to be honest.
- Are you drinking again?
- God no.
- Truly?
- It's not an option.
Because it would explain a lot.
You have every right to be
upset. This was my fault.
I'm more concerned than I'm upset.
I need you now, Doug, more than ever.
I know.
We're not young men.
If we fail, we'll die in a cage.
I haven't been myself lately.
That's what you said
to me 14 years ago.
When I gave you a second chance,
it paid off. You got clean, Doug.
Nothing means more to me
than this job, sir.
Nothing.
Whatever's going on,
I need to know it can be managed.
And if you need my help,
I'm here to help you.
I'm good, sir. I can handle myself.
Things will be different.
I've never given
someone a third chance...
...until this very moment.
And I'm grateful.
You won't regret it.
Please believe that, sir.
It was Remy who alerted
them to the footage.
His going-away gift.
Read the back.
- What do you think he's trying to say?
- I don't know.
But track him down
and set up a meeting.
- What about Dunbar?
- We can't run from the facts.
I'll say whatever you want me to say,
I'll take responsibility for all of it.
- She could indict you.
- That's what having a staff is for.
I have a better solution.
We'll both take responsibility.
- How?
- Set up an interview with Dunbar,
day after tomorrow. You and I
need time to do our homework.
Yes, sir.
- When did this happen?
- Meechum helped me fix it.
They're not gonna let me run,
I have to work out some way.
- You carried it all the way up here?
- For privacy. I had help.
- Meechum.
- That's right.
Jack-of-all-trades.
- Handyman, furniture mover.
- Human shield.
How bad is it?
Bad.
They have evidence of Doug being
where he shouldn't have been.
What are you going to do?
Tell the truth.
- You're not actually going...
- Selectively.
Don't worry.
It's a stumble, not a fall.
You aren't like this
when it's just a stumble.
- Like how?
- You're scared. I can tell.
Five hundred meters at 139.
That was my best.
Shoot for that.
- How have you been?
- OK.
- The meds are helping.
- Oh, that's good to hear.
Have a seat.
Those people at the end
of the street, it's intense.
They're there 24/7.
Twice as many on the weekends.
We're so used to it by now.
Can I take off my shoes?
I thought I should dress up,
but I am not good with heels.
Yes, of course.
My mom said
they went with the dress.
Much better.
Look, Megan, I know the last
six months have been difficult.
But I need your help.
We just don't have the support
that we expected
in the leadership.
Yeah, I figured this wasn't
just about checking up on me.
You changed your mind before,
and I understand why.
But now it seems as though
things are more stable with you.
- Are you willing? - It's hard to say no
when I'm in your house.
You hear those people out there.
They're loud, but I think
we need to be louder.
And it can't be my voice
because I'm the "baby killer."
The "cheater." It needs to be
your voice. A clear voice.
I'm already testifying
at the court-martial.
But that's closed to the media.
It's not enough.
There are so many people this has
happened to, why does it have to be me?
Because you're
the one who called.
Are you gonna try to put it out
before McGinnis gets sentenced?
- Seth, you have a minute?
- Matt, I have to call you back.
Close the door.
When the vice president brought you
on board I advised against it.
But I can't deny
you've done a good job.
I appreciate you saying that.
I'm very protective
of the vice president.
I find it hard to share
that duty with anyone else,
which leaves me open to error.
It's one of my faults.
As I told the vice president, I understand
that trust is something I need to earn.
- Given how I got the job...
- If the vice president trusts you,
then I trust you.
We're a team now.
And the truth
is I can't do this alone.
Anything and everything
you ask of me.
It might have nothing
to do with the media.
- Press secretary is just a title.
- Good.
We have two tasks.
First, find me Remy Danton.
- But be discreet.
- I'll track him down.
Second, I need you to go through
the vice president's travel logs.
- Everything in the past ten years.
- What are we looking for?
Anything that could hurt us.
I'll work forward, you work backward.
I'm on it.
And, Doug, thanks.
Nancy, I need you
to order me a new phone.
You said "odds and
ends." The "homestretch."
I was presented with this
information just hours ago.
We're talking about
impeachable offenses...
- Not at all, sir.
- Your chief of staff...
I had a gut feeling
that the casino was involved.
I sent Doug to get
to the bottom of it.
You should've
taken this to the DOJ
- the first inkling you...
- That's what I didn't want.
To create some ruckus
if nothing was going on?
You can't go on conducting
your own investigations, Frank.
Fact-finding, due diligence,
whatever you want to call it.
If any laws were being broken,
I wanted to know.
That's what you want
to tell Dunbar?
That I didn't want to disclose
our diplomatic protocols.
That I was concerned
about the midterms.
And I wanted to protect the
president of the United States.
Maybe what I did was wrong,
but I didn't do anything illegal.
- You're certain of that?
- I've discussed this with my lawyers.
Dunbar does not strike me as the
sort of person who will put on the brakes,
even if we admit all of this.
If fact, it might encourage
her to dig deeper.
You're right. Which is why I want
to hand over all of my travel logs.
- And I think you should too.
- Volunteer them?
- As a gesture of cooperation.
- Haven't we made enough gestures?
It will take the
wind out her sails.
No, I don't...
want her poring
over every one
of my comings and goings.
He's worried about his marriage
counseling, as he should be.
If you're worried about your
marriage counseling, you shouldn't be.
Imagine the fallout,
if the public were to find out...
A needle in a haystack,
and not a needle Dunbar is looking for.
She's interviewed half of Congress.
That woman's after blood.
But not for gossip. Even if she
does raise an eyebrow,
you were visiting a sick friend,
weren't you?
- Ostensibly. - Well, she couldn't
possibly find any fault with that.
- I'd like Galich in here.
- I'll let you two talk privately.
- When are you seeing Dunbar?
- Tomorrow, so you have some time.
I'll speak to Bill
and get back to you.
He'll advise you against it,
which is his job.
But I would just encourage you
to think politics, and not legalese.
Thank you, sir.
Congresswoman.
Why should I vote for you?
It's... it's OK. Good night.
You look tired.
Long day on the campaign trail?
What are you doing here?
You never told me
about Havemeyer's daughter.
Everyone knows that.
The whole world knows.
But not that you visited her.
That you leaked it.
You came all the way to
California to ask me about that?
I came to California
to find out about that.
I offered to buy Havemeyer's house,
but he told me for nothing.
You were right. It has been
a long day on the trail.
It's still a close race.
But not if the voters
knew how you became whip.
Are you honestly threatening me?
Set up a meeting with Frank.
I don't care what you talk about,
as long as you're alone and
the meeting is on the books.
Then you're gonna
sit down with Dunbar.
I've already done my interview.
Tell her Frank grilled
you on your testimony.
- Perjure myself?
- Save your seat.
You know what?
Tell everyone.
- Think how that would play out.
- I don't care.
You'd really toss yourself
off a cliff for Frank?
I have zero allegiance
to Frank Underwood.
I won't be manipulated by him, and I sure
as fuck won't be manipulated by you.
- I'm not bluffing.
- Then I was right.
- About what?
- How little I meant.
That has nothing
to do with this.
It has everything
I should feel disgusted,
but I don't.
Just supremely disappointed.
We got the call ten minutes ago,
direct from the White House counsel.
The president's
turning over everything?
- From the day he took office.
- We're sure this includes
- the visits to his friend?
- It has to.
- It was full-security detail.
- Phenomenal.
We have something
we can work with.
- Now, as for my logs.
- They're clean.
- You bet your life on that?
- I would.
- Me too, sir.
- We've been through them twice,
- backward and forward.
- My statement?
- In your inbox.
- I looked it over. Seth did a nice job.
We need to go wide with this
the moment the interview's over
so we beat Dunbar to the punch in
case she decides to release something.
I'll be at my computer ready to press
send the moment I hear from Doug.
- Have either of you slept?
- We're awake, fully operational.
You take a shower
and put on a fresh suit.
Yes, sir.
I'll see you over there.
You have at least three hours.
Take a nap.
You can use my office.
General McGinnis was in the courtroom
when you testified.
- Yes. - Had you seen him in person,
I mean, since he assaulted you?
- No.
- What was that like?
- Not fun.
- Not fun how?
It was hard. Really hard.
Look, Megan, I agreed to change
the focus of my piece
to focus on you, and, you know,
I know this has gotta be hard,
but I need you to help me
out a little bit.
I'm sorry, I'm not
very good at this. I'm nervous.
You seemed fine when you called
into Mrs. Underwood's interview.
She was there with me,
on the phone.
Your nerves, I know that's been
an issue since the assault.
The defense brought up what they
called emotional and mental instability.
That's what always happens.
The person who was attacked
gets attacked all over again.
- How did that make you feel?
- It made me angry.
The lawyer kept coming after me about
my panic attacks, my antidepressants.
But I just kept
staring at McGinnis.
I wanted him to see I could
take it. That I was strong.
- I wanted to make him look away first.
- And did he?
Yes, when I said he did
more than violate my body.
He betrayed his country.
He robbed it of a good Marine.
Let's talk about the sexual assault
bill in front of Congress now.
It's taken some significant opposition,
most notably from another veteran,
Jacqueline Sharp.
If you ask me, she's
betraying our country too.
- Ms. Dunbar.
- Mr. Vice President.
Thank you for giving us
a few extra days.
I have no problem being patient
as long as it leads to forthright answers.
Well, I won't make you
wait a moment longer.
Shall we?
Oh, you found it.
Have a seat, we're just
finishing up here.
What do you think, Mr. Tusk?
Keep growing it or have it shaved?
- I guess I'll keep growing it.
- No problem. Let me clean up the back.
No, Mack, if you'd give me
a couple minutes. Appreciate it.
I had this place built down here
about ten years ago.
I got tired of driving all the
way across town every two weeks.
- Now it's just an elevator ride.
- Convenient.
You know what isn't convenient?
Cramming eight attorneys in my office.
It was not designed for
the entire partnership of my law firm.
They're worried about Lanagin.
- He's a little shaky, but he'll hold up.
- Underwood?
Birch delivered.
- And did Dunbar bring up Stamper?
- The sessions are closed-door,
but I can't imagine she didn't.
And what about poor Havemeyer?
Was he any help to us on Jackie Sharp?
I do not take your hesitation
as a promising sign.
I never like disappointing you.
- He had nothing?
- No.
Hm...
Now, do you think that's
because there's nothing there,
- or because he's protecting her?
- There's nothing there.
- I can go to another congressman.
- No, no, no.
It has to be somebody
high-profile,
someone in the leadership
who will make waves.
- Let me get back to Birch.
- It's too obvious,
now that he's shown
no sympathy for Frank.
This can't look orchestrated.
Multiple fronts, Remy.
It has to be
Jackie Sharp. Mack?
Let's finish up here.
I gotta get back to work.
- You got it, boss.
- You need to get back to work too.
And what we discussed...
make it happen.
- You denied being a back channel.
- I did not deny.
I chose not to confirm
because it was classified.
- But your office has consistently...
- I instructed Doug to do so,
along with my communications department.
When a back channel becomes public,
- it defeats its purpose.
- An orchestrated deception...
If we had refused to comment,
it would've suggested it was true,
which would've endangered the
process. I really had no choice.
- Mr. Feng is currently in Dubai.
- I know.
He's fleeing corruption charges,
not the first time he's been accused.
- And your question?
- I know he laundered the money.
It's just a matter of time before
I have the proof to substantiate that.
So my question, which I am asking again,
is whether you knew?
And I'll repeat my answer.
I did not.
I did sense that something was awry.
Doug was aware of my concerns.
And I took it upon myself to find out.
The vice president didn't know.
You had no knowledge he was
going to the casino?
None. But that doesn't mean I don't take
responsibility for my staff's behavior.
- The buck stops with me.
- And what did you find?
Nothing.
No illegal activity.
I don't have the same
resources that you do.
If you suspected, why didn't you
go immediately to the NIGC, the BIA,
- the Department...
- You have to understand, we're facing
very difficult midterms.
I didn't want to bring attention
to a series of allegations that
may have no basis in fact.
Now, that may have been misguided
logic, but that's how I chose to act.
The mistake is mine and mine alone.
Not Doug's, certainly not the president's.
It shouldn't surprise you
if I say it feels
like I am not getting
the full picture.
Which is why I'm prepared
to give you the full picture. Oliver?
The White House believes
in transparency.
All of the vice president's
personal travel logs.
And the last ten years
since I became whip.
As well as the
president's since inauguration.
There should be no doubt
as to whom we met with and when.
- I am skeptical about what this contains.
- Which is what we anticipated,
and why Oliver will walk you through
anything you might need to know.
It's all there, but if you have any
questions or requests,
we'll be happy to facilitate.
I mean, at first,
I was really nervous,
but then, as soon as I
started getting into it,
started speaking from my heart,
all these things poured out,
everything I wanted to say,
that I've been wanting to say.
Seth told me that Matt
was very impressed.
- I want to do more.
- More interviews?
Articles, TV, whatever it takes.
- I want to help.
- That's great, Megan.
Thank you for making me do this.
- It was a big step for me.
- You have a plane to catch.
I can stay longer,
if you need me to do another.
Why don't you head
back to Chicago.
And as soon as we've put
a plan together, we can give you a buzz.
- Can I get a glass of water?
- Tap is fine, or you want bottled?
- I can get it.
- We've got Ms. Hennessey's car ready.
Edward.
Did she seem all right when
you picked her up from the airport?
- How do you mean?
- I don't know, normal?
Yes, I'd say so.
She's very up and down,
very skittish and manic.
I guess she did seem nervous.
We didn't talk much.
- I'll get her.
- I'll be outside.
Megan?
I've got it.
Really, I'm OK.
The car's ready,
whenever you are.
- Thank you for everything.
- Have a safe flight. I'll be in touch.
I just had a very productive
interview with Ms. Dunbar.
- Send out the press release.
- Thank you very much.
- You OK, ma'am?
- I'm fine. I just dropped...
- Please, let me.
- Oh, it's fine. I'm fine.
- I've got it. You're barefoot.
- Edward, you don't have to. Really.
- Oh, no, what happened?
- Damn it.
- Let me get some bandages.
- You don't have to.
No, I want to. Stay here.
The coverage has been
mostly positive so far.
- Dunbar's office? - All they've said is
they look forward to reviewing logs.
- Any heat on Doug?
- Some.
I'm getting a lot
of requests for comments.
I acted on my own and will fully cooperate
with the Justice Department.
- We can put that out?
- Sir?
- It might generate more interest.
- On me, not the vice president.
- I can handle whatever comes my way.
- Put it out.
I'll print you out the most
recent clips too, sir.
- Should I find a way to tip off Dunbar?
- Let nature take its course.
We got ahold of Remy.
He just got back to town.
- Where is he? - I've arranged
everything with your detail.
- You've done good work, Doug.
- Thank you, sir.
There, that's much better.
Thanks, ma'am.
I'm gonna get going.
- I'm sorry, I'm a little drunk.
- It's your house. You can
do whatever you want.
You should have a glass of wine.
I appreciate that,
ma'am, but I...
- You're off your shift, right?
- I am. That's true.
Then I won't
take no for an answer.
You shouldn't waste any
of your good stuff on me. I'm...
I don't really know
anything about wine.
Then how about bourbon?
I bet you'd like a little of that.
I definitely don't mind a
bourbon from time to time.
Then bourbon it is.
You're a tough man
to track down these days.
You got the watch?
"To improve is to change."
"To perfect is
to change often."
What sort of change
are you looking for?
- Whichever leaves me options.
- Trouble at Glendon Hill?
Paid leave until the
investigation is over.
Well, at least
you're being paid.
First step in terminating
my partnership.
You know how things go.
No matter what happens,
there's a stain I can't wash out.
So you're looking
for career opportunities.
I'm not offering myself
to you wholesale.
I keep fighting you,
but I can fight you less.
- And by "less" you mean...
- Enough to hurt, but not finish you.
And in return, I have a future
beyond Glendon Hill.
- Whatever that might look like.
- So you're offering neutrality.
- But you'll go with the victor.
- I figure let the best man win.
And if you go down, it won't be
because of me. That's worth something.
- Where's this coming from?
- Insurance, that's all.
Does it have anything to do
with Jackie?
That's over.
I know you've got Birch
in your pocket. Womack's not an option.
We're too close.
But Jacqueline...
This is about my future,
pure and simple. She's not a part of it.
Keep the watch,
as a token of good faith.
He might deny it,
but he's protecting her.
What he doesn't realize
is that I have even less regard
for Jackie than Raymond does.
Poor Remy.
The heart can choke the mind
when all its blood flows back unto itself.
He said, "I don't like
brunettes."
Looks like
I almost missed the party.
- I'm off the clock, sir.
- Oh, relax.
Francis, I broke a glass and
Edward cut his hand on a piece of it.
- Jesus!
- Oh, wow, it needs a change.
Take that off
and I'll get fresh...
I hope you don't mind, sir.
I was off duty...
- Is she...?
- Drunk? A little.
- How many of these have you had?
- A few.
More than a few.
- May I? Mm.
- Please.
Let me see.
It's not too bad.
- There's a lot of blood.
- Looks worse than it is.
Ow...
- Is it painful?
- The bourbon helps.
You let me know if this hurts.
Not one bit, sir.
- How's your head?
- Fine.
I took a couple of aspirin
before I went to sleep.
You?
I slept like a baby.
Good.
You needed that.
- What is it?
- Something weird.
- This one address keeps popping up.
- Underwood?
The president.
- Good morning, Meechum.
- Good morning, Mr. Vice President.
It's a beautiful day.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player