Previously on House of Cards...
The road to power is paved
with hypocrisy...
...and casualties.
Never regret.
- Somebody's tryin' to take you out?
- Appears that way.
Whoever it is, they done stepped on
the wrong motherfuckin' rattlesnake.
You help me repair
my relationship with Garrett,
Dan and I here get the money
flowing back in the right direction.
How about this? I get the BIA
to investigate both of you.
You implicate us,
you implicate yourself.
He sent them this. Is that you?
You and I are just
pawns, Mr. Galloway.
- How about I tell the press...
- Adam, shut up!
We're giving you an out, Adam.
And if you choose not to take it,
I will bury you.
My gut says there's more to
Xander Feng than has been reported.
It's a far better use of my time
than reporting on tabloid sex scandals.
- You scared of this?
- Darnell!
Hit 'em again, and hit 'em now.
We have to strike
back hard and fast.
More than that.
Let's make him suffer.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Look at that, Cashew.
Someone's being a bad boy.
"Do not grieve
the Holy Spirit of God,
by whom you were sealed
for the day of redemption.
Let all bitterness and wrath
and anger and clamour,
and evil speaking be put away
from you with all malice.
And be kind to one another,
tenderhearted,
forgiving one another."
Do you want me to keep going
with this, or something else?
Doesn't matter to me.
I just like hearing you read it.
Doug, there's something
I need to talk to you about.
You said that she was
just staying for a few nights.
Her roommate kicked her out.
She doesn't have anywhere else to go.
- It's not our problem.
- I can't put her out on the street.
What's her name?
- Lisa.
- Lisa what?
You don't have anything
to worry about.
- Where is she now?
- At the fellowship.
There's a sleepover with some
of the kids from the day care.
Does she know about me?
No, I haven't told her anything.
I have given you space.
I trusted you, Rachel,
- and you've taken advantage...
- I'm not kicking her out.
- I could have said nothing,
but I told you. - I have to go.
She better be gone
by the next time we talk.
- Sir.
- What took you so long?
I can have a briefing ready
in five minutes.
Don't bother.
I had Seth do it.
He doesn't have
security clearance.
Well, he does now.
Mr. President, after you.
I'll see you in my office.
Japanese sovereignty
is a matter of precedent.
Mr. Prime Minister,
my concern is escalation.
Well, I'm asking for a small
portion of the 7th Fleet.
We must bring China into line.
Show them that the US and Japan
maintain a strong alliance.
Have you reached out
directly to Beijing?
No recognition that
the island belongs to Japan.
Well, I'd like to speak to my
team and formulate a plan.
- Thank you, Mr. President.
- Thank you, Mr. Prime Minister.
Admiral,
for those catching up...
Two Chinese destroyers
entered waters
within three miles
of Yonaguni Island here,
approximately six hours ago.
See how close the island is to Taiwan.
This is different than the standoff
over the Senkaku Islands.
It could have to do
with shipping routes.
Or the trade war.
They can't pick on the big kids,
so they're picking
on the little one.
- Do you see that?
- What?
In the alley, camera two.
All posts, white male,
hooded sweatshirt, duffel bag.
Southeast side of Fair St.
Put down the bag.
Put down the bag
and place your hands
on your head.
Stay right where you are.
Mrs. Underwood? Will you
come downstairs, please?
- Where's Francis?
- He got delayed at the White House,
there was an emergency meeting.
- What's going on?
- I'll explain in the safe room.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
The 7th Fleet is near Guam?
Ninety miles north. We could have
ships to Yonaguni in less than a week.
But even sending them in that direction will
be picked up by the Chinese satellites.
Well, we have to stand with our allies,
that can't be in question.
What if we don't send ships,
just make a strong statement
condemning their excursion
into Japan's territorial waters.
We still have to offer the Chinese
an incentive to call back their destroyers.
Whatever overtures we make, I'd like
to have contingency plans in place.
- Already drafting them, sir. - Cathy, open
up a diplomatic channel with Beijing.
See if there's a concrete ask, if they don't
have one, let's create a list of options.
- Right away, sir. - How about coordination
with the Japanese navy?
Go. Don't engage
with our navy yet.
I want to talk directly to Prime Minister
Oshiro and express our intentions.
Former marine. He showed up at the outer
perimeter with explosives in a duffel bag.
- And strapped to his body.
- Jesus.
We apprehended him,
the press isn't aware.
- Well, let's keep it that way.
- He claimed he was responsible
for sending the package
of white powder to the capitol.
So this time he really wanted
to take me out for real.
Not exactly. His wife got an abortion last
week without telling him.
- Oh, my God. It was me.
- Yes, you were the target.
We'd like to keep you
down here with us, Mrs. Underwood,
- until we confirm he was acting alone.
- I'll stay.
No, you have to get back
to the White House.
- I can work from here.
- Francis, I'm fine. Honestly.
I'm just gonna be in here.
I want you to stick with her at all times.
Keep me informed of everything.
He's almost done with his shift, sir.
I can put another agent on...
- No, I want it to be Meechum.
- Absolutely, sir. As long as necessary.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
It's OK.
Don't go to California.
Mm...
Be nice to be reelected.
You're gonna win.
Not if I don't give
the voters more face time.
When did you get it?
- The Army?
- Yeah.
It's grown since then.
Tell me about it.
No.
Why not?
I don't want to.
What are you doing?
Tell me about the tattoo.
- That's not fair.
- So what?
You think you can just get me
wet and I'll spill everything?
- I don't think so...
- Mm...
...I know so.
Tell me.
I like the pain.
- Of the needle?
- Yeah.
How bad did it hurt?
It hurt a lot.
You like when it hurts?
I killed a lot of people.
What?
In the Army.
The pain...
...it helped.
Finish.
The most I could find
was some wrangling with the EPA
when he opened his first plant,
but that was almost 40 years ago.
- We need more. I want Tusk gone.
- Doyle and I will keep looking.
If you haven't found anything now,
what makes you think you will?
Maybe we missed something.
I doubt it, but we could try.
You think Tusk isn't planning
his next attack even as we speak?
We've been thorough, sir.
He doesn't leave footprints.
You want to shift tactics?
The casino. We go public
as soon as possible.
You said that was a last resort.
Seth, you need to find a way
to make that happen
so it doesn't link to us.
If we launch that missile,
it could blow us up too.
Not if we spin it right.
- If we keep the focus on...
- Seth.
You're here to listen,
not contribute.
I wouldn't have him here if I
didn't want him to contribute.
Sir... he's been sitting
with this for three hours.
I've been working on it
for three months.
And accomplished nothing.
It's time we go on the
offensive.
- What do you think?
- Ayla Sayyad.
- She's already digging into Tusk and Feng.
- How close is she?
She never mentioned a casino,
but now that I know what the dots are,
I can see that she's
starting to connect them.
The Pentagon isn't talking yet.
I imagine they're
waiting on the White House.
I hear there have been regular meetings
in the Situation Room since last night.
Let me call you right back.
- Hello?
- Hey, Lynne, it's Ayla.
- I just sent you a picture.
- Yeah, I got it.
- What does it mean?
- It's strange, it doesn't make sense.
- Tell me. - "Pursue currency" would be
the most literal translation.
Or "pursue money."
- Follow the money?
- That could work.
Thanks, Lynne.
I like what you've done.
This sofa, it's new?
- These lamps as well?
- I've made a few changes.
You get so used to a place,
the smallest things stand out.
I apologize for not
being responsive sooner.
I've been focused
on the midterms.
Oh, there's no need to explain.
Mrs. Underwood, you know how
much I respect your intentions,
but I've thought
deeply about this and
I can't cosponsor the bill
in its current form.
Civilian oversight
is too extreme a step,
but I'd be happy to revisit some
of the other less extreme proposals.
You think we're being extremist?
I want to help with this issue,
but this bill goes through...
This bill is through Armed Services.
This bill has a date on the floor.
Almost every woman in the
House supports this bill.
- And I can't be one of them.
- So you lied to us.
I didn't lie. I didn't lie.
I... I want to help. As long as
we rethink some of the language.
Are you trying to distance yourself
from us because of the Galloway scandal?
- No.
- Maybe you think it hurts your chances
- of reelection if you associate with me.
- That's not it.
It's because I honestly don't
believe in this approach.
Do you realize
the message this sends?
The only woman in congressional leadership
in both parties, and you bow out?
If the bill goes to the floor as is, I won't
just bow out. I'll actively fight it.
You never asked my position.
You assumed.
I can't imagine
what that position must be.
I've served in war zones,
I know firsthand how important...
We're not talking
about war zones.
We're talking
about sexual assault.
How about a military commission
to review the internal...
We don't need more studies,
we need reform.
Well, let's continue this conversation
when I return from California.
I'll be back the day
after tomorrow if you change your mind.
I won't, but I hope
you change yours.
China was insulted at the notion that
we could buy them off.
Do I need
to call President Qian?
I doubt he would contradict
one of his ministers.
See if he's willing
to talk one-on-one.
You should know, sir,
Japan is also preparing
to deploy three destroyers
and a light cruiser.
They're upping the ante.
Have Ambassador Hines
get in touch with the prime minister,
and ask if Japan will
hold off until I make contact with Beijing.
Yes, sir.
Have you gotten any rest at all?
- No, have you?
- No, not yet.
How's Claire?
Secret Service thinks it's an isolated
attempt, but they're being cautious.
After the Galloway thing
and the interview,
half the country thinks
she's a baby killer,
or an adulterer, or both.
But Claire's taking it in
stride. We're in good hands.
That's very frightening.
I can see why you haven't slept.
One of us should, probably
the one that's calling all the shots.
No, I can hold out
a little while longer.
No, go to the residence,
spend some time with your wife.
You'll come back feeling
like a new man.
Honestly, it's less
stressful here.
- Counseling hasn't helped?
- No, it has... slowly.
- I got rid of Christina
when Linda resigned. - I heard.
It's improved things some,
but...
...there's
still work to do.
Makes me tired
just to think about it.
Well, you probably wouldn't be the
first president to get a little shut-eye
on one of these sofas.
- I was joking.
- I wasn't.
Do the free world a favor
and get some rest.
- I'll let you be.
- No, stick around.
You should be nearby if President Qian
wants to get on the phone.
I've always loathed
the necessity of sleep.
Like death, it puts the most
powerful men on their backs.
DC Limo and Bus Rental.
I'm calling from the Adohi
Casino's travel department.
We've got a corporate account.
Let's see...
I'm sorry,
we don't have one
in our records.
My mistake.
I must've called
the wrong limo service.
Thank you.
Missouri Bus and Limo.
I'm calling from the Adohi
Casino's travel department.
- You're not Darlene.
- No, Darlene is out sick.
I'm filling in for her.
My name is Pam.
How can I help you, Pam?
We've got a flight
coming in from China tomorrow.
We'll need some transportation.
How many you got coming?
I don't have the manifest
right in front of me.
- The usual?
- That's right.
- So a luxury bus.
- How many does that fit?
Fifty-five, usually about 20 come in.
Should be plenty of room.
That's great, thanks.
Do you think
it's really her conscience,
or because the
bill's controversial?
I don't think she would have
threatened to fight us
if all she wanted to do
was avoid controversy.
I'll talk to her.
I really want this bill to pass.
I know you do, so do I.
We need Jackie more
than ever, Francis.
I'm damaged goods,
this whole Adam thing.
No, you're not.
We fought past that.
Well, there's plenty of people
who still believe it's true.
We'll get it passed, I promise.
- No, thanks.
- Come on. It's no fun doing it alone.
We could just go for a run.
No more runs until the death
threats die down, that's the new rule.
But they let you go
to the office.
Because I was
in a bulletproof car.
Does this mean
we've officially not quit?
We've never been quitters,
have we?
Sir, Mrs. Underwood,
sorry to interrupt.
I was gonna head home,
but I'll stick around if you want me to.
Oh, no. You've been up long
enough. Get some sleep.
I'll be back first
thing in the morning.
Thank you for looking
after me today.
My pleasure, ma'am.
Sir, Mrs. Underwood.
- He's very dedicated.
- He is.
It's rare to find
someone like Edward.
- What?
- You never use his first name.
Oh, did I?
I don't feel right
talking about her like this.
It's just... technically,
she's my boss now.
- There's a certain protocol.
- This is coming directly from Doug.
Which means it's coming directly
from the vice president.
Well, um, I have seen Mr. Danton
around from time to time.
Do you know what he and the
congresswoman were discussing?
No, they were private meetings.
Do you have the appointment schedule?
I'd like to look at the dates.
These weren't formal appointments.
He just stops by.
Most of the time
pretty late at night.
Did the money
originate in China?
The money came
from tribal revenue.
As our FEC reports
clearly stated.
Let me rephrase.
Did any of that revenue
come from Chinese visitors
who gambled at your casino?
We have visitors
from all over the world.
I'm speaking specifically about
a businessman named Xander Feng.
I have no idea who that is.
I'm looking at FAA
flight records that show
a private plane he owns
making numerous trips
to Kansas City. And I spoke
with Missouri Bus and Limo,
which has transported Chinese
visitors to your casino.
- Ms. Said...
- Sayyad.
Ms. Sayyad, the only reason
I returned your call
was because you work
for The Telegraph.
It's not every day that I get a call
from a paper as big as yours.
But I don't know what you're trying
to get at here, so if you'll excuse...
What about Raymond Tusk?
- What about him?
- Feng has ties to Tusk.
Tusk has ties to the president.
You have ties to Feng.
That looks like foreign money
being used to influence political...
What you're insinuating
is not only wrong,
- it's libelous.
- Not if it's true.
I won't bat an eyelash
getting my attorneys involved.
Tusk made the same threat.
If a man worth 40 billion
dollars doesn't intimidate me,
you certainly don't,
Mr. Lana...
Hello?
He hung up.
I had nothing
to do with it, Raymond.
I can smell the horseshit
through the phone.
You think I'd put
myself at this great a risk?
Desperate men
are capable of anything.
- I want it to go away, just like you do.
- Then pull her back.
I have no control
over the press, Raymond.
You'll destroy
yourself, Frank, not me.
Thank you for that
unsolicited advice.
Work with Doyle,
make sure we have no weak spots.
- I'll call him now.
- What did Nancy say?
Well, it looks like Jackie may
be sleeping with the enemy.
Lanagin is correct in saying
we run the risk of libel.
These links
are supported by fact.
Individually, but you can't
complete the circle.
I'm not saying the
headline should read:
Money Laundering Scheme Exposed!
Just that we present the
landscape as we currently know it.
We're first and foremost
a financial paper.
Many of our readers
worship Raymond Tusk.
So we just protect him?
We don't insinuate
connections we can't back up.
If there's any basis for litigation, you
can be sure his team will be aggressive.
They've bankrupted
papers before.
I think you should slow down and take
your time. When, and if, you have a story...
Mr. Maxfield,
Raymond Tusk is on the line.
- Did you put in a call to him?
- Yesterday.
He's specifically
asking for you, sir.
We got off the phone
with Lanagin less than 30 minutes ago.
That means Tusk was the
first call Lanagin made.
Tell him I'll return.
Did you reach out to the White House?
They're not talking to anyone
until after the president
does his press briefing
tomorrow.
All right, walk me through
all of this again,
point by point.
- Meechum.
- We can talk tomorrow, sir.
No. What is it?
I'd like to put in a request to
be on your wife's detail full time.
At least until the death threats
quiet down.
That's very thoughtful.
I'll only do it if you approve,
sir.
- Have you spoken to Claire?
- When she came home.
- She likes the idea.
- Then I think we should do it.
I'll let Agent Rockland know.
Sorry for interrupting you, sir.
You didn't interrupt anything.
- Good night, sir.
- Good night, Meechum.
- Hey.
You'll never believe
what just happened.
- What?
- Meechum came into the office
and found me
watching something...
- ...other than the news.
- Oh!
- Oh, no.
- He was very professional about it.
- Were you...?
- No, no. I was just watching.
That's really funny.
What about you?
What are you watching?
The video Connor gave me.
It's our first state senate race.
I forgot about that.
So did I, until I found it
in the desk this morning.
Let me see.
...been there, like I have.
Of course, it doesn't hurt to
have a little Texas in them...
My God, look how young we are.
I know.
Everyone here has been
so kind, and so welcoming.
We'll have her rooting
for Clemson before too long.
That's where
I have to draw the line.
Do you miss being with Adam?
Where did that come from?
Miss it? No.
Well, you must, sometimes.
He meant a lot
to me for a while.
But that's done now.
What about you?
What about me?
Are you unsatisfied?
There's just
too much at stake now.
No one we can trust.
We don't have
the freedom we once did.
Maybe it's better this way.
No room for distractions.
I don't mind the sacrifice.
We chose this instead.
I think the one thing
we can agree on
is the ribs here are better.
See, he's just trying
to get under my skin.
No, it's not even debatable...
- How was California?
- Oh...
Exhausting.
Twelve events in two days.
- Is this the Golden Gate?
- Yes.
I had an etching right there.
The capitol before it was finished.
Took 85 years to complete it.
- How long did it take to
complete the bridge? - About four years.
It opened a few months
after FDR's second inaugural.
There was a man
who got things done.
Strong beliefs
and he stuck to them.
But compromised when he had to.
I assume you're here
to talk about Claire's bill.
It's not a pet project.
There are three dozen
cosponsors on either
side of the aisle.
- It's a serious bill.
- I don't disagree.
- Except with the language.
- I can explain my thinking,
but I doubt I'll convince you
anymore...
Putting aside the military's
honor, chain of command,
all the things
that you hold dear...
...let's consider
one simple fact.
You wouldn't have this office
if it weren't for me.
I made very clear
that I wouldn't be a puppet.
I'm not trying to pull strings,
but you could show a little gratitude.
If it were anything else,
Mr. Vice President... but not this.
All you're doing is making
the inevitable more difficult.
It's not inevitable. Claire
doesn't have the votes yet.
You really want
to fight us on this.
I don't want
to fight you at all.
Which is why I suggested to
Claire that we sit down...
I neither have the time
nor the inclination to negotiate with you!
Cosponsor the bill, whip
the damn votes, I'm no longer asking.
Then I'm no longer listening.
You don't have just this office
to thank me for.
If you win reelection,
you can thank me for that, too.
Those attack ads didn't just
disappear on their own.
- What do you mean?
- Why don't you ask Remy Danton.
And ask him about Raymond Tusk
while you're at it.
That ought to make for some very
interesting pillow talk.
You keep up the good work,
Nancy.
I will, Mr. Vice President.
I miss having you around,
but you're my eyes and ears now,
otherwise I'd steal
you back in a heartbeat.
Well, thank you, sir.
It means a lot to me that you say that.
- Doug?
- I'm busy.
The story just broke.
They timed it with
the president's press conference.
Connect me with
the vice president.
So the 7th Fleet is
currently positioned near Guam,
where it will remain if China removes
its ships from Japan's sovereign waters.
I've been in frequent touch
with prime minister Oshiro,
and have made personal
overtures to President Qian.
And I remain optimistic
that tensions will be quelled
without any further escalations.
So, with that, I'll take some questions.
- Henry, you first.
- Can you comment
on the Wall Street Telegraph
article...
I was just notified of that
moments before I joined you.
I haven't had a chance to read
it yet. Yeah, Jane.
Mr. President, would
you walk us through
your history with Raymond Tusk?
I'm here to answer questions on
Sino-Japanese relations. Mark.
The article mentions Xander Feng, a wealthy
and influential Chinese business...
Unless this has to do with the
statement I just made...
It does, Mr. President.
Feng has ties
to the standing committee
and we're currently in a
standoff with the Chinese.
Economically...
Thank you all very much.
It's not beginning the story
that I fear,
it's not knowing
how it will end.
Everyone is fair game now,
including me.
This is par for the course, what we've
come to expect from President Walker.
Whenever he's selling a shiny
new car, he can't say enough about it.
The engine breaks down,
the transmission gives out,
he dodges, he ignores the warranty.
I'm gonna tell you something,
our warranty is the Constitution of the
United States,
and there's no limit on that.
He needs to read the fine print
and start answering
our questions.
If any of this is true, we're
talking Congress, the White House,
both parties...
Now, I'm saying "if,"
but when it look like dirty money,
and it smells like dirty money,
somebody has probably got dirt
under their nails.
Look, there's no real proof
this money laundering is even...
The connections are troubling,
especially Underwood.
He was the House whip the entire time
Adohi were contributing to the Democrats,
and he's working side by side
with the president now.
The president. So this goes all
the way to the White House?
- It might.
- It's hypothetical. And by the way,
you've cherry-picked the facts
to make your case.
I'm not making a case.
PAC Money Raises Questions.
And it has.
I haven't answered
those questions,
but I think the American people
deserve answers. Don't you?
You can bet your bottom dollar
the attorney general is gonna investigate.
- With the firestorm this is causing in
the media... - What's our course of action?
As your counsel, I would encourage you
not to speak to the press
until we have more information.
As your average citizen,
the longer you wait,
the more suspicious it looks.
If there's been any irregularity,
I had nothing to do with it.
Your friendship with Tusk
implies guilt by association.
Are we presuming guilt
before innocence?
I'm a lawyer, I presume nothing.
But public opinion
doesn't have a law degree.
Give us a few moments.
I have to advise you not to have
any conversation about this matter
- without me present.
- Your advisement has been noted.
I'll be right outside.
Is this what you were keeping
from me?
We should follow
your counsel's advice
- and not...
- Tell me if it's true, about the money.
With Bill out of the room,
we open ourselves up to...
Damn it, Frank! I've been in the dark
too long on this. That ends now.
I don't know any details.
Feng told me if the Bridge
project got approved,
the GOP would stop getting money.
We approved it, the money stopped.
Jesus Christ, that connects
the White House directly to the money.
No, sir. You knew nothing,
you still know nothing.
If the DOJ finds any concrete
evidence of foreign money...
That's Raymond Tusk's head,
not yours. You've done nothing wrong.
Guilt by association, Frank.
You heard the man.
If the DOJ investigates,
it will only prove your innocence.
Nobody walks away from something
like this without bruises.
Well, bruises you can survive.
I just don't know how we can
avoid it at this point.
Unless you want to accelerate
the process and get rid of it.
We could always have the attorney
general appoint a special prosecutor.
- That's a terrible idea.
- Maybe so.
And given where we are, Frank, I'm not
inclined to follow your suggestions.
Well, I wasn't suggesting it was
something you should do.
Just as a possibility.
No, in fact, I don't think you should.
I think it's better to drag these
things out as long as possible.
- Let the public fatigue on it. - And have it
hanging over our heads until the midterms?
- It'll lose steam.
- What if it doesn't.
I've got the Pentagon proposing tactical
drone strikes in the South China Sea.
I can't be dealing with
something like this for months on end.
Maybe you're right then.
A special prosecutor is the way to go.
I didn't say that, you did.
Oh, no. I just meant in terms
of getting it off your plate.
It wouldn't be on my plate
if you kept me better informed.
I have done nothing but try
to insulate you, sir.
Is that what you call the feeding frenzy
I just went through?
I make this solemn promise
to you, Mr. President.
I will take the fall
if it comes to that, but it won't.
However you decide to deal with this,
I think your instincts are right.
We probably shouldn't
involve a special prosecutor.
Send Bill back in.
You knew about this.
Tusk is a client,
doesn't mean I know everything...
Bullshit. The reason you're
a partner at Glendon Hill
is because you know the
things nobody else does.
What do you want me to say?
- Is it true?
- We don't talk about work.
We're not in bed,
we're in my fucking office.
And in here, you work for Frank.
- I work for no one but myself.
- Keep telling yourself that.
Unlike you, I don't peddle my goods
for whoever can pay the highest retainer.
I'm the bitch to a lot of top dogs,
I'm fully aware and willing,
but you're worse. You're Frank's bitch
and refuse to believe it.
- That's not true.
- Case in fucking point.
Don't turn this. You knew about
the money and you didn't tell me.
Even though it's thrown
my seat into contention.
Let's say there was money,
and let's say I did know,
- what good would it have done? - It means
you were willing to watch me lose!
It means I respected the
boundaries that you demanded.
- No changes, no special treatment.
- This is different!
- So now we're making exceptions?
- When it's this important, yes!
You can't have it both ways.
Were you...?
Was I what?
...fucking me
to get info on Frank?
- Is that what you think?
- I don't know what to think.
I care about
you more than I should.
But I'm getting tired
of having to say it.
He's being moved to a federal psychiatric
facility for assessment.
Then a high security detention center
until the official sentencing.
Well, that's good to hear.
The bad news is we don't want
you doing any public events for a while.
My bill's about to go to the floor.
I need to have a public profile.
Your death threats continue to
rise. We can't take the risk.
- Am I even allowed to leave the house?
- Of course.
But we want you
to avoid large crowds.
Our ability to protect...
Mr. Vice President.
- Anything wrong?
- We were just briefing Mrs. Underwood
on her new security protocol.
- Can we actually finish this later?
- Of course.
How did it go?
- He's skeptical.
- Should I call Tricia?
No. It could look like
I was trying to go behind his back.
We'll just have to wait and see.
I made my case.
Hopefully,
he'll disagree with it.
But this could've
been the wrong move.
Well, don't doubt yourself.
Seth has gotten over 3,000
e-mails in the last six hours.
- The phones are overloaded.
- So you ignore all that?
I can't ignore
the Department of Justice.
What can I do?
Come and visit me
when I'm in prison.
You don't have
to stand by that door.
Take a load off.
Thank you, sir, but I'm
supposed to stay on my feet.
Well, I won't tell if you won't.
And if anybody gives you
any trouble about this,
or anything,
they can talk to me.
- Beautiful night.
- Yes, sir.
It's been strange not having
you around these last few days.
You want me to switch back
to your detail?
No, no. I'm glad
you're with Claire.
I just...
...didn't realize how much I got used
to your company until you were gone.
Protecting her is the same
as protecting you, in my mind.
Oh, come on.
- Why do you do this?
- Do what, sir?
I've always been awestruck,
people who are willing
to take a bullet for someone else.
- That's how I serve my country.
- Well, there's a lot of ways
to serve your country.
And this is my way.
- I haven't finished with this one yet.
- It's not for you.
I can't drink on duty, ma'am.
It's not for you either.
Well, come on over
and join the party.
Haven't you got sick
of seeing my face yet?
Never, ma'am.
To Meechum,
for his loyalty and service.
To Edward.
I'm on my way
to my lawyer's office, Remy.
That's not where I want to be
when I'd usually be in bed.
I can't stop Frank
from leaking things.
No, but you can make sure
he suffers more than us.
And I say "us," Remy, because
your skin is in this game now, too.
- Are you gonna deny?
- Of course I'm gonna deny.
Every step of this was legal.
They can't prove
the links between them.
- What about Lanagin? - He'll cooperate.
It's Feng we need to worry about.
I'll find a way
to get in touch with him.
We do have one major advantage.
The public can hate me,
but as long as Clayton West
remains profitable, my
stockholders won't care.
Frank doesn't
have the same liberty.
Public opinion can demolish him.
You need to make sure that happens.
I can work with
the Republicans on that.
Well, we'll be under the
magnifying glass too.
This will be a witch hunt.
I'll make sure that they pick
the right targets.
What you need to do
is go after the leadership.
Make them hurt. They'll turn on
Frank to save themselves.
Birch, Womack, Sharp.
Especially Jackie Sharp.
She's his chosen one.
- Remy?
- I heard you. I got my marching orders.
- I'm counting on you.
- I'll deliver.
Let's talk in the morning.
The two names I like the most
are Justin Gaines and Heather Dunbar.
Gaines has better credentials.
But he's close
to the administration.
I would've made him
a federal judge
if the GOP hadn't blocked it.
That's an important point.
Dunbar's got grit.
- She's more than qualified.
- No baggage there?
- She's more unpredictable.
- I doubt the attorney general
would've put her on his list
if he thought she was a wild card.
Sir, I have to say,
I think this step is premature.
We should hold off and see what
the DOJ does on its own.
I don't want to do it,
Bill, but my fear is this:
if we wait until the water
goes from hot to boiling,
we seem reactionary,
not proactive.
But proactive could
also seem defensive.
Like the suspect that screams
"I didn't do it" before anyone asks.
Aside from that, we simply
haven't had time to prepare.
- Maybe wait a couple of weeks.
- That defeats the purpose.
- Then a few days.
- I'd like to go with Dunbar.
- Sir...
- I've made my decision.
Bill, I'd like you to convey my
wishes to the attorney general.
Ultimately, the decision is his.
We can't appear to be pressuring him.
- Of course not.
- Thank you, sir.
The only thing more satisfying
than convincing someone to do what I want,
is failing to persuade them
on purpose.
It's like a "Do Not Enter" sign,
it just begs you to walk through the door.
Doyle's about halfway
through our initial background check.
Every donor,
every political event.
Everything that Dunbar
might be looking into.
- Good. Seth?
- We avoid any official statement,
follow the president's cue.
In the meantime, I'd like to
make some off the record calls.
You welcome the investigation,
it's the right step, et cetera.
Give folks the personal touch.
That's fine, as long
as we don't come off defensive.
I'd like to see a list
of who you'd be calling.
Some of this is gonna be
on the fly,
it'd be great
if I had a little leeway.
Let Seth do his thing, you'll
have your hands full with Doyle.
I'll let you know
who I've called.
All right, let's get to work.
Sir?
Yes, what is it?
I understand that
you need to delegate,
but when you contradict me
in front of Seth,
it compromises
my authority over him.
You can't micromanage,
we have too much to do.
Seth is still new to the team.
I need to make sure that
he's doing his job properly.
- Well, I think he is.
- I'm your fail-safe, sir.
But I can't be that
if you won't let me.
Are you, Doug?
- My failsafe?
- Do you doubt that?
We're flying full throttle
into a hurricane,
and you're talking
office politics
instead of focusing on making
sure we don't get ripped apart.
You're right, sir.
I shouldn't have brought it up.
- Is she still there?
- Yeah.
I told her I was
going for a walk.
Look, Doug, I know you said you wanted
her gone, but you have to understand...
She can stay.
- What?
- She doesn't have to leave, she can stay.
I trust you to be smart.
Will you read to me?
- My Bible's inside.
- Doesn't have to be the Bible.
Just pull up something
on your phone.
- Like what? - A Tale of Two Cities.
My mom used to read it to me.
"It was the best of times,
it was the worst of times,
it was the age of wisdom,
it was the age of foolishness,
it was the epoch of belief,
it was the epoch of incredulity,
it was the season of Light,
it was the season of Darkness,
it was the spring of hope,
it was the winter of despair,
we had everything before us,
we had nothing before us,
we were all going
direct to Heaven,
direct the other way."
Hello?
Doug, is that you?
Doug?
Yes, Doug, it is you.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player