Previously on House of Cards...
I have never known anyone
more honest, ethical,
and patriotic
than Garrett Walker.
- You set me up, Frank.
- Let's say
that what the president
has accused me of is true.
Would that be so bad?
My enemies want me dead. You're asking
me to give them confirmation.
And we're giving you
safe haven in return.
This is a one-time
offer, Mr. Feng.
My client exercises his right
to plead the Fifth Amendment.
Did you ever use these contributions
to bargain for political favors?
My client exercises his right
to plead the Fifth Amendment.
Having trouble starting it?
She needs to be gone.
But you said you didn't care
if she was here.
I don't need to explain myself.
I don't want you here! OK?
I don't love you the way
that you love me!
What I don't think is brave is
Claire Underwood
dodging this debate and having
you fight this battle for her instead.
I'm actually working with
her now. I'm withdrawing the bill.
After what she did to me?
Maybe Jackie Sharp is right,
you are a fucking coward.
- But he prescribed us medication.
- Have you mentioned it?
The medication?
our president is seeking
psychological treatment,
and chose to hide this
from the American people.
I believe our colleagues
in the House certainly
have enough to consider
articles of impeachment.
What you're asking
is just shy of treason.
Just shy, which is politics.
We have a president
who not only took
mind-altering medication,
a man who has his finger on the button
while US ships
are squaring off with China,
but then instructed his White
House counsel to coach a...
- Allegedly, sir, not proven.
- To coach a witness.
Which is behavior either
resulting from the use of those drugs,
or worse, a deliberate attempt
to obstruct the law.
Wouldn't you call
either scenario impeachable?
That's for the United States
Congress to decide, sir, not me.
Were you aware that the president
was taking any form of medication?
- No, I was not. - Did you notice him
acting in a bizarre fashion?
- Unstable, incoherent?
- No, sir.
- Any odd behavior?
Not even firing his chief of staff
in the midst of a trade war?
He didn't fire me. I resigned.
- Would you tell us why?
- I resigned because I felt
I could no longer serve the president
to the best of my ability.
And what changed? How did you
come to that conclusion?
I had some fundamental
differences of opinion
with certain people
in the White House.
- Like who? The president?
- No, sir.
What "certain people" then?
One person, actually.
The vice president.
- Frank Underwood.
- He wanted you gone?
I can't speak as to what
the vice president did or didn't want.
Was he trying to hide anything?
Was he afraid you might expose something?
You'd have to ask him, sir.
What's happening in the
Judiciary Committee is a farce.
- The Republicans are exploiting...
- Excuse me, Mr. Vice President,
but it's not just Republicans.
A number of Democrats have come out
saying they would support impeachment.
Including the majority whip,
Jackie Sharp.
Which is egregious, since the committee
hasn't stopped hearing testimony,
nor has the special prosecutor
completed her investigation.
You vigorously
defend the president,
but there are reports that
you've had a falling out,
- that you haven't spoken in weeks.
- That is simply not true.
I've spoken to senior staff
at the White House
who say the president is worried
you want to run against him in 2016.
And just today Linda Vasquez
intimated that you...
Look, I fully expect that
the president will run in 2016,
and I hope that he's generous
enough to invite me to be his running mate.
Impeachment, conviction,
let's say it happens.
It won't.
He's completely innocent.
Let's say it does happen.
You become president...
That is not a scenario
I'm going to entertain.
The thought must
have crossed your mind.
And one could make the argument that the
president wouldn't be in this predicament
if it weren't for you. It's your staff's
involvement with Feng and Lanagin
that expanded Dunbar's
investigation,
- which resulted in the travel logs...
- These impeachment hearings
are the result
of political maneuvering, not...
Your maneuverings,
or the Republicans?
Morley, I've always liked you.
You ask the tough questions.
And you can certainly
question my judgment,
but do not question
my patriotism.
I serve this nation
and my president, not myself.
- He's lying through his teeth.
- What we're doing is working.
We keep the whisper
campaign alive.
We spin him as power hungry,
as duplicitous.
- Focus attention on him, not you.
- What's the latest?
- Twenty percent? - Zogby has you at 24.
Your speech made a difference.
The approval numbers
are moving in the right direction.
We need to do more
than play the spin game.
We need to destroy Frank.
Offer his head instead of mine.
- We use Raymond Tusk.
- How?
At his hearing.
When he goes to the judiciary.
Sir, you're already being
accused of coaching one witness.
- If you take steps to coach another...
- Not coaching. The truth.
Raymond admits
to the money laundering,
puts Frank at the center of
this, and says I knew nothing.
And then we'll reward him
for his honesty.
You mean a pardon?
- I want you to talk to him.
- And put myself at risk?
You're not part of this
administration anymore.
There's no law that says you can't
pay Raymond Tusk a visit.
And in return, resignations
don't have to last forever.
If I do this, you have to be
a million miles away.
Tricia and I will
go to Camp David.
It's not a million miles away,
but it'll do the job.
I can go after Linda,
dig into her past...
Neutralizing her won't
neutralize the bigger problem.
- The president is after blood.
- Then what's his move?
He can't ask me to resign,
he'd have to force me out.
And to do that, if I were him...
...I would return
to the hand that first fed me.
- Raymond Tusk?
- Exactly.
He'd have to implicate himself
to implicate you.
Not if he gets a pardon.
It's the one thing that only
a president can offer.
Tusk is a hand grenade.
If he pardons him...
You're right.
Tusk is a hand grenade.
We need to pull the pin
and throw him at Walker
before Walker pulls the pin
and throws him at us.
I want to meet with Raymond.
One-on-one.
Let me speak on your behalf.
That way if anyone finds out...
I know Raymond. He won't
respond to anyone but me.
- When's his hearing scheduled?
- Day after tomorrow.
- Two p.m.
- That gives us...
- ...40 hours to make it happen.
- Yes, sir.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
I think it's mine.
Seth, it's four in the morning.
- When?
- I want you to go with her.
I'll get it cleared right now.
Thank you.
Meechum says the plane
will be ready in 30 minutes.
- OK, good.
- Think it was just a panic attack,
- or was she really trying...
- I don't know.
It was bad enough they felt
they had to keep her overnight.
I'm gonna call the White
House physician's office,
- see if they can recommend anyone.
- OK.
- Oh, wait, my phone.
- It's in your hand.
I'll be back sometime tonight.
Impeachment is our only chance.
Here are the seats that are still in
contention in the midterms.
These 13 we're gonna lose, no matter what
we do. But even if we win all the rest,
that only leaves us
with a five-seat majority.
We either save the party
or we save the president.
Anyone who votes
against impeachment
is gonna get pummeled by attack ads
between now and election day.
- How many do you have already?
- We need 18.
- I have six.
- So 12 more to go.
Look, Donald,
I know this is a big ask,
- and you prefer to focus on policy...
- Jackie, you can stop.
- I'm on board.
- Really?
One hundred percent.
I have to say
I'm a little surprised.
When you rolled those dollies
into the cloakroom,
you said, "Work with me,
I'm not Frank Underwood."
And then you helped get my stimulus
package through, just like you promised.
And what do you
expect this time?
That you never
become Frank Underwood.
You must realize, if we're successful,
he will replace Walker.
I don't like Frank, but I hate being in
the minority even more.
We can't let the Republicans control
both houses of Congress.
You've changed
since I joined the leadership.
Just getting better
at playing the game.
I guess you can teach
an old liberal new tricks.
I guess so.
So tell me who you still need.
My lawyers are saying
fifty-fifty that I survive a trial.
Now, I'm not a big fan of those
odds, but I'm willing to take them.
If your lawyers are
putting it at a coin toss,
then you're paying them too
much to be overly optimistic.
How can I trust Garrett? He turned his
back on 20 years of friendship.
He could accuse you of the same.
Nobody on this planet wants to see
Frank Underwood go to jail more than I do.
I just don't want to be
sharing a cell with him.
That won't happen.
All you've given me
to go on is Garrett's word.
He's asking you
to tell the truth.
Good things happen to those
who do the right thing.
And you just expect
Frank to lie down, throw in the towel?
We don't even give him the chance.
Your testimony knocks him out cold.
Excuse me.
Yes? Oh, thank you.
Hold on.
There you go.
Care package, from my wife.
Now, you were saying.
I just want to warn you,
she's not herself right now.
They had to put her
on some heavy doses.
- Of what?
- Lithium, mostly.
It was either that
or commit her for 30 days.
She just took some,
so she might be a little...
Megan?
Stop.
Your mom told me
they found you in the lake.
- What do you care?
- I care very much.
No, you don't.
You don't use
somebody you care about.
Whore.
Slut.
Bitch.
Traitor.
That's what they call me,
in my mail, online.
I wish I had never called.
I wish I had never met you.
I feel so stupid, believing what you
told me, thinking that you did care.
I was getting better.
You did this to me.
Every time I take one
of these, I think of him.
And the next face I think of?
It's yours.
I'm sorry that you felt used.
You weren't.
I just, um...
Like I told you, the political
landscape shifted and we...
...found...
Megan?
- Hello?
- I got your text.
I know I shouldn't be reaching
out to you, but I thought...
No, that doesn't matter.
I'm glad you did. How is she?
In bad shape.
I'm surprised they even let her
out of the hospital, to be honest.
Is there anything I can do?
Should I contact her family,
or go out there myself?
We should probably
leave her alone.
- Are you OK?
- I'm fine.
- How about you?
-  Holding up.
I spent the whole day
talking to lawyers.
It's hard on the kids.
They're embarrassed, and
frightened, but we'll get through it.
I thought the speech you
and Garrett gave was very moving.
Well, it seems
to have helped some.
I was inspired by you, actually.
When you admitted
to the abortion on TV.
The truth is a powerful thing.
Tricia, I want... to apologize.
What for?
I feel partly responsible
for everything
your family is going through.
It was my suggestion
that you get counseling.
And had I known then,
I never would have said a word.
Claire, please.
Counseling was a godsend.
Garrett and I needed help, and it's made
things better. I should be thanking you.
And thank you for letting me
know about Megan.
It was kind of you
to make that trip.
You're a good person, Claire.
Be well.
I take it
this is about my hearing?
Did Walker get to you first?
Barely.
But sometimes barely is enough.
I'm sure he
offered you a pardon.
Always better to offer something
your competitor can't.
- Oh, but I can.
- Hm.
Last time I read the Constitution,
the most a vice president could offer
was a... smile and wink.
I think I've proven that I'm
not your typical vice president.
Typical or not,
you've lost, Frank.
I have an out. You don't.
Garrett will not
survive impeachment.
If there's one skill you can't deny,
it's my ability to whip votes.
In the House, not in the Senate.
Which the Constitution
makes me the president of.
And you saw what
I did with entitlement.
Hubris is giving you delusions
of grandeur, Frank.
Let's say Walker squeaks by.
Yes, you get your pardon,
but you've bound yourself
at the hip to a man
- who has zero
political capital.
And if he gets convicted,
we all go to jail.
- There's no pardon for anyone.
- I'll roll the dice.
Raymond, think
like a businessman.
Haven't you built a fortune
by minimizing risk?
Isn't that why you stacked
Congress all these years,
why you guided Garrett to the Oval
and why you kept me on as whip?
Walker is a junk bond
quickly depreciating,
whereas I can end the conflict with
China and keep you in the black.
You can't promise better
relations with China.
I wrecked them,
I can repair them.
Now, let's work together,
as we always intended to do.
When they put you in that box
barely bigger than a coffin...
...remember how beautiful
the music was tonight.
It might give you
some small degree of comfort.
Puccini's a downer. I prefer
something much more optimistic.
- They won't touch
Brown. The trial date is set.
- They can reduce the charges.
- Dallas won't give.
If I keep pressing,
it'll start to look suspect.
What I can do is make sure
you don't get prosecuted.
- And I stop working for you.
- Not quite.
I told the US attorney that we
wanted to bring you on with us,
- cyberterrorism division. You'd get
a clean slate... - No fucking way.
They're not gonna let your case go
unless we give them a compelling reason.
- There's no...
- I've spent half of my life
- fighting the bureau.
- It's the only way I could sell it.
Take this opportunity, Gavin,
before they change their minds.
I want to meet
with Douglas Stamper.
No. The deal was
I find you a way out...
No, the deal was you help out
Brown and give me my freedom.
You haven't done shit for Brown and
you want me to keep me under your thumb.
So I meet Stamper,
or any kind of deal is off.
Raymond said no.
He said neither yes nor no.
I'll keep the pressure on.
- So he could still name you.
- He could. Anything's possible.
- You have to stop him.
- I'm trying.
Trying's not enough, Francis.
Well, I can't sit next
to him in the hearing room
with a gun to his head.
- That sounds like an excuse.
- It's a reality.
You promised me I wasn't going
to have to prepare for the worst.
- And I intend to keep that promise.
- Well, I want to be sure.
- I want both of us to be sure.
- The only surefire way
- is for Walker to call him off personally.
- Then make that happen.
I cannot force a man who thinks I'm
his enemy to suddenly call me his friend.
I've done what I had to do.
Now you do what you have to do.
Seduce him.
Give him your heart.
Cut it out and put it
in his fucking hands.
Dear Mr. President.
I'm writing you on an Underwood
portable my father gave me
when I left for the Sentinel.
It was the words my father said
when he gave it to me
that resonated even more
than this 70-year-old machine.
"This Underwood built
an empire," he said.
"Now you go
and build one of your own."
Those words have been a large part
of what has motivated my life.
I've only written one other
letter with these keys.
It did not fail me then.
I hope it will not fail me now.
You said I wanted
to diminish you.
The truth is I don't.
You said I wanted
to challenge you in 2016.
The truth is I don't.
You said I wanted
the presidency for myself.
The truth is... I do.
What politician hasn't dreamed
about what it would be like
to take the oath of the
highest office of our land?
I've stared at your desk
in the Oval and coveted it.
The power. The prestige.
Those things have a strong
pull on someone like me,
who came from a small South Carolina
town with nothing.
But since you assumed office,
my only aim has been to fight,
for you and alongside you.
Whether that be in Congress
or, as now,
the battle over impeachment.
Maybe one day I'll have my
chance to serve as president.
But not while you
are the nation's leader.
And in you, sir,
I see a brave man.
A just man.
A president whom
I would follow anywhere,
no matter how strong
the wind blows against us.
I want to tell you something
I have never told anyone.
When I was 13, I walked in
on my father in the barn.
There was a shotgun
in his mouth.
He waved me over.
"Come here, Francis," he said.
"Pull the trigger for me."
Because he didn't have the
courage to do it himself.
I said, "No, Pop," and walked out, knowing
he would never find that courage.
The next seven years
were hell for my father,
but even more hell
for my mother and me.
He made all of us miserable,
drinking, despair, violence.
My only regret in life
is that I didn't
pull that trigger.
He would've been
better off in the grave,
and we would have been
better off without him.
I'm not going to put you
in the same position
as my father put me in.
You will find enclosed,
on a separate sheet,
a confession to the crimes
you have been accused of.
They're false words, but my signature
will make them true.
Use them if you must.
If you truly believe
that I have only served myself,
then I have forever
lost your trust.
All I can do now is give you
my freedom to save your own.
I said I would
take the fall for you,
and now I give you the means
to make that happen.
I am pulling the trigger myself.
We all must make sacrifices
to achieve our dreams.
But sometimes we must sacrifice
ourselves for the greater good.
It is my honor to make
such a sacrifice now.
Your loyal friend, still in my
heart, if not in yours...
...Francis.
The Constitution sets forth
the general principle...
Sir, the president's
on the phone.
- Mr. President.
- I got your letter.
I had Tricia read it too.
I'm torn, Frank.
Half of me wants to think
you're genuine.
The other half
doesn't trust a word of it.
Does Tricia feel the same way?
She believes in Claire,
which inclines her to believe in you.
I meant every syllable.
I wanted you to know
beyond a shadow of a doubt
that I'm willing to do
whatever is necessary.
Then why can't
I shake the shadow?
Because I'm a liar, sir.
Because I lack scruples and some
would even say compassion.
But that's just the image
that I present to the world
because it elicits fear and respect.
But it is not who I am.
My hope was that my letter
would prove that to you.
Even if you are being genuine,
that doesn't do much for me.
I won't survive impeachment because
I got along with my vice president.
No, I agree you need more
than my good intentions.
Proof, that's what
I want to see, Frank.
Not just falling on the sword.
Show me results,
and then I'll reconsider whether
you're worth any of my trust at all.
- You're talking votes.
- Whipping votes is your strong suit.
That's the side
of you I want to see.
- I've already begun, sir.
- You have a count?
An approximation,
the sands keep shifting.
- Can we survive the House or not?
- Possibly. But Jackie Sharp
- is making it very difficult.
-  Give me numbers.
Over half of the 18
that she needs,
which is why I'd like to start
focusing on the Senate.
- Don't you think that's premature?
-  We should be prepared.
The key battle is making sure
that you avoid conviction.
You keep whipping,
you keep getting me information,
I'll answer your calls.
But don't take that as a sign
of reconciliation, Frank.
I'll sing for my supper, sir.
I don't expect it for free.
- Let's talk again tomorrow.
- Thank you, Mr. President.
- You said you wanted options.
- Frank didn't leave me options.
- He fucked me. - You fucked him first,
when you sided with Tusk.
But who cares what
happened each inning?
It's the final
score that counts.
Eight years I spent
busting my ass in this office,
- I can't seem to escape it.
- Are you going to help us or not?
- I need to know what I gain.
- You'll be taken care of.
Specifically.
We'll see what makes sense
when all the chips have fallen.
So you just want me to leap off a cliff
and hope for a soft landing beneath?
No one will touch you now.
Nobody except us.
We're as soft
as you're going to get.
- A job at the White House?
- No promises.
Other than something commensurate
with your loyalty and experience.
I could just walk away
from it all, start a new life.
No, you can't.
You know you can't.
You'd wither away anywhere
but the Hill.
It's never been about the money,
no matter what you tell yourself.
When I left,
Frank begged me to stay.
Power vs. money, he said.
Don't reduce myself to a tax bracket.
He was right.
And I doubt he begged.
He was half right. Power is better
than money, for as long as it lasts.
- But it never lasts.
- What's your answer?
You've gotten colder since
you've taken over this job.
It makes things easier.
- On the outside.
- And the inside.
I miss you, Jackie.
Tell me if you'll cooperate.
Excuse me one second.
Mr. President?
I want you to call
Tusk. Tell him the deal is off.
- What?
-  You were right.
I don't want to take the risk.
But I already spoke to him.
Well, so speak to him again,
and tell him there's no pardon.
Sir, I was skeptical
of this strategy at first,
but now that we've gone down
this road, we should stick to it.
Linda, do you
still want your job back?
- Of course, sir.
- Then make the call.
I'd rather see what happens in the House
before I get involved in any way.
But if you come out vigorously
in defense of the president,
it might convince
the judiciary committee...
To be honest, I'm not
particularly inclined
to be doing Walker any favors.
Now, Michael, I know
he revoked your nomination.
- He didn't fight for me at all.
- He had just been elected.
- He wasn't in a position...
- Wrong. He had a clear mandate.
He was in a strong position
to defend me.
You're right.
If I'd been president,
I wouldn't have
given in so easily.
I would've stuck by you after
that article came to light.
In fact, if you'd been our secretary
of state instead of Durant,
I don't think we'd be
in the mess we are with China.
The truth is I wouldn't have
nominated you
for secretary of state
in the first place.
I would have nominated you
for secretary of treasury.
Because your expertise
in economics
is even better than your grasp
on foreign affairs.
Now, if I were president,
you'd be secretary of treasury.
- If you were president.
- That's right.
You can't do this.
What happened?
Was it Frank?
Linda, listen to me...
I understand.
Thanks.
- The deal is off.
- Did she say why?
No. Other than
he changed his mind.
But it must be Frank.
- Then we go back to the original plan.
- That's right.
You plead the Fifth, just like you
did before. This is political theater.
- We get past it and focus...
- Jesus Christ.
- What is it?
- Remy Danton is volunteering
to testify to Dunbar, right now.
He volunteered?
He wasn't subpoenaed?
- Looks that way.
- He's going to sell me out.
That would open
him up to prosecution.
Unless he's being protected.
- Where's Danton?
- I'll call his assistant.
Did you or did you not
facilitate foreign money
being funneled into
political action committees?
On the advice of my counsel, I reserve
my right to invoke the Fifth Amendment.
Xander Feng claims you not only
facilitated, you orchestrated the scheme.
What is your response
to that testimony?
On the advice of my counsel,
I reserve my right...
You can reserve your right
all day long, Mr. Tusk.
But when you appear
in front of a grand jury,
as I'm sure the
justice department intends,
your silence will
be your downfall.
Does the Congressman
have a question?
You can hide from us all
you want, sir,
you cannot hide
from a jury of your peers.
- Mr. Chairman.
- That's it. I'm done.
I relinquish
the remainder of my time.
The chair recognizes the congresswoman
from Tennessee. You have 12 minutes, ma'am.
Mr. Tusk, our nation is currently
embroiled in a trade war with China.
It has gutted our economy.
It has placed our Navy
in harm's way.
- The president who put us there has...
- He knew.
- Excuse me?
- My client reserves the...
He knew. Isn't that what
you're all wondering?
- Quiet, please.
- Knew what, exactly?
There was a mechanism by which
a great many contributions were made
over the last ten years.
The legality of this mechanism
is something I continue to believe
is within the boundaries of the law.
But as for the mechanism itself, Mr.
Feng is correct.
I orchestrated it, I facilitated it,
and the President knew about it.
Danton just cancelled.
Screw Danton. We've got Tusk.
Get me the attorney general.
That won't be necessary, Mr.
Tusk, if you'll come with us.
That's a shame. Handcuffs were
another item on my bucket list.
Right this way, sir. You have
the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you...
We'll want a bond,
for his cooperation in the hearing.
I'll talk bonds
if you'll talk a plea.
Response to the testimony
has been swift and vocal.
Protesters have been gathering in
front of the White House since yesterday
demanding President
Walker's resignation.
And an online petition has already
accumulate over 200,000 signatures
in the past 24 hours.
The list of lawmakers
publicly condemning
the president has grown
on both sides of the aisle.
This afternoon, the Chinese
ambassador also condemned
the Walker administration,
saying China would not
negotiate with a president
who dealt
with corrupt businessmen
behind Beijing's back.
This at a time when warships
from both countries...
Meanwhile, the president and First Lady
remain bunkered at Camp David,
and have offered no public response to the
most recent developments in Washington.
I'm here with Ayla Sayyad
of the Wall Street Telegraph.
I have to begin by saying
that sources on the Hill are telling me
that the Judiciary Committee
may bypass debate altogether.
No one on the committee has
gone on record about that.
But do you think these rumors would be
circulating if there weren't some sort
of strong preference to recommend the
articles of impeachment to the House?
I think it's safe to assume
there is strong support.
Every poll I've seen shows
an overwhelming majority of Americans
want this to move forward. I don't think
politicians are going to ignore that.
I've talked to a number
of my colleagues already.
There is support on my side
of the aisle.
- How many do you have?
- Five at this point, including me.
That would put us at 60.
We'd still need seven more.
You've seen the overnight polls.
He's dipped down into the single digits.
Are you willing to make
a public statement with us?
I think the country could use a little
bipartisanship right now, don't you?
Do you think they're bluffing?
That it's some sort of stunt
to sway the undecideds
in the Senate?
Michael Kern is bitter
and small-minded, sir,
but he wouldn't have appeared publicly with
Mendoza if they didn't have the numbers.
I imagine we're worse off in
the House than we were before.
In fact, I had a very productive
conversation with Jackie Sharp.
She agreed to stop the attack
if we give her our support
for majority leader after the midterms,
but once Raymond gave his testimony,
she called to say
the deal was off.
Raymond really has set us back.
- I can't fathom why he lied.
- It's retribution.
- For what? The energy crisis?
-  No.
Did you offer him something?
Well, Raymond's testimony hurts,
but it can't finish us off.
It's impossible to prove a lie.
Impeachment is inevitable.
Public opinion is the adversary
now. Facts no longer matter.
You should give Kern a call.
The personal touch.
If he came back to us, it might make
the other Democrats get cold feet.
China isn't helping. President Qian won't
return my calls. Beijing must smell death.
They're just exploiting
the situation for leverage.
Let's not worry about China for the moment.
One battle at a time, sir.
Maybe I'm finished, Frank.
Maybe I need to start accepting
that we won't pull out of this.
Mr. President, I know you're tired. I know
this has been hell for you.
And yes, impeachment
would be an awful blow.
We'd have to fight tooth
and nail in the Senate.
And yes, we'll have to beg and
compromise to regain our political capital.
But we have it in us, sir, no matter
how many scars it leaves us with.
It's not just us, Frank.
It's Tricia, it's my children.
I stay awake at night thinking
how much it would crush them,
seeing their father hauled off.
Sir, that won't happen,
because I won't let it.
If we're confronted by the worst, I'll make
sure you never step foot behind bars.
You have my word on that.
He's in the darkness now.
And I'm the only beacon of light.
Now we gently guide him
toward the rocks.
Mr. President,
you also still have my letter.
It's not too late,
if you want to use that option.
You're more useful to me
on the Hill than in handcuffs.
I'll call Kern.
- Good night, sir.
- How much did Green tell you?
- Enough that I showed up.
He probably didn't
mention Rachel Posner.
Don't worry, he doesn't know.
I do.
You have her in an
apartment in Joppa.
I have your movements,
I have your text messages,
before you destroyed your phone,
but that's more than enough.
I'll bet a lot of people would
like to know what she knows.
Now you listen
to me very carefully.
Whatever you think you've got,
whatever you intend to do with it,
I don't respond to extortion
the same way that Green does.
What Green promised you...
...it can be undone
in a heartbeat.
That's why you're here,
to make sure it isn't.
You want my protection.
I don't trust Green,
or anyone at the bureau.
- Who else knows about this?
- No one.
Why should I trust you?
'Cause we both
have too much to lose, man.
Get dressed.
- What are you doing here?
- Put some clothes on.
- Why?
- Now. Let's go.
Did anyone contact you?
- Where are you taking me?
- Answer my question.
No, nobody.
There's someone
who knows about us,
who knows where you are,
and when we've met.
Are you gonna hurt me?
Nothing's going to happen
if you tell the truth.
I am. I haven't been
contacted by anybody.
Stop lying, Rachel.
I will do whatever you want.
Please, just don't hurt me...
What I want is for you to answer
my questions, so I can help you.
All you have ever done
is fuck up my life!
You fucked up the Fellowship.
You fucked up what I had with Lisa!
Even when I did what you asked!
Your sick fucking visits and
reading to you like a fucking child!
What is wrong with you?!
Why can't you just leave me be?!
Why do you have to be such a fucking...
Stop!
Rachel? Don't be stupid.
Rachel, everything's
going to be fine.
All I've ever done
is try to protect you,
what I'm trying to do now.
You have to believe that.
I didn't have to.
It would've been a lot
easier if I didn't.
But I did. I did it,
because I...
What are you doing?
- Uh!
- Oof!
Yesterday we completed hearings with
regard to articles of impeachment
for the president
of the United States.
The chair will now entertain
motions from the committee.
- Mr. Chairman. - The chair recognizes
the congressman from Alabama.
I move that we put our
recommendation directly to a vote,
so that debate on this important
matter may take place on the House floor,
open to all 435 members.
Are there any objections
to bypassing debate in this committee?
We will now vote
on recommendation of the
articles of impeachment
to the full House.
Those in favor of
recommendation say "aye."
- Aye.
- Those opposed?
- Nay.
- The "ayes" have it.
This committee officially
recommends articles of impeachment
proceed to the House floor.
He's here.
The vice president is just arriving now
here at Camp David.
We expect President Walker
to speak within the hour,
announcing his official resignation
as president of the United States.
- How are you?
- All right.
Mr. President.
I have coffee in the kitchen.
Would you like some?
I'm fine.
Well, you're about to become the
most powerful man in the free world.
- You don't have to do this, sir.
- I spoke to Kern last night.
- He's not going to back down.
- So we'll beat him down.
No, Frank. My approvals
are at eight percent.
Even if I avoid conviction,
I have no mandate to lead, so...
...better I step aside with some dignity
so the nation can start to heal.
I can never fill
your shoes, sir.
You don't have a choice now.
Your letter.
Well...
...shall we go introduce the
46th president of the United States?
Effective immediately, I am resigning
the presidency of the United States.
Tricia and I believe that this
is the best course of action,
not only for us
and our children,
but for country.
It's a sad day for us.
I can't deny that.
But I take solace in this:
Frank Underwood will bring
virtue, experience and courage
to the Oval Office.
I have been blessed to have him
as my vice president.
But I'm even more blessed
to call him my friend.
It has been...
...the greatest honor of my life to serve
this country as president.
I thank my family, my staff,
and all of those
who have supported me.
Despite the last few months,
my faith in this country
has never been stronger.
God bless all of you.
And God bless
the United States of America.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Sir, please raise your
right hand and repeat after me.
- "I, Francis J. Underwood..."
- I, Francis J. Underwood...
- "...do solemnly swear..."
- ...do solemnly swear...
- Mr. President.
Madame Secretary.
The rest of the cabinet
is awaiting you at the White House.
We'd like to give you a national
security briefing right away, sir.
I'm aware of the particulars.
Please get Beijing on the phone.
Qian hasn't returned the
president's calls for two days.
Well, there's
a new president now.
Please get him on the line.
Two hours ago, President Underwood,
in his first act as commander in chief,
gave orders to the Seventh Fleet
to vacate Japanese waters.
This was a result of a productive
conversation with President Qian,
who gave similar orders to Chinese
naval vessels in the same region.
- He moves quick. - Do you mean
with the Chinese, or with Walker?
After a grueling night, the four
exiles make their way...
- Mr. Feng?
- What is it?
US Justice Department.
We need you to come with us.
- Where?
- You're going back to China.
- I have asylum.
- No, sir, you don't.
Your asylum has been rescinded.
I have it in writing.
Unconditional and permanent.
Sir, I'm telling you,
your asylum has been rescinded.
Now, please,
gather your things
and come with us.
Revoking his asylum
will have consequences.
But we're solid
from a legal perspective.
Legally, yes. His initial paperwork
hasn't been processed,
and we can claim he poses
a threat to our national interests.
But it diminishes the integrity
of our State Department.
What's more important, Cathy,
integrity or peace?
- You know they'll execute him.
- The Chinese are right about one thing:
Sometimes you have to sacrifice
the one for the many.
Let's get back to Washington.
OK, please let me know.
Thanks very much.
- Anything?
- Not yet.
See if you can track down anyone
from his regular AA meetings.
I spoke to the moderator,
he says he hasn't seen
Doug in several weeks. I checked all
the hospitals, his landlord...
- Sir, everyone's here.
- When this is all over,
I want you to work with
Nancy on finding Doug.
I've already alerted
the DC Metro.
- They put out an APB on his car.
- We'll find him, sir.
- Claire?
- Just outside.
Let's go, Nancy.
Ladies and gentlemen, the
President and the First Lady.
Francis.
I know your birthday
isn't for a couple of weeks,
- but I got you something.
- What's this?
Open it.
I had a new one made.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
- You go ahead.
- Come on.
We earned this together.
Take a few moments
for yourself first.
I'll be out here.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player