Previously on House of Cards...
We get killed in the midterms,
we can kiss 2016 goodbye.
You can deal with the Republican
majority and a Republican president.
Tusk.
Are you funneling money
to the Republicans?
What on earth
are you talking about?
I need the money to stop
flowing in the wrong direction.
You're sending money to Lanagin.
Lanagin's casino is in Tusk's backyard.
We can't offer you a gift if
I don't know what you want.
The Port Jefferson Bridge.
I have allies who want the bridge.
Without it, they become my enemies.
Get out. Please.
Rachel...
You should answer when I call.
I don't like leaving messages.
If you need a punching bag,
I will stand here and take the punches,
as I have done time and time again.
You are out of line, Frank.
- What should we serve the Walkers?
- Cyanide.
- Saving that for dessert.
- Oh, no. None, none for me, thanks.
I'll have some.
Trish, if it's eating at you,
make him talk about it.
The White House is finite.
Your marriage... is for life.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Evelyn...
- Mr. Danton.
- Remy.
- How are you?
- I'm OK. I'm good.
- Been awhile.
- Yeah, it has.
- Good morning.
- Mr. Vice President.
Chief Whitehall.
Is Andrew Jackson
going to be joining us?
No, I'm sorry, that's a terrible
oversight. Doug, will you... remove that.
Why don't we take
the photograph first.
Thank you.
Please have a seat.
Let's talk federal recognition.
Your tribe has waited
long enough.
Who is it?
It's me.
It's Lisa.
Can I come in?
Temp jobs, mostly.
Clerical work...
Right now I'm doing part-time
at a dentist's office. Reception.
You deserve better.
It is what it is.
This is the first time I've had
Starbucks since I can remember.
It's a luxury for me these days.
Maybe there's something
for you at Glendon Hill.
That's nice of you to say, but I'm not
the right fit for a place like that.
Sure you are. Twenty years' experience
in the non-profit sphere,
you coordinated all the time
NGOs, you'd be a valuable asset to us.
- Claire should've never let you go.
- Yeah.
Well... I'll hold my tongue.
She and I don't talk.
We had a falling out.
- Loyalty isn't her thing.
- No, it is not.
I don't think
she's loyal to anyone.
- Except maybe her husband.
- Maybe... maybe not.
- What do you mean?
- Nothing I know for certain, but...
...spend a decade
working for someone...
- She threaten you or anything?
- No.
She just wouldn't leave.
It's not like I wanted to call
the cops, she's not a bad person.
- No, no, but...
- I tried to talk to her,
then she lit up a pipe.
- Meth.
- Yeah.
When we were roommates
that's all it was.
I used to be really deep
into that.
Heroin too.
- And then I found the Fellowship.
- What can I do?
- I'm sorry, I shouldn't be here...
- No, I'm glad you came here.
- I know you're late for work.
- I'll call in sick.
- Don't do that, it's not...
- Don't go, stay here.
I mean, don't go back there.
Look...
- Are you sure?
- Keys. In case you need to come and go.
- I'll be back around 7:30.
- Thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
All the president has to do is pick up
the phone and the bridge is approved.
If the president had wanted to be involved,
he would've already made that call.
- It's his initiative, Linda. - Was his
initiative. We're in a trade war now.
That doesn't mean
we have to abandon good policy.
It's inconsistent
with his current stance...
The committee on foreign
investment has 30 days to approve.
There's only six days left.
They won't act without
a directive from the president
of the United States.
I'm confused, you've been the biggest
proponent of our position against China.
That is not true. I advocated
the opposite early on.
You seem fixated on this bridge.
Is something else going on here?
Unemployment is at
nine-point-two, inflation is skyrocketing,
we're on the verge
of losing our majority.
The president needs to offer
a piece of good news.
A bridge? That's a drop
in the bucket.
Jobs, infrastructure,
deficit reduction...
You're still not
being straight with me.
I have no ulterior motive here,
but if you feel that strongly
and the president feels that strongly,
then I'll back off.
I won't mention it again.
I think that's a wise decision.
We should be a united front.
- I couldn't agree more.
- Thank you.
Why does everything
have to be a struggle?
- Can't some people just
say "yes" for once? - Sir.
I need the president's schedule
for the next two days.
- She change her mind?
- What do you think?
- So what's our next move?
- I'll focus on the bridge,
you talk to the Indian affairs.
The sooner that Whitehall's
tribe gets recognized,
the sooner they can
break ground on that casino.
Yes sir.
Maybe it will help me, you know?
If I talk about it
more in the open.
I mean that's what
your interview did.
When I called. When I could
say those things out loud.
Well, we don't want you
to feel obligated.
I know the press
hasn't left you alone.
If they're going to keep taking pictures
of me, I should at least say something.
Well, that's only going
to become more intense
when McGinnis gets closer
to his court-marshal.
Yeah, I know.
I'm prepared.
If you come and speak to the
Armed Services Committee, tell your story,
I feel confident
we can get it to a vote.
- I'd be too much coverage to ignore it.
- And you think it will pass?
- We need to get it through committee
first. - But let's be clear, Megan,
it's not just the testimony.
We'll need you to do
a media avail after.
Photo ops, a statement.
- OK.
- You won't be alone.
- I'll be standing right next to you.
- And so will I.
OK.
Do you think we're doing the right thing?
Hauling her in front of the cameras?
We have to trust her
when she says she wants to.
But it's very important that
the White House backs us
up on this, not just you.
I'm not sure if Garrett
will get involved publicly.
Well, can you talk to him?
We haven't been doing much
talking about anything lately.
Things haven't
gotten any better?
We haven't said a word
to each other in almost a week.
- I've been there, it's awful.
- With Frank?
- Sure.
- What did you do?
We saw someone.
You mean a therapist?
- Weren't you worried about exposure?
- He was a minister.
He wasn't exactly a therapist. It was more
like a spiritual guidance, type thing.
The only difference
was that he had a degree.
I could put you in touch.
It's too risky.
Just a suggestion.
Let me know if
you change your mind.
Thanks.
In the meantime,
can you try to talk to Garrett?
We really need
his support with this.
I will.
Yes?
Show him in please.
- Remy.
- So formal.
Would you have a seat?
Shouldn't keep
your interns so late.
You and I might not
have lives but they do.
When there's work to be done,
we work. They know that.
- Why am I here at ten at night?
- Where's the GOP getting their money?
- That's a $25 million question isn't it?
- You must have an idea.
- What makes you think that?
- Because you know things.
That's why Glendon Hill
made you partner.
Most of our clients are Democrats,
I'm just as much in the dark as you are.
I'm losing in my district, Remy.
I wish I could help you.
Even if I pull off
a win, it doesn't matter.
The GOP takes the house,
I lose my spot in the leadership,
this office, everything
I've worked for.
I feel for you.
But you want information
I don't have.
Are you upset about
the last time we saw each other?
Not at all. I made myself clear.
Can we talk?
No work, no politics.
We can talk about
whatever you want.
I've never... been with anyone
for more than six months.
When I was in the army I was
always on the move and, um...
Since I've been in Congress,
I just haven't had time.
I wasn't asking to marry you.
Just to be more than company for a night.
Do you still want that?
I'm here, aren't I?
There would have
to be clear boundaries.
Whatever we have privately couldn't
affect our professional relationship.
Then we shouldn't be having this
conversation in your office.
I'm glad we had this meeting.
If you'd like to have
another, just call me.
We can leave the
secretaries out of it.
I'll review this
and have Linda get in touch.
Thank you, sir.
- Good morning, Mr. President.
- Hi, Frank.
I left my bourbon at home,
but you have time for some coffee?
I'm fine, you go ahead.
I wanted to talk to you
about the Port Jefferson Bridge.
Linda told me you two spoke.
Have you reconsidered?
It's not the right time, Frank.
We'll find some other project to showcase
our program once tensions subside.
During the campaign,
you repeatedly promised
to address critical
infrastructure.
We're well into
your second year.
This project is ready to go, you don't
want to have to start from square one.
I'm thinking midterms.
We have to project consistency.
Except people don't vote for consistency,
they vote for concrete progress.
Linda mentioned that you seemed
obsessed with this bridge.
I'm beginning to think
she was right.
The backstabbing,
vomit-inducing bitch.
Is she right, Frank?
Tell me why this bridge
is so important to you.
- I wanted to insulate you from this...
- From what?
You asked me to back channel with
the Chinese and I have continued to do so.
No, I told you to stop back
channeling and you did anyway?
- Without informing me, Frank...
- I needed to distance you.
There are issues that
a president cannot be aware of.
- What issues...
- But, what I can tell you...
...is that the building
of this bridge
directly affects our ability to
combat the Republicans in the midterms.
- Have the Chinese...
- Mr. President, you are asking questions
you do not want the answers to.
All right, how much
danger are we in, Frank?
None if we end this
conversation right now.
Sometimes I feel like I'm losing control
over my goddamn administration.
You're under pressure, sir,
but you're not losing control.
You have people who are
looking out for you: me, Linda, your wife.
I might be losing control
of her too.
I shouldn't have said that...
Of course she wants
the best for me.
Has Claire said anything?
I know they talk.
Not much... just that things
have been a little rocky.
Well, that's an understatement.
You have the most difficult job on earth.
It would take a toll on any marriage.
Which is why I'm urging you
to reconsider your decision on the bridge.
And I'd say that not as
your vice president... but as your friend.
Because I care about you.
All right, I'll...
I'll have another look at it.
Thank you, Mr...
Thank you, Garrett.
- Mr. Frost.
- Morning.
We filed all our paperwork
back in 2006.
We dotted all of our I's
and crossed all of our T's.
There's over 317 applications. Each one
requires at least a year to review.
- You need more researchers.
- It's not just personnel.
There's travel, filing,
administration...
Name the figure.
Twelve, thirteen million.
That requires an appropriation
from Congress.
The vice president
can make that happen.
But first we need you
to recognize the Ugaya tribe.
Our policy is first come, first serve.
There are other applications which we...
Daniel Lanagin disenrolled us.
We lost our right
to BIA benefits.
Is this more about
starting a casino?
It's about correcting
an injustice.
I can't be getting involved
in inner-tribal conflicts.
Yes, you can.
If you want that appropriation.
Two months. Maybe less
if all the ancestry holds up.
Lanagin knows.
And what did he say?
He wants to meet.
But on his turf this time.
I need a way to get to Missouri
without attracting any attention.
Womack's district is in Kansas City.
It's not far from the casino.
See if he has any events
coming up: rallies fund-raisers...
How's it coming with
cosponsors for Claire's bill?
Terrific, we're making
great progress.
One speech, it'll send a message to
Congress...
And a message to
the joint chiefs that I'm trampling on...
Twenty-four thousand assaults
last year, only 3,000 reported because...
- I know the figures.
- Do you know how many suicides
- result from the trauma...
- It's not the question of statistics...
- This bill will save lives.
- Can we discuss this later?
- I had to schedule this meeting, Garrett.
- It's the middle of the day.
- You know very well...
- Don't make me lobby you when I go home...
I'm sorry to interrupt Mr. President.
The secretary general's here.
I got two more minutes.
It's 12:30, he was schedule
for 12:15.
I'll go.
You were supposed to
tell me to stay.
But it's nice to know
I'm worth at least two minutes.
Hi, Tricia.
No, please,
don't worry about it.
Oh, that's awful.
Yes, of course, let me
grab his number for you.
Mm-hm.
Right.
His name is Dr. Thomas Larkin.
At 202-251-6258
And if you'd like, I can
give him a call before hand
and let him know
you'll be reaching out.
OK, you let me know
if I can be of any help.
Good night, Tricia.
What do you think?
We'll see.
The idea is to take color theory
and turn it on its head.
Break all the rules.
They're gorgeous.
Who'd you say your client is?
I didn't.
I was just wondering
if maybe I knew them.
You don't.
Let's say he's a collector
always on the lookout for new talent.
I understand you work
for Adam Galloway.
Yeah... it's a way
to pay the bills.
I mean, Adam's a good photographer
if you like that kind of thing.
I'm much more
interested in form.
- How much for all of them?
- What?
I'd like to buy them all.
Missouri is the
"Show Me State" for a reason.
We need to show the rest of America
that we can keep our leadership intact.
It is a pleasure to look out
and see a room full of smiling faces.
That's not something you see
everyday in Washington DC.
- What did your editor say?
- Five thousand words.
This should be twice that.
I could probably
get them to eight,
but I'm gonna need
the First Lady too.
Separate interviews.
Let me talk to Mrs. Underwood.
How come you're coming to me
with this instead of Connor?
Between you and me, he's out.
He got a job at SpaceX.
His choice or was he pushed out?
People don't like working with me, Matt.
You may be the only one.
I don't like you either. I might
if you give me the First Lady.
They'll both be speaking
to armed services tomorrow.
Along with Megan Hennessy.
She's the one the general...
That's right.
I'll set up a one-on-one,
text you for your piece.
All right, let me know, man.
Anything for the Times, man.
Anything for the Times, huh?
Then we get shut out
of donor meetings.
The magazine. And yes.
Raymond Tusk. Your boss
went to see him last October.
It's in his congressional
travel report.
- Before my time.
- You said they didn't communicate.
- I said, "not to my knowledge."
- We're in Missouri.
- He's not one of the donors.
- I can quote you on that?
If you spell my name right.
Now, normally, I don't quote
Northern writers, but every now and then
one of them says something
that makes a lot of sense,
and this Emerson fellow
you probably heard of,
once wrote that the only way
to have a friend is to be one.
I think you all know what kind of
a friend Terry has been to this district.
So I am proud to introduce him
today and to call him my friend.
Would you please welcome, the majority
leader, Representative Terry Womack.
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
We all set?
I told the press you were having some
private meetings with contributors.
- Any protests?
- We're good except for Ayala Sayyad.
Thank you. What's going on?
- Potential blind spot.
- Tell me on the way to the car.
Mr. Vice President.
Thank you.
Calm down. Now.
Welcome.
- What a pleasant surprise, Raymond.
- Mr. Vice President.
I was expecting to see you
privately today, Daniel.
When it's a serious matter
I invite all the chiefs to the circle.
Nice pool.
I've never swum in
it. The chlorine hurts my eyes.
You're welcome to take
a dip in it if you'd like.
Another time.
Raymond tells me
you're a ribs man.
I've got three of the
choicest pieces of meat
you'll ever see in your life coming out.
You do not want to pass on this.
I won't be here long.
So the Ugaya band.
Tip of the iceberg.
- They're not a real tribe.
- They're about to be.
No, they're a bunch of troublemakers
with too much hope on their hands.
Once they get recognized,
they're gonna have their own casino.
In two years... at best?
You better enjoy this pool
while you can.
I don't think your casino
can stand that sort of competition.
Who do you think Whitehall
called as soon as he left the BIA?
You offer them a casino two years from
now, we offered what they really want.
Reenrollment in my tribe.
A tip of your iceberg
is melting, Frank.
And you do not have time
on your side so how about this...?
You help me repair
my relationship with Garrett,
Dan and I here get the money
flowing back in the right direction.
How about this...?
I get the BIA to investigate
both of you.
Connection to Feng, laundering...
You could, but you won't.
You don't dare.
My money has been going
to the Democrats for nine years.
You were the whip
for all of them.
You implicate us,
you implicate yourself.
And everyone in the leadership.
- Ah, here comes the steak.
- Oh...
Now you are going to enjoy this,
Frank. There you go.
Thank you.
Now dig in, Frank.
Before the flies get to it.
- I'll pass, thanks.
- Are you sure?
This is soy-fed Matsusaka beef.
You know, my ancestors would've
prayed to this heifer to honor her spirit.
But at 200 bucks a pound,
I figure... fuck tradition.
Come on, live a little, Frank.
Mr. Vice President.
Not my vice president.
You're on sovereign land.
Dogs are so predictable,
aren't they?
Set up a meeting with Walker. Tonight,
if possible. I should be back by six.
-  Lanagin didn't budge?
- He reenrolled the Ugaya.
- We have to get the bridge approved now.
-  I'll call Linda.
Bypass her, I don't
want her in the meeting.
- I'm on it.
- Thanks.
Meechum, get in touch with the plane
have them make ribs for the flight back.
Yes sir.
Mr. Vice President,
do you have a moment?
I'm sorry, the president
asked to see me.
No he didn't, you requested the meeting
and I took it off the schedule.
- You did what?
- Let's go in your office.
You lied, Frank. You said
you would let the bridge go
and then you went behind my back
just like you're trying to do now.
- I do not require your permission!
- No, but you should involve me.
The president and the vice president
have issues they must discuss privately.
When you are secretive it prevents
me from being able to do my job.
And when you cancel meetings it
prevents me from being able to do mine.
Which is why I wanted to talk
so we can work things out.
- I will not waste my time...
- We should be working together...
...inflating your sense
of self-importance!
- Excuse me?
- How many elections have you won?!
How many congressional
committees have you chaired?!
Would you even be working
in the White House
if I hadn't recommended you
during the campaign?
I returned that favor and then
some. Look where your desk is now!
And I'd say we're even.
And if you want
to maintain my respect,
you're going about it all wrong.
I asked you in here
to work out a situation...
You didn't ask, you demanded!
I will not be left out
of the loop,
I'm the president's
chief of staff.
You call this being chief of staff?
Micromanaging his date book?
I'd say that's more
of a glorified scheduler.
The White House would fall off
its rails without me doing my job.
- Are you certain about that?
- Yes, I am.
I look out
for the president 24/7.
I keep him informed.
I keep his priorities straight.
We did just fine before you
became vice president, Frank.
All right, let's go over
to the Oval Office right now
and ask the president to choose:
his chief of staff or his vice president.
I know what the answer would be.
You wanna go?
I didn't think so.
Now I will see the president
tomorrow morning, schedule or no.
And please, turn out the lights
before you leave.
I thought you went home.
No, not yet.
Um, do you have a moment?
Is there something wrong?
I know you are reconsidering
the bridge project and I want...
I'm reviewing it.
I'll make my decision soon.
But you already
made a decision, sir.
I'm concerned that you
are overthinking this one.
- If we backtrack...
- Did I not make myself clear?
I'm just trying to offer
my advice, sir.
Which I've heard. And which I don't
need to hear again but... thank you.
I know the vice president spoke
to you yesterday and in fairness...
You know I value your input,
Linda,
but when I say I've heard it,
you need to know I mean that.
Of course, sir.
- Is there anything else?
- No, sir.
- Good night.
You disappointed me.
I told you it would take time.
Any leads?
I've been going over
his state senate days,
it's a slow process.
I have to be thorough.
So how is it that
I've found more in two days
than you have in two months?
- What do you mean?
- I've had to do your job for you.
You found something?
I'm the one who's supposed
to ask that question.
What'd you find?
Maybe I can help.
Are you working for Frank?
- Yeah, as his communications director.
- No, are you working for him?
Come on.
He couldn't pay me a fraction
of what you're offering.
- Don't lie to me. - Look, if you've lost
confidence in my ability...
Stop fucking around.
You made the wrong choice, Seth.
I don't think so.
You're nothing.
You're a parasite.
So are you Danton.
Just in a nicer suit.
Do you know what it might be?
Well, keep your ear
to the ground.
That was Seth.
He thinks Remy may have
something on us.
- What?
- He doesn't know.
- Do you think it could be...
- No.
If it's anything I'm sure it's innocuous.
Nothing we can't weather.
But my bet is they're bluffing.
Just to make us paranoid.
But he's a dangerous man,
isn't he? Raymond?
We can be dangerous too.
When we need to be.
Don't stop.
I used to be a call girl.
I had to get away from it
and that's why I came here.
It's a lot of stuff
you don't know about me.
You don't have to
say anything you don't want to.
When you tapped on
my shoulder on the bus,
there was something...
Your eyes.
- That sounds really, really dumb.
- No.
Um...
I don't know, I felt like...
I wanted to tell you everything.
Like...
...that I could trust you
even though I didn't know you.
You can.
I never trusted anyone.
Have you ever loved anyone?
No.
I've never expected
much from the world. It's ugly.
It's not a fair place.
I'm happy to have what I have.
I'm glad I have this.
I've thought it all out.
And there's a way to do it
so we don't risk any exposure.
Do we have to talk
about this now?
I'm beat.
My brain is f...
Yes, we do.
Because it's our marriage.
If we're going to survive
the next two years... or six.
We need to do something.
We should be each others'
support system.
Not cause each other stress.
The foundation of this White
House is not brick and mortar.
It's us, Garrett.
This is important to me.
And I want it
to be important to you.
I have to trust
that whatever you're managing,
to whatever extent you choose
not to inform me, that I'm neither at risk,
nor passively condoning
something blatantly illegal.
Any risk solely falls on me,
and you can't be accused of condoning
what you're not aware of.
Being not aware,
is just as egregious.
Not in this case. I'm steering the
ship away from the rocks, not toward them.
Then I'll call the committee
for foreign investments.
You're making
the right decision, sir.
I have another difficult
decision to make.
Linda submitted her resignation.
I was furious with her. That was
a very manipulative move.
I can speculate
as to why she made it.
Are her complaints valid?
I have a very biased view
on that subject.
Well, I've heard hers.
Give me yours.
Linda and I don't always agree.
But she's been very loyal to you,
and a more than competent chief of staff.
So you think I should keep her?
Do I think she oversteps
sometimes? Yes.
Does she wrongly equate
her advice with mine? Often.
But... the question that occurs
to me is not about Linda.
Let's say you refuse her resignation,
if this gets out, and it could,
won't you be sending a signal
to anybody who works for you that...
...you can be leveraged.
She offered her resignation.
She's already gone even if she stays.
Megan. They're ready.
I don't know,
my hands are shaking.
You can do this, Megan.
I'll be there.
I get panic attacks sometimes.
- You're afraid you'll get one?
- Yeah.
OK, why don't we ask for a couple
more minutes, that's not a problem.
It's not about that,
they just come.
I can't control them.
I don't want to do this.
OK, Megan, there's some of the most
senior congressmen and women in the room,
and they press, they've shown up
just to hear from you.
- I know.
- OK, I don't want to pressure you,
but a lot of planning
has gone into this.
Please don't make me do this.
We're not making you
do anything.
Then can I just go back home?
Back to Chicago?
Listen, you have nerves,
that's understandable.
I don't wanna fucking do it, OK?
I understand, it's OK. But
if you back out now, Megan...
- This isn't about me at all, is it?
- ...this is not good for us.
It hurts us, it makes us
look unorganized.
This is about your
fucking moment to shine.
You don't care if do...
I do care. I do care.
It is about me and about you!
And for whatever reason, we both
decided to share what happened to us.
And it mattered
and people listened
so let's go in
and finish what we started.
- I can't, I'm not the right person.
- Come on, Megan.
You know what I did last night?
I picked up some guy at a bar.
A total stranger. I let him
fuck my brains out at the hotel.
Night before, same thing.
I can't stop.
It's my only way to fucking...
Jesus, I fucking hate this when
my hands shake like this and I...
It's OK.
I'm not who you want
to be your poster girl.
It's OK. You don't have to be.
You don't have to be.
I'm sorry I'm letting you down.
It's OK, you're not
letting me down.
It's OK. It's OK.
When will it become official?
President will make
his call this afternoon.
Official approval will be
announced in the morning.
No revisions to the agreement?
None. Everything is
as spelled out in the proposal.
Then I will uphold
my end of the bargain.
The money will be cut off.
You required proof.
Now we want some.
-  What sort?
- Of your commitment.
You kill your
co-venture with Tusk.
-  That was never part of the deal.
- It is now.
The refinery can't proceed
while we're in a trade wall.
We want you to kill it for good.
And we want you to kill it today.
Make the call to Tusk.
It's business hours,
is this a business call?
No...
I was hoping it wasn't.
- What are you doing tonight?
- Just about to get on a plane.
Where to?
Boundaries, remember?
- Work related.
-  I don't take vacation.
Can you tell me
when you'll be back?
Tomorrow. It's a quick trip.
Do you want to have dinner?
I'd like that.
Bring your carry-on.
You can stay over after.
- Yes.
- Do you have a moment?
Absolutely.
The president accepted
my resignation an hour ago.
Yes, I know.
I almost told him
that I changed my mind,
but I realized
it wouldn't make any difference.
For whatever it's worth,
I did bring up your loyalty
and how good you are at your job.
Not that he needed me to remind him.
And I will always be grateful
you recommended me.
It has been quite a ride.
Shorter than I would've hoped,
but I have a long career ahead.
- No doubt.
- And just so you know,
I don't plan on making
any fuss in the press.
You'll hear nothing but
my praises if I'm asked.
I have something for you.
A few weeks ago,
the president told me about
a dinner he had at your house.
He went on and on
about your Civil War models.
How much fun he had painting
the toy soldiers with you.
This was given to me by the
director of the Smithsonian.
It's the first Medal of Honor
awarded to a Hispanic-American:
Corporal Joseph de Castro,
he fought for the Union.
Linda, I don't know what to say.
It's clear the president sees you
as a friend, I've never been that to him,
but his job is bigger
than friendship.
It's bigger than you and me.
I just hope you'll look out for
him the way I've tried to do.
I will. And I'll treasure this.
Goodbye, Mr. Vice President.
I've never thought higher of her
than I do at this moment.
She lost...
but she played to win.
Underwood got the phone.
The refinery's dead. Grayson played us.
We're running out of options.
What do you think Jean?
Fuck him!
Do it.
Thank you.
Thank you for doing this Sandra.
Richard.
How are you, Richard?
He has his good days
and his bad.
This is a good day.
He'd love to spend a few minutes
with you after your meeting.
Of course.
The reverend's in here.
- Mrs. Walker.
- Hello.
- Mr. President.
- Reverend.
How can I help?
You need to get
a fan in here, Francis.
Well, the AC is all the way
up to full blast.
I mean from the fumes, the glue.
Oh, that's half the fun.
Megan Hennessy
bailed on us today.
Why?
Her nerves got to her.
And she decided she didn't
want to be in the public eye.
- Well, we can
sympathize with that.
That was Doug.
Yes.
Seth.
I'll call you back.
When?
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player