Previously on House of Cards...
The issue at stake is whether the
White House was in any way involved.
Just the act of laundering
Chinese contributions is illegal.
Douglas Stamper,
your chief of staff.
This is him at Lanagin's casino,
July 14th.
They have evidence of Doug being
where he shouldn't have been.
- We're talking about impeachable offenses.
- Not at all, sir.
You're scared. I can tell.
I'll say whatever
you want me to say.
- She could indict you.
- That's what having a staff is for.
Even Achilles was only as strong
as his heel.
We need to be louder.
If the bill goes to the floor
as is, I won't just bow out.
I'll actively fight it.
If you ask me, she's
betraying our country too.
Multiple fronts, Remy.
It has to be Jackie Sharp.
Then I was right.
- About what?
- How little I meant.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
She's interviewed half of Congress.
That woman's after blood.
He's worried about his marriage
counseling, as he should be.
- If you're worried about your marriage
counseling, you shouldn't be.
- Imagine the fallout...
- This one address keeps popping up.
- Underwood?
The President.
You're parsing the law, and
I'm talking about a spiritual code.
Confidentiality is a covenant,
not only between myself
and those I counsel,
but also between myself
and the Lord.
Dr. Larkin, my chief focus here
is the money laundering.
If the President brought up Xander Feng,
Raymond Tusk, the Adohi casino...
Doesn't matter what the focus is. I can't
share anything we discuss privately.
Religious guidance is protected.
But you were also conducting
professional therapy.
- I never claimed that.
- Mr. and Mrs. Keith confirmed as much.
We were at their house.
But they didn't participate in our
conversations, so how would they know?
So you're saying that you
only gave religious counsel.
That's how I choose
to interpret it.
The President and his wife have
never once attended your church.
- They're not even the same denomination.
- Irrelevant.
Not legally speaking.
I'm certain I can convince a judge to
issue a subpoena on the grounds
that you weren't their
legitimate spiritual advisor.
Which is your prerogative,
but I can appeal.
- And I would.
- You'd lose.
The only circumstance
by which I would talk
is if someone personally
waived their privilege.
Otherwise, I'd rather face
contempt of court.
It's a matter of ethics.
Mr. President.
Aww... You brought it back in.
Floyd Mayweather visited
the White House this morning.
- I thought he'd get a kick out of it.
- Did he have a go at it?
He threw a combination I thought
would bust the stitching loose.
That must have been
a treat to watch.
He was telling me,
it's not just about the power.
There are plenty of boxers
more powerful than he is.
No, it's his tactics,
his precision, his speed,
most important,
his counterpunch.
He dances and dodges, then picks
the perfect moment to strike.
Does that sound familiar?
How do you mean, sir?
You gave this to me
as a gesture of friendship.
When I look at this now,
I don't see friendship,
I see calculation.
You set me up, Frank.
- What?
- Your back-channeling,
the special prosecutor...
When I think about Raymond,
about Linda, about Jim Matthews...
You are wrong, sir.
Questions from Dunbar,
about the marriage counseling.
"It's a needle in the haystack,
she's not trying to find."
That's what you said.
Well, she found the needle.
- I am shocked, sir, I never...
- Like hell you are.
- You want to diminish me.
- Diminish you?
Laying the groundwork
for a challenge in 2016.
I am sorry to have to say this, sir,
but you are being ludicrous.
Do you really think
I'm so blind?
A vice president has never
challenged a sitting president!
You've climbed the ladder doing
things other men would never do.
Always in service
to you and the party.
It was your idea
to hand over those logs.
You connected the White House
to China, the casino.
Raymond Tusk entangled us
with China and the casino.
- And if I hadn't intervened...
- You can't dodge and duck like Floyd.
I've learned your moves now.
This office breeds paranoia.
Don't give into it, sir.
I'd ask for your resignation if
it wouldn't make things worse.
But from this moment forward,
I don't want to hear your voice.
I don't want to see your face.
And if I do, I will put you
on your goddamn back.
Exile.
I've managed to isolate
the president from everyone...
...including myself.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
"Congresswoman Sharp is a perfect example
of how the military brainwashes us
into never questioning
the party line.
Her opposition to the bill
is disgraceful.
It will cost thousands of men and women
the justice they deserve,
- and some of them their lives."
- Those are Megan Hennessey's words.
- They're biased...
- They're Claire's words.
Hennessey's just the mouthpiece.
Why does it say I declined to comment?
You said you didn't want to kick
up dust if we could avoid it.
It's The New York fucking Times.
You should've let me know.
That was my call.
I'll take the blame.
Find out when Hennessey's
next appearance is.
- I want to beat this bitch down.
- I know she went after you.
- but going after her...
- Not her, Claire Underwood.
I understand how Garrett might misconstrue
things, given the pressure he's under,
but you can't honestly
believe it yourself.
I don't know
what to believe anymore.
Francis is devastated.
All he wants to do is help, but he
feels like he's being unfairly accused.
I don't want to believe it, Claire,
but Garrett is convinced.
Will you talk to him?
I have to concentrate on keeping
my family together right now,
not getting
into arguments over...
If Francis were
really up to something,
don't you think he would've
told Dunbar about the therapy?
He basically did, by forcing us
to hand over the logs.
Your husband chose
to hand them over.
If he had said no, Francis
wouldn't have pressed the issue.
I don't want to debate this
with you, Claire.
All I'm asking is that you
really think this through, Tricia.
- Is he with you right now?
- Who?
- Frank.
- No, it's just you and me.
I want to get off the phone.
- Will you please talk to Garrett?
- Goodbye, Claire.
What do you think?
I don't think she's going to side
with me instead of her husband.
Did Tricia tell anyone else
about the Xanax, besides you?
I doubt she would.
She's very sensitive about it.
If she'd only told someone else,
then we could just leak it.
- But it'll too obvious.
- The doctor.
He's protecting them.
He won't say anything.
Unless they waive the privilege.
They have absolutely
nothing to gain by that.
But we do.
- You have to meet with Tusk.
- Why would he talk to me
- after I backstabbed him?
- That's precisely why he'll talk to you.
- I can't go to St. Louis.
- Tusk will come east.
Your job is to get
in the same room with him.
- What's the play?
- Remy Danton, go.
- Get me Durant, in person.
- I'll set it up.
And Doug, let's make sure we're
airtight on everything else.
- No Achilles' heel.
- Yes, sir.
"Cry 'Havoc,'" said he who
fought chaos with chaos,
"and let slip the dogs of war."
Missed appointments,
no contact in weeks...
- You know the rules.
- I'd like to speak to Agent Green, please.
- What are you up to?
- Put Green on the fucking line, please.
Anything you have to say,
you can discuss it with me.
What I have to say
is way above your pay grade.
Where do I turn off this shit?
Look at the other screen,
to the left.
- What is this?
- That is the access grid
to all eight
of AT&T's data centers.
So, what do you say you uncuff
me and tell Agent Green
I'll be waiting for his call.
I'm trying to repair
relations with China.
Giving Feng asylum
would be a slap in the face.
Garrett's in trouble.
He needs to appear resolute.
We're only as strong as the president
we serve. We have to rescue him.
How can you be sure his testimony
won't implicate the White House?
He knows where
his bread is buttered.
This isn't about
you saving the president.
- Of course it is.
- We've been down this road before, Frank.
Michael Kern, Adam Galloway.
I wanted to become secretary of state
in order to engage in productive diplomacy,
not full-time damage control.
Which is why we have
to put Garrett back on his feet.
You want him on his ass, Frank.
Is this what
the president told you?
He's paranoid, Cathy.
He's trying to turn people against me.
You're turning them against
yourself. You're asking me
to undermine the president.
All right.
Let's say that what the
president has accused me of...
...is true.
Would that be so bad,
if taken to its conclusion?
Wouldn't you stand to benefit?
Wouldn't the country?
- I don't want anything to do with this.
- Just one more time, Cathy.
Let's unshackle ourselves.
This is a one-time
offer, Mr. Feng.
I would need it in writing.
Open-ended, no restrictions.
The same goes
for legal immunity.
First I need to know whether or not you
funneled money through Lanagin's casino.
No. I will speak freely once I have
arrived safely in the United States.
Unless you provide
valuable evidence now,
the attorney general will not
grant immunity on any level.
I have denied
these allegations in China.
My enemies want me dead. You're asking
me to give them confirmation.
And we're giving you
safe haven in return.
I already have
safe haven in Dubai.
Your asylum there is only temporary.
We're offering you permanent status.
I'm confident that they will
grant me permanent status.
Did you hear that directly from
the minister of foreign affairs?
Because I just spoke to him.
Right now you are a man
without a passport.
Whatever assets
Beijing hasn't seized
are frozen in every country with close ties
to the United States or China,
which is just about every
country in the world.
You want your freedom
and fortune.
We want information.
Mr. Feng?
What do you need to know?
Confirm for me the existence
of a money laundering scheme.
Yes.
We used the casino
to mask foreign contributions.
All right.
One of you wanna tell me
what this is all about?
- You have to comply.
- You mean I have to show up.
- Unless we appeal.
- We'd lose.
She wouldn't have issued the subpoena
unless she had something substantial.
I agree, which is why I think you
should go and plead the Fifth.
- What do you think she has?
- I don't want to speculate.
Goddamn it, I pay
the six of you more in one day
than it costs to put
a kid through college.
I pay you to know
more than I do.
Her line of questioning
will tell us a lot.
We could use that to prepare
a defense in case there's an indictment.
- When do I have to go?
- Your interview is the day after next.
Forty-eight hours?
- Having trouble starting it?
- Yeah.
I think the battery
might be dead.
I have some cables
if you want to try and jump it.
- You sure you don't mind?
- Not at all.
All right.
That's really nice of you.
Pop your hood.
I'll bring my car around.
Sure.
- Hey.
- Hey. This is Peter.
- He's the guy who drove me back.
- Oh.
- Where do you want these?
- I'll take them. Thanks.
- Rachel, right?
- Yeah.
- Lisa said you two are roommates.
- Can I get you something?
- A glass of water?
- No, thanks. I should get going.
All right.
I can't thank you enough.
My pleasure.
Good luck with the car.
- Thanks.
- I hope it's only a dead battery.
Have a good night.
We should give him some money.
- What?
- Peter!
She needs to be gone.
- You told me she could stay.
- I changed my mind.
But you said you didn't care
if she was here.
I don't need to explain myself.
You can't stand it, can you? The idea
that I might actually love somebody,
that I might have somebody
in my life who isn't you.
If you care about her,
make it happen, Rachel.
- Hey. Is everything OK?
- Yeah.
You need to tell your friend
that I won't take any money.
I was happy to do it. We all need
a good Samaritan every now and again.
Did you feel justice was served
when General McGinnis
got sentenced to 40 years?
Yes, as far as his crimes go,
but not for thousands
of servicemen...
I'm sorry to interrupt, but my producer
is telling me that Jacqueline Sharp
has called in,
the House majority whip.
- Congresswoman, are you there?
-  Yes, I'm here, Chris.
- Thank you for taking my call.
-  Thank you.
- Hello, Megan.
- Congresswoman.
First of all, as a veteran like
yourself,
I want to thank you for your
service to our country.
- Duty doesn't require thanks.
- I'm glad you brought up duty,
because you recently
equated it with brainwashing.
- That's not what I meant.
-  You said "toeing the party line."
What I meant was the culture
and the system is one...
I didn't call to argue with you,
Megan. The opposite.
We can't fix this problem until we find
some common ground, wouldn't you agree?
There is no middle ground,
as far as I'm concerned.
- The military needs to change...
- Can't we agree that you and I served
so that we could protect open debate,
which is the very bedrock of democracy?
Yes, in theory, but that's not
what I'm talking about.
Not in theory, in reality.
Brave men and women
die fighting for that freedom.
The meaning of bravery is fighting for the
freedom of those with whom you disagree.
Sure, but let's get back
to the issue here.
What I don't think is brave
is Claire Underwood
dodging this debate
and having you fight this battle
for her instead.
That's not true.
Then why am I talking to you
instead of her? It's her bill.
It's not just hers.
It's all of ours.
Except one of you
is brave enough to say it,
and the other is a coward.
Mrs. Underwood was brave enough to go
on national television and admit that...
And where has she been since?
Deflecting scandal
and hiding from the press.
You called me disgraceful in
The New York Times, Megan,
and you have every right.
But I also have the right to say
that Mrs. Underwood is disgraceful,
because nothing is more
disgraceful than running from a battle.
- Megan?
- That isn't...
We're not even...
We'll be right back.
- Where are you going?
- To the Capitol.
Did Feng mention either
me or the president?
Dunbar wouldn't say, but the fact that
Feng confirmed the money laundering
increases focus
on the White House.
As long as we're innocent,
which we are...
Raymond Tusk
has been subpoenaed.
Why did you ask for this meeting, Bill?
Just keeping us in the loop?
Did you encourage Secretary
Durant to offer Feng asylum?
Bill, for godsakes.
The president could have
asked me that question himself.
As White House counsel,
it is my responsibility...
No, I did not.
So you're saying Durant
acted of her own accord.
I have no idea what her
motivations were.
I'm just as shocked as the president
that she would have gone through with this
without his direct approval.
There's another matter
I'd like to discuss, privately if we could.
Just give us a few moments.
- The therapy.
- Yes.
To be specific,
the confidentiality waiver.
Feng's testimony puts us
in a very awkward position.
We're under a great deal of
pressure to waive the privilege.
If we don't, it implies that the president
may have confessed to things he didn't.
Dunbar is just grasping,
don't give in.
I don't want to, but Larkin's argument
for spiritual confidentiality
is shaky at best.
We want to control
how this thing plays out.
How can I help?
We need to know if anyone else
might pop out of the woodwork.
Well, I haven't mentioned it to
anyone and neither has Claire.
I would never betray
the president's trust like that.
Thank you for your time.
Tell the president it saddens me that we
now have to communicate through lawyers.
I will make myself available if
he wants to discuss any of this in person.
Yes, sir.
What Megan said was offensive.
She shouldn't have
questioned your character.
Those were talking points,
carefully crafted and not by her.
I'm not here to pick a fight,
Jackie. I'm here to end one.
It'll end soon enough,
when the bill goes to the floor.
It won't go to the floor.
I've spoken to Elaine Brooks
and I'm withdrawing the bill.
What you said had some truth.
Early on, you offered to sit down
with me and find a middle ground.
I decided to draw a line
in the sand.
The braver thing would've been for me
to swallow my pride and sit down with you.
If you're still open to that,
I'd love to start over.
- Are you and Frank up to something?
- A passable bill.
He had Nancy spy on me. He
brought my personal life into...
Francis is used
to getting his way,
and he'll do anything
to make sure he does,
especially if it's something
important to me.
I don't know, Claire.
I'm skeptical.
We're deeply sorry
for the way we've treated you.
And we want to rebuild
the trust we've lost.
Do you think that's possible?
I'm sorry to ambush you,
I tried calling.
You can't do this to me, Claire.
I was very clear that I have
to respect Garrett's...
Not that, the sexual assault
bill, it's not going to a vote.
Did the Speaker
remove it from the docket?
No, I did.
I just spoke to Jackie.
This is because of what
she said about you?
My main concern is that
she doesn't come after you next.
Not while you and Garrett are
going through the investigation.
I thought you should be aware, because
I know how much this bill meant to you.
- All the work you've put in.
- That we've put in.
But we'll pass Jackie's version,
take this baby step and build on it.
I'm disappointed about the bill,
but I have to say, I'm relieved.
How are you holding up?
Did you hear what Catherine did,
giving Feng asylum?
- Inexcusable.
- Garrett's beside himself.
He feels cornered, like we have no choice
but to waive the privilege now.
- But what about the medication?
- I know.
I shouldn't be sharing this.
We don't have to talk about it.
You should go.
I know you have
a packed schedule.
Thank you for doing this.
All I had to do was
get her alone in a hallway.
- I meant with Jackie.
- We have our priorities.
I know it isn't easy to let go
of something like that.
- Promise me something.
- Anything.
- I can't live in this house alone.
- I'm not going anywhere.
You say that,
but this could all backfire.
Raymond will plead the Fifth.
If he names me, it's an
admission of his own wrongdoing.
I'm more worried about Garrett.
You've made a powerful enemy.
- We're stronger than they are.
- And he's still the president.
I promise you, of all the
sacrifices that you've had to make,
divorcing a convict
will not be one of them.
We can't waive
the privilege, Garrett.
- We don't have a choice anymore.
- Feng confirmed the money.
Over the phone,
not in a formal interview.
Rescind the asylum,
send him back...
- Obstruction of justice.
- Is that what Galich said?
Definitely how it will be perceived.
And anything we do that looks
like a failure to cooperate
amplifies that perception.
I just don't want
our marriage put on display.
Look, Dunbar will ask
if I brought up China. I didn't.
So Larkin can only help
to exonerate me.
And if the marriage counseling
ends up in her report, so be it.
- We can survive that.
- But he prescribed us medication.
- Technically, not us.
- You took mine, Garrett.
Larkin wrote the prescription
to me knowing you would.
Wait, have you mentioned it?
The medication?
- Claire?
- I'm sorry, but she's the only person
I can talk to who really
understands what it's like...
All the more reason
we have to waive the privilege.
If they leak this, we can't
control the information.
- Claire wouldn't do that.
- Don't underestimate her.
If they were going to, don't you think
they would have done it by now?
She dropped the sexual assault
bill to reduce pressure on us.
That may have been
what she told you.
They're not going
to say anything.
I'm begging you, Garrett,
don't waive the privilege.
The things we talked about
were so intimate.
- Imagine if the kids...
- I know, but Tricia...
When we ran, I knew every aspect
of our lives would be under scrutiny,
but I thought we could
protect at least this.
What happens in here...
I'll protect us.
Whatever I have to do.
You have to believe that.
We checked the USB dongle.
The code you're claiming
infected the data center isn't there.
I programmed the code to
self-erase as soon as it hit the server.
It was gone before
Lucas was in cuffs.
You don't believe me?
This is one of the most
sophisticated firewalls in the world.
Even if your code did get you in there,
you couldn't break it down.
Your wife uses AT&T.
- So does her lover.
- What?
She's over there right now.
Jonathan Kemp.
It's her chiropractor, right?
Want to see
their texts to each other?
- No.
- Oh, I see, you already know.
I don't blame you for not making a fuss,
with the kids still at home.
But you walked my code
right through that door,
into 32 million people's phones.
And that's on you,
and it's on the FBI,
and it's a shit storm that will bring
the bureau right in front of Congress.
So you tell me, how much is
making that disappear worth?
You have a hundred years hanging over your
head, extorting the FBI won't help you.
Did Douglas Stamper tell you
to set up Lucas Goodwin?
Counterterrorism Director, that's
a big step up from White House Liaison.
- I think you had a helping hand.
- Not true.
Keep lying.
Meanwhile, here's what I want.
One... I'm no longer your bitch.
Two, all of my charges
are dropped.
Three, all of Barrett Brown's
charges are dropped.
- That's up to the US attorney.
- Figure it out.
If I'm hearing you correctly,
you'd like to keep Larkin's testimony
focused on the money laundering.
Which I never brought up,
because I knew nothing about it.
But your concern is other
matters, private matters.
Which are irrelevant
to the investigation.
I can't prevent Dunbar from
asking what she's going to ask.
Of course not, Bill.
The most I can do is ask
Dr. Larkin how he would
respond to certain questions.
But he's a smart man. He'll
understand what I'm getting at.
And this approach keeps us within the law?
We're not tampering with testimony?
It's a fine line,
- but I'll stay on the right side of it.
- Thanks.
He shut me out, Frank,
just like he did with you.
My undersecretary has been
assigned full diplomatic authority.
A temporary setback, Cathy.
Where I go, you go.
At this very moment, the president
is in the Situation Room.
China responded to Feng's asylum
exactly the way I predicted.
They're doubling their naval
presence off the coast of Yonaguni.
And you know who isn't in
the Situation Room? You and I, Frank.
You're thinking about where we
are instead of where we're headed.
Now, that isn't the Catherine Durant
I waltzed with at the Jefferson Ball.
She understood potential.
She had her eyes
toward the future.
I told that Catherine Durant that
we needed her in the State Department.
We still need her.
I wish I knew where she was,
because she's not the Catherine Durant
sitting in front
of me right now.
But I'll tell you something.
If she doesn't show up soon,
I'm just gonna have to keep waltzing alone
because I'm done trying to
convince this woman in front of me...
...to take my arm.
Oh, don't let me keep you.
I'm here.
I'm not going anywhere, Frank.
You still have access
to the presidential briefing?
Yes, I have it right here.
Walk me through everything
that's going on with China.
Feng is in play now.
We might be able to use him.
- How?
- I don't know yet.
But he's clearly valuable to Beijing,
which makes him valuable to us.
- Nothing about Xander Feng?
- Never.
Daniel Lanagin? Raymond Tusk?
We only discussed
their marriage,
nothing about the business
of the White House.
Any oblique reference
to work-related pressures
he was feeling?
He said he wasn't getting
as much sleep as he'd like.
Did you ever prescribe
him any medication?
As I've always stated,
I provided religious counsel.
I understand,
but I'm asking about medication.
How is this relevant?
I'm trying to assess whether his
judgment may have been impaired.
In my opinion, he and his wife
were dealing with standard marital issues.
That's not what
I asked, Dr. Larkin.
So I will ask for a third time,
and let me be more specific,
was any medication prescribed or taken
as a result of your counseling session,
by the president
of the United States?
His faculties were operating at
100 percent, if that's what you're asking.
Has anyone from the
Administration spoken to you?
- How do you mean?
- About this deposition.
Has anyone approached you,
coached you?
If you tell me now, I will qualify that
as a timely declaration.
- I'd like to leave.
- The president waived his privilege.
- But I'm here voluntarily.
- Dr. Larkin, at first you wouldn't
talk to me because it violated
your ethical code, I respect that,
but let me ask you,
as a man of faith,
is deliberately lying to me
an exception to that code?
Because that is what you're doing
by refusing to share the truth.
- I don't understand.
- It wasn't going to pass.
But you said
we almost had the votes.
We needed to be 100 percent
solid, and we weren't.
If the bill failed,
that would set us back.
We need to accept
incremental reform.
You sound
just like Jackie Sharp.
I'm actually
working with her now.
- She's a powerful ally for us to have.
- After what she did to me?
After what she said about you?
If I let the things people say
about me get under my skin,
I wouldn't be able
to leave my own home.
You know how this will go.
Everyone will say, great, we did
something, which is really nothing.
They'll pat themselves
on the back and they'll forget about it.
We helped put this on the radar.
I thought we were doing
something real, changing people's lives.
How naive, right? But at least
I didn't want to give up.
Maybe Jackie Sharp is right,
you are a fucking coward.
I'm the one that pulled
you out from under the covers.
You were hiding, you and your pills.
You tell yourself whatever you need to.
I'm sorry.
There were political realities
we couldn't ignore.
Do you ever wonder why
so many people hate Washington?
It's because of people like you
using phrases like that.
Raymond?
I'd turn the lights on, but when you're
paying for the room with the best view,
you might as well
make the most of it.
I've never been in
the penthouse here, have you?
What's going on?
Do you know why I'm in DC?
Oh, it's OK, Remy, there's nothing you
can say that I don't already know.
Feng is on his way to testify.
Whatever Seth has told you,
don't believe a word of it.
What might he have told me
that I shouldn't believe?
You met with
the vice president in a church,
- don't pretend you didn't.
- Playing both sides?
- Raymond, look.
- I want to hear you say it.
That you met with Frank.
I'll talk to you, Raymond,
but not with him here.
Leave us.
- Should I hold the elevator for you?
- Go fuck yourself.
OK, you can take the stairs.
- They're toying with you, Raymond.
- No doubt,
but so are you, Remy.
I wanted to lead Frank on, give
him a false sense of security.
If you're going to lie,
lie better than that.
They want to tear us apart.
I don't blame you for wanting
to keep your options open,
but clearly you have bought
the wrong insurance policy.
Don't shoot yourself
in the foot like this.
Your foot,
and you're holding the gun.
- Now go some place else to bleed.
- You want to talk about blood?
How much have you spilled
in this war with Frank?
All I've tried to do
is keep the peace.
You could've let him
have the upper hand.
What would that have really
cost you, other than your pride?
Such a shame.
You have just made 42 billion
enemies, Remy, and some change.
Thirty-nine billion, Raymond.
Your market cap is shrinking.
White House counsel Bill Galich
was called into questioning this morning
by Special Prosecutor
Heather Dunbar.
According to Dunbar's office,
there are suspicions that Galich
may have tampered
with witness testimony.
The witness in question
is Dr. Thomas Larkin,
a reverend and therapist who allegedly
conducted secret marriage counseling
sessions for the president
and First Lady.
The White House counsel wouldn't
be manipulating testimony
without explicit direction
from the Oval Office.
And just as disconcerting is the fact
that our president is seeking
psychological treatment, and chose to
hide this from the American people.
If we can't trust him about that,
how do we know he wasn't involved
in a money laundering scheme?
How do we know he's mentally fit to lead?
And most important, how can he
enforce the law when he's breaking it?
I believe our colleagues in the
House certainly have enough
to consider
articles of impeachment.
Both trust and laws
have been broken.
Whatever the House decides to do,
we must hold this president accountable.
Fully support the president, will stand
by him no matter what comes his way.
Put that in, put it out.
And get me Ayla Sayyad.
And as for Remy, let's let him
wither on the vine a little longer.
In the meantime, have his better
half come by the house tomorrow.
- Raymond?
- No, Jackie.
Mr. Tusk.
Well, Ms. Dunbar,
in 67 years on this planet,
I have never once
been issued a subpoena.
I can now cross that
off my bucket list.
This interview is being
recorded and sealed.
As the subpoena mentioned,
Mr. Tusk, I spoke with Xander Feng.
He verified that you were
his partner in laundering Chinese money
to political
super PACs since 2005.
How would you respond
to his allegations?
My client exercises his right
to plead the Fifth Amendment.
Did you ever use these contributions
to bargain for political favors?
My client exercises his right
to plead the Fifth Amendment.
What was your relationship
with Daniel Lanagin?
My client exercises his right
to plead the Fifth Amendment.
I don't even remember
why I came over here.
- You mean when you first showed up?
- No, to the kitchen.
I'm sorry.
- Please don't think that I don't love you.
- Then why? I don't get it.
Everything's been so fast.
And...
I don't know, it's hard to explain.
But I'm not ready for this...
- That's bullshit.
- No, it's not.
I'm still trying to figure out
this new life, and this is too confusing.
This is the only thing
that's clear and you know it.
You're afraid,
but it's good to be afraid...
I need you to leave, OK?
For your own good.
I'm just going to hurt you.
I have thicker skin
than you can even imagine.
Please don't make this harder
than it has to be.
Everything was fine yesterday.
It's so sudden.
- It's like it's coming out of nowhere.
- Well, it's not.
I've been thinking
about it for a while.
No, you haven't.
I would've sensed it.
Would you please,
please, please just go?
- Just tell me what's going on.
- I don't expect you to understand!
- Maybe if you try...
- I don't want you here! OK?
I don't love you
the way that you love me!
I was using you because it felt good
to have you around, but it was selfish!
I said the words because
I knew you wanted to hear them,
but I didn't mean them and I
don't want to keep saying them.
I'm gonna go for a walk
while you pack your stuff.
No, I don't want anything
that's been here.
Lisa.
There was a steaming
mist in all the hollows,
and it had roamed in its
forlornness up the hill,
like an evil spirit,
seeking rest and finding none.
A clammy
and intensely cold mist...
...it made its slow way through
the air in ripples that visibly followed...
and overspread one another, as the waves
of an unwholesome sea might do.
It was dense enough to shut out everything
from the light of the coach-lamps...
I'm surprised you wanted
to speak to me.
I haven't been the biggest
friend of the administration.
Isn't that the very best
reason to speak with you?
- I'd like to begin recording.
- By all means.
A number of political analysts predict
that the House Judiciary Committee
will commence with hearings
on articles of impeachment.
Let's just stop right there.
So these analysts you speak of,
they're making predictions prior to
Dunbar's report even being released.
That could take months.
There's no way the Judiciary
will sit on this for that long.
And isn't that the fundamental
flaw with these hearings?
The Committee feels compelled
to act because of hypotheses
advanced by those in the media,
such as yourself.
I can't speak for all of my colleagues,
but I'm just reporting facts.
Well, you may call them facts,
but if we're being honest...
In every article and interview,
I report alleged activities.
And if you repeat allegations enough,
again and over and over and over,
people start to believe they're
true. That's human nature.
I've done my research. Xander Feng
admitted to the money laundering.
But you're no longer writing
about Xander Feng, are you?
You're writing about
the administration.
The truth is these hearings have
been initiated by the press.
And my fear is that the President
will be tried by the press.
- Do you believe he's innocent?
- Absolutely.
I said so in my written
statement, and I say so again now.
The White House counsel has denied
coaching Dr. Larkin, but according...
Whatever comes to light, it will only
prove the president's innocence,
and I'll tell you why.
I have never known anyone
more honest, ethical,
and patriotic
than Garrett Walker.
His reverence for the Constitution
and the laws of this country
are surpassed by none.
Tricia and I have been blessed
with a strong and loving marriage,
but even strong marriages
face challenges.
Like millions of Americans, we sought
counseling from a spiritual advisor,
one who happened also
to be a professional therapist.
Over the years, we have often turned
to our faith in times of adversity.
Many have criticized us,
but would you rather have
a president that doesn't ask for help?
I ask for help
from my wife every day.
We've relied on one another
for 23 years,
we've raised two beautiful
children together,
endured the
campaign trails together.
From the state capital in
Denver, to the nation's capital,
we've always been
at each other's side.
I married this man for the same reason
that so many of you voted for him:
because he's a man of God,
because he believes in family...
...because he is
compassionate and loving.
Now, none of us are
perfect: I'm not, Tricia's not,
although she certainly
comes close.
Good morning, Mr. Feng.
I won't ignore
what makes me human,
that's a form of blindness.
Good leadership means tackling
my imperfections head on.
Not bad for a man on the run.
You mean a man with immunity.
Wherever you're most comfortable.
We have a lot to discuss.
I do so with open eyes,
just as I love with open eyes...
...my wife,
my Maker and my country.
Come in.
Thank you, Meechum.
Jackie, in these circumstances,
normally I would come to you,
but we need to keep a public
distance for the time being.
I thought I was here to discuss
the sexual assault bill.
- You are.
- Among other things.
I see.
- There's a price.
- We don't think of it that way.
I'm going to support your bill,
no matter what you say today.
- Regarding?
- Impeachment.
- Well, if it goes to the Judiciary...
- It most definitely will.
I'm not sure about that. Did you
see the president's address?
- We did.
- I think it will help,
stop the bleeding.
Impeachment can be defeated.
But that's what
we need to avoid.
You want impeachment.
Why fight a losing battle?
- We have a majority in the House.
- We do now,
but not if this party fails to distance
itself from a toxic president...
We're thinking ahead here.
It's why I came to you
about the bill,
because it wasn't worth
burning a bridge over.
In the long run, we have
a lot more to gain by working together.
I don't understand. You said
in the Telegraph article...
I had to. My office is three
doors down from the president's,
I can't publicly deride him.
You want me to do it.
We want you to do what
you do so well: whip the votes.
I can't abandon the president.
If the party rescues him, we'll lose
50 seats in the House in the midterms.
You will lose your position
in the leadership
and it will take us a decade to
regain the trust of the electorate.
All we're asking
is that you have an open mind.
Claire kept an open mind and you'll
pass sexual assault reform as a result.
- You can't possibly compare impeachment...
- It's an illustration, Jackie,
of what the future looks like.
What we offer is progress,
with a promise of more to come.
It's only the beginning, Jackie.
Ruthless pragmatism, remember?
That's why I wanted you
to be the whip.
The three of us,
we're cut from the same cloth.
Mr. Vice President,
what you're asking
is just shy of treason.
Just shy, which is politics.
Oh, be careful, it's delicate.
What is it?
Something I've been working on
for a very long time,
and it's nearly finished.
Jackie... help us finish it.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player