Previously on House of Cards...
If a bullet comes my way
tomorrow, it will not be an accident,
and I must be quick to duck.
Do you know how Grant
defeated Lee?
He had more men.
And he was willing to let them die.
It was butchery, not strategy,
which won the war.
You used to be an alcoholic, correct?
- Not used to be.
- Do you miss it?
You both disappointed me.
Greatly.
Raymond, are you still there?
That's the first time
he's ever hung up on me...
Oh, I feel for you.
I just got off the phone with
a guy named Seth Grayson.
Did Dr. Marbury perform an abortion
for Claire Underwood?
- He kept a journal.
- That journal is my version of a résumé.
This is gonna work.
I don't have a choice,
but you still do.
You wanted to see inside one, right?
This needs to be clean, Doug.
One fall of the axe.
- On the ground.
And the butchery begins.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
We've got an energy crisis, Frank.
And what the White House needs...
The president chose
to remain tough on China.
-  No, you forced him to.
- You chose Feng.
You're the one who
put me in a room with him.
The cook can't blame
his ingredients
if he doesn't like
how they taste together.
If samarium prices don't reduce,
the market will have no choice
but to compensate.
That's bad for everyone
who owns an air conditioner.
You should speak to the
president himself.
Well, the president hasn't placed
much value on my advice lately.
I'm in the same boat
as you, Raymond.
Yeah, difference being
you've got an office
three doors down from the Oval.
Let's work together,
for Christ sakes.
I'm willing to put Spotsylvania
behind us if you are.
-  I want nothing more.
- Then you'll talk to him?
- Look, I'm late for a meeting, Raymond.
-  Yes or no, Frank?
- I can't guarantee he'll listen.
- That's not a yes.
But it's better than a no.
Any pugilist worth his salt
knows when someone's on the ropes,
that's when you throw a combination
to the gut and a left hook to the jaw.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Samarium is the last thing
they'll let go of.
As long as our energy prices
rise, they have the leverage.
Why don't we offer nothing?
Move toward attrition?
If China doesn't show
at the refunding auction,
- long-term interest rates will spike.
- - And in a week,
yields on our ten-year notes
will pierce the seven percent threshold.
That could happen. But if we
go soft now, that will happen.
- You mean go on the offensive.
- We should at least consider it.
The Chinese don't like carrots?
Let's see how they like the stick.
What might that look like?
We could raise inspection
rates on foodstuffs.
- Hold them in ports till they rot.
- How much of a raise?
Twenty percent
if we wanna draw blood.
Bury the move with increased
spot checks all the way around.
These sort of tactics don't
solve the immediate problem.
People are paying triple
the standard rate for electric.
We'll hit a fivefold increase
by August.
What if you, Mr. President,
by executive order,
purchase samarium
through a third party?
Cut the Chinese out, force them to
either raise their prices worldwide
or lower them
to keep direct flow with us.
We stockpile samarium
for defense purposes, of course,
and quietly sell what we don't
need to our friends in nuclear energy.
- At a discount.
- - A subsidy for nuclear power?
The richest of the rich?
How's that gonna play?
Dealing with a national crisis. We can't
get sidetracked with public opinion.
It would show China
we're willing to wait this out.
Do we have the resources?
I'd have to run the numbers,
anticipate fluctuations,
- consider different models...
- Your best guess.
We do, for a moderate stockpile.
All right. Draw up a request
from the Defense Department.
- Yes, sir.
- Linda, draft the executive order.
And, Cathy, make sure we have a third-party
conduit to purchase the samarium.
We'll go through India.
That won't fly well
with Pakistan.
I'll alert them in advance.
As long as they're in the loop,
we'll be all right.
- Not that we owe them any favors.
- All right, let's get to work.
Come on, Betsy.
Three additional counts under Section E?
Three is low. It reflects a narrow
interpretation of criminal intent.
- Your client broke into a data center.
- And what's the offer?
- I'm not doing a plea.
- Will you let me handle this?
They don't want a trial.
The questions I'll be raising,
loud and clear, in open court...
- Lucas, please.
- We have our own questions, Mr. Goodwin.
For example, what were
you doing with these?
- I didn't take these.
- They were in your apartment.
Underwood took them.
Do you really expect a jury
to believe that?
- He did. They were having an affair.
- Are they gonna see them
for what they are? Proof of
your obsession with Ms. Barnes
and the ludicrous conspiracy you have
concocted to explain her death.
Tell us what you're offering.
Client pleads to one
count under Section E
for breaking into a data center.
One count for fraud
for stealing a password
from the Herald.
Ten years under Section E,
ten years for fraud, served concurrently.
Eligible for parole in seven.
I'd like to speak
to my client alone.
Cameras and recording equipment
off, please.
I'll introduce the president.
Then he'll introduce you.
If he's there, we can't
mention the military.
- Just the endemic problem nationwide.
- Of course. I understand.
Good. So we should go
through these speeches
and make sure
that there's nothing...
- Hi, Mrs. Underwood.
- Hello, Christina.
- Mrs. Walker, you asked for me?
- We need to confirm
whether the president's
gonna make it to New Orleans.
- This Friday, correct?
- Yes.
But I know he had a cabinet meeting
this morning, so I imagine...
- I'll talk to Linda right away.
- Thanks.
I know you want Garrett there,
but with this energy crisis...
- No. It's not that.
- What?
- I shouldn't say anything.
- Well, now you have to tell me.
I've just never been
very fond of her. Christina.
- Why not?
- Peter Russo.
I just have a thing about women
who sleep with their bosses.
Anyway, I'm sure whatever
they had was genuine.
It's none of my business, 'cause
if she's doing a good job,
- that's all that matters, right?
- Garrett seems to think she is.
Then I should just keep
my feelings to myself.
So, if the president
is not able to be there,
that could be a silver lining for us. We
won't have to hold back with the military.
Phone taps, video surveillance,
premeditation, sustained intent.
They've got you cold.
If I plead out, that's it.
No one hears the truth.
You don't plead,
no one will hear you, period.
Not until you're
in your seventies.
Have you talked
to Hammerschmidt yet?
You're in no position
to make demands.
- It's not up to you.
- All you'll do is piss them off.
Look...
We've got a good deal here.
A great deal, considering what you did.
You should take it
before they change their mind.
Tom Hammerschmidt. I talk to him
or we're going to trial.
Raise your arms, please.
- You have something here?
- My neck chain.
- May I see it?
- Really? I gotta take off my tie.
I need to see it, sir.
- You're a good Christian, Remy.
- My mother's.
- She was the good Christian.
- Well, then you're just the good son.
- Thank you, sir.
- Hot out there, huh?
Ninety-six according to my car.
We had heat like that
back in Gaffney,
but we didn't know
what air conditioning was,
so we just accepted as fact that
summer was meant to be miserable.
- Neat or with water?
- Just the water.
You can hold the bourbon.
We need to find a solution
so that this one isn't miserable
for 300 million people.
I already have found a solution.
Oh, please, Frank.
A samarium subsidy?
- Is that your skepticism or Raymond's?
- Mine, anticipating his.
So you haven't
spoken to him yet.
I want to offer him
something he can agree to.
- Well, he doesn't have much of a choice.
- Why are you cornering him?
I'm cutting the rate by half.
I'd call that liberating him.
You know that's not
how he'll see it.
This trade war
is preventing the refinery
from being approved in Beijing.
His co-venture with Feng is not
our highest priority right now.
A rare earth refinery solves
this crisis permanently.
Three years from now.
Not this summer.
It's not just that. With the subsidy,
he'll break even, at best.
There's no point in doing business
to hover between red and black.
Raymond's profits are an even lower
priority to me than his co-venture.
Tell me what
you're up to, Frank.
There's nothing to gain
by locking horns with Tusk.
Ask your client. It's Tusk
who's locking the horns.
- He's not a man who likes conflict.
- Neither am I.
Then make the ask. 'Cause I know
you don't care about the subsidy.
This is about something bigger.
I'm a good Christian, Remy,
like your mother.
I would tell you the truth
if I wanted more.
- You trying to send a message?
- Perhaps.
- Which is?
- That stubbornness is far more costly
- than obedience.
- Thanks for the water.
- You're on the wrong side, Remy.
- Yeah, well, one of us sure is.
And when the bumblebee
flew home,
all his friends were waiting
with buckets of honey, right?
And he's got his worm friend, and
his mouse friend, and his spider friend,
and his snail friend,
and they all had tons of honey.
- I like his feet.
- - And he looks happier now, right?
- Yeah!
- Yeah?
- They're funny, right?
- So they all buzzed with happiness,
because life is sweet when
you spend it with your friends.
Right? Can you all buzz your
wings? Buzz your little wings.
Buzz, buzz, buzz,
buzz, buzz, buzz, buzz.
I think it would make
a fluttering noise, like...
- I don't know.
- Your flutters.
It's too hot out here for you
to be doing this, Francis.
I'm keeping hydrated.
- That even regulation?
- It's only half,
but I don't want the press
to see me practicing on the street.
You remember when you threw out
that first pitch in Greenville?
I was wondering how long it
was gonna take to bring that up.
That wasn't even
on national television.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
- What happened in Greenville?
- Oh, the Greenville Drive.
Single A team for the Red Sox.
It was a home game,
I get on the mound...
- You threw from the mound?
- Well, I wanted to throw a real pitch.
- Didn't make it.
- Not even close.
Halfway?
Ball slipped out of my hand
just before I released it.
Went straight up in the air
and hit me on top of the head.
The whole stadium
burst a gut laughing.
- Comic relief pitcher.
- Oh, that's very clever, Meechum.
- Don't tell Claire.
- I heard that.
- You're really good with them.
- Nah.
Did you see Robbie,
when they were finger-painting?
He pulled down his pants and
started painting himself blue.
- No!
- Yeah. I hope I got it all off.
I'm sure Alex and Daria
don't care.
They let him run around
naked all the time.
Yeah, but probably not
with his Smurf ass.
Probably not.
What do we want to do
for dinner tonight?
I've got some leftover chicken
or we could order pizza.
- Pizza. No dishes.
- Yeah.
I'm really sorry, I totally forgot I've
got a friend picking me up tonight.
- I completely blanked.
- That's fine.
- I'm really sorry.
- Don't sweat it.
- Is it your boyfriend?
- No, no... just an old friend.
- Can I meet him?
- Um... He's... kinda shy. I don't...
- ...know if he'd be up for...
- Totally cool. Don't worry about it.
- We'll just do dinner another night.
- All right.
- I'll see you tomorrow?
- Yeah. You know where I'll be.
- Yeah.
- OK.
- How long?
- Couple of months.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I can't go to church?
Anywhere you interact with other
people opens us up to risk.
I'm just supposed to slave away
at the fucking call center
- and then lock myself in the apartment.
- Don't get dramatic.
I like the Fellowship, OK?
There's nothing to worry about there.
All it takes is one person's
cousin to visit from Lynchburg.
Someone you went to school with, or
some client that you spent the night with.
- Those guys would never end up here.
- You don't know that.
- Yeah, I do.
- You ended up here, didn't you?
What?
- I can't live like this.
- Yes, you can.
You're a strong girl.
That's it?
That's everything?
I know, you've heard it before.
As a friend, Lucas,
not as a reporter.
Now I dig.
I make the phone calls.
I do the legwork.
They treating you OK?
- It's fine.
- That's not what I asked.
They're pushing
the plea deal pretty hard.
How seriously are you
considering it?
I want to see how this
article impacts things.
- What does your lawyer say?
- He thinks that's a bad idea,
that I should take the plea.
- Maybe you should listen to him.
- No. I want the article.
-  That I'm certain of.
- All right.
- I better get to it then.
- Thank you.
You need to know, I'm gonna treat
this the way I would any other story.
Whatever the facts bear.
You might not like what I write.
- I get that.
- I'll let you read it first.
- Then you can decide.
- That's all I'm asking.
Hang in there.
Can you wipe this shit off?
Please!
And the other nuclear
providers are on board?
Most. Except Raymond's
company and a couple of others.
Lakeport Nuclear, Wolf Springs.
Now, I can't prove it,
but I am absolutely sure
they're colluding.
Raymond wants to embarrass me.
I offer a solution,
nuclear lobby turns its back.
He has a right to refuse,
Mr. President.
What he cannot do is manipulate
the energy market.
You want to put pressure
on the distribution side.
More than pressure. Ban vertical
integration entirely.
We don't have that
regulatory power.
We add an antitrust agreement
to the emergency energy bill.
We break up the regional supply
and distribution monopolies
like the Bell System.
It'll be challenged immediately
in the courts.
We don't need it to pass,
we just need to threaten it.
See if he falls into line.
Is there a way to do that without
it making its way into the news?
I don't want the world's wealthiest
one percent on my phone sheet.
There is absolutely a way
to do that, sir.
Here you go.
- Crowded for a Tuesday night.
- We keep it at 65 degrees.
- And it's free.
- If you call 18 bucks
- for a vodka soda free.
- Still cheaper than a Pepco bill.
- Depends on how many you have.
- You trying to get us drunk?
Drunker you are, bigger you tip.
I don't have to be drunk
to appreciate good service.
- I'll get your change.
- No, you won't.
- Thank you.
- You're shameless.
Makes me a good lobbyist.
Cheers.
So, Jackie... bold move,
but it won't work.
You know we can pass this
amendment in a heartbeat.
Maybe, but no one will comply.
It'll get overturned.
- Big fuss for nothing.
- It might get overturned,
- but it gets ink along the way.
- One thing about Raymond Tusk
is he doesn't give two
bird shits about public opinion.
- His stockholders do.
- They'd jump in a pit of snakes
and light themselves on fire
if he gave the word.
All I'm asking is
that you convey our intentions.
Why me? Frank could
easily pick up the phone.
You still call him Frank?
Not to his face, which I try
to keep to a minimum.
Don't you appreciate having
an ear in the White House?
I would, if I had an ear.
But lately all I've got is a mouth.
Yeah. He's not
the best listener, is he?
- Try working for him.
- You were on his staff?
Eight years. Press secretary.
Before you joined Congress.
That explains a lot.
- Like what?
- Like a lot.
- I'll take that as an insult.
- You should.
That's it? You abandoning me?
No, I'm buying the next round.
I can't accept
gifts from lobbyists
without reciprocating.
Plus, I'm a good wingman.
This gets you more face time
with the barmaid.
You already got 'em ready?
Your guys gave me the
heads-up you were comin'.
Well, I hope that they didn't
wake you earlier than usual.
Fuck, man, with this heat,
I ain't sleepin' much anyway.
- What? No AC at home?
- I got a unit.
I just don't wanna pay
the damn bill.
It's not too bad in here,
all things considered.
That's 'cause we in the shade.
You get outside a couple hours
from now on that pavement,
fry your damn dick off
from three feet below.
Must be bad over that grill.
I can't tell the
difference no more.
I tell you what, though,
stuff goes down 'round here
when the mercury pop a hundred.
Man who beat his wife at home
will beat her right out on the street.
- Brings out the animal in us?
- That ain't no joke.
What used to wake me up?
Gunshots.
Now you know what does it?
People fuckin'.
Moanin' and screamin'
like goddamn cats in the alley.
You know what they say,
when you get hot and sweaty,
it make you ripe and ready.
- Hey.
- I drank too much.
- We both did.
- Last night didn't happen.
- I know.
When I walk out that door,
it's business as usual.
- No special treatment.
- Don't worry.
You won't need
a restraining order.
I'm surprised you didn't
go for the waitress.
- You're much sexier.
- Yeah, OK.
She works for tips.
You run Congress.
- Only half of it.
- That's half more than she does.
So it's not my body.
- Those legs don't hurt.
- You're so full of shit.
OK. It's your voice.
- My voice?
- Mm-hm. It does something to me.
Let me know what Tusk
has to say.
Business hasn't started yet.
You haven't walked out that door yet.
Watch me.
Thank you, Jackie.
We're going to the White House.
Little John on the move.
We raise the bet.
We get FERC involved.
- An investigation?
- We don't need Congress
- to activate the regulatory commission.
- But a price-fixing review?
- That would take months.
- Again, it's the threat,
- not the actuality.
- He'll employ the same logic.
Draw it out,
fight back with appeals.
But he'll have to divulge his
accounting if FERC takes action.
Now, no businessman
wants to open up his books,
especially one with $43 billion.
This is getting out of hand, Frank.
We shouldn't be duking it out with Raymond.
- Maybe we should talk to him.
- That's exactly what he wants.
To force himself
back into the mix.
What's to be gained
by shutting him out?
The simple lesson
that you cannot strong-arm
the president
of the United States.
We can't devolve
to a pissing contest.
I'm gonna call Raymond.
Invite him to Washington.
He won't accept anything
but total surrender.
- I'm making the call.
- Don't put yourself in that position.
I know how to maintain
the integrity of my office.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Mr. President.
Two minutes with the president and
Tusk may be back in his good graces.
I need to disrupt the nuptials
and prevent a second marriage.
- Christina?
- Good to see you.
Oh, please.
- You look great.
- Thank you.
- How are things?
- Great.
Linda works me to the bone,
but that's what I signed up for.
Well, from what I've heard,
you're doing a great job.
Well, that's really nice
to hear.
Look, I wanted to talk to you
about Tricia.
I'm sure you've noticed that she's still
sort of adjusting to her role.
You mean her... confidence.
I think it would be great
if you reached out to her.
Just let her know that you're there
if there's anything she needs.
I don't really know her that well.
I mean, we've met, but I...
That's OK.
Maybe just tell her
that you enjoy
working for the president,
and you're there to be of help
to her in any way you can.
You don't think that's a little,
I don't know, brash?
- How?
- For me to just approach her like that?
No. Not at all.
You've reached the Skorsky residence.
Leave a message after the beep.
Tom Hammerschmidt again. I'm
still trying to reach Janine.
Still important. Thank you.
Hammerschmidt's been
calling our press office all day.
I don't want a story to come out
any more than you do.
We lose a major asset
if it does.
Can you squash it
for security reasons?
Not once it's been shared with
the press. First Amendment crap.
Ward isn't making things any easier.
She wants a notch in her belt.
We're giving her one.
Not Goodwin. She wants Orsay.
Most-wanted list for six years.
I'll handle Hammerschmidt.
You need to make sure Goodwin
takes the plea.
If 35 with no parole doesn't
scare the piss out of him,
- I don't know what will.
- Then don't try to scare him.
Remove hope from the equation.
I tried to keep this contained.
I didn't anticipate
Hammerschmidt.
- Is Ms. Skorsky cooperating with him?
- He's called her.
My guy at the bureau says
they haven't actually spoken.
At least not on the phone.
- If this goes to court...
- That won't happen, sir.
It will if he publishes.
I'm bringing this to you
because I can't control Hammerschmidt.
I don't know what to do.
We need to invite a full-frontal
attack. Then hold the line.
- You want to speak to him?
- Face-to-face. Just the two of us.
- I don't think that's a good idea, sir.
- You have a better idea?
- No, sir.
- We can't avoid the battle,
but we can choose
the battlefield.
Set up a meeting at the White
House. We'll intimidate him with formality.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Vice President?
I know you don't have patience
for apologies,
but I'm sorry if I've
let you down in any way.
Let's concentrate
on what's in front of us.
I'll let you know
when I have a time set up.
- As soon as possible.
- Yes, sir.
So this is a sort of outline
to the larger piece?
With questions on the next page.
- We're off the record?
- Yes, off the record.
Now, Tom, I know that you care
about this young man,
and I respect you as a
journalist, but these questions?
Why don't you just ask me
when I stopped strangling people's pets.
Sir, the death
of Congressman Russo...
You mean my friend, Peter Russo,
whose suicide left two
small children with no father.
No, I will not answer
questions about that.
Yes?
I'm aware of that. No, tell her
I'll call her right back.
Two minutes. Secretary Durant.
- I can wait outside...
- No, let's finish.
Now, if you decide
to print any of this,
assuming you find an outlet
that's willing to, then yes,
it might cause me
a headache for a day.
But I will not engage.
And I think it will only
prove to highlight
how ridiculous Mr. Goodwin's
claims are.
I pity him. I truly do.
I think he needs help.
I've interviewed many mentally
ill people. He's not one of them.
Well, I would suggest that you
read your own article again.
He's distressed.
There's a difference.
Look, I understand. It must be
a terrible blow to see him in prison,
- but Tom...
- Rachel Posner exists.
I haven't been able to find her,
but I've proven she's not a fantasy.
The same goes for Roy Kapeniak.
These people were born.
They have Social Security
numbers, past addresses.
So does everyone from California to Maine.
Have I conspired with all of them?
You have to admit there are some
troubling details regarding the DUI.
You know, people say the same
thing about Area 51.
You can conjure up little gray
men if you really want to.
- Did you kill Peter Russo?
- Tom, you're embarrassing yourself.
Did you kill Zoe Barnes?
I've given you more time
than this nonsense deserves.
- I have to ask these questions.
- The only question I would ask is:
does this sort of article
hurt or help Mr. Goodwin?
You have to do what you think
is right. But I hope you can understand
if I don't demean myself
by taking any of it seriously.
I appreciate your time,
Mr. Vice President.
- How'd it go?
- I did my part. Now put it to bed, Doug.
I won't submit myself
to this sort of exposure again.
- Yes, sir.
- Has Tusk met with the president yet?
- Linda said they're meeting at 4:30.
- Call Remy.
Make sure he doesn't get on
his plane before I see him.
I'm on it.
Oh, Mrs. Walker?
I just wanted to say how rewarding it's
been working here in the West Wing.
And I'm so proud to be working
for your husband.
Thank you. I know he
appreciates all your hard work.
Well, now that I'm working
so closely with him,
if there's anything
I can do for you,
anything that would make yours
or his life easier...
- Just keep doing what you're doing.
- Truly, anything.
I want you to know you can
rely on me. Both of you.
I know that.
Thank you, Christina.
Thanks, Mrs. Walker.
- Oh, here. Let me.
- Oh, it's just my hands...
- Are they bothering you?
- Yeah, probably gonna get rain tonight.
I'll get it.
Um, no, just keep
the broth moving.
Agent Green, FBI. Do you have
a moment, Ms. Skorsky?
- Yeah, I...
- May we come in?
I just need to
turn the stove off.
- Stay in here, Mom.
- Who is it?
Just stay in here.
Only that once?
And I haven't seen him since,
or returned his calls.
- How many times has he tried to call you?
- I don't know.
Eight or nine times, maybe.
And then he stopped after a while.
Did he mention anything about
Heronymous Bot or Gavin Orsay?
You know, I think
I should talk to a lawyer.
Right now you're not suspected
of being an accomplice.
If you call a lawyer,
we might have to reconsider.
- He mentioned some hacker.
- Heronymous.
I told him I thought it
was a bad idea to contact him.
- Are you aware of what he's claiming?
- No.
That you and he
were working together.
That you believe
in this conspiracy theory.
That it was you who received
explicit photos of Ms. Barnes.
Is any of that true?
We need you to come back
to DC with us
and sign this statement in the
presence of the US attorney.
- You want me to call him a liar.
- Isn't he?
I can't do that to him.
We also need you to speak
with Tom Hammerschmidt.
You know what, please, can you
just keep me out of this?
I had nothing to do
with the hacker or the...
Ms. Skorsky, we want
to believe you.
And we will,
if you put all of it in writing.
He's not a criminal. You're
going after the wrong person.
And if you think
that you can intimidate me,
harass me like this in my
own home, I will file a formal complaint.
You're starting to sound
an awful lot like him.
You can't arrest me.
I haven't done anything.
I'd like you to leave.
I have a right to legal counsel
and you haven't presented a warrant.
We can arrest you, Ms. Skorsky,
for abetting an act of cyberterrorism.
Who's going to take care
of your mother
while you're spending the next
three years in courtrooms?
Would you please
raise your arms?
- No, Meechum.
- Sir.
Meechum.
I know you don't want
to shake my hand,
so we'll just skip that part.
The president didn't
mention anything about it.
Why would he?
Better to catch you off guard.
- Then why would you?
- So we can avoid unnecessary conflict.
Garrett's not a good liar.
The gift of a good liar is making people
think you lack a talent for lying.
I know him far better than you, and so
I know what talents he has and lacks.
But let's assume he did lie.
I'm not intimidated
by a FERC investigation.
You'd have grid overload and brownouts
before you could even get a hearing.
You are deliberately keeping
electric prices at inflated rates,
- which is illegal.
- No.
- I'm responding to the free market.
- A regulated free market.
Why are you doing this, Frank?
Remy asked me the same thing.
- You're making this about me.
- This isn't personal, Raymond.
The integrity of our energy
markets is my only concern.
Of course it's personal.
I asked you, personally,
to convince Garrett to pull back
from China.
You personally chose not to.
You personally sabotaged
the summit.
- I have never once in my career...
- You personally advised...
- ...allowed personal...
- ...to push me up against the wall.
Do not try and spin me, Frank!
I am too old to tango!
Then I'll be blunt. Accept the
subsidies or deal with FERC.
There is no third way here.
Are you intentionally trying
to destroy the president?
I'm trying to protect
the president... from you.
This is about the secretary
of state nomination, isn't it?
I'm the vice president now. I don't cry
over what happened in kindergarten.
You're vice president
because I vouched for you.
Because you had no other
options. Political necessity.
- You have 24 hours to decide.
- I'll show myself out.
Hello.
Raymond, this is Claire.
Mrs. Underwood, it is an honor.
Jean... my wife, has been very
taken with your recent efforts.
Well, I'd like
to meet her one day.
She would very much
like that, I'm sure.
- And what about you?
- I'm sorry?
What are your thoughts
about our recent efforts?
Oh. I am in favor of anything
that prevents
unnecessary violence.
It's nice to meet you,
Mrs. Underwood.
And good luck with that
first pitch tonight, Mr. Vice President.
Make it to the plate this time.
Ma'am.
♪ Gave proof through the night ♪
♪ That our flag
was still there ♪
♪ Oh, say does that
star-spangled...♪
- This Kevlar is cooking me.
- We have to use it, sir.
Well, I didn't practice with it.
Now I can hardly rotate my arm.
I should have mentioned it.
I apologize.
If this ball doesn't make it
over the plate, it's your ass.
And what are you doing here?
Don't you have things to do?
Never been to Camden Yards.
♪ And the home of the ♪
♪ Brave ♪
Ladies and gentlemen,
here to throw out the first pitch tonight,
we are honored to introduce
the vice president of the United States,
Frank Underwood!
Boss, boss. Use his ball.
Thank you very much. Where's
the mascot? There you are.
Pleasure.
Beautiful job.
Good evening. Now, I know it's a hot night
and you all want to get to the baseball.
So as soon as I throw this sucker,
grab a drink, enjoy the game,
and best of luck to both teams.
Ah, scratch that.
We're at Camden Yards.
Go Orioles!
Let's go, sir.
We've gotta move!
Got him.
We're on the move.
I'm told the distribution line that
controls the pinch point
caused the outages.
BAPCO, one of your companies.
Yes, sir.
There was a capacity issue.
We're working as quickly
as we can to resolve it.
I've got
three governors calling,
hospitals on emergency power,
so quickly better mean quickly.
The latest estimate I got
was two to three hours,
maybe sooner.
Raymond, was this intentional?
Sir, I know you don't hold me
in the highest regard at the moment,
but I am alarmed
that you could even
entertain such a thought.
Well, the timing makes
coincidence hard to swallow.
There is a heat wave. That always
pushes the grid to its limits.
Let's get the people out of the dark.
Updates every 30 minutes on your progress.
I should inform you, sir, that I may need
to take two of my plants offline tomorrow,
-  for unscheduled maintenance.
- Why? Which ones?
Georgia and Tennessee.
This blackout has put
a great deal of stress on them.
My engineers are concerned
about the seals on the fuel rods.
So we're looking at outages
on the Southeast grid, too?
-  Could be, for a few days.
- That's unacceptable.
Safety comes first.
We don't want an accident.
- Let's get a full report to Linda ASAP.
-  Yes, sir.
Thank you, sir.
- He's toying with you.
- This could be a legitimate safety issue.
He wants a seat back at the
table. Those plants are fine.
Why is he doing this?
We've had our differences,
but something drastic like this?
Well, I did tell him
about the possible FERC action.
- You did what?
- He called me, I answered the call.
Why didn't you inform me
immediately?
He told me you had
a productive talk,
that he was on board
with the subsidy.
I assumed everything was fine.
He was proposing renewed trade
talks. We didn't talk about subsidy at all.
He's playing both of us then.
If he told you he was on board,
why'd you bring up FERC?
I told him I was relieved, that we
could've taken action if he didn't comply.
You think he's fishing, to see
what our next move might be?
I think so, sir. I mean, he is lying
about those two plants in the South.
But we can't guess.
We have to be certain.
Do you want Raymond Tusk
to assess that risk,
or the United States government?
Are you suggesting
we take over his facilities?
There is precedent there.
Woodrow Wilson did it with the
railroads for three full years.
In a time of war.
In a time of emergency,
which is what this is.
The country needs a leader,
Mr. President. Give them one.
Do not bend to Raymond Tusk.
I'm done.
- I said you might not like it.
- It makes me seem crazy.
This is the most
toned-down version.
I tried to be as kind as I
could without being biased.
I don't think you want this
going out into the world.
Can I talk to Janine?
Tell him to go.
He wants you to leave.
- You lied.
- Luca...
You lied to Tom.
You lied to the US attorney.
I didn't know what else to do.
Tell the truth.
They'll arrest me.
They'll discredit
everything I say.
And nobody is going to believe
me more than they believe you.
But we can get the story out there.
Get people asking questions.
No. It'll just look like
two crazy people instead of one.
So you're saving yourself.
I'm trying to save
the both of us.
Please. Take the plea.
- I'm not guilty.
- You are.
You committed a crime.
Multiple crimes.
Not murder.
Take the plea. Be good.
Get out early.
Everybody...
everybody's fucked me.
If I was trying to fuck you,
I wouldn't be here.
He's gonna get away with it,
isn't he?
Yes.
He is.
- I'll take an iced tea if you have any.
- We don't.
I wish I didn't have to keep coming
through back doors like this.
Well, we wouldn't want our
friends in the fourth estate
to know you were here, would we?
Especially since you've gone
to such lengths to remain
above the fray of politics.
You can't seize
the plants, Frank.
We haven't seized anything yet.
We're ready to, but we won't...
if you cooperate.
- It's illegal.
- It's not. You know that.
The president can issue an executive
order in times of emergency.
- I'll fight it in court. - Which will take even
longer than a FERC investigation would.
And in the meantime, you make
nothing from those plants.
We agreed, right here
in this room,
we agreed to work together.
We agreed as men of our word.
And I held up my end of
that bargain until you abandoned me...
I sent Remy to help you.
After I got it passed through
the Senate, with no help from you.
I had to protect my relationship
with the president.
And then you tried to use me
during the summit in Spotsylvania.
I was not put on this earth
to be your best friend,
or to share every piece
of information I have with you.
We agreed to a mutually
beneficial partnership,
that's all.
Yes, and what's
become very clear to me
is that I benefit in no way
from this partnership.
Let's not pretend to be naive.
We both respect self-interest
above all else.
Our versions of that
no longer align.
You are on the verge of making an
irreversible mistake, Mr. Vice President.
I may well be making a mistake.
Who knows?
What I do know is that you'll be
calling Linda and telling her
that you'll accept
the subsidies.
You may have all the money, Raymond,
but I have all the men with guns.
It's a burner.
Pre-dialed. She's expecting.
Oh, and uh, yes...
from last night.
The ball's in your court,
as they say.
Oh, Jesus Christ!
You scared the shit out of me.
Are you supposed to take the
Lord's name in vain like that?
- Leave it on.
- Costs too much.
I'll take care of it.
Goodwin took the plea.
He's going away.
- So does that mean this is all over?
- No.
- We still have to be careful.
- Well, why?
If he's gone, then nobody's
looking for me, right?
Not that we know of.
Until we know, nothing changes.
So what, you just came over here
to get my hopes up?
I came here to make sure that
you don't go to church tonight.
Do you want to fuck me?
- Is that what this is all about?
- No.
- You've done it before.
- That was different.
Stop it.
If there's one thing I know,
it's when a man wants me.
I learned who Rachel
was in church.
She was young and beautiful.
Jacob fell in love with her
while she was watering a lamb and...
...she became his wife after he worked
seven years to earn her hand in marriage.
Rachel had one son, Joseph.
He became a king.
Are you hungry?
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player