Page 43, section 7.
We'd like some clarification.
Section 7 has to do with
the evaluative measures--
"Evaluative measures."
What we're talking about here
are performance standards,
plain and simple.
We can't have that.
We open that can of worms--
Gotta take it out, Frank.
The administration wants it in.
Then we're all wasting
our time.
Well, look, I can cut down
the frequency of testing,
but it's got to be
part of the overall--
That's the thin edge
of a two-ton wedge.
- No way, non-debatable.
- All right, hold on.
There's no harm
in hearing them out, right?
Frank, what do you have
in mind?
We adjust article 4.
Hand me article 4.
We go every three years
instead of two.
Frank, for us to even
consider testing--
Marty, we can't
negotiate time intervals here.
If-- I'm just saying if--
The frequency could never be
more than five years.
Look, five is a little high,
but if you can bend on that--
- Marty.
- Wait, wait, wait. And it's not just frequency.
Veteran teachers would have
to be exempt
if they have a proven record of
excellence with the students.
Well, excuse me for a moment.
Corey, will you take
the reins on this?
Right, so, article 4--
in terms of exceptions--
I've been saying for years
that we should tear it down.
It's vulgar, it's an
embarrassment to the county,
but time and time again
Frank Underwood
has fought to keep it standing.
If it weren't for him,
the Peachoid would've been
replaced ages ago.
And Jessica masters
would still be alive.
The congressman needs
to answer for this tragedy.
What exactly happened?
A 17-year-old girl
ran off the road texting
her boyfriend, and I quote,
"doesn't the Peachoid
look like a giant..."
- And then she lost control of the car.
- Jesus.
Orrin's making a big fuss
in the local press.
And he's pushing
the parents to sue Gaffney.
Sue Gaffney?
It's in his own jurisdiction.
It's worth throwing
Gaffney under the bus
to drag you into the mess.
He's after my seat again.
Has he learned
absolutely nothing?
It's a full-on smear
campaign, boss.
He's out to destroy you.
With this? It's a peach,
for Christ sake.
Let him make a fool
out of himself.
No, he will make a fool
out of you.
If he spins this right,
gets national coverage--
National coverage?
It's a joke.
And you will be the butt of it.
We can't afford that right now,
not when you're in the spotlight
with the education bill.
This thing has caused me
so much damn trouble.
- I know.
- So who should I call, parents?
Phone call's
not going to cut it.
- You need to go down there.
- Can it wait until Monday?
We get on this thing right now,
we can contain it.
We wait until Monday,
then there's no way to know how much
this is going to blow up on us.
I can't go down to Gaffney.
The unions have just--
- We postpone--
- They're gonna be livid.
Marty's reasonable, okay?
He will explain to them.
And they're just supposed
to understand and accept
that I had to get up
from the negotiating table
because some two-bit county
administrator wants to--
I don't want
to interrupt you, sir,
but this is not just
about Orrin.
It's about the parents.
Now, you think
about the lawsuit.
What happens
if you have to testify?
Subpoenas, depositions.
You get dragged
into a court battle,
there is no education bill.
We can't ignore this.
I just hate
this small-ball crap.
It's called the what?
The peach what?
The Peachoid.
It's a giant water tower
in the shape of a peach.
Oh, wow.
I just googled it.
"The Peachoid."
She was 17, Linda.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
- I need another week.
- No, that's not going to work.
The president makes
his speech on Tuesday.
We've already announced.
Speeches can be rescheduled.
We have to show some progress
on education, Frank.
The first hundred days
is almost over.
If we push back the speech,
it'll look like we're
spinning our wheels.
All right,
I'll work something out.
Thank you, Linda.
Frank, these are the heads
of the two largest teachers
unions in the country.
- I understand.
- They flew here on a weekend.
Doug will lead the charge.
Congressman Phillips is well vetted--
They flew here to see you,
Frank.
You're managing this bill.
Put this in the other bag.
And I'll be in
constant communication.
Anything big comes up,
I'm a phone call away.
It's a 300-page document.
We need you in that room.
I would stay if I could,
but this is my home district.
Now, Marty,
cut me a little slack here.
We'll get it done.
You and I go way back.
Have I ever let you down?
No, you haven't.
And I don't intend
to start now.
Hello?
- Gillian?
- Claire.
It's so nice
to finally meet you.
Yeah-- I'm a little
under the weather.
I don't want to get you sick.
Well, if you're feeling ill,
we can--
No, no, no, I'm fine.
It's just a cold.
Well, thank you for coming in.
Of course.
Shall we talk in my office?
These are really cool
photographs.
Oh, thank you.
Adam Galloway
took the pictures.
Have you heard of him?
No.
I met him at the Whitney
biennial a couple years ago
and commissioned him
to do these.
He just had a big show at ps1.
I'm not up to date
on the art world.
That's all right.
We're not here to talk
about photography. Are we?
My office is over here.
You run into any trouble,
you call me.
I got it covered.
Gene Clancy know I'm coming?
Just spoke to him.
Get to it.
Your flight is booked,
leaves in 55 minutes.
Ed will be joining you.
Where's Steve?
He went home sick
about an hour ago, sir.
I'll be filling in.
What's your name again?
Edward what?
- Meacham.
- You drive fast, Meacham?
You wanted to talk to me?
Come on, Zoe.
This is Mrs. Tilden, owner of--
She knows who I am.
Mrs. Tilden liked your profile
on Catherine Durant.
No, I didn't.
I loved it.
In depth, uncompromising.
Normally I don't read things
before they go to print,
but Cathy's a friend.
Tell me how you knew she'd be
nominated before she did?
You want my source?
Tom says you won't tell him.
I haven't told anyone.
Well, I own the paper.
And I'm very grateful
to be working here.
So you're not going to tell
me either.
Which do you want,
my source or my integrity?
Tom.
Move Zoe's piece to the front
page of Sunday's edition.
Let me think that over.
You think it over
as much as you want.
Then put it on the front page.
I've worked really hard to gain
a foothold with world well.
Six years ago it was just
me and a macbook.
I understand.
And I had to juggle two
temp jobs just to pay the rent.
It's your baby.
You don't want to let it go.
Well, I just--
And you wouldn't have to,
Gillian.
All I want is for you to grow
what you've already built.
I heard you fired
half your staff.
Yes, I did.
That worries me.
I let them go to make room
for you.
I'm just not sure
we're the right match.
To be honest,
I'm a little uncomfortable
working with someone who's
commissioning famous photographers
when I can't even buy my
volunteers bus fair to the office.
Do you know
who Nicky Hemler is?
No.
Nicky owns one of the
biggest galleries in Chelsea.
She desperately wanted
to represent Adam Galloway.
I delivered on Adam,
and in return she contributes
almost 40 grand a year to CWI.
That money goes
to impact studies,
lobbying efforts, research.
World well could benefit from
that sort of money, Gillian,
and we can benefit
from your expertise.
Can I think about it?
Of course.
We don't have to jump
into anything.
I grew up here,
in the up country--
Bibles, barbecues,
and broken backs.
Everything gets
just a little bit thicker
this far south--
The air, the blood, even me.
I try to make it down here
at least once a month.
Every trip is a reminder
of how far I've come.
I hated Gaffney as a kid,
when I had nothing,
but now I've come
to appreciate it.
It's not as suffocating
as it once was,
except when I have to deal
with the sort of nonsense
that makes me want
to hang myself.
Turn left on route one--
Don't listen to her.
I know a better way.
Yes, sir.
We don't have the money, Frank.
The legal bills alone
will kill us.
How about a settlement?
I'll look at the numbers.
What's it look like to you?
Like a peach.
No, I mean what does it
really look like?
As mayor, I stick with a peach.
As a private citizen,
well, it looks like the sun
is shining
where it shouldn't be.
There's a
better way to handle this.
Really, Frank?
And what's that?
I'm not trying to start
an argument here.
You make it sound
like I'm in the wrong.
No, you know exactly
what you're doing, Orrin.
You're using
this poor girl's death
for your own political
advantage.
You're the one that fought me
when the peach farmers
bitched and moaned
about me tearing it down.
You're the one
that took their money.
- It's a water tower.
- It's ungodly.
- Orrin.
- This is cut and dry, Frank.
I fought to tear it down.
You fought to keep it up.
That girl's blood
is on your hands,
and I'm taking you
to task for it.
All right, I'll tell you what.
Dick Peters is going
to retire this term.
That means there's an open
race in the fourth district.
How about I help you
lock up that seat?
I'm not looking to make
a deal, Frank.
It's not a deal.
It's an opportunity.
I'll be just fine.
You may despise me, Orrin,
but the classy thing to do
would've been to invite us up
for some of that iced tea.
What are you doing?
You shouldn't run here.
It's disgraceful.
Have you no respect?
The criteria
is a starting point.
They're suggested,
not mandated.
We assemble
a council of experts
who will determine exactly--
Nowhere here does it say
who these experts are,
how they'll be chosen.
The president selects
the council.
What sort of oversight?
We'd like input
on the selection.
Doug, check with Linda.
Calling her now.
Okay, so now can we talk
about charter schools?
Charter schools are a no-go.
They have to be in there.
You keep them in, we walk.
The same goes for us.
Let's not jump to ultimatums.
Well, let's figure out a way
to reduce non-public spending.
All right, give me a few
minutes to think about that.
We can't move forward
without addressing this point.
- I understand, but this is the cornerstone of the bill.
- Let's talk it out.
Give me five minutes, Marty.
I'll call you right back.
No-- no--
If we consider
settlement as an option,
we need to be able
to pay for it.
But if we offer a settlement,
- aren't we saying--
- That's my point.
We're admitting that
the town's responsible
for this kid's death.
I say make the peach farmers
cough it up.
Oh, man, talk about
a shit storm.
Y'all mind catchin' me up?
Wayne and Travis
want to go to court.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
We can't be pouring
money into a settlement
when we can barely afford
to run the city.
What do you think, gene?
I think that we gotta worry about
the peach farmers association.
If there is a hint that
we're blaming the Peachoid,
they're going to raise
holy hell.
Who gives a crap.
They gotta suck it up.
Let him talk.
I'm just saying that we need
to keep them in mind.
She was breaking the law.
End of story.
You can't text while you drive.
Yeah, but all
a jury's going to see
is a beautiful 17-year-old
girl who's now dead.
No offense, Frank,
but you just got here.
We've been dealing with this
for the last week now.
And where's your solution?
What?
You think you know
better than us?
I'm just trying to be
realistic.
Frank, I know you want
to swoop down
and save the day,
but there's a principle
at stake here.
We allow ourselves
to be extorted
because of this teenager--
When Orrin gets a jury to weep
a river of snot
over this dead girl,
when Gaffney goes tits up
because you can't afford to pay a
seven-figure award in damages,
when you all get booted
out of office
and I lose to Chase,
then you can chew my ear off
about principles,
because we'll all have
nothing but time on our hands.
Until then,
you either contribute,
or you keep it shut, Travis.
Now, here's
what we're going to do.
Gene, how much
can we pull together
- for a settlement if we had to?
- About 150.
That'll work.
Jamie, get your boys down
to the hardware store
to build two billboards.
Put them out a mile out on
either side of the tower.
Have them read, "drive safely.
No texting behind the wheel."
- Got it.
- And get those up by tomorrow morning.
I'll issue the permits.
And let's stop lighting
the thing at night.
The peach farmers
aren't going to like that.
Well, how much does
the electric cost?
4,100 plus change per month.
About 50,000 a year.
Jesus, you could put
a kid through college on--
Let's use that money to start
a scholarship fund in her name.
Meantime, you tell
the association,
if they want it lit up,
they can pay for it.
I'll deliver
that message happily.
And do me up a budget
and a plan
for removing the sphincter.
The what?
He means the emergency valve.
That's interesting.
I always thought
of it as a clitoris.
But it's on bottom.
I believe the clitoris
is above the--
But if you imagine a woman
on her belly--
Enough. I want it done.
And, gene, give me everything
you've got on road regulations.
County statutes, not municipal.
And do you remember
that power line business
we pulled up
at the last election?
Sure do.
Let's make sure
we're rock solid on that.
Does this very expensive dinner
at least buy me an evening
of mind-blowing
sexual congress?
It was good, but I don't know
if it was that good.
Fellatio good?
Hand job maybe.
No promises.
Deal.
Okay, um, Peter, there's
something I need to tell you.
I have been thinking lately.
You know, um, it might be good
to work somewhere else.
So I did some interviews,
and the speaker's office
offered me deputy LD.
Peter.
Christina, um--
I just thought
it could be good, right,
if we're going to have
any future,
to stop this
boss-staffer thing
and be a real couple.
We are a real couple.
I mean not have to hide it
like we do at the office.
And it's a great opportunity.
The speaker?
Would you hate me
if I took the job?
Baby, I want what you want.
I'm not--
I won't fight you on this,
not if this is what
you feel you need to do.
- Really?
- Yeah.
And you're right.
This is a great opportunity.
When do you have
to tell them by?
There's no deadline.
I don't have to decide right away.
Okay, well, when you decide,
just, you know, help me find
a replacement.
You know, give me a heads-up.
Yeah, of course.
I haven't even decided
if I'm going to take it.
We don't have to talk this
through right now.
I just-- I just thought
I'd bring it up.
Should we get out of here?
Yes.
Let's go find the parents.
You hang back by the car.
It's a big crowd, sir.
If I get shot or stabbed
consoling two grieving parents,
I'm a hero from now
until the end of time.
Let's roll the dice.
Shall we?
Sir, I can't allow you
to go unescorted
into all those people.
Allow me?
Let's get one thing
straight, Meacham.
You are never to dictate
what I can and cannot do.
The only two words
I want to hear from you
when I ask you to do something
are "yes" and "sir."
Is that understood?
Yes, sir.
Good. Then we're gonna
get along just fine.
Mr. and Mrs. masters, I'm Frank
Underwood, your congressman.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
I cannot begin to fathom--
You're right. You can't.
You have no idea.
Forgive me.
I don't mean to intrude. I just--
- Well, you are intruding.
- Dean, please.
What?
It's his fault.
Isn't it?
Anyway, I just wanted
to express my condolences,
and say if there's anything
the two of you nee--
Dean, you don't want to be
talking to him.
We got legal action pending.
Look, I know what Mr. Chase
has been saying, and believe--
Nobody invited you.
Nobody wants your condolences
or your excuses.
Frank, please.
You shouldn't have to put up
with this right now.
I'm sorry.
Well, that went well.
Hang on a second.
Reverend.
Congressman.
Nice to see you again.
I wish it was under
better circumstances.
Terrible, isn't it?
It's just terrible.
This is so thoughtful
what you've organized here.
Least we can do.
Tell me, are the masters
in your congregation?
They are.
They come every Sunday.
Do you think they'll be
at the service tomorrow?
I'd be surprised
if they weren't.
I'm wondering.
Can you do me a favor?
Anything for you, Frank.
Oh, the blue toothbrush
is yours, right?
Uh, yeah, the blue one.
- Hey, Peter?
- Yeah?
Where do you keep
the light bulbs?
The lamp in the bedroom is out.
In the kitchen, under the sink.
Here's what I think.
I wish I could be bigger
than this, but I can't,
and I'm being selfish,
and I realize it's mostly
about me, but fuck it.
I have to say it. Please don't
take that other job, Christina.
Anyway, that's how I feel.
I'm glad you told me.
Charters jeopardize
our ability to organize,
which is reason enough,
but the bigger issue is
that measuring their success--
Charters schools have operated
under the same evaluative
standards that every--
Apples and oranges.
No matter how you look at it, you can't
use the same standards to compare.
What, you're advocating a more
demanding criteria for charter schools
- than other schools--
- Our point is simple, Frank.
Several funds should only go
- to public union school districts
- Hold on a second.
Yeah, but we've already increased
non-charter funding by 10%.
The amount going to charter
schools is negligible.
It's the precedent, Frank,
not the number.
We're setting a lot
of precedents, Marty.
That's the nature of reform.
Well, some of them we can stomach.
Some of them we can't.
All right, let's not get
bogged down in abstractions.
Let's deal with specifics.
Corey, can you walk us
through it?
There's a three-prong approach
to determining
the amount of funding...
Miss me?
Maybe. A little.
What's it been, 15 hours?
Not even long enough
to notice you're gone.
Tell that to Marty Spinella.
How's it coming?
It's coming.
Slowly, painfully.
Hey, have we always had
tulips in the front yard,
or am I slowly going insane?
I planted them last fall.
You did not.
When I was down with you
for the campaign.
You've never gardened
a day in your life.
Not true. I have gardened
exactly one day in my life.
You were down in Spartanburg
doing some sort of fundraiser.
Gene's wife came over
with a bucket of bulbs,
and next thing you knew, I was
down on my knees in the dirt,
earthworms and all.
I can't even picture it.
Neither can I, and I was there.
What else?
Distract me from giant
peaches and dead teenagers.
What else?
Oh, I went for a run today,
and the strangest...
I-- I don't know.
This woman...
That's interesting.
What is?
Oh, a text just came.
Zoe Barnes.
Who?
Oh, that reporter from
the herald you met one night.
Oh, her.
I remember.
Yeah, go if you need
to call her back.
No, she can wait.
I'm talking to my wife.
That's okay.
I'm going to bed soon anyway.
See you tomorrow?
I hope so.
Wish me luck.
Mm, bonsoir,
my petite Peachoid.
Disgusting.
- Good night.
Yeah, all right, that's fine, Corey.
Marty?
Frank, let me explain it to you.
Here's our problem.
Frank? Frank,
did we lose you?
Uh, yeah, I'm here, Marty.
Look, we can talk ourselves in
circles about charter schools,
but here's what I propose.
In your profile,
you go into great detail
about the sexism Durant faced
early on in her career.
That's right.
When she was first elected,
it was still an old boy's club
in the senate.
Journalism used to be that
way, too, not so long ago.
I feel really lucky.
I've had lots of trailblazers
come before me.
For instance, my colleague
Janine Skorsky
was the first woman
at the herald
to become chief political
correspondent,
and that was
only five years ago.
Has it been those trailblazers
who've allowed you
to rise so quickly?
You've moved up
from the Metro pages
to the front page
Sunday edition.
Uh, well, I don't know
that that would be possible
if Janine hadn't already
paved the way.
So does that mean that the herald
is not particularly progressive?
I think that they are.
Tom is very open minded.
He's the reason Janine
got promoted.
That's Tom Hammerschmidt,
the executive editor.
Yes, we actually call him
the hammer.
The hammer? Why?
Because he's tough.
How tough?
He's, uh--
Tom has very high standards.
I love him.
He's a-- he's a great mentor.
Um, it can be frustrating
at times.
Um, he makes you double
and triple-check things,
and you want to get
the news out
the moment you have it,
and he makes you rewrite
until it's perfect,
but that's what makes
the herald the herald.
Is that a workable model
in the Internet age?
Our readers think it is.
Well, you have
a declining readership.
But I don't lay that
at Tom's feet.
I think that that's the times
we live in, right?
Should newspapers adapt
to the times we live in?
It's not that the herald
refuses to adapt.
We have an online presence.
Is that maybe not adapting
fast enough?
I wouldn't argue
with that statement.
We could do more.
We've got a special guest
with us today.
He asked for the opportunity
to share a few words
with us this morning--
Our very own congressman,
Frank Underwood.
- Good morning.
Thank you, reverend,
and thanks to that choir
for that beautiful hymn.
I want to read,
this morning, from...
No.
You know what no one
wants to talk about.
Hate.
I know all about hate.
It starts in your gut,
deep down here,
where it stirs and churns.
And then it rises.
Hate rises fast and volcanic.
It erupts hot on the breath.
Your eyes go wide with fire.
You clench your teeth so hard
you think they'll shatter.
I hate you, God. I hate you!
Oh, don't tell me you haven't
said those words before.
I know you have.
We all have,
if you've ever felt
so crushing a loss.
There are two parents
with us today
who know that pain,
the most terrible hurt of all--
Losing a child before her time.
If Dean and leanne
were to stand up right now
and scream those
awful words of hate,
could we blame them?
I couldn't.
At least their hatred
I can understand.
I can grasp it,
but God's wantonness,
his cruelty,
I can't even begin to--
My father dropped dead
of a heart attack
at the age of 43--
43 years old--
and when he died,
I looked up to God
and I said those words,
because my father was so young,
so full of life,
so full of dreams.
Why would God take him from us?
Truth be told,
I never really knew him
or what his dreams were.
He was quiet, timid,
almost invisible.
My mother didn't think
much of him.
My mother's mother hated him.
The man never scratched
the surface of life.
Maybe it's best he died
so young.
He wasn't doing much
but taking up space.
But that doesn't make for a very
powerful eulogy, now, does it?
I wept.
I screamed, "why, God?
How can I not hate you
when you steal from me
the person I most love
and admire in this world?
I don't understand it,
and I hate you for it."
The Bible says
in proverbs,
"Trust in the Lord
with all your heart
and lean not on
your own understanding."
Lean not on your
own understanding.
God is telling us to trust him,
to love him despite
our own ignorance.
After all, what is faith
if it doesn't endure
when we are tested the most?
We will never understand
why God took Jessica
or my father or anyone.
And while God may not
give us any answers,
he has given us
the capacity for love.
Our job is to love him
without questioning his plan.
So I pray to you, dear Lord,
I pray to you
to help strengthen
our love for your
and to embrace Dean and leanne
with the warmth of your love
in return.
And I pray that you will
help us fend off hatred
so that we may all truly
trust in you
with all our hearts
and lean not on
our own understanding.
Amen.
Your job is to report
the news, not be the news.
I was promoting the paper.
You were promoting Zoe Barnes.
Is this about how I said
we called you the hammer?
- Because if that upset you, I apologize.
- You're missing the point.
I don't want you talking about
anything that happens here,
not nicknames,
not how progressive we are,
not whether we are adapting
to the Internet.
Any thoughts you have
about this paper,
you keep them to yourself,
or you bring them to me.
You don't get on national
television and sp--
I'm sorry.
I wasn't trying to--
Don't interrupt
when I'm talking.
You can speak to me
like an adult, Tom.
You don't have to lecture me
like a little girl.
You haven't earned the right
to be treated as an adult.
You think a few front-page
stories and some face time on TV
makes you the next Judy Miller?
You've got a long way to go.
Don't be so arrogant.
Okay, so you think when a woman
asks to be treated with respect,
that's arrogance?
Are you accusing me of sexism?
Just making an observation.
No TV for a month.
- What?
- You heard me.
No interviews.
That's completely unfair.
You want to make it
no TV indefinitely?
We're done.
You can go now.
Hello?
Gillian, it's Claire Underwood.
Can I come up?
Have you seen a doctor?
Giardia's not so bad.
It'll pass in another
week or so.
You don't have
health insurance, do you?
Nope.
I'll make an appointment for you
to see my personal GP tomorrow.
Medicine doesn't
really do much.
You have to let it run
its course.
Well, we'll let it run its
course under proper supervision.
I won't take no
for an answer on this.
- Claire--
- I'll drag you to the hospital myself
if I have to.
You're going to the doctor.
No argument.
Thanks.
They're about to walk.
They won't listen to a word I say.
- Both unions?
- Yeah.
Put Marty on the phone.
Hang on.
Marty.
Yeah. It's Frank?
This isn't working, Frank.
Marty, you have got to keep
them in that room.
They lost their patience.
They're upset you're not
in the room, Frank.
- I'll be back this afternoon.
- No, it's too late.
Look, tell them I'll come down on
subsidies for charter schools.
Even so,
they're angry about
the performance standards.
We're not even halfway
through this thing.
There's so much in it
that they--
Tell them that I'll roll over
on performance standards,
five-year intervals.
It should be you
telling them that, Frank,
you here, at this table.
I know that.
I'm doing the best I can,
but I can't be
in two places at once.
Now, look.
I promise you,
if you keep them in that room,
we will get through this hump
as soon as I get back.
Marty, you are their lobbyist.
You know what's best for them.
Save them from themselves.
Okay, I'll see what I can do.
Stamper.
Do not let Spinella
out of your sight
and lock the goddamn doors
if you have to.
You got it.
Here we go.
I know you're a busy man.
I hope we're not keeping you.
No, no, no, I've got all
the time in the world.
This is ham
and these are turkey.
And there's some potato salad.
Shall we have a prayer?
Gracious loving God...
Have you had this before?
This is the third time.
I'm used to it by now.
Well, I'm not used to it,
but it beats malaria.
You've had malaria.
In Zimbabwe.
That took me out for a month.
You make a lot of sacrifices.
I don't see it as a sacrifice.
You turned down
a six-figure salary at Google
to start your own non-profit.
People don't get malaria
in Palo Alto.
You do your research.
When it's someone I care about.
Claire, I turned down that job
because I would've hated myself.
It was a lot of money,
but for what?
So they could fulfill
their diversity quota
with an Asian girl
peddling a Stanford degree?
Not just any Asian girl.
A valedictorian.
Let me offer you
what Google couldn't.
I know what it is
to be capable and beautiful
and ambitious
and be on people like Sergey
and Larry's checklist
of things that look good
to have on a shelf.
I'm not trying
to acquisition you.
What I see in you
is a woman I admire,
which doesn't happen often.
I want to enable you.
I want to clear the way for you
so that you can achieve
what you want to achieve,
on your own terms.
Thanks for the tea.
And I will send a car to pick
you up for the doctor tomorrow.
When you're back on your feet,
do you think maybe we can work
something out?
Yes, I think we could.
That's her at junior prom.
Beautiful.
Here she is
in her letter jacket.
She made varsity as a freshman.
I remember the day
she found out.
Coach called.
Jessie starts jumping
up and down.
"Mom, guess what?"
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
It's fine.
Why are we doing this?
Honestly, what's to be gained
in dredging up all this stuff?
Remembering the good things
helps sometimes--
Not when it puts my wife
in tears.
I appreciate what you said
at the church,
but it doesn't do us any good.
Neither does this.
Well, what can I do to help?
You can't do anything.
She's gone.
You're right.
I can't change that,
but I can make sure
the city offers you
a sizable settlement.
You mean buy us off?
No, I mean help you avoiding
years of court battles.
Jessica was going
to go to Furman.
Is that right?
On a volleyball scholarship?
Yes, a full ride.
Well, I spoke to the president
of the university this morning,
and we'd like to create
a new scholarship
in your daughter's name.
If you'd like that.
It's entirely up to you.
But, most importantly,
we have to make sure
that this never happens again.
We've got safety billboards
going up,
we're going to stop lighting
the tower at night,
and we're putting
the guard rails in.
Should've done all that
before she ran off the road.
Would you like me to resign,
Mr. masters?
Just say the word,
and it's done.
If it will bring you
any satisfaction.
I asked the reverend once,
"What are we supposed to do
in the face
of so much senseless pain?"
And he said to me,
"what else can we do
but take what seems meaningless
and try to make something
meaningful from it."
He's right.
That's how God works--
Through us.
Will you let me work for you?
What you have to understand
about my people
is that they are
a noble people.
Humility is their form
of pride.
It is their strength,
it is their weakness,
and if you can humble
yourself before them,
they will do anything you ask.
Tell us more
about the scholarship.
- Hey.
What are you doing?
- Working.
- On what?
The, uh, BRAC commission stuff.
I'm behind on it.
It's Sunday.
So?
You don't usually work
on the weekend.
Well, now I do.
There's, uh, coffee in the kitchen.
You want some?
Peter...
Peter.
If I decide to stay,
it's because it's what I want,
not what you want.
I understand.
Which draft are you reading
of the written testimony?
The one you sent on Thursday.
I actually changed it
on Friday.
Can I show you?
Yeah, I was thinking that we
could start with job numbers
and then go to
economic multipliers
instead of
the other way around.
What do you think?
Let's see what it looks like.
Picture this--
A 17-year-old girl
traveling at 60 miles an hour
spins out of control
in no traffic.
She hits a guard rail.
But if she's wearing
her seatbelt,
which she was,
and her car doesn't roll
over three times
down a 20-foot ditch,
which it did,
then that young woman
is still alive.
But you know what?
The county administrator
didn't build those guard rails,
so now she's dead.
We looked up the statute.
Guard rails are under
county supervision.
Are you trying to turn this
around on me?
That's not all, Orrin.
Your easement.
You see, every couple of years
the piedmont electric,
they apply to bring power lines
through Gaffney.
The route comes
right through your lot.
Now, gene and I
always fight them off,
but this year, if they
were to reapply, hmm...
Eminent domain.
It would be such a shame
to have to tear down
this beautiful home.
Fuck you, Frank.
You can't just roll up
on my property
and act like you own it.
Oh, but I can.
We just did.
I've won this district
11 times.
Do you think that's just luck
and a firm handshake?
But I'll tell you what.
I'm not a vindictive person.
I don't like for anybody
to lose if everybody can win,
so I'm going to help you
get elected in the fourth.
You get to keep your house.
I keep the fifth.
We put the Peachoid behind us,
and everybody's happy.
What do you say?
Well, that's all right.
You think about it.
I'm sure you'll do
the right thing.
Oh, and I'm looking forward to
having you in congress, Orrin.
It's always good to have friends
on the other side of the aisle.
I've been offered a spot
on Nightline.
You want my advice?
I don't want it.
I need it.
Close your eyes.
Okay.
It's 11:25.
Nightline is about to come on.
Millions of people
are watching.
Where are you, home?
No.
At the studio?
Yes.
And what do you see?
I see lights.
I see a camera.
And that little red dot
goes on.
Tell me what you hear?
I hear my voice.
And those millions of people,
what do they hear?
My voice.
And what do they see?
My face.
So you don't need my advice.
Hammerschmidt's going to freak.
You don't want to work anywhere
you're not willing to get
fired from, Zoe.
Treading water's the same as
drowning for people like you and me.
Good luck.
I'll be watching.
- Hey, wait.
- Yes?
When do you get back?
When I get back, you'll know.
Hello, Nancy.
Welcome back, sir.
Linda Vasquez called for you.
Tell her I'll call her in a
couple hours with an update.
- Very well.
- Sir?
Unless you need anything,
Kyle has you covered.
No, go home.
You did well this weekend.
Thank you, sir.
Oh, and before you go home,
can you do me a favor?
Would you swing by my house
and make sure these get
to Claire?
Yes, sir.
And thank you, sir,
for being so patient.
Okay.