Set them up over here.
Vice President Matthews.
- Bob.
- Mr. Vice President.
- Frank.
Sir, I'm gonna need you
to stand on your mark.
I'm fine right here.
Two minutes, people.
So they pull me from the car.
Both legs broken,
fractured skull, punctured lung.
My heart stops. Two full minutes.
They're pumping my chest. Nothing.
They grab the
defibrillators. Pachoom!
Nothing.
Third time,
the pistons start firing.
Doctors tell me it's
a miracle I'm alive.
But, seriously, you talk about
a wake-up call from God.
You don't get to come
back from the dead twice.
The President of the United States.
Good morning.
"The education reform
and achievement act
that I sign into law today
will affect every child and
parent in the United States,
will ensure a better educated
workforce for decades to come,
and will reinforce
America's preeminence
as an intellectual superpower.
And I'd like to thank one man in particular
who never lost sight of the larger mission,
who spearheaded this
bill from the beginning,
and that's congressman
Frank Underwood."
Invited guests, please join us
in the east room for refreshments.
Media, we will convene immediately
in the briefing room
for our conference.
Linda, thank you so much for
all the help you gave us
in getting this bill passed.
No, thank you, Frank.
This was your baby
from the beginning.
I appreciate you standing your
ground on this one, Frank.
I'm smart enough to
admit when I was wrong.
I was just telling Frank
we should set up a weekly
so he can keep us up to date on
what's going on in the house.
That sounds like a great idea.
Congratulations, sir.
Garrett, I was wondering if we
could talk for a few minutes.
That thing I mentioned a couple of
weeks ago about the jobs tax credit...
I've been giving it a
lot of thought, Jim,
and I think it's a good idea.
But I'd like to look over my
notes first, if you don't mind,
so I can talk about it
intelligently with you.
Sir, you have your call
with the Prime Minister.
Busy man.
Yes, he is.
Frank, I hear that
you are heading up
the special election
in my home state.
- Peter Russo.
- We're trying to keep that
under the radar until
he officially announces.
In fact, we're not even working out
of my office until that happens.
- Where are you working from?
- The basement of my house.
Any reason why the D.N.C.
didn't ask my advice on the candidate?
Well, I thought they passed
it by you, or Linda did.
- Nobody did.
- Well, that is unacceptable.
And I have major
doubts about Russo.
His inexperience? - Yes,
and he's urban-based.
- Mm.
- I don't know if he'll connect with rural voters.
Look, frankly, that's one
of my concerns as well.
We're working on that.
But if you were to come
out and stump with him,
that would go a long
way to convince...
Frank, I can't stump for
somebody I don't believe in.
It's early days yet.
I'd ask you to keep an open mind.
And let me know if you want me
to set up a meeting
between the two of you,
because, sir,
an endorsement from you
would be a big coup for him.
It's good to see you,
Mr. Vice President.
Frank.
Congressman Underwood?
Miss Barnes,
I was under the impression
you didn't wanna cover
the White House.
Slugline just got access yesterday.
- I know.
- I left the herald
because I didn't wanna
cover the White House,
and now here I am.
Access isn't the same
as a ball and chain.
Am I only gonna see you
at bill signings now?
I haven't heard from
you in three weeks.
Insecurity bores me.
I feel the same way
about condescension.
Your place, this evening,
and I'll text you when
I'm about to arrive.
What if I'm busy?
You're just afraid I'm
gonna stand you up again.
I just wanna make sure
it's worth my while.
It'll be worth your while.
This'll make up for last time.
It's a piece of history.
From the President's hand to yours.
You believe in all that higher-power stuff
they talk about in the room?
I believe there are
things beyond our control.
Who or what's controlling them...
that I don't know.
I don't believe in God.
Heaven, hell. None of it.
- Too much catholic school?
- Maybe.
I'm not saying you have
to believe in God, Peter,
or anything, for that matter.
But you shouldn't
rule anything out.
I should go.
It's on the campaign.
Our cross tabs show 81% of likely voters
are willing to consider
a recovering alcoholic.
Now, those numbers dip a little
when you introduce cocaine,
but not by much. Randy?
It's a risk, but it'll make waves.
Free coverage across the board.
The narrative has to be redemption.
A Phoenix from the ashes.
Well, let's not focus on the ashes.
We don't want people to
think Peter was a disaster.
No, no. We focus on the positive.
A "fresh start" and a "clean start"
both did well in focus groups.
"Clean start" sounds too
much like "clean slate."
I like "fresh start."
Yeah, I do too.
- How we doing on the fund-raising?
- The alcoholic thing
will turn off some of
the in-state donors,
but it's an off-year election.
We can hit up the usual suspects
in New York and California.
Walter, how vulnerable are we?
I'm not prepared to
answer that question.
Peter and I have yet to perform
the holy sacrament of confession.
We still need to address
the shipyard closing too.
Claire's helping us with that.
We are pushing a bill
called the Delaware
river watershed act,
and I think it's going
to bring about 5,000 jobs
into Peter's district
over the next three years.
We have a draft of
the bill completed.
Peter's in the process
of securing cosponsors.
And who have you called,
by the way?
I have some e-mails out,
but most of them wanna
see a bill first.
Have you set up a meeting
with the shipbuilders yet?
I don't think they're
gonna back me.
That's the entire point
of the bill, Peter.
Well, if I go to them and I say,
"hey, some of you maybe
will get your jobs back,
"not tomorrow,
but three years from now,
and most of you won't be getting
your jobs back anyway... "
all right, let's put a pin in this
until we get more sponsors.
I have to go to the office.
I'll catch you all later.
Okay, let's move on
to our field plan.
I want to go through the
regions one by one...
Francis.
We spent six weeks on that bill.
It'll be fine. He'll come around.
I'll see you later tonight?
I have an appointment.
So I won't see you until morning.
I'll be back before you get up.
I appreciate your taking
the time today, sir.
Did you get that tax credit memo
the economic research
team put together?
You didn't ask me here
to talk about memos.
I know small talk
when I hear it, Linda.
The President has asked
that you take a step back from Pennsylvania.
You've been taking a lot of trips there,
meeting with legislators...
it's my home state.
There's a jobs crisis.
We can't afford to play favorites.
The message is 50 states,
one solution;
not one state, 50 solutions.
I never expected to be involved
in every policy or decision,
but I have been completely
cut out of everything.
We value your input,
Mr. Vice President,
- but right now, we can't...
- Don't condescend, Linda.
No one even asked me who I
thought should fill my seat.
Why is Frank Underwood leading
the charge on that, not me?
That is a D.N.C. issue.
We are staying out of
it and so should you.
And so I'm supposed to just cut
ribbons and go to funerals?
You knew what you signed up for.
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
I didn't get my pen.
- Your pen?
- From the bill signing.
Oh, we'll see what
we can do about that.
I can see your security guy.
Meechum?
He's cute.
He'd never go for you.
Why not?
You're too intimidating.
He's the one with the gun.
But you're the one
with the congressman.
Uh-uh.
We'll talk after.
We'll talk before.
Peter Russo.
Pennsylvania's first district.
He's gonna run for governor.
Fill Matthews' seat.
It's an exclusive profile.
With someone no
one's ever heard of.
What's the angle?
Alcohol, drugs.
He's a kid from the streets.
I want the profile to come
out as soon as he announces,
and I'd like it to be kind.
I don't write puff pieces.
Then get someone else to write it.
I thought you had something for me.
It's too easy for people
to link me as your source.
It's dangerous.
I don't benefit from handing
out headlines to other people.
Generosity is its own
form of power, Zoe.
Step six.
Step seven.
You always wear
sunglasses at night?
How did you find me?
I figured you had
to be in government.
I kept googling till
I found your picture.
This won't work, what you're doing.
It was a one-time deal.
- You don't get to keep coming back for more.
- I'll go to the police.
They'll laugh in your face.
Look at you.
If the police won't listen to me,
I'll call TV stations.
I know the names...
Douglas Stamper, Peter Russo,
Frank Underwood.
You are walking down a road
you do not want to walk down.
Please, I won't call anyone.
But I need your help.
I don't have anywhere to go.
I don't have anyone I can call.
I've had to do things.
And I don't wanna do it anymore.
That's all I've got right now.
Find a place to stay and
let me know where you are.
I'll figure something out.
You hungry?
What's your name?
Sapphire.
No. What's your name?
Rachel.
Your ex-wife... anything uncouth?
- How do you mean?
- Bondage, orgies, water sports?
- No. Definitely not.
- Narcotics?
- She wasn't into that.
- Not even a little ganga?
- Okay. Once in a blue moon.
- Ever with your children?
- God, no!
- Ever in front of them?
Look, I'm not the world's best dad,
but I would never do that.
Fine. Let's move
on to prostitution.
How long is this gonna take?
Until there's nothing I
don't know about you.
I wrote all this down.
I've been doing this a
long time, congressman.
I know when I've scraped
all the shit off the shoe.
Prostitution.
After my divorce, I took a trip to Thailand.
It was about two weeks.
How many women?
Ten. Fifteen.
- I... I don't know. It was a bit of a blur.
- There were drugs?
Uh, yes.
Opium, speed, some smack.
- Powder or needles?
- Both.
Would any of these
women know who you are?
No. None of them spoke English.
And I never mentioned
I was a congressman.
Have you mainlined heroin
back here in the States?
- Just once.
- Any scars on your arm?
No. I was mainly into cocaine.
What about prostitutes
here in D.C.?
How often?
- I fucked around a bit, okay?
- Details, please.
Do you get off on
this or something?
Does a doctor enjoy it
when he cups your balls
and asks you to cough?
You wanna know how
many times I came?
I honestly don't
care whether you win.
But if you do, work with me.
How often did you solicit
prostitutes in D.C.?
Once every two or three months.
Sometimes more frequently,
sometimes less.
Do you have reason to believe
any of them were underage?
Jesus! No. Look, they were mostly high-end.
That doesn't mean they were 18.
I need a fucking break!
What's going on?
He's an amateur, Frank.
If I can get under his
skin in less than an hour,
how do you think he'll
hold up under the press?
It'll be a Turkey shoot.
All right. I'll speak to him.
Frank, it's just...
it's not gonna work.
I'm gonna get crucified.
You'll be fine. We've got
a crack team behind you.
It doesn't matter how good the team is.
With my past? Come on.
From the very beginning,
I said this was the plan.
- You agreed to it.
- I didn't think it through.
We have to tackle this head-on,
or the G.O.P. will crucify you.
We have to steal their ammunition from them.
Honesty is your best
defense and offense.
I'm the one that has to get in front
of these cameras and say this shit.
They don't have to say it. I do.
- Peter...
- I wanna be governor. I do.
But not this way.
I just can't do it.
If you weren't unsure now,
there'd be something
wrong with you.
I expected this.
Not easy... what we're
asking you to do.
It's okay to vacillate a little.
I'm not trying to throw
a wrench in the works.
I know you're not.
I'll tell you what.
You take the rest of the day off.
You go back to your office, you catch up
with whatever you have to catch up on,
you get a good night's sleep,
you go to a meeting tomorrow,
and then you come here and we'll
talk the whole thing through.
Can you give me at least that?
Yeah. Okay, Frank.
Good.
What's going on with all
the little sculptures?
I found a flower on
the dining room table
and a bird on the nightstand a few days ago.
It's a swan.
You made them?
Yes.
A new hobby?
No.
It's an interest.
May I bring up something
else I've noticed?
What's that?
You...
Standing in front
of the refrigerator.
Is there a reason you haven't
talked to me about it?
I haven't felt the need to.
Is it bad?
It's not pleasant.
But, no, it's not bad.
What can I do?
Nothing.
If there was something, I'd ask.
- Did you think it was weird that I called you?
- Totally weird.
Except for the fact that I
was planning on calling you.
Really? Why?
I was a real grade-a bitch
to you at the herald,
and I almost apologized when
I saw you at the White House,
but I chickened out.
So, anyway, I am drunk enough,
and I am sorry.
Why did you call me?
I was just wondering how things were
going at the old stomping ground.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
It's just not the
same since tom left.
And I don't blame you
for doing what you did.
But this new guy?
Six years running E.W. Online
does not a managing editor make.
Would you ever wanna
come work with us?
I mean, it'd be a
huge fucking deal.
Chief political
correspondent of the herald
moves to Slugline?
Did carly heath put you up to this?
No. Not at all.
But if you want, I can talk to her.
You think she would go for it?
Honestly, I don't know.
She's got this sort of
anti-establishment "fuck you" attitude.
Conventional news bores her.
But if you had something
gritty to show...
I've got a story if you want it.
It's pretty fucking great.
You would give away a story?
If you're not interested...
no, I'm interested.
If I seem a little hung over,
it is because I am.
A lot hung over, actually.
God, I almost had a
couple of months,
and then last night, I...
Well, I don't remember much, so...
But anyway, here I am.
Keep coming back.
It works if you work it.
Thank you for sharing, Diane.
I'm Doug, and I'm an alcoholic.
Hi, Doug.
One of the things I do
for a living is count.
I count votes.
Yeas, nays, neutrals, abstaining.
And I'm good at it.
But the most important count I
do has nothing to do with work.
It's the number of days since April 4, 1999.
As of this morning, that's 5,185.
The bigger that number gets,
the more it frightens me,
because I know all it takes is
one drink to go back to zero.
Most people see fear as
a weakness. It can be.
Sometimes for my job,
I have to put fear in other people.
I know that's not right.
But if I'm honest,
like the fourth step asks us to be,
I have to be ruthless,
because failure is not an option.
The same goes for my sobriety.
I have to be ruthless with myself.
I have to use my fear.
It makes me stronger.
Like everyone in this room,
I can't control who I am.
But I can control the zero.
Fuck the zero.
Thanks for sharing.
It works if you work it.
Who would like to share next?
- Was he at the meeting?
- He was.
I tried to find him afterwards,
but he was gone before I
could catch up with him.
- Did he say anything?
- No. He never shares. He looked preoccupied.
- You think he'll show up at the house today?
- I have no idea.
He's not answering my calls.
Mine neither. Anything
else I need to know?
I hear silence.
I don't like that sound.
Something came up. I'm handling it.
- Something serious?
- Serious but solvable.
- Do I wanna know more?
- I don't think you do. We'll be okay.
I might have to involve Nancy.
I'm hoping I won't have to.
But if I do, she'll have no
knowledge of anything damaging.
All right. Use your best judgment.
Of course, sir.
I've gotta go.
Miss Gallagher?
Can the congressman have a moment?
Things are... they're complicated.
I realize that,
but he truly needs you.
I don't know what I
could say to him.
I think just showing up would
do him a world of good.
Today is tough. The speaker
has a full schedule...
look, I already spoke to Bob,
and he said he'd be fine
if you took the
rest of the day off.
In fact, he said he'd be
fine if you wanted to take
- the next six months off.
- What?
I want you to be deputy
campaign manager.
You work under Nash Aarons.
No. I spent years being Peter's crutch.
If you just want me there...
well, of course we want you there to help,
but not as a crutch.
Peter is a talented young
man with a lot of potential.
He knows this,
but he needs to hear it
from someone other than me.
Someone he truly cares about.
I'm sorry. This is
just a lot right now.
Well, you don't have to make a decision now,
but at least talk to Peter.
I mean, there's no harm in that,
now, is there?
Ten grand.
We divert it from your
campaign accounts.
- We itemize it so it looks like...
- Wait.
You want me to pay for this?
Use Frank's reelection fund.
Commissioner, the majority of
the money that you've raised
has come from people
we've sent your way.
And you sent them because I sprung
your boy Russo in the first place.
We're even. I don't owe you shit.
There's a girl in trouble.
Let's help her out.
- Not my problem.
- It could be.
We put her back on the streets,
there's no telling what she could do.
I'm a hell of a lot more afraid
of the U.S. attorney
than I am of some hooker.
This is a very inexpensive insurance policy.
I already broke the law once, Doug.
There's no fucking way
I'm gonna mess with campaign
finance regulations.
I don't even wanna
be hearing this shit.
Funeral for the former
ambassador of Japan
tomorrow at 9:30,
followed by a luncheon for the
national board of directors
for the girl scouts of America.
- Mr. President.
- Jim.
After that, you've got a meet
and greet with the finalist...
I'll catch up with you in a minute.
This way, sir.
Hi.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
The congressman wanted
me to come over.
- Why?
- He wants me to work for your campaign.
- Deputy Manager.
- Frank!
He said you're having some doubts.
I was just about to tell him
that I decided not to run.
Oh. Oh.
Okay. Um, if you've
made up your mind,
then I should probably get going.
Did he tell you about the whole plan?
About coming clean?
Yeah, he did.
I have Kevin and
Sarah to think about.
- Everyone has a past.
- Not like mine.
You don't know half the
things I've done, Christina.
My kids read. Their friends read.
I can't take that chance.
Look, if you don't wanna run,
then you shouldn't.
I do wanna run. I wouldn't have let
it go this far if I didn't want it.
Then maybe it's a good thing...
confronting your past,
even for your kids.
They're a lot stronger than
you give them credit for.
Look, if Underwood, if the D.N.C.,
if they all think you
can do it, then...
I don't care what they think.
I care what you think.
I think you'd be great.
- So, she really wants this?
- That's the impression I got.
What about ego? I don't need
to be dealing with a diva.
She's not a diva,
she's an award-winning journalist
with 15 years' experience.
You told me she
treated you like shit.
There was some friction.
So why are you going
to bat for her?
Don't we want to work
with the best people?
Plus, it'd be big for the site.
The herald's senior
political writer?
Sure, but she's so old guard.
Everything's by the book.
- There's no bite to it.
- She told me about a profile she's working on.
- It's got serious bite.
- What is it?
She can tell you herself.
You should talk to her.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
Here's the deal.
My children stay out
of the limelight.
No photo ops, no press.
We wouldn't dream of it.
Okay.
Let's do this.
Sit down.
- Where you from?
- Outside of Lynchburg.
- Virginia?
- Yeah.
- Are your parents still living there?
- No. I can't.
If I find a place for
you to stay for a while,
can I count on you to be smart?
- What kind of place?
- A nice place.
A safe place until we can
figure out something permanent.
But I need to know
that you won't pull
anything like this again.
Promise me.
I promise.
Look at me when you say it.
I promise you.
How you doing on money?
I don't have enough for tomorrow.
What are you doing?
- I thought you wanted me to...
- You said you were done with that.
I'll be in touch.
If you own up to some
of the shenanigans,
sweep the rest under the rug,
you might have a shot.
How much do we have to sweep under?
Well, the kid had a talent
for covering his tracks.
I've highlighted all the items
I think he should admit to.
The rest I wouldn't mention.
It's a lot not to talk about.
- I need your help with something.
- Right now?
- Yes.
- Is it important?
Because you told me I could
leave early this weekend
to go visit my daughter
down in Virginia.
You have a guest room
in your house, right?
Well, it's Mary's old room,
but, yes.
I need you to put someone up
for a while. A young woman.
- What? Who?
- Her name is Rachel.
I can't tell you anymore than that.
I don't understand.
Why do you need...
no questions, Nancy.
I just need you to do this for me.
I wouldn't be asking
if it weren't serious.
Put up for how long?
I don't know. It could be a while.
I'm supposed to put up a complete
stranger and not ask any questions?
Nancy, please. You're the
only person I can trust.
Is something illegal going on?
No. She's just a girl in trouble
who needs a place to stay.
- We have to be discreet.
- Can I at least meet her first?
I need to know now.
Okay, I guess.
Thank you.
There's no catch, Larry.
Your district gets over 20
million if the numbers hold.
And most of the money is earmarked
for economic development,
not research.
That's great, but I need
more than your support.
I need you to be a sponsor.
Fantastic, Larry.
Great. I'll put you down.
You too. Bye.
So that just leaves
Clayburn... and Price?
- With Jennings on the fence.
- And I know Roger. I'll call him.
And I'll track down these
other two over the weekend.
Really good work today, Peter.
Do you know where I put my purse?
- It's right here.
- Oh.
Did you make those? I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to pry.
Oh, this? I've been fooling
around with it a little bit.
Can I see? Sarah learned how to
make these birds in her art class.
Then she taught it to Kevin,
and they got obsessed,
and there were little pieces of
paper all over the apartment.
- Do you wanna take them for the kids?
- Oh, no. I can't.
Oh, please. I'll just
throw them out eventually.
Thank you. They'll love them.
So you should bring the kids
by the house sometime
so I can meet them.
Kevin and Frank can
play the video games.
- He told you that?
- I was a little surprised, I have to admit.
If anybody knew he came home every day to...
- it's embarrassing.
- There's worse secrets to have.
Yeah, there are, I suppose.
I'll call you Monday after I
talk to Clayburn and Price.
Okay, great.
Have a good weekend, Peter.
You too.
I had Linda talk to
the Vice President.
- He'll keep his nose out of it.
- I appreciate that.
He's a good man, but this is a very
delicate moment in the campaign.
- You start spreading doubts, and...
- He's a pain in the ass.
We all know it. You don't
have to mince words, Frank.
I have to say, sir,
the Vice President has a point.
I'm not 100% sold on Russo.
Do we really wanna go with
someone this untested?
- Frank?
- We're grooming him, sir.
- When do you announce?
- Next month.
- That's not enough time.
- What do you see in him?
I was wondering the same thing.
There's not that much to see.
What I see is a
recovering alcoholic
with a history of drug abuse.
- What?
- Excuse me, Frank?
But he's clean now.
Has been for a year.
This is a redemption story,
Mr. President.
This is a bright young man who's
put his life back on track.
Now he wants to help put
Pennsylvania back on track.
- Drugs, Frank?
- People love an underdog, Linda,
and people love someone who
stands up after they've fallen.
Combine those two,
it's a very powerful narrative.
All of our polling indicates
this is gonna work.
You want us to endorse someone
with a history of substance abuse?
Let us get his story out there and
watch it connect with the voters.
All I care about is a win, Frank.
And I believe Russo
is our best chance.
This is not a hail Mary,
Mr. President,
- this is a well-thought-out game plan.
- Mr. President...
I realize that I sometimes
think out of the box,
but the last time I did,
we signed an education bill.
All right. We won't
stand in your way.
- But if it backfires, Frank...
- I'll guide Peter every step along the way.
We will not disappoint you,
Mr. President.
Okay.
Thank you, sir.
Linda.
I didn't plan on telling
him so much so soon,
but if I didn't,
Linda would've swayed him.
There's no better way to
overpower a trickle of doubt
than with a flood of naked truth.
This is why the education
bill was so important.
It bought me influence precisely
when I needed it most.
How long have you been drinking?
A long time. Since I was a kid.
How old were you when you
had your first drink?
- Nine.
- Nine years old?
Yeah. My dad gave me a
beer for my ninth birthday.
When did you first
start using drugs?
I won't go into too many specifics
other than to say I had
a few minor brushes
with marijuana and cocaine
in the past but not recently,
and only a handful of times.
No other drugs besides
marijuana and cocaine?
No.
Under what circumstances?
Occasional social gatherings.
That's the most I'll say.
Ever while you were
in public office?
No. Never. My chief
problem was alcohol.
And you've been sober how long now?
- A little over a year.
- And what made you want to get sober?
Two things. My children,
whom I love more than
anything else in the world,
and my renewed faith in God.
Zoe.
Lucas.
I was just in the neighborhood,
and I thought...
No. That's a lie. I was at
the bar around the corner.
The one with the, uh...
and I remembered that time
that I dropped you off after work.
I knew it was...
This block.
And I, uh, buzzed,
and then I waited...
- you're wasted.
- I'm pretty wasted.
Do you wanna know a deep,
dark secret?
Now we don't work together...
Anymore.
Lucas...
I'm really flattered.
But I'm just not in a place
where I'm even thinking
romantically right now.
I'm sorry. I, uh...
Yeah.
Hey, hey!
You want me to pull up now, sir?
I still have my key.
I'll be in the kitchen if you need anything.
Thank you.
Hey, I got us wine, but I can't
find a corkscrew anywhere.
Give it to me.
I need a pen.
- The pen the President gave you?
- That'll work.
Did you talk to Ms. Skorsky?
I did. She said it was intense.
I think Carly's gonna offer
her a job at Slugline.
- Was that your doing?
- Janine expressed interest.
I took the next step.
Well done. Always good
to be owed favors.
I was wondering.
Do you ever think about my age?
No. Does my age bother you?
You must have other lovers...
men that are younger than me.
- No.
- Not that I would mind.
I am married, after all.
I don't have time for other lovers.
Mm.
Mm. Shit.
It's turned. Give me that.
Mm.
You could've just stepped on it.
I have asked the super to get an
exterminator in here, and he won't do it.
So anytime I see a cockroach
or a spider, or whatever,
I try and trap it,
and then I leave it by his door.
You really ought
to get your parents
to let you borrow some money.
Then you wouldn't have to
live in the third world.
I would never take money from them.
Because they don't have it,
or because you don't want it.
Because I don't want it.
It's father's day, you know.
It is?
You should call your father.
I'll call him tomorrow.
Tomorrow you'll be the daughter
that forgot father's day
instead of the one who remembered.
Go ahead. Call him.
Hey, dad. Sorry it's so late.
'Cause you weren't home the
last time I called her.
There's so little she'll ever
reveal to me or I to her.
I bet her father knows even less.
I'm sure she's speaking
half an octave higher.
Same voice she had when she was 16.
Telling him all about her new job,
how much she misses him,
and sorry she didn't send a card.
Telling him everything
but the truth.
Just like she wouldn't tell me
about that young man downstairs.
I'm calling now, all right?
Don't make me feel bad about it.
It was the best thing
that could've happened.
I didn't fit in there.
I've been called worse, dad.
There's a value in having secrets.
Creatures like myself,
like Claire, like Zoe...
we wouldn't be
ourselves without them.
But Peter Russo,
on the other hand...
he's trapped by his secrets.
What I'm trying to do is
give him the opportunity
to set himself free.
I don't know.
I don't know yet.
After all, we are
nothing more or less
than what we choose to reveal.
What I am to Claire is not what I am to Zoe,
just as Zoe is not to me
what she is to her father.
Probably Thanksgiving.
'Cause I don't think I can
make it back before then.
Okay. I'll try.
I said I'll try.
For Christmas. Uh... no.
Mm-mm.
No. I'm not seeing
anyone right now.
I don't feel like it.
Because I'm not interested in that.
I would tell you, dad. Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Okay.
Don't be worried about me.
I'm fine.
Yeah.
Dad, I'm in...
I'm in a really great
place right now.
I'm gonna try.
I'm gonna try to come, okay?
Happy Father's Day.
Aren't you gonna wish
me a happy Father's Day?
You don't have any children.
Don't I?
www.addic7ed.com