Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
FEMALE REPORTER:
For decades, millions
of people have come here
in search of
the American Dream,
but for many, that dream
is quickly disappearing.
MALE NARRATOR:
Are you unemployed
or stuck in a dead-end job?
FEMALE REPORTER:  Thousands
of people around the state are
losing their jobs every day.
NARRATOR:
Are you homeless, or living
in a bad neighborhood?
FEMALE REPORTER:  Unemployment
shot up to its highest level
in nearly 26 years.
NARRATOR:
If the "American Dream"
broke its promise to you,
don't worry,
we have an answer.
50 CENT:
Let me help you
help yourself.
I'm gonna give you
three and a half grams.
You know what to do with this?
'Cause if you know
what to do with it,
you gonna be all right.
NARRATOR:
Welcome to the game.
This is your guide book.
Our experts are going
to give you everything
you need.
It's very easy
to make a lot of money
with cocaine. (LAUGHS)
NARRATOR:
You could have a six
figure starting salary...
It's hard for me to believe
that something that small
could be worth so much money.
NARRATOR:  You can
make a million dollars
in a week
In this program,
masters of the trade
on how to get paid
in this exciting $400
billion global industry.
For the next 90 minutes,
we're going to focus on
marijuana and cocaine,
but the same lessons work
for any illegal substance
Americans are willing to buy,
or climb to the very top
of the food chain
and make billions.
This training guide
will show you how to do it.
You want to know
how to make money
selling drugs?
BOBBY CARLTON:
Name's Bobby Carlton,
I've lived pretty much
in every ghetto town,
and my mom
had it rough raising us.
She had me very young.
A year after
I was, uh, born,
my brother was born.
Years later,
I'd have two sisters.
Stepfather, two sisters,
he'd eventually leave,
and then she'd be
stuck with four kids.
She'd basically just
try to raise a family
and try to earn enough
to put food on the table.
I look at people,
they got to get up,
they got to be in an office,
they got to go to a factory,
they got to bang their
heads against a wall,
they're trying
to earn, earn, earn,
but really, what they're
doing is just barely
making their payments.
(STUTTERS)
They're working
just to get by.
I wanted to make
money to go live.
I was always looking up
to the bigger kids,
who, people
I perceived cool and
trying to emulate them.
The guys hanging
on the street corner,
not working,
they have girls,
they have cars,
they have money,
they seemingly don't ever
have to be anywhere
at any certain time.
And I want in. I'm in.
NARRATOR:
What Bobby Carlton
was about to discover
is that marijuana
makes money.
More money than tobacco,
cotton, even corn.
It's the most profitable
farmed product
in the country.
I smoked a joint,
and then you just
get into it.
And then other
people want to do it.
seven joints were in a bag,
it's a dollar for a joint,
you pay $5
for that bag.
Okay. I'll buy a bag,
break it down,
sell five joints,
smoke two myself.
It's kind of
innocent, right?
CARLTON:  Ninth grade...
but then they were like,
"How many grams
are in an ounce?"
They were like, "How many
pounds are in a kilo?"
I was like, "2.2."
"And do you want me
to tell you how much
that costs?"
Hence, everybody
at school knew what
I was up to that day.
NARRATOR:
If Bobby Carlton
can do it, so can you.
How do you expand from
a small circle of friends
and attract more clients?
Making money
selling drugs is easy.
(LAUGHS)
NARRATOR:  Meet Pepe,
a retired Southern
California drug dealer,
who's going to tell you
how simple it is
to get customers.
Like I say, is not hard.
Everybody can do it.
Well, you just
walk out to the street
and the park
and everybody is gonna
say, "Hey! Spark it up,"
and you'll start rolling.
If you smoke outside,
you make a friend,
because weed makes friends.
Weed makes friends.
NARRATOR:
Now that you've
got some customers,
you're gonna
need some product.
Where do you get it?
NEILL FRANKLIN:
Most people know
where to get it,
and if you don't
know where to get
marijuana in bulk to sell,
all you have to do is
ask one or two people,
and someone's gonna know.
People will front you
as many drugs
as you can sell.
As long as you can continue
to pay people back,
they will front them to you.
NARRATOR:  And if you want
to skip the middle men?
Grow your own weed.
Pepe spent quite a few winters
making a lot of money without
ever having to leave home.
To grow some weed,
uh, in your house,
you only need electricity,
big lamps, and water.
PEPE:  You get in the internet,
you have the seeds, you know.
CARLTON:  This is just
kind of like a starter kit
for people.
You can get it
at any hydroponics store
and get your whole setup.
They'll sell you the tubes,
the nutrients,
the little planters.
In about 45 days,
these will grow to
about six feet tall,
be lush, green,
and lovely.
let it dry for a couple
of days, and then pick
all the buds off.
NARRATOR:
So how much money
can you expect to make?
Yeah, you can make
a lot of money.
I mean, like,
is gonna grow a pound
for each plant,
and a pound
in the streets
goes $2,500, $3,000,
if it is a good weed.
Per 10, how much
you gonna have?
$30,000.
In three months,
people, they doing
a whole house.
If you put 50,
150 thousand.
(LAUGHS)
NARRATOR:
For many dealers, the risk
of jail time is worth it.
You make $100,000
selling drugs.
Hide the money,
and go to jail, and when you
come out, you have money.
If somebody gave me
$100,000 to go to jail
for five years,
I would take it,
you know.
What the fuck.
I mean, you...
Sometimes, you work
10 years
and you don't
even see $20,000
in your bank account.
NARRATOR:  But the nearly
one million Americans arrested
each year for marijuana
are caught on
possession charges,
and never even sold a joint.
Given the risks,
you'll want to save your
money as fast as you can
and start trading
more expensive drugs.
I got into cocaine,
and I loved it.
NARRATOR:  When it comes
to cocaine, America is
the land of opportunity.
It's the number one
consumer of coke
in the world.
WOMAN:  The largest study
of bank notes
has found that
nearly nine
out of 10 bills
circulating in the U.S.
are tainted with cocaine.
NARRATOR:
It's a law of nature.
Where there's demand,
there's supply.
And that's where
you come in.
The life of a coke dealer
isn't easy.
When you start out,
you're alone, unprotected,
at the bottom of
a ruthless, international
crime syndicate.
Most of the world's cocaine
is manufactured by drug lords
in South America.
They smuggle over
500 tons into the U.S.
every year.
Along the way,
it passes through
a long line of distributers,
until a couple
of grams get to you,
a pawn in a massive,
70 billion dollar game.
Pawns, man, in the game,
they get capped quick.
They be out
the game early.
Unless they some
smart ass pawns.
NARRATOR:  Curtis Jackson,
otherwise known as 50 Cent,
had to learn quick.
My mom hustled
to provide for me,
financially.
And her friends were all
the people that were out
selling drugs as a lifestyle.
NARRATOR:
Curtis was raised
without a father,
and his mother
was murdered when
he was eight years old.
My mom was all I had,
so when I lost her,
I lost everything that was
pretty much good in my life.
Her old friends
bought me things,
then they got tired
of just buying me things.
They gave me an eight
ball of cocaine.
And they told me,
if anybody bothers you,
you know, you tell them
you got it from us,
and you'll be all right
in the neighborhood.
I was about 12 years old
when that happened to me.
NARRATOR:
That's the incredible
thing about cocaine.
You can use it to make
ends meet when there
are no other options.
You can be anybody,
even a kid.
I would say about 14 or 15.
That's when I pretty much
started into the drug trade.
NARRATOR:  Let's say you're
down and out, like John was,
living in South Central L.A.,
crashing at your
family's place,
with no money,
not even for food.
HARRIEL:
We were living in the back
of my uncle's house.
He had this lemon tree,
and one day he came out
and he was like,
We didn't have no food.
You know, me and my mom
was eating lemons for dinner.
So, after that,
I had to get paid.
The money that you could
make on the corner
was real good.
I started off with
small amounts, then I got
to the big amounts.
NARRATOR:  Crack, the most
popular form of cocaine
sold in the open market.
It's cheaper than powder,
so low income users
can afford it.
When you work
for an organization,
they'll supply you with
$10 crack cocaine rocks.
Because most of your
customers are addicts,
they'll be impatient
to make a buy
right out on the street.
And the good thing
about crack fiends is
they'll keep coming back.
Some guys will make
anywhere from $1,000
to $10,000 a day.
MAN:
Are you the man
with them jumbo 6s?
I'll take about three
or four hundred.
Damn.
(GUN COCKING)
(LAUGHS)
50 CENT:  It's harder than
functioning in mainstream
or corporate America
because the dynamics
of it is different.
In order to take a position
in that world, you can just,
"pow." Just shoot.
CARLTON:  The chances
of getting robbed are
pretty great, you know?
You do
as much as you can
to minimize that,
but somebody at some point
is gonna want what you have,
and they're not gonna have
the money to pay for it.
They are gonna try
and take it from you.
with 30 years' experience
investigating
the criminal drug world.
If I steal
a television set out of,
uh, you know, Best Buy,
it lists for $1,000,
I'll sell it for $200
on the street.
If I go rob
the dope dealer,
I get all his cash,
and I get drugs.
And the advantage
of stolen drugs is
when I steal
a guy's coke
that's worth $1,000,
I get to sell it
for $1,000!
There's no discount
for hot dope.
MAN:
Ever happened to you?
Mmm.
Not me. No, I never had
no problems like that.
'Cause at the end of the day,
you fuck me, you gonna
know what's happening.
Are you gonna give them
your drugs or are you gonna
tell them to fuck off?
And I'm the person
that's gonna say fuck off.
If you don't have a pistol,
I don't know why you even
selling dope.
You won't last.
'Cause somebody
gonna try you.
FRANKLIN:
Anyone who is dealing
drugs in this community,
if they do not have
a gun on them,
believe me, it's close by.
It's under a stoop,
right around a corner,
tucked behind a phone booth,
but it's close by.
They look up in your face,
they look up in your eye,
they see the gun
and they know
who's gonna use it,
who ain't gonna use it.
A, assess.
"Don't shoot them,
kill them."
Because if you shoot them,
you gonna make them
angry enough to come back
and really hurt you.
So, if you're gonna shoot,
shoot to kill.
It was like motherfuckers
were shooting each other
every day on the news.
It was like,
New York, very much like
a stabbing society, you know.
Something goes wrong,
somebody sticks a knife
in your chest.
It was a drug deal gone bad,
I got the worst of it.
Stabbed here,
stabbed here,
stabbed here.
Once in the back of the head,
once in the chest,
entered the left ventricle,
and this is from
the open heart surgery.
I don't want to say it's
a miracle, but the doctor
brought me back to life.
NARRATOR:
If you really want to lower
your risk of getting hurt,
stabbed or shot,
packing a gun can
only get you so far.
Hiring backup
is a great idea.
Who do I hire?
Do I hire nobody...
Nobody's heard of?
Or do I hire a guy
who's got the biggest
reputation
for being the craziest
motherfucker?
The illegal drug market
hires people with
reputations for violence.
NARRATOR:  But don't think
just because you have
a gun and a few guys,
you can just go out
and start
acquiring territory.
Officer Neill Franklin served
33 years on the Maryland State
and Baltimore police forces.
Having overseen
17 drug task forces,
he can tell you,
if you want to be
a corner hustler,
you're gonna need
permission first.
FRANKLIN:
As you try to acquire
your market place,
there's probably gonna
be someone already there.
They're not going
to share or give up
their territory that easily.
They're not going
to share it
or give it up. Period.
They would definitely
approach you,
trying to sell it
in an area without
someone's consent.
So I registered with
the neighborhood thugs,
and that's how I got on.
Basically,
you got to protect
your neighborhood,
and do the things
that the organization
require you to do
FRANKLIN:
I remember having
a homicide one day,
and they set
this inmate before me.
Two seconds into
the conversation, I realize
I used to play with this kid
and knew his brothers.
"How'd you get in here?"
He said, "Well, I'm
in here for homicide."
He says,
"Well, I was in the game.
I was in the game.
"And in an alley
behind Callow Street,
"I had to do what I had
to do, and I ended up
taking someone's life
"defending myself
because I had to
defend my territory
"and my business."
NARRATOR:  So now you know
what it takes to make it on
the street in the open market.
But prices for drugs nowadays
are way cheaper than
when Big John was selling,
and the risks
are just as high.
If you don't wind up
getting killed by rivals,
or hooked on
your own product,
In today's drug market,
you're risking your life
for less than minimum wage.
If you want to go
for the real money,
you got to get off the corner.
Detroit.
City of opportunity.
Once upon a time,
the symbol of America's
might and power.
The heart of our
manufacturing industry.
The home of
the American Dream.
One of the highest
unemployment rates
in the nation.
Twenty-five percent of
the population has left
in the last 10 years.
For those without a job
or who can't move,
they need to hustle.
Mr. X wants to get out of
the downward spiral
that's hit Detroit today.
And he's going to tell you
what that means.
or coke, or whatever
the fuck they're
selling that's illegal.
Because that's
the only way out.
I have a lot of bills.
I got rent to pay.
But don't nobody
really care about
your problems, man.
You got to have the money,
so, welcome
to the cocaine game.
I rarely show
my face on the scene.
Oh, man, I play
the phone game, man.
Switch up my phones.
Keeps me off the corner.
(CLIENT TALKING
OVER PHONE)
Uh, what is it
that you want?
(CLIENT TALKING
OVER PHONE)
Yeah I can get you
a T for 70.
CLIENT:
Okay, cool. I'll see you
in 30 minutes. Bye.
Bye.
And bam.
(DINGS)
That's how you win.
Shit, I'll be damned
if somebody tell me,
"You got us working
eight hours for fucking
$60, $70, man."
That's crazy.
That's too much work.
I just made that shit
in a phone call.
The American Dream
is just to have
enough money
to be able to do whatever
you want to do, whenever
you want to do it,
based on your own
hard work.
Shit, just what I have
on the counter
would probably get me
anywhere from 10 years
to about 15 years.
I'd rather be
out here getting it
than not getting it at all,
I've been really trying
to free myself,
use the coke to free myself.
NARRATOR:  As a private cocaine
dealer, you'll be mostly
selling Ts and eight balls,
sixteenth or eighth of
an ounce little baggies for
up to 150 bucks a pop.
Ramping up
to 20 customers
a day is easy.
You'll be paying $500
for your day's worth
of cocaine,
and you'll cut it in
half with baby laxative,
which brings your profit
to a total of a grand a day,
and you just got started.
MR. X:  Fiends from outside
into your home.
They might bring the police
with them, with the wire
taps and everything.
Man, they try to get as close
to you as possible, and you
keep them at a distance.
But you got to keep
that friendship with them.
You can't be like,
aggressive with
your customers.
You got to treat them fair,
you got to treat them
like regular people.
Man, a stash spot
is stashed away, hidden.
Get that shit out the house,
keep it out the house.
Don't let nobody come
to the house to buy it.
I wouldn't put my money
anywhere that someone
else can control it.
It'd be best
to hide that wherever
you put your dope at.
You get about 500,000
or something like that.
Start me a couple
businesses, man, get right
up out of this shit.
If you decide that
you ever want to
pick up this game,
shit, pick it up
for the right reason,
the money only.
Save from the time that
you get it to the time
that you quit, man.
And you won't be
in it so long.
NARRATOR:
If you choose
to be a cocaine dealer,
If you're black, you're about
four times as likely to be
arrested than a white dealer,
because white Americans
buy and sell more cocaine
than anyone else.
It's the circumstances
to where they're actually
setting up to sell the drugs,
See, the black drug
dealers will be
in the neighborhoods
where the law enforcement
will search people
without very much reasoning.
I mean, my first case,
it was like a fluke.
He, uh, ran where we're at.
I happened to be just
standing outside,
and the police say,
"Get up against the fence."
And I'm like,
"Man, come on, why I got
to get up against the fence?"
"Shut up."
Next thing you know,
they pulled this
big brick out my pocket.
(CHUCKLES)
So, that was the beginning
of the end, right there.
NARRATOR:
You're not only more
likely to be arrested,
but prosecuted,
with heavy prison time.
The reason that
94.5% of people
incarcerated
under the Rockefeller
Drug Laws are
black and brown
is that's the way
the DA's operate.
NARRATOR:  Business mogul
Russell Simmons spent years
lobbying against
the harsh Rockefeller
Drug Laws of New York City,
which treated the non-violent
crime of drug dealing
the same as murder.
I mean,
imagine you're a model.
You know, a fashion model.
You know, like
some blonde girl.
It doesn't matter
where you're from,
you're not going to jail.
And if you're some guy
from the hood,
maybe you'll go
to jail for 20 years.
Hell, they tried
to give me 45 years.
So, I did a lot of time.
I did, like five years,
spring something like that.
And a white drug dealer
will be in middle America,
somewhere in the suburbs.
That isn't in a space where
he can just be searched for no
reason at all or go to jail.
NARRATOR:  Curtis Jackson,
Russell Simmons,
and many others
have successfully
persuaded New York
to reduce some of their
harsh sentencing practices.
But 90% of those
convicted on drug charges
are still African-American
and Latino.
Like they say
for any business,
the golden rule,
location, location,
location.
MIKE WALZMAN:
I didn't care if people
knew where I lived.
People would
just come to my house,
and I would go outside
and just give them
the gram, and we would do
the transaction that way.
In 2003, I was the main
coke dealer for all
the private schools in L.A.
If you're gonna be
a private coke dealer,
this is the way to go.
In a nice, suburban
neighborhood,
selling to the largest
cocaine market directly.
and already knew
where to buy cocaine
for him and his friends.
So, he was in a perfect
position to go into
business for himself.
WALZMAN:  What's going on
through my head is,
just start selling drugs
to support my habit
and to support
the lifestyle that
I wanted.
People want drugs,
so I can sell drugs.
'Cause I know where
to get it already.
My first rock
was about this big,
and I remember
showing my friends this.
They were like, "No fucking
way you have this big of
a rock with you right now,
"like, this is insane."
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
It was like,
"This is awesome,
this is exciting."
The stories that grew out
of me being a coke dealer
just went from this
to like, you know, this,
and I was suddenly,
you know, the guy...
You know,
that everyone's
talking about,
I threw a party at
the L'Ermitage hotel,
and I got, like,
the Penthouse suite.
I've always wanted
to be loved and accepted.
And that's what
selling coke gave me.
It gave me that power,
it gave me the feeling
of acceptance.
It was definitely addictive
to be a drug dealer.
Not only the money
that you got from it,
but the way people
talked about you,
the way people looked at you,
the power that I felt from it.
I just liked having money.
It gave me security,
it made me feel good.
People don't know
what's a gram,
and what's not a gram,
they've never seen
coke before in their life.
The market rate for a gram
was about $50 for coke,
but if you're a rich girl
who didn't know anything,
I would probably sell you
.5 for about $60 to $75.
NARRATOR:  A guy like Mike
makes half as much as
our Detroit dealer,
working half as hard,
but with virtually
none of the risk.
The word got out
that I have coke,
and I'm selling coke.
The dean in the school,
they pulled me in,
and they said, "Hey look,
you know, we're hearing
that you're selling drugs,
"and we want to do
a drug test on you."
So, at that point,
you know, I thought
to myself,
"Well, I better really
slow down on this
and not do it anymore."
NARRATOR:
Mike failed his drug test,
and was kicked out of school,
but never did any hard time.
When dealing small amounts,
the nicer the neighborhood,
the less chance
of getting busted.
it'll still take years
to get that mansion
in the hills you want.
To be a big time player,
you need to get committed.
It's time to start
building a business.
Instead of selling ounces,
I started selling keys.
NARRATOR:  A key is
a kilo of cocaine.
A single kilo
can run you
about $20,000.
I had what I believe
was skills.
NARRATOR:  This is Skipp.
He did really well
as a corner hustler.
I had the skills to sit
on the wall and make
about $8,000 a day.
NARRATOR:  Once you've
stacked up enough money,
you can buy larger quantities
and supply dealers yourself,
which is what Skipp's
gonna teach you to do.
SKIPP:  I was 10 or 11
years old, my family life
was dysfunctional.
My mother worked two jobs,
my father wasn't in the home,
so before drugs came
into the community,
lot of people who would hustle
would rob banks
or rob jewelry stores.
The aggression,
the violence
wasn't for me.
NARRATOR:
Skipp was struggling
to make ends meet
in order to protect himself
from the Crips bullying
his neighborhood.
but it was
the relationships
I had with the Crips
that actually
introduced me
to drugs.
I saw them having money,
and I was asking them
what are they doing,
and the more I hung out
with them, I got more into
the culture of drugs.
We used to go to, uh,
different areas
that weren't populated
by the L.A. culture
so they wanted it,
but they didn't have
the connection,
so we would come out
and be that connection.
You'd have to have,
uh, a family contact
or a friend.
I myself went
to Las Vegas.
There are more than
a hundred street gangs
in Los Angeles.
Police now say
they have become
heavily involved
in the drug trade,
exporting their crimes
throughout the west.
Going out of town
when people knew
you were from L.A.,
that number one,
made you a star celebrity.
And then,
if you were the guy
who had the drugs,
it made you an even
bigger celebrity.
Made all the girls love
and want to come to you.
The difficult part
became how to get it
out of town.
I myself would always
buy a bucket.
Put whatever I want
inside of it and go get
a girl who likes me.
Don't tell her
what's in the car,
and let her drive it.
MAN: Did the girls
ever get pulled over?
Nah, I've been
fortunate that
that has never occurred.
Um, however,
they did get pregnant,
and I now have children.
The relationships that
I wanted for a weekend
have lasted longer
than I expected.
NARRATOR:
A lot of smugglers get
someone else to drive.
But how do you keep
track of you driver?
The DEA make a living
chasing drugs across country.
So they can tell you how
the smartest suppliers
keep track of their cargo.
the source of supply
had rigged this car
with a GPS locator
and a phone,
so he could actually
dial into the phone
and he could monitor
if the transaction was
going correctly or not.
He would know
if the vehicle was
out of position.
NARRATOR:
Now, you don't want to put
your drugs in the trunk.
You're going to want
some new options
on your vehicle.
Designing "traps"
is standard practice
for any local chop shop.
It's kind of like
a combination safe.
It has to be a series
of things activated
in the vehicle
Like, they may have to have
the air conditioning on,
the blinker on,
and a couple of other
things within the vehicle
for it to activate.
You got money
to spend, you'll get
a real good trap.
We've seen
some sloppy ones,
this is good work.
When they're closed,
you would never know by
looking at it with your eye
so whoever
constructed this one
was a professional.
It goes the whole length
of the back seat area.
So you could fit
probably in excess
of 10 kilograms
of, uh, narcotics,
large amounts
of currency or weapons.
NARRATOR:
Now you're ready.
But before you hit the road,
Pepe has some tips from
back in the day when
he was running cocaine.
Get up in the morning,
you be ready.
Check your car,
no lights broke.
Insure your car,
everything.
Even the speed limit.
25? 25. No more.
75? 75.
You know?
15, school? 15, school.
Take it easy.
(LAUGHS)
And you get there.
You be there.
NARRATOR:
So how much does
a smuggler expect to make?
If they take 10 kilos,
they give me $4,000
just to smuggle it,
or if it was more?
5,000. It all depends.
NARRATOR:
So you've driven a few
kilos across country,
you might be making
mid six figures a year.
Once you're in the game,
you realize just how
many people want drugs.
There's everybody from
the Wall Street types
to the people on the streets,
to kids going
to concerts, the stoners.
Everybody wanted cocaine.
NARRATOR:
What domestic smugglers
make in a month,
Bobby Carlton would
eventually make in a day.
In the 70s,
all the cocaine was coming
in through South Florida,
and uh, back then
they used to call it
the South Florida shuffle.
Everybody and anybody
was selling drugs,
running drugs, moving drugs.
They were coming in,
and they were going
everywhere.
MALE BROADCASTER:
The posses buy cocaine
for about $5,000 a kilo.
The drugs are then
brought here to Miami,
where they're divided up
and shipped all over
the United States.
The initial
$5,000 investment
is worth $125,000.
CARLTON:  A girl that we had
known, me and some friends,
we had gone over
to her house for a party,
and I went with her into her
garage, and I was shocked.
There was boxes
and boxes of cash just
all over the garage,
and it was just
packed with money.
I just looked at her
and I said, "Look I don't care
what you're into,
"or how you do it,
I want in."
And she introduced
me to somebody,
and, uh, that somebody
put me on a boat.
The way it works
is their drop-off
point is Bimini.
Bimini's literally
like 70 miles off
the coast of Florida.
You can go to Bimini,
load up,
"Go fast boats"
are called go fast boats
for a reason.
These, like, Colombian
cats hedge their bets.
What they do is they
send about 15 to 20
of them at a time.
the odds of getting
arrested are very slim,
the money's very good.
You get into Fort Lauderdale
or you get into Miami,
and uh, you drop a boat off,
and you get a bunch
of cash and that was it.
When you're 18 years old
and you come from
a very poor family,
like stuff's just not
happening for you,
that's a lot of money.
NARRATOR:
Fifty grand a day
would satisfy most people.
But not Brian O'Dea.
Brian was one of
the most notorious drug
smugglers in the world.
He and his 120 employees
would take in over
$100 million a year.
Brian's going to show you
how a college dropout
can become
the CEO of a major
import-export business.
I sent two pounds of hash
to myself from England.
I got 19 months for that,
and went to prison.
When I got out of prison,
I had no money
and nothing going on.
So, I thought,
maybe I can kick start
my getting back
into the world
with a little coke.
I had $500 in my pocket,
and an address.
Couldn't speak a word
of Spanish, but figured
I could figure it out,
so I took off
to Colombia,
and I said,
"Do you know, uh, Benny?"
Showing him my card
with Benny's name on it.
I won't say
his last name right now.
I might get myself shot.
So the guy, he said,
"What do you want?"
I went like that,
and I said
"Well, I got
$500 with me."
And, you know,
everybody started
crying laughing, right.
I told him I just
got out of prison,
I got my hands on...
That's all I could
get my hands on,
and I'm just trying
to get a life started.
So he said,
"Senor, muchos huevos."
He thought I had
a lot of balls.
He said, "I'm gonna get
you 50 grams of coke.
"You can
cut it in half 'cause
I'll give it to you pure.
"You should be able
to get about 10 grand
out of that back there
"if you sell it in grams."
I don't know where
I came up with this,
but I got a pin,
and I heated it
with a lighter,
and you can put
a hot pin under
this cellophane here,
and that will pop open.
So, then you can
slide the cigarettes
right out of the pack
without breaking the seal.
The 50 grams of coke
fit into this pack
like it was made
to fit into that pack.
I thought,
"Ah, this is brilliant!"
I put the cigarettes
with the coke in it
in my pocket
with the pack
I was smoking.
Leaving Colombia,
you have to go
through immigration.
There's no just going
and getting on the plane.
So, I'm going through
immigration, there are
two guys there, and they go...
"On behalf of
the Unites States Government,
we're checking all people
"who fit a profile,
who seem to be
involved with drugs..."
I said, "Are you kidding me?
I'm a reporter!
I'm a journalist!"
But they said,
"We still have to take
your clothes off, please,
"and get your suitcases
off the plane."
I'm going, "No!
I'm not taking my..."
"Sir, there's nothing
we can do about it.
You have to."
I take my pants off,
still have my jacket on.
I pass them my pants,
cursing and swearing,
and my socks,
and I reach my hand
into my jacket pocket.
I put the cigarettes
I was holding the coke in
on the bottom
and the cigarettes I was
smoking on the top,
and I flipped it open,
the one I was smoking,
pulled out a cigarette
and lit it.
Offered them a cigarette,
which they each took.
I mean, these guys
are making 30 bucks
a month, we can't forget.
I'm lighting their cigarettes,
and I take my jacket off
and hand it to them,
and my shirt,
holding the cigarettes
and the coke in my hand
the entire time.
The moment they handed me back
a piece of clothing that had
a pocket in it, shwamp!
I immediately stuffed
the coke back in the pocket.
And that's how I got
in the coke business.
NARRATOR:
After that, Brian O'Dea
was in business.
He got a small amount of coke,
and he dissolved it in water,
and then poured in material.
What we used were ponchos,
or ruanas as they're called
in Colombia.
So, here we now had this piece
of material that had a couple
of grams of coke in it,
and then I just folded up
those ponchos buddy,
put them in my suitcase,
and headed on
a direct flight
to L.A. from Bogota.
You just soak it in
the water, and then evaporate
the water off. Simple.
Of course, methanol is
what you should be doing it
with, and not water,
'cause methanol
evaporates off at
room temperature.
Water, you got
to wait forever for
the shit to evaporate,
which is, you know...
It's a learning process.
JOE GILBRIDGE:
If these individuals were
putting their expertise
towards a legitimate goal,
could probably be very
wealthy as entrepreneurs.
We have seized drugs
in prosthetic legs,
heroin in kidney beans,
in the back of paintings.
Individuals swallow condoms
filled with heroin.
Heroin pellets, we call them.
Once that condom
breaks open or that
balloon breaks open,
there's not much anyone's
going to be able
to do to save your life.
NARRATOR:
A million dollars in a few
months is a lot of money.
But how would you
like to make that
in a few days?
Everyone dreams
of climbing to the top
of the game one day.
Some people can play
baseball, basketball,
or sing, or dance.
(SINGING)
With some of the icons
being millionaires
from selling drugs,
of course, I wanted...
I didn't want to be
like Mike.
like Michael Jordan
or Magic Johnson,
I wanted to be like...
I wanted to be
like Freeway Rick!
My name is
Freeway Rick Ross.
My claim to fame
is being a drug kingpin.
At that time,
I never did drugs,
I had never smoked weed.
I was going to a junior
college playing tennis when
my car was broken down.
I was in financial
ruins at the time.
I needed some money.
MAN: Narcotics is
a thing of the future.
If we don't get
a piece of that action,
we risk everything we have.
I mean, not now,
but 10 years from now.
When they put
those movies out,
that made us curious.
I mean it was almost like
being a movie star.
You know,
how people wished
to be movie stars.
That was the way I felt
about cocaine.
(SNIFFING)
We went to the movie,
it might have been
15 or 20 of us.
And we were all curious.
Most of the older people
were saying, you know,
that, uh...
"You can't make
any money in South Central
off of cocaine."
What I found out is that
the PCP dealers made
so much money for PCP,
they had the money,
and they became
my first customers.
We just kept escalating
and escalating
until my mom found out
and put me out the house.
I was ghetto-rich at that time
so I had plenty of places
that I could move.
NARRATOR:  The trick
to becoming a kingpin in
any industry is innovation.
Freeway Rick introduced
crack to the West Coast.
When people snort cocaine,
they snort so much
their nose start bleeding.
So, they needed
another way to get it
into their systems.
People would come by
early in the morning,
you know,
like, doctors and nurses
and truck drivers.
They want to get some,
and they want to smoke it.
They started saying
stuff like, "Man, I wish it
was ready to go already."
So we got hip,
and we started
cooking it up for them,
so we would have
the powder here
and the Ready Rock here.
Eventually, everybody started
wanting it, uh, Ready Rocked.
For one minute,
it was like,
in South Central,
then it moved to Inglewood,
then it moved to West L.A.
Then it moved to Compton,
then it moved to Watts,
it's like a virus.
Pretty much every day
I could do a million
dollars' worth of drugs.
There was days
that I would go to two
and three million dollars.
I gave a lot of
money away.
I mean, that's part of,
you know, being successful,
so that you can
help your family
and friends, you know.
Somebody would
come up to your house
when it was due,
car notes, light bills,
you know, friends in jail.
So much stuff...
You know, just give
to kids on the street.
I mean, it's a good feeling
when you can help
somebody else, you know.
One of the best feelings
that you can have, so...
I probably used to take
about $40,000 a day around
with me just to give out.
You know, 'cause
people be coming up to me
all day, anyway, to see me.
So, you know,
you got to give it to them
if you see them.
NARRATOR:
When you're a kingpin,
word travels fast.
Like Pablo Escobar was
to many Colombians.
For communities with
struggling economies,
you are a primary job creator,
community leader, godfather,
bank and charitable
organization.
You know, if I was in trouble,
I would want somebody
to give me a helping hand.
NARRATOR:
When you're this high profile,
there's enormous pressure
on law enforcement
to make a bust.
And if your
operation is tight,
collecting evidence
can be nearly impossible.
TV REPORTER:  That's when
Meltin puts a bag of marijuana
into Ferral's pocket.
(OFFICER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
California Judge Jim Gray
can explain their thinking.
"I know this fellow may
have been involved
with drugs before,
"so I'll plant some
on him now.
"So, he's good for it
from before,
maybe not this time,
And then, they actually
go to court and they
involve themselves
in what they call
"testal lying."
NARRATOR:
And that's how they
busted Freeway Rick.
The cops on my case
had planted drugs on me.
I pled guilty to 10 years.
NARRATOR:  So, knowing
the cops are going
to arrest you at some point
no matter how good you are,
what can you do?
The first thing you need
to understand is how
drug cases work.
Drug cases are
prosecuted unlike
any other criminal case.
Here's a cop and
a lawyer to explain how.
HOWARD WOOLDRIDGE:
It's impossible for the police
to have a normal procedure
in a crime where
nobody wants to report it.
Nobody calls 911
when they use a drug,
buy a drug, or sell a drug.
In traditional
law enforcement,
a crime gets committed,
police try to find
who committed the crime.
This is the way
drug enforcement works,
you look for a suspect,
and then you try to trick them
into committing the crime...
For you!
It's backwards.
So the government
goes around sort of saying,
"Let's find suspect,
who should be a...
"Well, let's try
to set some fucker up."
NARRATOR:  Here we are,
observing the DEA,
who've arranged to buy
drugs from a suspect.
He's the guy
on the right with
the baseball cap.
He's completely surrounded
by law enforcement,
and has no idea.
(INDISTINCT TALKING
OVER RADIO)
Just chill, just chill.
Got any weapons on you?
Anything on you?
Nothing? No guns,
no knives, no drugs?
All right. But just
to protect, do you have
anything on you,
NARRATOR:  The reality is that
the cops don't really care
too much about this one guy.
Their objective is
to just use him
to cuff more dealers.
MAN: We'll lock up
this middle man,
hopefully, this middle man
will cooperate and get us
the distributor,
and we'll just go
up the ladder
and keep going up
the food chain.
It's very intimidating
and overwhelming.
I'm gonna say to you,
you know, you got
a lot to lose,
you're looking
at a lot of time.
I mean, even if...
Even if you're not,
you're gonna try
to sell him
that he's going.
You know,
you're going to jail
for a long time.
If they don't know,
they may give it up.
FRANKLIN:
You either go to jail,
you get a record.
From there, you have
trouble getting a job,
can't support your family.
Or in the other hand,
you become
an informant for us,
and we'll let you
off the charge.
NARRATOR:  This exact scenario
is what gets most dealers
into trouble.
One of your employees
or customers
gets picked up by cops
and turned into
a snitch.
Yes, this was
a situation in Vegas
where there was a guy,
he started using drugs
and Las Vegas Police
somehow got a hold of him.
MALE NEWS REPORTER:
Eighteen-year-old
Clifford Townson
denies he belongs
to any gang,
but admits he traveled
from Los Angeles here
to Las Vegas.
He has been arrested
for selling cocaine,
and police suspect
he is a gang leader.
They actually put it
in the newspaper,
and on TV.
We were celebrities,
we were the L.A. guys
who had
all the drugs, so...
Well, we were
looking at 55 years.
NARRATOR:  Skipp
was offered a deal.
If he would plead guilty,
and save the prosecutors
the trouble of going to trial.
The offer came
that it would be five years
as opposed to 55 years.
Um, I signed up for it.
NARRATOR:
And what happened
to the snitch?
He didn't get
any time at all.
Matter of fact, he was
let go, they might have
even paid him, I'm sure.
Federal drug money
is allocated to states
based on
drug arrest numbers.
NARRATOR:
Alexandra Natapoff
is an award winning scholar
and nationally
recognized expert
on snitching.
Snitches are very good
at producing arrests.
They may not be
very good at solving
important crimes,
or getting drugs
off the street,
or making communities safer,
but they are very good
at producing arrest numbers.
I was standing
on the side of
18, 12 officers.
Everybody pack
a big gun.
You hear me?
And they,
they are police.
They can shoot you.
NARRATOR:
Meet Derek Migras,
a Texas crack addict
who police demanded
give them 20 drug dealers
in a local housing project.
OFFICER: Mr. Pascal
told you if you got
incarcerated,
bad things can happen
in prison, right?
No, he told me
that he would
make a phone call,
and have the biggest dick
son-of-a-bitch,
excuse my words, y'all,
females, but these
is his exact words.
"I have the biggest dick
son-of-a-bitch in there
fuck you every day."
So what you gonna do
if you was in my shoes?
Cooperate and say
what they want you to...
NARRATOR:  So Derek
gave the police
a list of names.
And 28 people
were arrested.
Most snitches in the arena
of street and drug crime
will never have a lawyer.
They'll never talk to anyone
about their rights,
about the nature of the case
that the government
has against them.
They'll negotiate
with the police officer
right there on the street
or maybe
in the back
of the police car.
All right, let me
tell you like this here.
I never bought drugs
from Regina Kelly.
Straight up.
NARRATOR:  It turns out
that all the names
were fabricated.
But cases like this
happen all the time.
There's another reason
Derek Migras
gave a list
of innocent people
to the cops.
Because snitching
on a real drug dealer
can have very
serious consequences.
Rachel Hoffman
was a young woman
in Tallahassee, Florida.
She was
a college graduate,
she had a bright future
ahead of her.
But she was caught
by the police
with a small amount
of marijuana
and some
non-prescription pills,
and the police
threatened her.
They told her
that she could
work it off.
She could do
an undercover drug buy.
She was supposed to buy
15,000 ecstasy tablets,
50 grams of cocaine,
and two handguns.
She said,
"Mom I don't want you
telling anybody,
"'cause I'm getting
all my charges dropped."
NARRATOR:
Rachel called her father
just hours
before the sting operation
was to begin.
She said,
"Dad, I'm really thinking
about you today."
And that was my last
conversation with her.
LAWYER:  The people that she
was set up to meet knew
that something was fishy,
and so they shot her.
And at the end
of the day,
when the police
were confronted
with whether they had made
the right decision
to send in a 22-year-old
college girl to make
this kind of drug deal,
do you know
what they said?
They said,
"Well, she didn't
follow protocol."
Now, see that's where
everybody feels we're
looking to blame someone...
But I asked you what happened,
you said, "She deviated
from the plan."
Well,
and that's where, uh...
Whenever the plan
started going, um, south,
if you want to say,
uh, where we lost
contact with Rachel
because she did not show up
at the location she was
supposed to have gone to.
You don't think
she was pushed into it,
coerced by your officers?
Threatened with prison?
For charges
that were never filed?
Again, we don't threaten
people to become
confidential informants.
That's not part
of how we operate.
No, sir.
NARRATOR:
The moral of the story
for most dealers is
But if you do,
name innocent people,
or demand a witness
protection program.
is having a few counter
surveillance guys
on your payroll.
you run an investigation
on the cops following you,
so when cops break the law,
you've got it on tape,
and can negotiate a deal.
I went in and told them
they planted drugs on me,
that I didn't have drugs
that particular night.
That I was a drug dealer,
but that night,
I didn't have drugs.
What these cops were doing
were going around and doing
this to a lot of people.
They wind up getting indicted,
and when they got indicted,
I agreed to cooperate
against the cops for
what they had did to me.
NARRATOR:  And that's how
the King of Crack spent
only five years in prison.
(HIP HOP BEAT PLAYING)
It's a great idea
to get an ex-DEA officer
on your team as well.
When you're moving
tons of illegal cargo,
like Brian O'Dea was,
you can never
be too careful.
We all agreed
that we would move
this thing forward,
that everybody would
go on a salary,
and the deal was no coke.
If you did coke you were out.
NARRATOR:
The problem was,
Brian loved cocaine.
He loved all drugs,
ever since he was a kid.
BRIAN O'DEA:  I can tell you
about the first day at school,
first period, first class.
Around the corner
came this guy,
He took me to his office,
and half an hour later,
I suffered
the first sexual abuse
by an adult in my life.
As a Catholic, we were
taught sex was punishable
by eternity in hell.
So I came out of that office
negotiating with God
not to strike me dead today.
It was horrible, buddy.
My mind became a place
to get out of.
And so I, you know,
when I discovered that
there were substances that
could take me out of there,
I was going for them.
The moment I take cocaine,
it's a nightmare
from that point until I stop.
Coke has such
an ownership thing,
it wants all of you.
NARRATOR:
Brian knew this was the
biggest deal of his career.
And as long as
he stayed clean,
he'd be all right.
The first part of
the load was 25 tons.
And we met it up
in the Bering Sea,
and then took it off up
into a fjord in Alaska,
repackaged it all
in wetlock fish boxes,
put it all on the trucks,
I mean, it was
as smooth as silk.
Once it was all offloaded,
we started partying.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
NARRATOR:  There was
only one little problem,
and it wasn't Brian O'Dea.
Brian's partner couldn't help
but party with a little
cocaine one night.
Then another night,
and then another one.
He'd show up at the house
in the middle of the night at
2:00 and 3:00 in the morning
in a limousine, prostitutes,
cocaine, booze.
Well, when he found out
that the load came in,
he came looking for his money.
And we were very concerned
about him getting out there
with a whole pack of money
and creating
a giant heat-score
with these bags
of coke and hookers,
so there was a concern
about giving him anything,
giving him something,
giving him a million bucks,
what do we do?
So the boys decided
to give him 50 grand,
and I thought,
"He is not going to be
happy with 50 grand."
He took that 50 grand,
he left that meeting,
and he went right to the
DEA's office with the money
and put it on the table.
And said, "I can tell you
where there's millions more
just like that."
NARRATOR:
A few days later,
Brian and his team
were expecting 50 tons
of marijuana to come in.
So Brian took the precaution
of hiring an ex-DEA agent
to run surveillance
on any law enforcement
activity in the area.
O'DEA:
The load came in,
a huge load.
We got a guy out
from San Diego who has
a spectrum analyzer.
He's able to isolate
the transmission frequencies
of the DEA,
and on the way up,
my scanner lights up,
And the moment
it crossed the border
between Canada and the U.S.,
DEA, the FBI,
alcohol tobacco firearms,
coast guard.
Expecting to find reefer.
There wasn't a joint
in sight,
but there was
fresh donuts made
and coffee on the brew,
and they took that
as insult.
You know,
you can't help doing stuff
like that sometimes.
Seventy-five tons generated,
approximately
200 million U.S. dollars.
NARRATOR:  So where do you find
an ex-DEA agent or narc
who's willing to work for you?
We've got someone
we can recommend.
BARRY COOPER:  In high school,
I wore overalls with no shirt,
my jeans tucked into my boots,
and I could yell "yee-haw"
louder than the rest of them.
Well, any of the kids that
we heard of smoking marijuana,
we would beat them up.
The entire time,
we'd be drinking
and fighting each other.
I decided to be cop
because I wanted to be able
to fight legally.
I loved everything
about law enforcement.
I learned
how to manipulate citizens
into running, or fighting.
I was very popular
among all the other
police officers
because of the excitement
I could get them in.
We were trained
when a motorist was speeding,
to get real close
and then activate
the red and blue lights.
Well, I learned
to lag way back
then turn my lights on
to give that motorist
the opinion that
"I might have a chance
to outrun this guy."
you're addicted
to the adrenaline
and you don't realize it.
I was the best drug agent
in the area.
There's not a day
that we don't put somebody
in jail for narcotics,
for finding mainly marijuana.
I only had 5 miles of highway
in my jurisdiction
and I made over
100 drug arrests in one year.
MAN: He's got a gun! Shoot!
The DEA, they were jealous,
because they were supposed to
be making all the big arrests.
The first month,
I performed
seven drug raids.
The DEA were only doing
one a year.
The entire DEA.
And they had jurisdiction
of every county,
I only had jurisdiction
in one city.
I'll never forget
the last marijuana arrest
I made.
And something hit me,
I thought, "I make
three or four of these a day."
Almost everybody I stop
has marijuana.
There's marijuana roach
in your ash tray,
and I smell marijuana.
Ladies, any of y'all got
any marijuana on you?
I thought there's got to be
something to it.
Well, for years,
I had pounds in my house
as training aids
to train my drug dog.
So, I went home,
and I smoked that pot,
and I loved it.
I'm like,
"This is what it's about."
It's one of
the funniest things
I'd ever done.
I married my pot dealer,
this girl named Candy.
Candy and I were talking,
and I said,
"Should I make a film
on how insane
the drug war is
"or should I just teach people
how not to
get busted for pot?"
All these secrets I had.
And she said,
"You gotta teach 'em
how not to get busted."
High Times,
Cannabis Culture,
everything out there.
We went on the Internet,
and nothing was out there
like it.
Coming off the success
of the  Never Get Busted
video series,
we begin getting
thousands of emails
of people being arrested
and mistreated
by law enforcement.
And if I got an email
and it fit exactly
what I used to do,
I knew
they were telling the truth.
And we were getting
thousands of these.
So Candy and I were talking
and she said,
"You know, Barry,
you were so good at busting
all those citizens,
"you should start busting
some of these crooked cops,"
and I'm like, "Yeah!"
Barry Cooper's
a guy you can call
if cops plant drugs on you.
Even if you've never
dealt drugs in your life.
RAYMOND MADDEN:
My granddad told me
a long time ago,
tough times
don't build character.
Tough times show character.
he called us and he said,
"Tell you
what I think happened.
"They made
a mistake in identity."
Confidential informants
ended up planting drugs
on the wrong person.
It struck me later on
that evening,
it just kinda, you know,
my eyes popped open, like,
"Wait a minute.
How do you plant drugs
on the right person?"
and informant
was instructed by police
to plant a bag of meth
in his daughter's car.
But unfortunately,
the information was wrong,
Yolanda Madden was a working,
single mother of two
at the time of her arrest.
So Raymond
flew to East Texas
and met with me.
And I told him how we could
catch those officers that
planted the drugs on Yolanda.
Because some of them
were my ex-partners.
NARRATOR:  Barry planted
two Christmas trees
under some grow lamps.
Then, Odessa cops
received an anonymous tip
that a major drug operation
was under way.
As Barry knew they would,
leading up to
an illegal invasion
and search of his house.
Barry proved that Odessa cops
routinely break the law,
as standard operating
procedure
in fighting the drug war.
COOPER:
Get these cameras ready.
Hey, I'm Barry Cooper
with  KopBusters!
Why are you
in my house?
I'm busy making sure
these Odessa cops
quit planting drugs on people.
POLICE OFFICER:
We're not giving
nobody no hassle.
COOPER: You did too.
Y'all planted drugs
on Yolanda
and she's in prison
because of it.
That's giving people
a hassle.
You guys are wrong
on this one and you know it.
You got burnt.
He got a media event,
and that thing
went national.
In 2008, ex-drug officer
Barry Cooper
set up Odessa police
to bring attention
to Madden's case.
It was a success.
And to prove we were right,
the judge let her go.
She got out of prison.
NEWS REPORTER:
Painful memories
that melt away
as Yolanda Madden
emerges a free woman.
I went to prison
a single mom of two kids,
16 and 11.
My son is 20 and married.
And of course my daughter is,
she's getting ready to be 16.
And I'm talking to this
young woman, you know,
that was just a child
when I left.
So, I mean,
I miss the years,
you know. But...
I've got lots of ways
to sting cops.
It just takes money.
If you've come this far,
you've learned to beat cases
and outsmart the law,
while stacking up hundreds of
millions of dollars in cash.
This concludes chapter six,
How to Be a Kingpin.
You're almost ready
for the top level,
Running a Drug Cartel.
there's one more way
to make money in the game
here at home,
even more than kingpins.
This is the secret level.
For all you
government officials
out there,
we're going to teach you
how to expand your power,
and take out
political opponents.
All you need is a drug war.
Drugs used to be legal.
Heroin, cocaine, everything.
Until about 100 years ago,
when America appointed
its first drug czar,
a man named Harry Anslinger.
In his report
to the U.S. Senate,
Anslinger detailed the reasons
drugs must be outlawed.
This is what he said.
"There are 100,000
marijuana smokers
in the U.S.,
"and most are Negroes,
Hispanics, Filipinos,
and entertainers.
"Their satanic music,
jazz and swing,
result from marijuana use.
"It causes white women to seek
sexual relations with Negroes,
entertainers and others."
Anslinger's popularity
soared with voters,
and lawmakers
began outlawing drugs.
Then the evangelical movement
inspired Congress
to ban alcohol as well.
and battles
for exclusive territories
erupted with a violence
unparalleled in the history
of law enforcement.
NARRATOR:
Guys like Al Capone were
suddenly making big bucks.
The black market exploded
with such violence
that public opinion turned
and Roosevelt
ended alcohol prohibition,
crushing
the burgeoning industry.
But Harry Anslinger
didn't stop pushing
drug prohibition.
In the 1960s,
he took his case all the way
to the United Nations,
and lobbied the whole world
to adopt the U.S. policy
of outlawing drugs.
Richard Nixon would pick up
where Anslinger left off.
America's public enemy
number one in the
United States is drug abuse.
NARRATOR:  While publicly
claiming to address addiction
and violence,
Nixon used drug policy
as a weapon
to move against those
he thought of
as his political enemies.
(RICHARD NIXON SPEAKING)
To fight and defeat
this enemy,
it is necessary to wage
a new, all-out offensive.
NARRATOR:  President Nixon
created the Drug Enforcement
Administration,
with an annual budget
of $65 million,
and started the war on drugs.
If you are a governor,
mayor, police chief,
or any public official,
an enormous amount of money
was suddenly available
from the federal government.
All you had to do
was enlist in the drug war.
FRANKLIN:
All of us in law enforcement,
we're soldiers.
We developed the cases,
we got the informants,
we did the search warrants,
we did the wire taps,
but we didn't
take the money out of it.
All the wonderful
little entrepreneurs said,
"Now it's my time."
NARRATOR:  Twelve years later,
the federal drug war budget
had grown to over
$1.5 billion a year.
And the Reagan administration
stepped up the rhetoric.
For the sake of our children,
I implore each of you,
to be unyielding
and inflexible
in your opposition to drugs.
Say yes to your life.
And when it comes to drugs,
just say no.
"Just say no"
is sort of a fraud,
it's one America
talking to the other
not even knowing
how the other half
has to live.
NARRATOR:  David Simon is
the creator of the critically
acclaimed series  The Wire.
When you're at war,
you need a fucking enemy.
And pretty soon damn near
everybody on every corner
is your fuckin' enemy.
NARRATOR:
David based the characters
in his show
on the real world events
he observed
during his many years as
a Baltimore police reporter.
Yeah, we were saying
"Just say no"
to involving yourself
in the drug trade.
It was like telling people
in a factory town,
"Don't go to work for steel."
Or telling people in Detroit,
"Don't go to work for GM."
"Just say no"
in West Baltimore
is telling somebody,
"Don't go work
for the only factory that is
hiring in your neighborhood."
And the country
is telling you implicitly,
"We don't need you."
You're a human being
without purpose.
And that's 10, to 15, to 20%
of our population
at this point.
You got to realize
we ain't got no jobs
around here or nothin'.
You know, so, every time
we try to make
a little somethin'
to get on our feet,
to try and help
to feed our family,
they come kicking the doors in
and knocking, knocking us
back down again.
Even as you fall
into the corner culture
and ruin your life,
um, you're granted meaning.
You're granted a purpose.
You're gonna go out
and you're going to
sell this G-pack today
And you're going to
bring that money home
to your people.
So "just say no"
was a problem.
Um, in that, we had not given
the slightest bit of thought
as to what people
in these worlds
were supposed to say yes to,
NARRATOR:  By 1986,
the U.S. was allocating
$2.9 billion per year
That's when
the Democrats seized
an incredible opportunity
over the media frenzy
surrounding Len Bias.
COMMENTATOR 1:
Len Bias with 29...
COMMENTATOR 2:  Oh, my!
Len Bias was
a college star athlete.
He was signed to go
to the Boston Celtics.
he signs, like,
a contract with Adidas
for millions of dollars.
He's got it made.
He flew back that night
from the signing,
celebrating in his dorm room
at the University of Maryland,
he's snorting cocaine...
And his heart failed
and they said it was because
of, uh, heavy cocaine use.
And he has a seizure
and he dies.
NARRATOR:  Eric Sterling
was working as a lawyer
at the House of
Representatives at the time.
ERIC STERLING:
The story is a horror
of how Congress operates.
The Democratic leadership
figured if they put together
an anti-drug bill,
and they play it right,
they can win big
in the November election.
Responding appropriately
to the public's alarm
about drugs,
which, an alarm
they helped create.
We're dealing with nothing
less than chemical warfare
against the youth
of this nation.
STERLING:
Press conferences, speeches,
"The Plague."
"Should we put in
the death penalty?"
"Yeah, let's have
the death penalty!"
People who push drugs
must be put in jail
for a minimum of 50 years.
It had this quality of, like,
Sotheby's auction, you know.
"I'll see ya! I'll raise ya!
I'm tougher, I'm meaner!"
In my nine years
working for the Congress,
this is the only time
we wrote legislation
in such haste
and without
careful consideration.
NARRATOR:
Actress Susan Sarandon
worked with many others
to fight against
the harsh drug sentences
that were spreading out
across the country.
I just think people
don't understand really.
They just hear
"tough on drugs"
and they just go, "Yeah!
"Let's do that."
You know, "We'll be safer."
They don't understand
what it, what it means.
Hamida Hassan,
a mother of three children,
moved to her cousin's house
in Nebraska to escape
an abusive boyfriend.
HAMIDA HASSAN:
They were selling drugs,
and I knew that, you know,
but I didn't concern myself
with the particulars
of what they were doing.
It seemed more safe to me.
Hamida was given
the mandatory minimum
of 27 years.
HASSAN:
I'm 25 years old,
I'm six months pregnant,
and I'm going to be sentenced
to a natural life sentence.
Right now,
the way the laws stand,
you can murder somebody
and get out quicker
than be in a house
where there's a drug bust
and you don't even know
what's going on.
You can end up
serving 30 years.
It's crazy.
I mean, it's not right.
NARRATOR:
Since 1993, Hamida Hassan
has been in prison.
And her children have grown up
without their mother.
HAMIDA'S DAUGHTER:
I just always break out
in tears,
because I just
miss my mom a lot
and I just hope that
she come home soon.
STERLING:  Many of the people
in federal prison,
as I'm speaking right now,
who are there on drug charges,
are there
on mandatory minimums.
Whatever charge
they're serving,
they're serving
a longer sentence
that in part
reflects my failures
to be a better lawyer
in blocking that law.
It pains me very much,
you know, when I meet
the family members
of these people,
uh, it breaks my heart.
NARRATOR:
It was a total success
for the Democrats.
Many of the congressmen
behind the mandatory minimums
were re-elected
the following term.
If you really wanna
do good in politics,
be tough on drugs.
the CIA discovered
that drug money could help
U.S. foreign interests.
POLITICIAN:  Now we all know
that the U.S. government
and the CIA supported
the contras in Nicaragua,
in the middle '80s.
Now it is alleged the CIA
also helped the contras
raise money for arms
by introducing crack cocaine
into California.
There's no question in my mind
there is complicity
in the flow of drugs
into this country, period.
NEWS REPORTER:
A senate investigation led by
John Kerry of Massachusetts
found that individuals
who provided support
for the contras
NARRATOR:  Freeway Rick's
former South American
cocaine supplier
was a major contributor
to the contras.
Eventually the DEA hired him
to set up Freeway Rick,
putting him in jail
for 20 years.
The DEA paid Rick's supplier
for services,
and American
crack cocaine users
helped pay for
a U.S. government-supported
war in South America.
And when that first cocaine
was smuggled in on a ship,
it may as well have been
a deadly bacteria,
so much as it hurt the body,
the soul of our country.
But take my word for it,
this scourge will stop.
NARRATOR:
President Bush Senior
doubled the war budget.
And by the end
of his administration,
it had doubled yet again.
During the '90s,
government asset forfeiture
was also on the rise.
is they permit the government
to seize assets
and money of people
where they believe that
those assets are connected
to drug enforcement.
It's very easy
for the government
to get assets this way
because the standard of proof
is so much lower.
No one needs to be charged
or convicted of a crime.
NARRATOR:
The message to law enforcement
officers was simple.
In the event that you are
an undercover officer
and you see someone
carrying two suitcases,
one is full of money,
the other is full of drugs,
follow the money.
Drugs coming up from Mexico
go north and east.
To seize the large amounts
of money,
I was instructed
to begin working
south and west bound traffic.
I got extremely talented
at seizing money
under the rules of law.
That's highway robbery.
I have heard
a police officer say
"Chief, we need
a new vehicle."
He'd say "All right, go out,
find a drug dealer
and seize one."
And so they literally
try to find this property.
If I found
100,000 dollars
drug money,
that paid my salary
for a year, auto expenses,
dog expenses,
whatever it took
to keep me on board,
everything after that
was profit.
The same problem
comes up with regard
to police corruption.
You go out in the field
and you will see
a stack of cash.
So you just lift
maybe 10, 20, 30, 40 dollars
off the top
and nobody notices,
and of course
there's no accounting anyway,
so next time you will lift
maybe a hundred.
If I found
a stash of money,
I'd take a couple
hundred bucks,
stick it in my pocket
and then turn it in.
I'm not proud of that.
NARRATOR:
Between 2000 and 2003,
the Department of Justice
earned over
one billion dollars
in forfeiture proceeds.
By 2008,
that number had tripled.
By the time
Clinton left office,
High school students'
use of methamphetamines
had doubled.
And heroin and cocaine
were cheaper and purer
than they were
when the first drug laws
were passed in 1914.
The war on drugs
is not winnable,
but it's eminently fundable,
and the government
is addicted to that funding.
OFFICER: You know,
the worst thing
about this drug war,
it just ruined this job.
You know I began
as a police reporter,
somebody very sympathetic
to good police work,
and I still am sympathetic
to good police work.
But I have no regard
for the drug war anymore.
If you're a fan of
the HBO series  The Wire,
you see this emphasized
over and over again,
that it's all about
statistics and numbers.
NARRATOR:
Radley Balko is a journalist
who spent years
studying the effects
that federal drug money
has had on law enforcement.
You need to make
as many drug arrests
as possible,
and that's how
you get your grant
in the federal government.
NARRATOR:
If you're running
a police department,
you don't get
massive grant money
for solving murder cases,
or rapes, or theft.
Your only
major financial incentive
is to solve drug crimes,
and if you don't make
the same drug arrests
as last year,
you won't get
the same budgets this year.
And yet, all you're doing
is making
meaningless street arrests
that have no consequence.
NARRATOR:  This incentivizes
police departments to set up
specialized SWAT teams
so police can conduct
more drug raids.
And the U.S. government
will provide money
for SWAT equipment as well.
No-knock raids
are some of the most cruel,
horrible tragedies
a human can go through
because it's so terrifying.
I raided over 100 houses
in my law enforcement career.
There'd be 15 of us
in all this riot gear,
and the biggest, fanciest
guns we could get.
I was always the guy
who kicked the door in,
'cause I was
the most aggressive one.
And we threw flash grenades
in the window to confuse
everybody.
The one that really
stands out in my mind was,
I remember
a blonde-headed girl
with blue eyes,
like my daughter's,
and it almost seems
like it was one
of my daughters now.
And uh, she had a brother,
and they were so scared.
POLICE OFFICER:
Don't move,
you understand?
MAN: Did you shoot my dog?
MAN: Did you shoot
my fucking dog?
(FAMILY YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
MAN: Why did you do that?
And we ripped that family
apart for a bag of pot?
Sometimes people feed
them wrong information,
sometimes it's just
an accident,
where they read,
instead of "863"
they read "868"
And when they got to the house
of the former marine,
Jose Guerena,
he had already
been alerted by his wife
that someone was outside,
so he grabbed his rifle.
But before Guerena
could remove the safety
from his rifle,
he was greeted by
more than 60 bullets
from law enforcement.
The SWAT team refused
to let anyone attend
to Guerena,
leaving no hope
for him to survive.
We've raised a generation
of cops in Baltimore
who can make a drug arrest,
but can't do police work.
You don't know
how to use an informant
and not be used
by an informant.
You don't know how to write
an intelligent search warrant,
you don't know how to
retroactively investigate
a crime,
you don't understand
how to maintain a crime scene.
All the things that count
as quality police work,
that's a direct consequence
of the drug war that
nobody thought about.
NARRATOR:  In the 1980s,
there were about 3,000
SWAT raids a year.
Today, that number is
estimated at around 50,000
SWAT raids a year.
Most serving warrants on
non-violent drug offenders.
These raids gone wrong
are actually pretty common.
They happen, by my estimate,
a few times a week,
across the country.
when narcotics officers
knocked down the door
at her home on Neal Street,
and then opened fire.
a 68-year-old grandfather
of 12 was killed in his home
in Framingham, Massachusetts.
NARRATOR:
While drug war money
has financed
an unprecedented expansion
of U.S. law enforcement,
the bulk of drug money
has continued to flow
outside U.S. borders
and into the pockets
of true masters of the game.
As a cartel drug lord,
your biggest problem is going
to be counting your money.
But you'll have a few guys
hired to do that.
And a few more guys to count
your mansions, houses,
planes, boats, luxury cars,
and all the material
possessions you could
possibly dream of.
Like all the kings
and emperors before you,
you too will have
your very own army.
Driving around in custom
made tanks designed by top
military equipment engineers.
and too many of your men
find themselves in prison,
you just send a couple hundred
of your best guys down there
and get them out of jail.
The guards won't stop you.
Anyone you perceive
as being a threat,
you send a message.
You chop off people's heads.
You roll those heads
into nightclubs
or pile them up and hang
their bodies from bridges to
keep your competition in line.
As a cartel drug lord,
you kill anybody
who gets in your way,
literally gunning
down civilians,
as long as
you hit your target.
You'll be so used to killing,
nothing will faze you
anymore.
Since 2006, over 50,000
people have been murdered
in Mexico's war on drugs.
Most of those cases
remain unsolved.
Not because you're
careful about covering up
your crimes,
but because you terrify
the police.
What happens when
you as a public official,
or a police chief,
receive an envelope
with photographs
of your family?
It won't take you long
either to resign,
or to go along
with their wishes.
The cartels have more
money and more guns
than the police do.
In a lot of ways,
that doesn't make
any difference
because the police
are on their payrolls,
but where they're not,
they can literally
outgun the police.
NARRATOR:
To run a global company,
you need operatives
all over the world.
An international work force
rivaling any other
Fortune 500.
So where do you find
your employees?
Like business school does
for our corporate leaders,
jails are like
the ultimate job fair
for gangs, dealers, hitmen,
and other criminals for hire.
HARRIEL:  We was in there
beating people up,
robbing people.
I almost killed a guy.
I beat him so bad
that I almost killed him.
SKIPP:  You know, tensions
are high at all times.
If it's not between
the Bloods and Crips,
it might be between
the blacks and Latinos,
or might be between
the prison guards and inmates.
80% of the guys
in there don't have
a high school diploma,
So if you have no one
to show you what manhood is,
you'll be just like
the sharks just out there.
From 1920 to 1970
the rate of incarceration in
the United States was level.
From the depression,
World War II,
the postwar boom,
through the '50s,
through the '60s,
the rate of incarceration
was level.
Public enemy number one
is drug abuse.
STERLING:  In 1970,
the rate of incarceration
starts going up.
And it has not stopped
going up for a half century.
NARRATOR:
Only 5% of the world
is American.
But today,
America has 25%
of the world's prisoners.
GRAY:
The United States of America,
the land of the free,
leads the world in
the incarceration
of our people.
And incarcerate them
at levels unheard of
in the rest of the world.
NARRATOR:
No other nation comes close.
Not China, not Russia, nobody.
There are only
two explanations,
one is that
we are uniquely evil,
and the other is that
we have uniquely
counterproductive laws.
NARRATOR:  And while
the prison population
continues to grow,
the demand for illegal drugs
is still rising.
50% of America has consumed
an illegal drug.
Do they think they can lock
up half of the country?
There's just no stopping us.
Everybody I know
wants to do drugs
is doing them.
They don't care
if it's legal or illegal,
they're doing them.
Some of America's
most famous business
leaders, like Steve Jobs,
has said taking LSD
was one of the most important
experiences of his life.
I don't think it's as much
a question about drugs
as it's about freedom.
Whatever this
freedom word means,
we really gotta
grab hold of that.
Either we have
the right to do
what we want to do
as long as we aren't
hurting someone else,
or we're not living
in a free country.
I'm just horrified by the way
that we think of people
because of the choice
of substance that they
put in their bodies
to alter their perception.
And we judge them
as good or bad,
while we sip our wine
and have our cocktail parties
and you know...
Stick that hypocrisy right up
society's ass for me.
Some of them can kill you
the first time you try them
and other ones are really fun.
And someone's lying to you
if they say they're not.
Our own power as individuals
over our own bodies,
our thoughts,
our minds, our ideas,
and our feelings,
those are not things
that can be taken away
from us.
And anybody who would allow
the state to take them away
doesn't deserve the title
"American citizen."
NARRATOR:  The vast majority
of drug dealers never make it.
They're either killed,
or wind up in prison.
But Americans just keep
demanding more drugs.
MAN:  Approximately half
a million Americans are
incarcerated on drug charges.
In recent years
we've spent more money
building new prisons
And they are beneficiaries,
the people who manage
these prisons,
the prison guards' unions,
they all have a vested
interest in perpetuating
this broken system.
NARRATOR:  And famous
American freedom advocates
have been speaking for years
about the conflict of
interest for politicians.
Are you running for office,
and you need more dough?
Adopt a tough
on crime position,
you'll get a lot of money
from the prison industry.
Think about it.
NARRATOR:  But even
the largest prison system
in the history of the world
is just another market
for drug dealers.
There are drugs inside jail.
Oh, you can find weed, coke,
crystal meth, ecstasy.
Even heroin, you can find.
People work there,
bring it over,
or visitors.
There's drugs inside jail.
NARRATOR:  Congratulations.
you're the number one
organized crime threat
in the United States,
having set up franchises in
over 1,000 American cities.
You have an operating budget
larger than most countries.
You and your partners
in crime make over
150 billion dollars a year.
And business shows
no signs of slowing down.
Because like any good game,
the machine creates an
endless supply of players.
The government always says
drugs are illegal,
because they're bad for you,
and we're trying
to protect societies,
but the government doesn't
give a fuck about your safety.
The government,
they don't want you
to use your drugs,
they want you
to use their drugs.
So every night on TV,
you see a weird ass
drug commercial
trying to get you hooked
on some legal shit.
And they just keep
naming symptoms till they
get one that you fucking got.
I think once
I took my first Vicodin
it was just like
this feeling of, "Aah,"
you know,
like everything
was not only mellow
but didn't feel any pain,
it didn't...
It just kind of
numbed things.
I don't know
at what point exactly
it started to be a problem,
I just remember liking it
more and more.
People tried to tell me
that I had a problem,
I would say, "Get that
fucking person out of here,
"I can't believe
they said that shit to me.
"They know nothing
about my fucking life.
"Are they out of
their fucking mind?
"I'm not out there
fucking, you know,
putting coke up my nose,
"I'm not smoking crack."
You're struggling
with the argument of,
do you have a problem
or do you not have a problem,
can you control it
or can you not,
and I literally thought
I could control it.
NARRATOR:
And for one out of ten people,
this is how easy it is to fall
into the hands of addiction.
I snorted OxyContin
and I remember just
falling down on that couch
and just feeling euphoric,
and feeling that,
"This is how I should feel,
this is how it should
always be."
I had fun for a lot
of those years.
But for five or six of them,
every time I did it,
it was a freaking nightmare.
NARRATOR:
Once you're addicted,
the drugs become
interchangeable.
You're taking things
that people are giving you
that you don't even know
what the fuck they are.
They look like a pill
and they're shaped like
something that you take,
so you take it.
You know. Xanax, Valium,
tomato, tomahto.
You know what I mean,
it's the same thing.
All in the same family,
fuck it, take it.
You know, OxyContin
is very expensive,
and I couldn't afford it,
so eventually a friend said,
"Well, you can do heroin.
"Heroin's a lot cheaper
and you can...
It's easier to get, actually."
And the cost was huge.
Beyond the price,
beyond the dollar.
I was doing too much cocaine,
becoming too paranoid.
People started smoking it,
I started smoking it.
I was sweating,
I was shitting,
I was vomiting everywhere,
and, you know, I said,
"I need to go to a hospital."
Had I have gotten
to the hospital
about two hours later,
I would have died.
Having my mom
look over me crying,
over her little baby boy,
in a hospital,
at 2:00 in the morning,
I just felt like shit.
My organs were shutting down,
my liver, kidneys, everything.
They were going to have
to put me on dialysis.
They didn't think
I was gonna make it.
My bottom was going
to be death.
Within a month,
I had relapsed,
and shot right back up
to the same amount
of pills I was taking.
I remember just walking
around my house
and thinking
every single day like,
I'm gonna fucking die.
I'm looking at my kids
and I need to be here
for this.
It was everything
that I loved.
And everything that loved me
was a price that I was
willing to pay to do coke.
That's a horrible price.
if they can't afford
to support their habit,
I think when you come
from a poor family,
you wanna do drugs,
and drugs cost money,
and then you see a way out.
OxyContin is very expensive.
And people keep calling you,
you know, people want drugs.
And it was hard
not to give them it,
because I knew
I could make 50 dollars
just like that.
The day I ate LSD,
the next day I sold LSD.
The day I did cocaine,
the next day I sold cocaine.
The day I shot drugs,
I was selling dope.
I never meant to get
in the dope business.
That wasn't my plan.
But it just started that way.
Eventually I would make
my way to a Narcotics
Anonymous meeting
and a kid was reading
"What is an addict"
and it said very simply,
"An addict is a man or a woman
whose life is controlled
by drugs,
"in one form or another,
the getting and using,
"and finding ways
and means to get more."
And I heard that,
and a light went on
in my head.
I knew I was an addict
for the first time in my life.
When people asked me,
"What's wrong with you?"
Coming off of everything,
I literally was up 24 hours
a day for 3 weeks straight.
And I mean, not sleeping,
not even nodding off
for a fucking minute.
Like I was literally just up,
looking at the TV.
I had to regain
motor skills,
talking skills.
It's been a learning process,
like, it's been...
I'm growing.
I just couldn't believe
that anybody could be
naturally happy
or naturally function or be
enjoying life in general
without being on something.
So I would say to anybody
it does get better,
you know.
It just, it does.
NARRATOR:  Marshall Mathers,
Mike Walzman, Brian O'Dea,
and Bobby Carlton
would take years in and
out of treatment programs
before they finally got sober.
And this is normal.
Addiction is still
a modern mystery.
Rehabilitation programs
are underfunded,
and often unavailable,
except for the very rich.
But in promoting
a culture of addiction
and substance abuse,
drug cartels have an
even more powerful ally than
the pharmaceutical industry.
The number one
gateway drug in the world.
Yeah, it's the worst
drug on the planet.
95% of the violent offenses
ever committed by anyone
locked up in prison
NARRATOR:  And as
any addict will tell you,
the quickest way to relapse
is compromising your
judgment and willpower
with alcohol.
With legal drug companies
promoting drug use,
it would seem almost
impossible to fight the
monster of addiction.
But there's one industry
that's mastered the
art of drug dealing,
and they know the secret
approach that could threaten
the entire addiction market.
I'm Patrick Reynolds.
My grandfather founded the
R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company.
My only memories of my dad
were of a man dying
from smoking.
Tobacco is killing more
than a combined total
of all the murders,
all the drugs,
all the suicides,
and all car accidents
combined.
Throw AIDS in,
tobacco is killing
more than the total.
If tobacco
were banned tomorrow,
and the DEA was going
to come after you
for smoking,
the first thing it would
do is it would make it
really cool to kids.
We'd have a black
market tobacco,
there would be tobacco
probably manufactured
in Mexico,
or some other country
and imported...
They'd find their way.
We know what works
for fighting tobacco.
Smoking bans in public places,
high tobacco taxes,
secession programs,
education,
and banning
tobacco advertising.
NARRATOR:  What would happen
if we used the same approach
Patrick Reynolds described
succeeding with cigarettes
and applied that to all drugs?
That was tried in Portugal,
which had a huge drug problem,
NBC sent reporters to
study the drop in addiction
and abuse rates among teens.
So have you ever
used hashish?
GIRLS: No, never.
Why not?
It's bad for us.
NARRATOR:
Portuguese Prime Minister
Jose Socrates
was one of the architects
of the new policy,
has some advice
for the rest of us.
(SPEAKING PORTUGUESE)
TRANSLATOR:
I think the strategy can work
in any country,
of prejudice and take an
intelligent approach.
NARRATOR:
Even America's current
drug czar admits
that law enforcement
isn't the answer to drugs.
If you read the research,
you clearly and quickly
come to realize
I think for too long
we probably thought
we could either
arrest our way
out of the problem,
or solve it through some
criminal justice lens,
and I think we know
from past history
that is not the case.
the single greatest
public policy failure
of the last 50 years.
The DEA don't want
the drug problem to stop.
District attorneys don't want
the problem to stop.
Prisons don't want the
drug problem to stop.
They're pushing it on.
The only person who's
paying is the taxpayers.
NARRATOR:  Freeway Rick Ross
and Brian O'Dea continue to
give inspirational speeches
on the dangers of
addiction and the
failures of prohibition.
O'DEA:
I was sentenced to 10 years.
Within an hour and a half,
I met guys in there who were
doing 75 years for pot.
One of these guys
has since died in prison.
And the other guys are
gonna die in prison.
But I got the government
selling me cigarettes in
there for 50 cents a pack.
Don't make sense, does it?
Didn't to me. Didn't to me.
NARRATOR:  Bobby Carlton,
now clean for over a decade,
runs a sober living house
in Los Angeles,
You know, it's just the money
is so stupid that everybody's
a part of the problem,
NARRATOR:  Big John now works
as a union electrician and
earns over six figures a year.
He and Skipp Townsend
volunteer as
community activists
and gang intervention
specialists
in Southern California.
I understand that
I can't do any better
unless I know better.
And so for the most part
when individuals ask me
for a job,
I understand that
nine out of ten,
It's just what they're sayin'.
But they're gonna revert back
to what comes easiest.
The current takes the path
of least resistance.
So, what's the easiest,
what's the easiest path?
That's drugs.
NARRATOR:
After a friend of his was
killed by one of the cartels,
Pepe left the game.
For the time being.
Right now I'm a painter.
A simple painter.
And this... I enjoy my
life right now, I'm fine.
But I know the way to make it.
If one day I need to,
I will go.
NARRATOR:
Barry Cooper,
after constant arrests
and raids on his
family's home,
outside the United States
where he continues
to dedicate his life
I'm not going to use our
energy to try and change the
minds of the old Americans
that made the laws and expect
us to live under those laws.
I'm going to use our energy
to rally the masses
who already get it.
NARRATOR:  And Neill Franklin,
after 30 years fighting the
war on drugs,
is now the executive
director of LEAP,
an organization
of law enforcement
who are demanding an end
to the drug war.
It wasn't until after his
retirement that Neill Franklin
chose to speak out.
What I have here is referred
to as, in law enforcement,
as a shadow box.
And it basically contains
the law enforcement
officer's career.
And in my
retirement celebration,
this was presented to me
by Ed Toatley.
Ed Toatley was probably
the best narcotics agent
that the Maryland state
police had ever seen.
Ed Toatley was assassinated
in October 2000
by a drug dealer.
You get killed in this thing,
I'll be like, my generation
died in Vietnam.
It's perhaps heroic,
but it's absolutely
without meaning.
Because whether you make
the five kilogram bust,
500 kilos, a truck load.
None of it makes
any difference.
Drug dealers and cops
are replaced just like that.
FRANKLIN:  People losing
parents, people losing sons,
people losing daughters.
You know,
Ed's kid's lost a father.
And those who are involved
in the illegal activity,
because you know what,
their lives are just
as important.
NARRATOR:
If we decriminalized
all drugs,
we would have billions
of dollars to battle
addiction,
drug abuse and poverty.
But as long as we support
a drug war,
we will continue to encourage
our children to pick up
the game
and discover for themselves
how to make money
selling drugs.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player