Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Where are you?
Oh, yeah.
All right, all right, later.
You all right, Alisa?
You girls coming
to my party, yeah?
It's gonna be wicked,
everyone's gonna be there.
So, I was, like, Listen, yeah, brush
your teeth after you lick me out...
don't try and kiss me,
you get me?
- That's proper grimy.
- I know, proper ghetto.
Moony's buff,
you know.
- Have you got a spare cigarette?
- No, I'm giving up.
Shaneek and Carleen are over there.
They're watching us.
Did you finish the coursework
for them?
No.
Katie!
You girls gotta come to my party.
It's gonna be heavy.
- Who's gonna be there?
- Everyone's coming.
Mum and dad are away,
so anything goes.
Anything.
- Please come.
- Safe, yeah?
Hey, pussyhole,
seen Claire around?
You like this,
isn't it, Charlotte?
Why you calling me that?
You know my name's Claire.
So that if anyone else hears, they don't
think that you're, you know, Sam's girl.
- You scared of him, Jay?
- Of Sam? No.
All right, girls.
Wanna come to my party?
Are you gonna come? Surely your mum
can low you, it's Friday night.
I don't know,
I'm not feeling too good.
And I ain't got nothing to wear.
Okay, if I score some money to get us
something to wear, will you come?
- Where you gonna get that much money?
- Don't watch that.
What go on, bitch?
- You seen Claire anywhere?
- No.
- What?
What the fuck you looking at,
you fat bitch? You know me?
Have you seen Claire?
Can't we kick, man?
I'm not your fucking security guard.
- Yes, Moony.
- Yo, Trife.
- Where you been, man?
- I had a couple things to do, man.
What's wrong with these batty holes,
man. Always fucking playing football.
Come in the class,
stinking it up afterwards.
Hey, just light the zoot, man.
Come on, Becky.
Let's go.
You know what? Them two girls
over there are fucking weird, blood.
I know. What the fuck
she's looking at, man?
How can you make her watch you
like that, blood?
See me now, if that was me,
I wouldn't have it.
You should spark
in her fucking face.
Yeah, you watch.
I'm gonna mash her up.
- Hey, come on, let's go, Jay.
- All right, man.
- Ring me tonight, yeah?
- Yeah, yeah, course I will.
- Come on.
- Yes, man, there...
- and that Claire's pussy is live, man.
- You're gonna be late.
Let's get inside
before the second bell.
Come on.
Oi, Alisa's looking tit, boy.
Why you split up with her?
I don't know, man.
I dashed it, isn't it?
She just... I don't know.
- Boy, you're a fool, Trife man.
- Hey, fuck off, man.
You're brave, blood...
I would never leave that, man.
- I'd fuck that everyday.
- Everyday, blood, standard.
- What you talking about?
- Rub them titties all night, blood.
What you uniform pussyholes know about
titties and pussy and all them thing?
And what you doing chatting about Alisa?
I fucked that girl a few weeks ago, blood.
Everyday for a week
when she's supposed to be your girl.
Think you're so bad, isn't it?
What did I tell you before, huh?
When I call you, you must come.
Beat her, Shaneek star.
- What did I tell you your name was?
- Big bird.
Leave me alone, please.
Get up.
Fucked her hard, blood,
you understand me?
Bareback, no rubber smutting.
What you gonna do? What you gonna do?
- What you gonna do, man?
- Leave us alone, blood, man.
Who the fuck you talking to?
Hold this fool.
Low it, man, low it,
low it, low it, man.
What you got for me, blood?
- Got nothing, blood, man.
- What you got for me?
- Who you talking to?
- Got nothing man.
- Don't answer me back, bruv.
- Got nothing, man.
Fuck you talking to, blood?
- Yeah, Tribal two.
- Hi, that's my sister's, blood, man.
Hey, leave him, blood.
Who told you to pick him up?
What you doing?
No-one fucking likes you,
virgin fool.
Didn't she tell you before?
Don't answer her back.
So what are you?
Slag then?
Go on, bitch,
tell everybody you're a virgin.
What?
Pick up my ring
and tell everyone you're a virgin.
Pick it up, man!
Well?
I'm a virgin.
You know what, blood. Hug him up like
the fucking batty hole you are.
Hug him up, blood!
Hey, what you doing, man?
What, you can't fuck with mans
your own age? You gotta trouble us?
Who the fuck you talking to?
Hey, where you going, blood?
Where you going?
Where?
Fucking idiot.
- Smack her up.
- Beat her up, Shaneek. Beat her!
Look at her just fucking
sitting there. Fool.
Go on, fuck off
and clean your duty self up, man.
And none of you lot better say nothing
or else you'll get the same...
as that bitch did
with her virgin self.
She ain't no virgin.
How the fuck would you know?
Because me and her fucked
the day I turned you down.
- Is there gonna be girls there, though?
- Yeah, Jay, everyone's coming.
Hey, don't be on no hype,
you know.
Trife.
- You reaching that?
- I don't know, man.
- Hey, what are you...
- Billy.
- Go on.
- What, you out of here, yeah?
- Safe.
- Bless, man.
Laters, Jay, man.
All right, Moon.
Hey, hey, wait up, wait up.
Don't say anything.
Hang on a minute.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
- Look, why aren't you speaking to me?
- I am, man.
You ain't chatted to me in, like,
three weeks.
I've been doing
better things, isn't?
- I need to speak to you about something.
- Come on, Alisa.
Call me later, yeah?
Listen, hear what, right.
If you say anything to your fucking dad,
I'll kill you, you understand?
I can make things so easy for you,
you know that?
- Hi, poppet.
- Hey.
Who's that boy you were with?
I thought maybe
it was the one from before.
No, I fell.
He was helping me up.
Oh, right. Only I saw him giving you
a peck on the cheek.
- I thought maybe it was him.
- No.
How was biology?
Katie?
Katie, what the hell's happened
to your face? Look at me.
I fell.
You all right?
Hello?
Yeah, I'm Dan Fineal.
Yeah, Arthur. No, you were supposed
to be there two hours ago, mate.
Trevor.
Get in.
School finish at four.
Why you take so long?
I had to chat to one girl,
isn't it?
This here is Andreas.
Nice to meet you, bruv.
- This is my nephew Trevor.
- Trife.
You have the thing?
You see...
if you don't drill
the replica good...
the bullet won't leave and pop!
Is it okay?
The last boy used to do this
for me, was shit.
Guns always used to blow up.
But this looks good.
But I will have to test it.
Saying?
So, listen, come see me
when you finish school tomorrow...
and we can discuss business,
all right?
- Cool.
- Yeah.
Now get out.
Me just a joke with you.
Me see you tomorrow, yeah?
- Don't be late, you know.
- I won't, I won't.
- Later.
- All right, Trevor.
My little gun driller.
Hi, Katie.
- Hi, love.
- Hi.
- Is she okay?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, she's fine.
Oh, that.
She fell over at school.
Christ, Arthur's really fucked up
my day.
Under the seat.
Oh, shit.
Curtis, I've forgotten the change, man.
I've left it back at my place.
I'm really sorry. I'll bring it round
to yours later, yeah?
Fuck it, I fuck, I fucked up. Look,
take it back, we'll sort it out tomorrow.
Cool. Cool.
You sure?
Go on.
Cool. Cheers, man.
- See you tomorrow.
- Cool, man. Cheers.
I think she's being bullied
at school.
- Did she say that?
- No. But...
Well, don't worry about it.
She's a bright kid, she'd tell us.
Have you seen
my address book anywhere?
Don't worry about it?
What sort of thing is that to say?
Aren't you worried about
your own daughter?
Have you asked her?
There you go.
She's fine.
Lenny, could you get your sister
to turn that shit off, please.
- It's been playing for ages.
- Doesn't bother me.
Fine.
Katie! Katie!
Katie!
We are number one for hip-hop
and in London.
And around the country, Sky Digital,
Telewest and Digital DAB Radio.
Billy-Bob Thornton,
Angelina Jolie's ex-husband...
has said that she's not
that good in bed.
Hey, mum, I got it, yeah.
- What go on, coz?
- Yes, blood.
- What's happening, man?
- Like the trim still, man.
- Hey, what you want, though?
- Hey, come say hello to my mum, blood.
- Morning, Jason.
- Morning, Mrs. Hector.
I hope you two boys use this day
to remember that poor girl...
and not for foolishness.
- Yes, mum.
- Course, Mrs. Hector.
Go on.
That's right, blood,
do what your mum says.
Shut up, man.
Yeah, blood...
school called here this morning.
Told my mum the whole year
had the day off.
- This is proper sad, man.
- I know, man.
I was just about to leave my yard,
like had my uniform on and everything.
Listen, blood, Sam and them girls
always picking on her.
Yeah, but Sam
troubles us too, blood...
and we ain't committing suicide
over it, are we?
If anyone should fucking die,
it's him man.
Can't believe someone
I pressed is dead.
So why didn't you tell me
then, man?
She asked me
not to say nothing, isn't it.
Thought people would call her
sket and thing.
Plus her dad caught us...
Hey, you got a zoot?
No, I got a roll up, though.
Jacked it off my mum.
Spark that, man.
Blood, weird thing is, though...
her dad came by late last night.
That's how I found out
she was dead.
In her suicide note, she said
something about Sam troubling her.
- But I was always nice to her.
- A note?
Well, did she mention me?
I never see you chat to her
anyway, man.
Blood, don't watch
what I do, man.
You ain't always with me, and
you never knew I pressed her either.
You come like some secret agent
or something, man.
Let me have two draw
of that, man.
Hey, listen bell Moony.
I wanna duck out quick.
The whole day?
Don't lie, blood.
Yeah, I'll have
to take a cab still.
Moons, just hurry up though, man.
All right, bless.
- Hey, blood, you see Katie, yeah?
- Yeah.
Do you reckon
she would have banged me, like?
No, man.
Why not?
I think I'm buff.
Blood, I beg you,
play the fucking game, man.
Oh, fuck's sake.
Hello?
- Yeah, who's that?
- It's me.
You didn't call me.
Did you hear?
Sad, isn't it?
- Look, what are you doing today?
- Gonna jam with Moons and Jay.
Might go up West End later.
Gotta check my uncle, why?
- No, just tell me now, man.
- I'd rather see you.
You don't need to see me,
you ain't my girl no more. What is it?
What the fuck do you mean
you're pregnant?
Oh, my days!
You can't be fucking pregnant. I thought
you'd get the morning after pill?
It's not just up
to the girls, you know.
Yeah, of course I'm sure.
I've been taking tests all week.
Look...
I want us to get back together.
Later, fuck that.
After you fucked Sam a few weeks ago?
Yeah, he told me he bare backed you.
That's even worse man.
- You never knew I knew that, did you?
- But we do know!
Hey, and don't bother trying
to explain, man.
You know what,
for all I know the baby's his.
Fact now that I think of it,
I know it is, and you know it too.
Yeah, blood, she's loose, man.
Cut her off, man.
What?
I slept with Katie last year.
Me and you weren't even together,
so fuck off!
Standard, blood. You get me. I told you
about that girl, man, she's a sket.
Pregnant, though.
It's a bit deep, still.
- So what you gonna do?
- I don't know, man.
Fuck it, it can't be mine.
I just don't need
this shit today.
So what, can man's come
and reach your uncle with you, blood?
No, I think he wants
to see me alone, still.
So, what did he say?
He said he's going out.
And that fucking Sam told him
we slept together.
So why didn't you tell him
what happened?
He didn't give me
a fucking chance.
You know what, yeah,
fuck him and this fucking baby.
- All right, girls?
- Mum, don't you knock?
Oi, none of your lip.
I know you're upset,
but that's no reason to be cheeky.
- Do you want a drink, Becky?
- No, thanks.
Right, I'm off to work.
Lis, I want you back by midnight.
- Oh, mum!
- One, then, on the dot.
And if you think you can't get back here
call your dad and he'll pick you up.
- All right?
- Okay.
Alis...
I know you're upset, but there's
nothing you could have done.
Now, I'm sad for
that other girl's parents...
but all that really matters
is that you're all right.
Are you all right?
I'm...
I'm fine.
Good.
See you later, darling.
- I love you, Lis.
- Love you.
Yo, D. Guess what, man,
I got the day off school.
And I'm going to that party
tonight as well.
Yeah, I know.
Your school belled a while ago.
Hi, Lenny.
I'm sorry about your sister, bro.
Tell your mate Trevor
I said thank you.
See you.
So, you gonna help me or what?
Yeah.
I still can't believe
Katie killed herself.
So, what do you wanna do?
You know what...
I wanna get fucked up.
I wanna go shopping for tonight,
that'll make me feel better.
And if Trife don't want me,
I'm sure someone else will.
I meant about the baby.
Lose it, if I'm lucky.
Well, at least
you're thinking straight.
We've got the whole day off,
we might as well do something...
constructive with ourselves.
I know where we can score
some wicked draw.
I'd get so fat if I kept this.
Taxi!
What the fuck, man?
What's fucking taking him
so long, man?
Taxi!
Fuck off!
Fucking hell, man!
Come on.
Fuck, man.
Look at this girl's pussy. Looks like
her guts are hanging out and shit.
Man, that's nasty, man.
I hate that shit, ugly pussy.
- Still poke it, though.
- No, that's not for me, star.
I won't fuck no girl, yeah,
unless she's got a DV?
DV?
Designer vagina, man.
Neat tucked in lips and shit.
It's the way forward, blood.
So, who's this guy again?
Rupert. I met him at some rave.
He gives me weed and shit for free.
Is it? Safe.
Finally.
Let's roll, man.
Yes, Jay, what's cooking, bruv?
- Yeah, like the trim, rude boy.
- Bye, mum.
- What took you so fucking long, man?
- There weren't no cabs, isn't it.
I've been having a good week, actually.
Come on in.
So, Rebecca,
who's your lovely friend?
- I'm Alisa.
- Alisa? What a pretty name.
Ladies, this is my friend
Hamish.
Hi.
Go and take a seat on the sofa, take
your coats off, make yourselves at home.
How much do you want this time?
- As much as you wanna give.
- Not a problem.
But I want some E's today
and maybe some coke.
The weed I can do for free, but,
coke and E's is gonna cost.
I haven't got no money on me.
Who needs money?
- Get your knickers off then.
- In your fucking dreams.
- What, you're not gonna let me fuck you?
- No.
- What about a blow-job then?
- Fuck off.
- Wank?
- Keep talking and you'll get a smack.
Oh, come on, Al,
we'll make dollars when we sell it.
Do you wanna shop or what?
- Yeah, but...
- Stop being such a boring bitch then.
But I'm not gonna suck it, okay?
What is that?
- How old are you?
- I'm old enough, blood.
"Blood", you're too young
to buy these beers.
- What? Oh, shut up, man.
- Oi, come back.
- Come back!
- Come back or what, man? Shut your mouth.
- I'll have you arrested!
- You ain't gonna do shit, man.
- Get out of my shop.
- What?
- You're banned!
- Man, I'll leave when I wanna leave, man.
What? Come.
- Dickhead.
- Fuck off.
Bastard!
I ain't fucking with her no more, man,
after she got banged by Sam.
Fuck that, you get me?
She's any girl to me now. Fuck her.
Bloods, I wouldn't care whose baby
it is, yeah, but I'd still bang that.
Hey, bloods, where's yours?
Had to dash it at that guy,
isn't it, man.
- He was shook, though.
- You're a bad man.
Let's dust, man.
I ain't standing on the corner like
a fucking rent boy all day.
- So what, which way are we going, bruv?
- Let's roll this way, isn't it.
What's wrong, man?
What are you looking at?
Sam lives over there.
- You wanna get your GameBoy back?
- Yeah.
Yeah that, I'm on that, man,
let's do it. Come, come.
Let's not be stupid, man.
- So, what are we gonna do?
- Sam's gonna be at school, blood, yeah?
Only our year's got the day off.
We'll just go up there,
say we're his friends...
and we're picking it up,
isn't it? Simple.
Or, we ding the bell,
get through the main door...
and boot down his fucking
front door, isn't it.
No, man.
That's some police shit.
Look, blood, there's three
of us alie...
we'll just go up there, yeah,
ask for it back.
And if he's gets brave, blood, we'll
handle it at school together, isn't it.
- Standard, let's roll.
- But he rolls deep, man!
- Hey, fuck it, man, let's do it.
- Oh, shit.
What the fuck is he doing at home,
man? He's gonna kill us.
- Hey, don't worry, man, he's gone.
- What if he comes back, though, like?
He won't, man. What's wrong with you?
What you scared for, man?
I'm not, man.
I think we should just duck, man.
- Just shut up, man, you're scared.
- I'm not.
- Hello.
- Hi.
We're Sam's friends. We've just come
here to pick something up.
Sam's not here.
He's just gone to the shop for me.
Yeah, we saw him downstairs, he told
us to come up and wait for him.
He just left, right?
Hey, that must be his room.
- That's where your GameBoy is.
- Is that my GameBoy, bloods?
Oh shit, shit, oh shit.
What if he comes back now?
What the fuck
are you lot doing here?
Sam jacked my sister's GameBoy,
yeah, I'm just here to take it back.
- Hold this boy.
- Hey, Moons, hold him. Hold him, man.
He told me he bought that,
he's such an arsehole.
Yo, what's out there?
Balcony, where he stashes
his weed and shit.
Come and take this boy
outside, man.
If he's such an arsehole,
why are you with him?
I don't know, he's older,
more mature.
Then why you cheat him?
- Blood, you can't take his weed, man.
- Fuck that, man.
- Hey, Jay, man, we got him.
- Just give me one minute, man.
I don't even know
why you're with that boy, man.
Look...
you could be my girlfriend.
It's just, he said if I leave him,
he'll tell everyone I was a shit fuck.
No, no, I know you're not shit,
I bet you're cold in bed, man.
I don't know...
He says I'm not that good
and I've only slept with him, so...
Yeah, well, let me be the judge
of that then, isn't it.
What?
- What, has he got any rubbers in here?
- Yeah, in that drawer. Why?
Not now, Jay, man, his mum said
he only went down the road.
- Maybe you lot should go.
- You know what, don't watch that, man.
Oh, no, no, no, low it, man.
- I'm sorry, yeah, this don't normally...
- It's okay.
It's because you're so buff,
yeah, and like you're good, man.
In fact, yeah, you should leave
that pussyhole and be my girlfriend.
- What do you think, yeah?
- What if he beats me up or something?
No, he ain't gonna do that.
Look, you know what, darling.
- Come with me. Come.
- Are you done?
- One minute.
- You fucking know about it.
You let the side down!
What's up, man? You don't even know
about sex live, man.
What the fuck you lot doing
in my yard?
Look, blood, you took
my GameBoy, man, I just...
Are you dizzy, blood? You're gonna
come up here like you're bad.
You see, yeah,
I'm gonna fuck you up, blood.
And you, see, you, Claire, I'm gonna
shove this bat so far up your pussy...
Shit.
Hey, fuck you, you fucking prick.
- Fucking idiot!
- Hold on, hold on, man.
Oh, shit!
Come on, lets go.
Run, blood!
I can't believe
what you lot just done.
Hey, fuck him, man,
he deserved it.
Hey, you know
he fucked Alisa, isn't it?
No, I didn't.
Sam's gonna kill me.
He ain't gonna do shit to you, man.
You know why?
Because you're my girl now,
you get me?
Yeah, man, let him come, man.
You see my uncle I'm checking today?
He's a proper bad man. And if Sam
thinks about doing anything...
my uncle will murk him
on the spot, standard.
You keep talking about your uncle
that's gonna do this and that, yeah?
But we ain't even met him, man.
I mean, what...
are you sure my man
even exists, like?
He comes like the invisible man
or something, blood.
- Yeah. Hollow Man, rude boy.
- I'll slap you, you know that, Moons?
Just wait till we need him
and he'll be here.
If he's there, I'm there. I'll jook
some up, blood. I don't business.
Shut up, Moons man,
you ain't gonna do shit, man.
I can't believe you swallowed
that guy's spunk.
I hate it, it tastes like
salty egg whites.
Yuk, but what
if he's got something?
You can't catch nothing like that.
All the acids in your stomach kill it.
- Did you like wanking that guy?
- No.
Was you wet?
- Yeah, a little bit.
- A little bit?
- Yeah, but his thing's so small, man.
- I bet you was mad wet, I was.
Well then, why didn't you
just fuck that Rupert friend...
and I wouldn't have had
to wank him.
You just said you liked it.
Anyway only my man gets the pussy.
Unlike you, obviously.
You sure you know whose baby it is?
- Don't try it, Becky.
- Yeah, well, I couldn't have that in me.
If I was you, I'd want to rip it out
with a coat-hanger.
- Fucking hell, man!
- What, blood?
Didn't I tell them no onions?
Yeah, you did, man,
you did say no onions, blood, man.
Didn't I say no onions?
Fool.
- Oi, what's going on?
- We got money, relax yourself.
Drive, man.
So, what, are me and you on
or what now?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm your girl.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
Come here.
Well, I gotta go home.
I'll see you tonight, yeah?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
all right, take care, yeah.
Coke head baby.
Whatever, man,
it'll be gone soon.
God, I ain't changing
no fucking nappies for it.
Look, yeah, there's an abortion clinic
number here, do you wanna bell it?
Not now, man. Not today.
Look, can I use your toilet?
Are you gonna do a shit?
Because if you are, then, no.
That's loose, man, I don't do that
in other people's houses.
Well, hurry up, we need to get
the money for the garms.
Yeah, she's banged up, babes.
Yeah.
All right, see you soon.
- Who was that?
- My man.
- Listen, lads, where you off to?
- Oxford Street, man.
Well, why don't you walk?
It's only down the road.
Because we wanted
to catch a cab, man.
Why don't you shut your mouth
and mind your own business, blood?
Well, to be honest might have
to drop you off at Marble Arch...
- because the traffic's...
- What's wrong with you?
Yeah, man, yeah, Trife
and them two little pussyholes.
Yeah, man, yeah. No, no, don't reach,
don't reach, I'm cool, yeah.
Listen I swear down, blood,
if I see them before you see...
I'm gonna bang them up.
I'm gonna bust their heads,
do you understand me?
Listen, if you eye them, yeah if you
see them, you just ding me, yeah.
- Can we go and get something to eat?
- No, I don't wanna look fat for Mark.
- But I'm starving, though.
- We'll get a pizza when we get to his.
- Cheers, mate.
- That's nine pound twenty, mate.
You know what, mate, I got passed
by five black cabs today.
- Well, that ain't my fault, mate.
- Just because I'm black.
Ain't that ironic, though, like?
Black cab don't take black man.
- So, what's your point?
- My point is that...
it becomes a vicious circle.
- Well, what's that mean?
- It means...
Come back!
- Come on.
- You little black bastard!
Now I'm hungry.
Why did you bring me here again?
We give him some dope and he gives us
money for our dresses.
Can we get it and go, please,
because I'm really tired...
of listening to you two fuck.
Look...
I didn't know he was gonna be so old.
He's twenty-eight. He's an actor.
That's almost twice our age.
I know, but he thinks I'm eighteen,
though, so...
You were good, baby.
You lot want anything else?
No.
Hang on, hang on,
I thought she was pregnant?
Yeah, she is right now,
but she's getting rid of it.
- Go on, Lis, it's good.
- Okay.
So how much do you want for all this?
Three hundred?
Yeah.
All right, I'll go get it.
Right, I'll be back
in a minute, yeah?
So, you like what you see, huh?
No.
So what do you
come upstairs for then?
- I wanted to see if she was all right.
- She was fucking great.
- I bet you are as well.
- Fuck off!
You're sick.
- You know she's only fifteen?
- Yeah, of course I do.
I found her student card.
She thinks
it's her little secret.
Do you know
what my little secret is?
Go on, have a guess.
I'm a fucking bastard.
You know, I've never fucked
a pregnant girl before...
but, with you,
I think I'd make the exception.
How about you fuck yourself?
You should take the chance
while you can, you little slag.
- What did you just call me?
- I called you a fucking little slag...
because you're fifteen years old
and you're pregnant.
Probably some little black fellow
who hasn't hung around.
But that's cool,
because I like you.
So when you've decided
to dump it...
why don't you come back
and see me?
You won't have to get jealous of me
fucking your mate...
because I'll probably
fuck you too.
You know...
- you're not right about everything.
- What's that, then?
You're not a bastard...
you're a cunt.
Right, ready for round two, baby?
Boy! This shop is heavy.
Good afternoon, sirs.
Can I help you?
- Yeah. Where are your hats, rude girl?
- Downstairs, sir.
- It's here?
- It's over there.
This is what you want, isn't?
What do you think?
You know what,
blood fuck that guard, man.
can we kick, man?
I'm sure they've got better stuff
down the road anyway.
Hey!
Wait.
Come on, come on.
Come with me. Come on.
Get the fuck off me, man!
What you doing?
- You're in a lot of trouble, mate.
- For what?
- Stealing that hat.
- I had it on when I come in, man.
- What's he taken?
- The cap.
He had it on
when we came in, bro.
Hey, pipe down, please.
And I'm not your bro.
Oi, fuck off, blood, about pipe down.
Get off me, man!
Listen, I told you,
I fucking had that when I come in.
- Don't swear at me.
- And what the fuck you gonna do?
You better watch it,
the police have been called.
Hey, call them, man.
I don't give a fuck.
I'll tell them, too.
I had the hat when I come in.
Hey, check your cameras, man.
Nisha, would you call
the police, please.
This young man has taken this hat
and is now causing a commotion.
- Is that all he's taken?
- Yeah.
But he was wearing that cap
when he came in.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, because I greeted him.
Thank you!
- I'm not sure that he was.
- I am sure. Sorry.
Move out the fucking way
and let us out, man! Yo, blood.
- Are you gonna fucking apologise, coz?
- Just leave, please.
- Hey, hold up, man.
- What?
Do you know what?
You want your hat so much, take it.
Fucking prick!
I'm stinging. Were you watching?
I bet you could hear, isn't it?
So, three hundred squids, yeah, babes.
We'll split it down the mids.
You got shoes, right?
We can't be looking like no tramps.
Yeah.
You are looking forward
to tonight, yeah?
I don't know, yeah, probably.
What's the matter, then?
You look like someone just...
Exactly. Look,
I've been thinking about stuff.
Me like this,
Katie killing herself.
I mean, that is why
we got the day off.
I don't know, maybe
we shouldn't go to the party.
What?
I don't know.
It's like, it's weird. It's strange.
She was so tall and pretty...
I wish I was that tall.
You know, I reckon
she could have been a model.
I knew she was troubled, but...
I never thought it was that bad
that she'd have to kill herself.
Well, it's done now.
Nothing we can do.
- I could have stuck up for her.
- So why didn't you?
I don't know.
Well, she's dead now.
Get over it. I am.
Don't you ever think about anything
but yourself?
Yeah.
Clothes, shoes, money, sex.
Wait, sex involves me
though, don't it?
Do you think Moony likes me?
- I don't know.
- He's so fine.
I won't fuck him
unless he eats me out.
- Do you think he will?
- I don't know.
So when you gonna get rid
of this baby?
- Lis?
- Just leave it, Becky, yeah?
Saint Martin Girls.
What you lot saying?
Oi, do you hear about that big bird
girl that committed suicide?
Proper sensitive, isn't it?
She got so upset.
We was only joking with her.
- Didn't look like a joke.
- Lis, shush.
She just got a bit feisty, that's all.
She needed a little bit of slapping.
But we was only playing with her.
We never meant her to slit her wrists.
- She hung herself.
- Whatever. She's dead.
- Because of you.
- What?
She killed herself because you
and your friends bullied her...
till she couldn't take it
no more.
- You killed her.
- Shut up, you sket.
- Fucking shut up.
You killed her.
Listen, right, if you don't fucking
shut up, you're gonna join her.
Look she don't mean it, yeah. Please,
don't beat us up. She's pregnant.
You're that girl
that Sam fucked.
Wait till I tell everyone
about this ho.
You know what?
Yeah, tell them.
Tell them Alisa's pregnant
and she's keeping the fucking baby.
- What?
- I ain't scared of you.
If you're gonna do something
to me, then do it.
Go on.
I got bigger things to worry about
than what you can do to me.
What's the matter?
- You should bang her up, star.
- I should, shouldn't I?
What the fuck were you thinking,
Alisa? They could have beat us up.
- So?
- You're so selfish.
What if my face got scarred
or something?
And what the fuck are you talking about
"keeping the baby"?
You're not gonna have
an abortion now?
- Just leave it, Becky.
- So, what, are you like pro-life now?
No, but a girl we both
knew just died...
and I didn't do anything
to stop it.
- But I can do something about this.
- So, okay...
what about school?
What if you'd have got raped?
Would you have an abortion then?
- I don't know. Yeah, probably.
- You have to get rid of it.
- Who's gonna help you?
- I don't need any help.
- You all right?
- Yeah, it's morning sickness.
- It's not morning though.
- Look, I need to speak to Trife.
Let's go and buy our garms.
And then we'll find him, okay? Come on.
Curtis lives up there.
- What, is that it?
- I think so.
You think so?
You think...
you think so?
Do you think I've got time
for what people think now, Del?
- Is this the place, bro?
- Yes, it's the place.
But you gotta do this
on your own, bruv.
I'll wait for you back at mine.
- You're gonna go now, is it?
- I can't be seen here, man.
What would you do, man?
- That was a forty five pound hat, bloods.
- So?
You could've give it to me
for tonight, like.
Blood, it wouldn't have fit
your big African head anyway, man.
Oh my days!
You man, you man, you man,
check that gash over there, blood.
- Shit, check the back of, rude boy.
- She's bathing as well, you know.
See, that's what I want, blood.
I want a rich bitch like that.
Yeah, so, so what, who's on it?
Me, yeah?
No, blood, that's me, man.
I saw her first, isn't it?
My size.
Hey, darling, I'm...
Hey, girl,
I'm talking to you, man.
I'm chatting to you!
I don't think she's on it.
Blood, can't chat to a girl
like that, man.
You think you're nang, blood? Why
don't you show him how to do it, then?
Fuck it.
Let's duck, man.
He don't wanna check for that
because he's still on Alisa, isn't it?
Man, I'll show you now
I can chat to that girl, man.
Go on then.
- Why is he always on our hype, man?
- He thinks he's big, man.
- Hey, can I help you?
- Do you work here?
No, sorry,
just making conversation.
I wouldn't buy
these trainers, though.
- Seriously, I wouldn't.
- Why not?
Well, the front always comes off.
Plus, those are the old ones.
New ones are upstairs.
Trevor.
Stella.
- Want a zoot, blood?
- Yeah. Come, we get out of here, man.
You know I could have got
the number though, isn't it?
- So could I, blood.
- I don't think so, blood.
You look smart...
What do you do?
Smart. That's a new one.
What... like smartly dressed?
- No, clever, intelligent.
- Thank you.
I'm an architect.
Rings? You married?
Yeah, my...
husband's been away
a while.
If I was your husband,
I'd never leave you.
And I don't need Viagra,
you know.
Thank you...
that's useful to know.
Don't you get lonely
by yourself?
Yeah.
Yeah. I do.
Actually, sometimes I could use
a bit of company.
- I'd keep you company.
- I bet you would.
- How old are you?
Twenty-six. You?
- I'm twenty-three.
- You're not twenty-three.
All right, I'm twenty-two,
but I'm mature, man.
- Twenty-two? Really?
- All right, I'm twenty, I swear.
It's not like I'm trying it on
or anything.
Good.
Because I wouldn't want
to disappoint you.
My girl puts onion in my burger.
But, blood, man, you shouldn't have
thrown it, though, isn't it?
She didn't do what I asked.
You should have gave
the burger to me, blood, man.
- Man, I don't like onions.
- Hey, what happened, man?
She's a cock tease, man. She's on it,
and then she ducked, isn't it?
That's a bit weird. White girls
usually fuck you for a browns.
- I knew you wouldn't get that, rude boy.
- Standard.
Shut up, man. I'm still gonna bang
that when I go see her.
How are you gonna bang her, blood
and go see her when she kicked out.
Are you stupid or something?
No.
I got this,
and I'm gonna bring it to her.
Hey, blood, hold him,
hold him, hold him.
Jay, I beg you, pass it back, man.
Hey, Moons, Moons, Moons. Hey, Jay.
Blood, she got plenty dollars in here,
you know. And she's a...
Boy! What the fuck are you doing, man?
Where are you going?
- Leave it. Leave it out, he's a youth.
- Or what, coz?
Or else I'll bust you in your head
you fucking white pussyhole!
What? Blood, you think because
I'm white, I won't knock you out?
Is that right, blood?
Yo, let me take my hat off.
How about white boy,
skinhead nutter, mate?
Does that work better for you,
dickhead?
Oi.
- Shit.
- That's really good though, cousin.
What, man,
you think that scares me?
Man, you don't even know me.
Low it low it, come on, come on.
Just get out of here, man.
You men got murked, like.
- What the fuck is wrong with you, man?
- What are you talking about?
You! Starting fights
in the middle of the street, man.
I was backing you up, blood.
That's not what
I'm talking about, blood.
If we plan something together,
that's cool.
But that was under control
until you started, man.
You can't just start arms house
in the middle of the street.
- What's wrong with you, blood?
- Just cool it, Jay, man.
All right, man.
So where's the purse?
Wait, blood. I told you, yeah,
I want the fucking cards, isn't it.
No, man, who fucking took it?
Give me the purse!
Blood, man, you want,
you want the cards, yeah?
- Yes, I want the fucking cards.
- You want the cards.
- Hey, Moons. Moons.
- Hey, blood, don't fuck about.
So what, you can share
your girl with Sam...
and you can't even share
the purse with us, blood.
You fucking prick.
- Get the fuck off me!
- Fuck is wrong with you, blood?
We're gonna split that or not?
All right, that's what it's got to?
You know what, take your fucking
purse, you like it so much.
You're a dickhead, man.
Hey, blood,
don't take it out on us...
because your girl
got pressed by next man.
If you was somebody else, I would have
stabbed your claret, rude boy!
Stab me then, blood!
My uncle'll kill you!
You and your fucking uncle, man!
If my man's even real.
You know what, blood, if he is real,
yeah, you better go to him, isn't it?
Because, blood, you ain't got no-one
no more, man. You ain't got Alisa.
You ain't got that sket no more.
And we ain't backing you no more.
Come, Moons, man.
Hey, who the fuck you chatting to, man?
Without me, you two ain't shit!
And Alisa, I can have her if I want,
but I don't need her.
I don't need pussyhole friends
like you, either.
Yeah, you keep telling
yourself that, blood.
Remember, we might call you Trife
but your name's Trevor.
- Remember that, blood.
- Come, we jet, blood.
Claire, honey,
Sam's here to see you.
Thanks, Mrs. Parkinson.
I'll leave you kids to it.
- Where are they?
- Who?
Don't try to boy me off,
them three little pussyholes.
I don't know.
I'm only gonna ask you this
one more time.
- Where are they?
- I don't know.
Jeez.
Listen, yeah.
My mum nearly broke her arm.
You better start talking,
or I'm gonna bang you up, you hear me?
When we get to school, I'm gonna tell
everyone what a rubbish fuck you are.
And how bad you smell.
If you know what I'm saying.
Please, don't, I really don't know
where they are.
All I know is that they're going to
that party tonight.
That's where they're gonna be.
So why weren't I invited?
Because no-one
that's going likes you.
Sam, stop, please.
I'm sorry.
Claire?
Claire, baby, are you all right?
Yeah, mum, I'm fine.
Me and Sam are just talking.
Okay.
Use a condom,
sweetheart.
That brings me
to my next question.
Whose girl are you?
Because I don't even know
why I bother with you.
You're ugly, you're a shit fuck, and
you're with me, like sixth-form top boy.
If it weren't for me,
who would even look at you?
I don't know.
- Why did you sleep with Alisa?
- Why'd you fuck that fucking Jay?
In my drum as well!
I don't know. I'm sorry.
It's all right, it's all right.
It's just... I do everything you want,
whenever you want me to.
So why are you mean to me
and all that? I don't understand.
Come here.
Okay, so Plaza, yeah?
In an hour.
- All right, then. Bye.
- Right, see you then. Bye.
Come fuck on, man.
Look, what you need is
some retail therapy, yeah?
Alisa says to meet her in the cafe thing
downstairs in one hour.
What, did you tell her
that Trife ain't here?
No.
Are you a fool or something,
blood?
You don't think she really wants
to chat to you, do you?
I don't know.
You know, fuck it isn't it, I'll tell her,
I'll give her a piece of my mind, man.
You get me?
Oh my God, that dress looks dark
on you. Is that the one you want?
Yeah, I think so.
Well, I got all these.
I can't make my mind up.
We are gonna be the hottest girls
there tonight.
Everyone else is gonna look like
tramps compared to us.
Hi, madam, can I help?
Is that the dress you like?
- Yeah.
- It looks great on you.
Well, if you pull your
hair back like this...
it will accentuate
your fabulous figure.
- Thank you.
- Nice figure?
Not for long.
She's knocked up.
Congratulations.
My wife is pregnant.
- Wife? I thought you were a batty man.
- Excuse me?
- Ain't you gay?
- No.
- There's nothing wrong with it.
- I know, I'm just saying.
- All right, calm down, Yankee.
- I'm Canadian.
- Same thing.
- Excuse me, how much is this one?
This one is a hundred
and thirty pounds.
Becks?
Well, I want this one.
How much is it?
This one is two hundred
and ten pounds.
Lis, can you not find another one?
I really want this one.
- We've got three hundred between us.
- Yeah, and you said you'd split it.
Look, who got the money?
I'm doing you a favour
in the first place by getting you one.
Come on, soon you'll have
a big fat belly anyway.
You won't be able to wear it.
You've still got ninety quid.
I'm sure you can get something nice.
Don't worry, honey.
I'll find you something to make
you look even more fabulous.
- Trevor?
- Yeah.
He'll be with you in a sec.
You're a handsome one,
aren't you?
Trevor.
- What happen?
- You told me to reach.
Debbie look after you?
Yeah.
Come.
Me like the work you did
on that thing.
This...
is for you.
See, I told you I would, man.
If you want me to do
anything else, I'm...
Just cool yourself, man.
What's that?
Heroin.
- You want some?
- I'm cool, man.
Go on...
take some.
You grow fast, man.
Anyway...
me like the work
you did on the gun.
- It's easy, I can...
- Don't speak, just listen.
You know...
all you need in this world
is money...
and if you know how to get it,
you laughing.
- You seen that nice TV in my front room?
- Yeah.
You got one? No? But you'd like one,
of course you would.
Curtis, I've got Keith
on the phone. He wants you to...
Tell him that I talk to my nephew.
Tell him wait.
But he's already on the phone.
He says he's...
Me said tell him wait.
Anyway...
why you don't come work for,
with me?
Trust me, I want to, man.
Fucking had enough of everything else.
- So, what do you want me to do?
- Just a few little things.
That sounds like something
you can do?
Sounds live, man.
I'm there.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Me did sell the last
of the bad guns to some youth.
Me have more of the replicas
for you to drill in the back.
In the meantime...
you did so well with this one
that me think you should have it.
- So where is he?
- I told you.
When he switched, yeah,
we just kicked out and left him, man.
And don't bother trying to call him,
because his phone's off.
Look, I really need
to speak to him.
Listen up, everybody.
Me say listen up.
This is my nephew Trevor.
Real family member that will be joining
our family from now on...
so, treat him nice.
What going on, bro?
What's up with this baby shit, man?
Is this true or something?
Of course it's true.
Who's gonna lie about being pregnant?
- Nuff people, man.
- Well, I'm not lying.
All you do is lie.
And now you've been caught out, you're
trying to drag Trife back into this.
Try and fuck up his life,
isn't it?
Look, I think I should be speaking
to him about this, not you.
You are talking to me.
And what exactly
are you gonna say to him?
"I'm sorry, Trife I fucked another guy
while I was with you."
Because it don't matter
because he knows now.
I'm gonna tell him the truth.
Listen, Trevor.
Come, I want you to handle
something for me.
You're bad, isn't it?
You behave yourselves, yeah?
Anything?
You see, this is the reason
me want you to come work for me.
- Curtis.
- Shut up!
You see this fucker?
Him take my property,
but my money never come back.
Where the fuck is my money,
nigger?
I can get it for you, man.
It's at my place. I told you
I was gonna bring it round later today.
Hey, shut your mouth, blood.
If he wanted it when you decided to
bring it and not when he asked for it...
you wouldn't be tied
to a fucking table, would you?
What are you waiting for?
I'm sorry.
Please, I'm sorry.
You know what, boy?
I want you
to get my money today.
- I will.
- But before you go...
I'm gonna make sure you remember
that you don't fuck with Curtis.
Trevor...
I want you to carve a C from the corner
of him eye to the corner of him mouth.
- Me?
- Yes...
you.
I want you
to carve a blood clotline...
from here to here.
Carve the fucking line.
No, let him.
Cut him.
Man.
Man, please!
Please!
No.
No!
Good.
Trevor... come.
Come here.
Trevor!
Please.
The best thing you
could do right now is fuck off...
and get an abortion of Sam's baby.
Because he don't want you,
and Trife don't want you either.
What, has he said that?
- Who wants a sket like you?
- Has he told you he don't want me.
Yeah.
Now fuck off, isn't it.
What's up with your girlfriend,
though? Fucking Sam.
No wonder Trife dashed her, man,
she's a fucking ho like.
I know.
I couldn't be like that.
Only give my things
to special mans like you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Becks, can we go?
- Where, to the party?
- No, I just wanna go home.
Well, I'm not ready.
- Becky, please, can we just go?
- Look, go if you wanna go.
Don't come to the party tonight, be a
boring cow. I'm staying with this lot.
You know what,
just do what you want, yeah?
Fat cunt.
I fucked that girl
a few weeks ago, blood.
Every day for a week
when she's supposed to be your girl.
Why aren't you speaking to me?
So this party, where is it?
You're not still gonna go,
are you?
You saw what they done to my mum.
Where is it?
Nice invite.
- I don't think you should go.
- Why not?
I just think this thing with them lot
should stop or someone's gonna get hurt.
Your mum's all right
and you got me.
Stay here tonight,
we can fuck all night.
Promise me you'll stay.
All right, I promise.
I just wanna go home and check on
my mum, make sure she's all right.
- Cool. I'll see you later.
- Yeah, I'll see you later.
Alisa!
Wait. Alisa!
- What you doing?
- I'm going home. I only live over there.
- Your hand's bleeding, are you okay?
- Oh, shit.
Yeah, yeah.
- Have you been crying?
- No.
You look like you have.
Are you coming to Blake's party?
Oh, no, I'm really n
in the mood.
Come on, come with us.
I don't know.
You look like you need to be around
some friends to cheer yourself up.
Yeah.
I promise I'll do anything I can
to get you smiling again.
And how are you gonna do that?
Come on, come with me.
Okay. Let me just go home
and get changed, yeah?
But I'm only gonna come, like,
if I can hang out with you.
Hi, this is Alisa.
Please, leave...
Trife... enter, my friend.
While the parents are away and what not.
Want some of this?
It's Cuban.
Where's Alisa?
She's inside.
I think she went into the garden.
Bruv...
blood, sorry, man.
I'll see you later.
Sorry, bruv.
- What you doing?
- So, what, he's your man now?
No, but at least he's been nice to me
today. Look, what do you want?
I wanted to say hello, isn't it.
- Hello.
- How you doing?
If you wanna say something to me,
then say it and leave me alone.
- Hey, what happened to your hand?
- I got it cut.
- Are you all right?
- It's fine.
No, are you all right?
- So what do you do today?
- Nothing that would interest you.
Look, Lis, can we go somewhere
a bit more private, please?
So, what, where is he, then?
I don't know, I just saw him
come out here.
I'm going back in, man. This is...
I don't know why
I come to your party, man.
- So what time you staying till?
- Cool, baby, we just got here, like.
True, it'll probably
get better later.
Would be better
if Blake weren't such a chief.
Look at him trying
to friends up Jay.
I mean... I'd consider this
a success, wouldn't you?
Jay, did I mention
how sharp you look.
Go away, Blake.
I know you tried to speak to me earlier
and I didn't want to listen...
but I wanna talk to you now.
Look, don't worry about your little
life, Trevor, I don't need your help.
And I'm sorry you had to hear
what you heard from Sam...
and I understand
that you don't want me...
but I thought you ought to know
that I never slept with...
All right. I know you never meant
to hurt me and blah, blah...
but before you carry on there's some
things I need to get off my head...
and if I don't,
I'm just gonna forget.
- Look, Trevor, you don't...
- Wait...
I'm on that, boy.
Excuse me, you came with me.
No, there's a difference.
You came with me.
But don't worry, though,
babes, like...
there's enough Moonies
to go around, isn't it, like.
So safe, yeah?
Yeah, Danielle,
what's going on then, man?
I see you at school the other day.
I wanted to come and talk to you...
but you're always with
your friends, man.
- You can still come up to me.
- No, but I don't like...
Please.
Danielle, I'm gonna come
chat to you in a sec, yeah?
So, with both your little buddies
doing there own thing...
is there anything
that you wanna do?
Like what?
Like me.
What?
Do you want to fuck me?
No, not really, I got a girl.
So? I won't tell her.
I thought you liked Moony?
No, I like you.
He's a bit of a fool.
That's one of my best friends
you're talking about down there.
Look, do you wanna fuck or not?
You can put it in my arse as well.
It hurts, but I don't mind.
No, low it, man.
Hey, Danielle.
What I wanted to say is this.
I know we were only going out
for a couple of months...
but it was fun, dred. You made me feel
like feel good, you get me?
I mean, not just sex. I mean, your
things feel good and everything, but...
you.
It was you.
But I didn't know what to do when you
started wanting hugs and that in school.
I started thinking about what the boys
would think and them stupidness there.
When I broke up with you,
I realised I was stupid.
I told everyone, "I ain't going back
out with her", but...
I wanted to.
When I found out you fucked Sam,
it hurt me.
- Look, Trevor...
- Wait.
That hurt me.
That's why I said
what I said today.
I've seen some shit today...
makes me think about life.
You're one of the best things
in mine.
So even though
it's some next man's baby...
I wanna be with you.
And I wanna look after
you both.
I wanna change for you.
Because...
I love you.
Why you laughing?
I said I love you.
- Trevor, I never slept with Sam.
- What?
I've been trying to tell you.
He lied. He told everyone
I went to his house.
He said I might as well go...
because he was gonna
tell everyone he fucked me, but...
I never, I swear.
So, the baby...
You're the only one I've slept with.
It's yours.
- What's wrong?
- Shit.
- My mum's gonna kill me, man.
- Mine too.
Listen, listen, we're gonna work, yeah?
We'll stay together forever.
I'm not sure we will...
but we're gonna have this baby,
so, we should try.
Yeah, pussyhole, what now?
- You think you're a man? Get up.
- Sam don't!
No... you think you're bad?
You wanna act like a big man?
I'm gonna beat you
like a fucking big man!
Where's your two boys? Because you
three pussyholes are finished tonight!
We can work something out,
I swear to you.
Fuck...
- Sam, man, fucking hell, what you doing?
- Shut the fuck up!
Moony! Jay, look, Sam's beating up
Trife outside, right now!
- So, what, are you gonna back us or what?
- No, he's your mate, blood.
You pussy!
You must have lost
your fucking mind fucking with me.
We can work something, I swear to you.
Hey, Jay, don't, man.
Hey, blood,
get the fuck off him, man.
I'm sorry.
Come on then... Come, come.
Hey, low it, man, low it.
Yeah, you are.
You wanna disrespect my mum?
You wanna fuck my girl?
You're not fucking real,
blood, you hear me?
Stay down!
All you fucking pussyholes, yeah.
Any of you fuck with me, this is what
you get, you understand, blood?
Just leave us alone, Sam.
Everyone knows
you never fucked me.
What are you gonna do,
beat us all up?
Who'd wanna fuck you anyway?
Look at you.
- Shut up.
- Suck my dick, you fucking bitch.
Hey, don't fucking touch her!
Fuck you! You fucking prick.
Fucking dickhead.
Trife, get off him, please.
I thought you were gonna change?
Listen to your bitch, Trevor.
Trife, Trife, man!
Something's wrong with Trife!
Are you all right, blood?
Someone call an ambulance, man.
Hey, pussyhole!
Blood. Blood, low it, man,
Trife's hurt.
Low it. He's bleeding.
It's gonna be all right, coz?
- Call a fucking ambulance!
- I've already called one.
What you gonna do, blood?
What you gonna do?
Shit!
Who the fuck is Sam? Hey, you better
tell me who the fuck Sam is, now, man!
You better start fucking talking
because I know he's fucking here!
Who the fuck is Sam?
Baby, baby, listen...
we'll go out on the weekend, yeah?
Me and you, we'll do something nice.
Tell me now!
Blood... Sam's not here,
you know, he's not here.
He's Sam!
What the fuck you talking about,
you fat bitch? Just...
I don't know who you are, coz,
I don't know.
Do you know
my little sister Katie?
- Oh, shit, it's really bad.
- Oh, fuck.
Trife, you're gonna be all right,
though, coz.
Better shut the fuck up, man.
Shut up!
- Get down on your fucking knees, man.
- No, come on, bruv.
Get down on your fucking knees now.
Put your head on the stone. Fucking cry!
See, man look at this,
look at this shit.
I fucking found this shit yesterday,
Sam says he's gonna fucking kill me,
so I'm gonna save them all the trouble.
I'm not even... fuck...
I'm not even scared any more.
Anything's better than here.
And it fucking goes on, you cunt.
She was fucking fifteen, man.
- She was fucking fifteen.
- I never done nothing to her, blood.
Give me one fucking good reason why
I shouldn't fucking blow your head off.
You give me one.
Why you shouldn't die.
Give me one fucking reason
why you shouldn't die!
Because he's not worth it.
Baby, baby, it's really bad!
Oh, fuck. Trife!
He's stopped breathing! What?
Man, where's the doctor?
Trife? Trife?
Let's go, blood, feds.
Come on.
- Pussyhole!
- You're the pussyhole, man.
- No, blood. No, blood, blood.
- I beg you, please!
- Fuck! Fuck!
- Come on, let's go!
Shit, man. Fucking hell, Derek.
Fuck! Come on.
No, man.
What the fuck are you lot
doing, man? Fuck off!
Fuck you,
you didn't do shit to help, man.
Fuck off and leave him, blood, man.
Why you around watching now?
None of you did shit to help, man.
Fuck you lot...
Get off me, blood.
Get the fuck off me, blood!
Get off me, man.
Subtitles edited by LeapinLar
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player