Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
...
LOOPER
Time travel has not yet been invented,
but 30 years from now, it will have been.
It will be instantly outlawed.
Used only in secret by the
largest criminal organizations.
...
It's nearly impossible to dispose of
a body in the future,
I'm told, for tagging techniques
and things like that,
So when these criminal organizations
in the future need someone gone,
they use specialized assassins
in the present, called Loopers.
And so, my employers in the future
nab the target,
they zap them back to me, their Looper.
He appears hands tied, head sacked.
And I the necessaries, collect my silver.
So the target is vanished from the future,
And I've just disposed of a body
that technically does not exist.
Clean.
...
- How's your French?
- Slow.
- How's the coffee?
- Burned.
...
Two, Jed.
Hey Joe.
Be at the club tonight?
Yeah.
Four, Jed.
...
You walk around.
Around the bike, I'm not kidding!
Hey, I don't want no problems,
- you're rude, if you had a mama...
- Wide around, you shit!
she didn't raise you right.
That's funny, because I'm gonna pick
your mother later on my bike,
and I'll take my Blunderbuss...
- Hey Seth.
- Hey Joe.
- That's new.
- Yeah, thanks.
God damn thing won't fucking tart.
So you're going to the Belle?
- So you bought a slab bike?
- Yep!
How much did that thing set you back?
How much?
I was gonna pull up it tonight.
Congratulations, you're
pulling up with me instead.
Don't.
If we're going in, don't do that.
- Chicks dig the TKs.
- Ain't true, pal.
- Yes, they do!
- Well that's tacky. Don't do it.
About 10% of the population
has this TK mutation.
When they first appeared,
everyone thought
we were gonna get superheroes.
But it turns out this was it.
Now it's just a bunch of assholes
who think they'll blow your mind
floating quarters.
It's like this whole town.
Big heads, small potatoes.
Full house tonight, Joe.
We'll stick back stage.
Just meetin' up, in and out.
Cash in your Blunderbusses?
Hardly. Right, Seth?
Hardly. I'm with Joe.
Just meetin' up and in and out.
- Hey, Suzie!
- Hey!
- You're working a shit tonight?
- Yeah.
Yeah, but a Gat Man bought me
out already for the night.
Sweetie, I gotta work.
Joe.
What?
Zack, he's in there right now with Abe.
- For what?
- Closed his loop.
No shit.
There's a reason we're called Loopers.
when we sign up for this job,
taking out the future's garbage,
we also agree to a very specific provisal.
Time travel in the future is so illegal,
that when our employers
wanna close our contracts,
they'll also wanna erase any trace
of their relationship
with us ever existing.
So if we're still alive 30 years from now,
they'll find our older self,
zap him back to us,
and we'll kill him like any other job.
This is called 'closing your loop. '
And you get a golden pay day,
you get a handshake,
and you get released from your contract.
Enjoy the next 30 years.
This job doesn't tend to attract
the most forward thinking people.
So we're... celebrating?
Look out!
You did it!
- Jesus.
- Fuck, Joe!
...
What's that, fourth loop
closed this month?
Loop closed! Here we go.
Loop closed, baby!
Yeah.
Seth. Jesus...
They'll be here any minute,
Are they here?
- No. Who?
- Christ.
Joe, Christ!
- What are you doing?
- Give me the gun.
- Alright...
- Come on.
- Get away from the window.
- Christ, Joe.
Quiet down.
You can protect me a little, right, Joe?
- Just so they don't...
- What did you do?
Jeez.
This is like a nightmare.
This is a nightmare.
I knew then what he did,
so I don't know why I asked.
What did you do?
He... he was singing.
through the gag-it-sack,
but I could hear the tune.
Deep memories...
My mom in a dark room,
taking care of me, singing that tune.
That's how I knew... it was me.
I...
Joe, I couldn't.
I couldn't, I had to see.
He told me...
I remember.
He told me... there's a new
holy terror boss in the future,
and he's closing all the loops.
The Rainmaker, they call him.
He told me and...
and then he wanted a cigarette,
so I untied him and he gives me this look.
And he just starts running.
I had my Blunderbuss,
so I know I've got
fifteen strides 'till
he's out of my range.
And they come, and they go,
and I just watch him till he's gone.
This is called, 'letting your loop run. '
It's not a good thing.
What do I do?
You're the only friend I got, Joe.
You gotta help me.
Fucking idiot coming here.
You can't be here.
I'll give you some money,
that's it, then you leave.
Joe, a little money! Where am I gonna go?
You hop a freight train,
you beat it the hell out of town...
Shut up and don't move.
Tell Cor to watch the window outside.
Yeah, I'm on my way.
Kid Blue, Joe, come on!
Just a minute!
Open this goddamn door!
I can't do anything for you, Seth.
You gotta hide me! Please, Joe! Please!
Hide me! Please, Christ!
Please, buy me some time, and I'll go!
Please!
Are you gonna make me
bust this door down?!
Yeah, hold on!
Please...
Move!
Come on, Joe! Open up!
Ok...
Jeez...
That took a while.
You think it's easy lookin' this good?
Tye is gonna watch your apartment
while we go have a talk with Abe.
- There's coffee in the tin.
- Thank you.
Give me two minutes.
Do you know why they call that
pea shooter here a Blunderbuss?
Cause it's impossible to hit
anything further than 15 yards.
Impossible to miss anything closer.
It's a gun for fuck-up turkeys.
Not like a Gat.
A Gat has a range.
Accuracy.
Kid, cut it out, or you'll
blow your other foot off.
What the hell's goin' on out there?
- How you doin', Abe?
- Hey.
You didn't shoot your other
foot off, did you, Kid?
Right.
My great-grandfather
told my grandfather,
mens are like spiders.
It's the little ones you
gotta be careful of.
I don't know if I agree with that.
Yeah?
What the fuck did my
great grandfather know?
This man is from the future.
He was sent back here by the mob.
A one way ticket to run the Loopers.
That's low effort, even for Abe,
so to pass the time, he recruited
some real muscle, the Gat Men.
Now he runs the city.
Any other city, that'd be impressive.
How can you kids stand
to wear those chilipers?
- ... cravats.
- Ties.
Ridiculous. You're aware
we don't have a dress code.
Fashion.
You know... well, you don't know.
The movies that you're dressing like
are just copy of other movies.
It's Goddamn twentieth
century affectations.
Do something new,
Put a... glowing thing around your neck,
or use rubberized...
Just be new.
- OK.
- Well.
Well, it's nice chatting with you, Abe.
You do like you, Joe.
But I'm sure enough that
Seth paid you a visit,
and we're gonna have to do
something about this.
Seth?
You're expecting that we're
going to break your fingers
with a hammer or... something awful,
but, I'm gonna diffuse
that tension right now.
That's not gonna happen.
What is gonna happen,
is that I'm gonna talk for a little.
Not even that long.
And then you're gonna
give up your friend.
My friend? Seth!
Sorry, I'm... I'm confused.
Well then, I'll talk a little.
You know, you were the
youngest Looper I ever hired.
You looked Goddamn ridiculous, they said.
Blunderbuss up to here on you.
I remember they brought you in,
I forget what it was for.
Watch shop.
That's... yeah.
You rolled one of our fronts,
the watch shop.
And they had you, you know,
you know this kid,
like an animal. But you...
you looked at me,
your hair stuck to half your face,
just one eye looking at me.
I could see.
I could see in it happen on the TV,
the bad version of your life.
Like a vision,
I could see, how you'd turn bad.
So I changed it.
I cleaned you up,
and put a gun in your hand.
I gave you something that was yours.
And I am grateful for that, Abe.
And I remember that, kid...
And I think if you ask yourself,
if you ask who would I sacrifice
for what's mine,
I think Seth would be deep
and cozy inside that circle.
Hey...
Now I'll show you how much I know you.
I'm not even gonna break you,
I'm just gonna set you back aways.
Now we know that you've
been stashing half your bars.
Which is smart, no law against it.
You're gonna get out,
you're gonna go overseas, right?
- Studying up your Mandarin?
- French.
French?
You give him up,
or you give us half your stash.
You're willing to dump your silver
in the dirt... for Seth.
- You gonna kill him?
- Not if we can help it.
It's too cataclysmic
a change for the future.
Now, what we'll do is
dangerous in that regards,
well not... that dangerous
than just killing him,
on top of which a man from
the future runs free long enough,
this... time travel shit just...
fries your brain like an egg.
Why the fuck French?
I'm going to France.
- You should go to China.
- I'm going to France.
I'm from the future,
you should go to China.
- I'm going to France.
- You're going...
Floor safe's under the rug.
6-7-4-2.
It's the little ones that get you.
Why don't you kill an hour, Joe?
On the house.
Call the Doc.
Be at 75 Wire street
in 15 minutes.
Wait!
Wait.
Wait...
I can't remember my mother's face.
She used to run her hands through my hair.
Just like this...
I think I've just let my
best friend get killed tonight.
For silver.
Shit!
Yes. Shit...
Sorry.
I'm gonna give you some money.
I've been stashing my silver for years,
and I'm gonna give you half of it.
It means you can leave.
You wanna give me half your silver?
Silver's got strings.
I got my job...
you got yours.
It's sweet of you to worry about me,
but I'm doing fine.
Why don't we just stick
to 'services rendered'?
Is this what you want?
"HOP A TRAIN OUT OF TOWN. RUN."
- There's 24 of it.
- Count.
Two more trips, just do it.
Goddammit!
Look, the Kid, I'm sorry!
Tell Abe I'm gonna fix this!
I'm gonna find him.
Tell him I'm gonna kill him!
Motherfucker!
...
Shit!
You got any aspirin?
All of them, please.
I'm gonna take that coat too.
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Joe?
I told you to run.
Don't do it, you idiot.
Fucking Kid Blue.
That's two more trips, just do it.
You stupid little shit.
Walk the pavement,
sweep the train yard,
every second that passes is bad.
Get on it!
Little shit!
I can fix this.
- I can find him!
- Go home.
Let the grown ups work...
Kid Blue.
You bastard.
How do I find you?!
...
Coffee?
Please.
Black, and some water.
Anything else?
Are we eatin'?
I ordered something.
Steak and eggs. Rare and scrambled.
Two steak and eggs, coming up.
It must hurt.
I wasn't sure you'd remember her.
Yeah, I put it together.
Clever.
You know...
There's another girl who
works here on the weekends.
- Jenny.
- Right.
Less letters.
That'd be better.
...
- How's your French coming?
- Good.
You gonna tell me how
to be learnin' Mandarin?
I never regretted learning French.
...
No? Well, you'll get there eventually.
Look, obviously.
Alright, listen. I know this
is a hard situation for you,
but we both know how this has to go down.
I can't let you walk away
from this time alive.
This is my life now, I earned it,
you've had yours already.
So why don't you do what old men do,
and die? Get the fuck out of my way.
Why don't you take your little gun
out from between your legs and do it...
.. Boy.
It's hard staring into your eyes.
It's too strange.
You're face looks backwards.
Yeah.
So, do you know what's gonna happen?
You've done all this already, as me?
I don't wanna talk about time travel shit.
Cause if we start talking about it,
then we're gonna be here all day
talking about it,
making diagrams with straws.
It doesn't matter.
If I hurt myself, it changes your body.
This is what I do now,
change your memory.
It doesn't matter!
My memory is cloudy.
Too cloudy,
cause my memories aren't really memories,
they're just one possible eventuality now.
And they grow clearer...
or cloudier as they become
more or less likely.
But then they get to the present moment,
and they're instantly clear again.
I can remember what you
do after you do it.
And it hurts.
So even when we're apart,
you can remember what I do after doing it?
Yes. But this is a precise
description of a fuzzy mechanism.
It's... it's messy.
All I know,
I know two things.
I know what's happening in my head,
and I know that
you're still gonna meet her.
Who?
She's gonna save your life.
For a long time she thought
we were gonna...
we'd have a baby.
Would have been a great mother.
She wanted it so much.
Yeah, but she...
How?
You say she saves my life?
Yes.
Let's take a look at your life.
You're a killer, you're a junkie
with a fucking child mentality.
What's mine? My life, save your life?
You're asking me how?
The question is why? Why would
some sacrifice their life?
Why would someone waste themselves?
Cut your high and mighty bullshit.
I don't need my life...
Shut your fucking child mouth.
You're so self absorbed and stupid,
and she's gonna clean you up
and she's gonna take...
You are gonna take her love...
like a sponge.
And you think, maybe
I'm clear of the past,
maybe I'm safe.
Yesterday...
Yesterday what?
Thirty years from now is yesterday.
And I can remember it.
And I'm gonna tell you what happens
to this beautiful woman,
who saved your worthless fucking life.
Have you heard of the Rainmaker?
Yeah, Seth said... that night.
A new boss from the future,
he used the words 'holy terror'.
Yeah, the reign of terror.
Mass executions,
vagrant purges, everywhere at once.
Legend is that the Rainmaker
came out of nowhere.
In the span of six months, he took total
control of the five major syndicates.
That would take an army.
But he didn't have an army.
The story is that he did it alone.
Alone, alone.
- So how did he do it?
- That's the mystery.
There's no pictures of him,
either if it's a him.
It's insane.
There's stories he has a synthetic jaw,
saw his mom shot, shit like that.
But word spread about him
through the ex-Looper grapevine,
because the first thing he did
was start closing loops.
All of them.
You know what this is?
This number?
Here, wait, slow down.
It could lead us right
to the Rainmaker, Joe.
It was in the hospital records.
Write this down!
0, 7, 1, 5, 3, 9, 0, 2, 9, 3, 5!
This is a piece of identifying
information on the Rainmaker.
He's here. He lives here, now.
In this county.
And I'm gonna use it to find him
and I'm gonna kill him.
And I'm gonna stop him
from killing my wife.
Fuck you. And your wife.
None of this concerns me.
This is gonna happen to you, you stupid...
It happened to you,
it doesn't have to happen to me!
You got a picture right there in my watch?
Let me see it.
Show me the picture, and
as soon as I see her, I'll walk away.
I'll fucking marry someone else.
I promise.
So when I see that picture,
that fog inside your brain
should just swallow up
all the memories, right?
She'll be gone.
If you give her up, she'll be safe.
Giving her up?
Yeah, give her up!
You're the one that got her killed!
If she never meets, you she's safe!
You don't understand,
we don't have to give her up.
I'm not gonna give her up.
I'm gonna save her.
Get to the fields!
We can lose them in the fields!
Hop a train!
Stay out of town!
What the hell is everybody doing?!
You wait for my signal!
- Out back, he's running!
- He went off the back!
Shit!
No, alive!
Fuck! Shit mob! Come on!
Come on, you piece of shit! Come on!
Get the tracker! The tracker!
Come on! Come on!
Shit!
...
Come on baby, time to get up.
Listen up, fucker!
I have shot and buried
three vagrants in the past year!
So I don't know care
what a hobo sob story you got!
I get a dozen a week, pal,
it cuts no cash with me.
But if you show your face here again,
I will cut you the fuck in half!
Well... you found him.
Tracking Seth's bike, that was clever.
And you rustled up the posse
and went out to get him.
I could do it again.
You can fuck up again? Really?
I got too much riding, Kid.
I can't afford a fuck-up playing cowboy.
Put your Gat on the table.
I wanted you to say I did good.
It's all I wanted.
This is all I have.
Please just give me one more chance.
I'll bring him here alive,
and I'll hold him...
and you could put a bullet
in his brain yourself.
No, no!
Hey, who's there?
Stop right there, I will shoot you.
You stop! Stop right there!
I'm telling you to stop.
You stop!
...
Hey! Look up at the light.
Look up at me.
How long since you dropped?
- Dropped?
- Dropped.
- A day.
- A day...
I can't feel my legs.
That's because you're going through
withdrawal, you fucking junkie.
You gotta help me.
I'm gonna die.
I'm thirsty...
Water. Water!
Sid!
Come inside, baby.
- Who's that man?
- He's just a vagrant, baby.
- No, he's not.
- Yeah?
His shoes are too shiny.
Well, you're a smart monkey.
- Is he sick?
- Yep.
- Will he get better?
- Yeah.
Promise?
Just go to sleep, okay, baby boy?
- Good night, sweetie.
- Good night, Sara.
Hey!
The first time I saw her face,
the first time I saw her face...
Look at me.
No!
The first time I saw her face...
the first time I saw her face...
Morning, monkey. Want something to eat?
The man's up.
Is he staying here now?
No.
Toss it.
- I'm about to finish cleaning it.
- Put it down.
- How are you feeling?
- I'd say I'm a 30%.
You take it slow, by the end
of the week you'll be a 50.
I took you in so you wouldn't die.
Now you're not gonna die,
so just take the morning to rest,
then you need to get off my farm.
- I can't do that.
- I'm sorry?
I'm gonna stay here for a little while.
- I'm not cool with that.
- I'm sorry.
Well, I'm sorry too,
you just lost your
'take the morning to rest' privileges,
get off my farm.
- No.
- Get off my farm.
You couldn't scare a retarded
hobo with that thing, literally.
This is a Remington 8-70,
one blast cuts you the fuck in...
...Fuck in half, yeah. That's telling,
you're holding a gun,
I say I'm not afraid,
so you describe the gun to me.
It's not the gun I'm not afraid of.
What are you gonna do?
Shoot in the air?
Try to scare me? Go ahead.
You wouldn't let me die,
you're not gonna kill me.
So now I saved your life,
that makes me weak?
Look, I'm not a threat to you,
or your boy.
I need to be on your property.
Alright, there's no contact at all,
I'm gonna stay in the fields.
There's just one thing I need you to do,
and you'll never have
to deal with me again.
Just verify for me this is
your house on the map,
so I know I'm in the right place.
- What's this?
- It's a map.
Yeah, it's my house. Why is it marked?
Okay, it doesn't matter. Look,
I'm gonna be out of the barn in an hour.
If you can spare it,
I'm gonna take this canteen.
Is there somewhere
I can fill it up with water?
This number, how did you get this?
Does that mean something to you?
What?!
Hey... hey, hey!
Yeah, you're right, I'm not a killer.
But I'm fine with how a blast of rock salt
to your face won't kill you.
Now you gonna tell me who you are
and what the fuck you're doing on my farm.
Time travel hasn't been invented yet.
But in 30 years it will have been.
They've been used
by the big criminal syndicates.
You're a Looper?
I can't go back to the city
with Abe, my boss,
his men have been searching for me 24/7
so they find me,
or find him.
All I got is that map.
You have three houses marked on them.
Yours is one of them.
I know he's coming here.
So what do you know about Loopers?
You know what we do?
So he's coming here...
to murder my son,
cause he thinks he might be this...
Rainmaker?
And once he kills the Rainmaker,
what happens?
I think... he thinks that if
he'd killed the Rainmaker,
then he never would have been sent back,
so he'd just vanish.
He'd disappear just like he appeared.
He'd be back with his wife.
Who is he, this guy you let run?
Is it just some random
guy from the future?
He's... this is somebody.
You know what... the numbers mean?
This is Sid's birth day.
And this is the main code of
the hospital he was born in.
How many other kids were born in
that hospital in that day with your son?
- Like two?
- Sound right.
Three kids, three houses
marked on this map.
He knows one of them is the Rainmaker,
he doesn't know who he is.
What's he gonna do?
God...
Will he really do this?
Think about doing this would fix
what he thinks it will fix.
If he comes here, will you stop him?
I'm asking, can I trust you?
I don't care if you trust me.
I don't care about your son!
I've lost my life, if I kill
this man, I get it back.
He'll kill the other two kids,
and come here last.
Pull out facing me.
And those Goddamn cane, we're just blind!
He can get 50 yards from this place
without a hawk spotting him.
It would make sense if we burn
the fields. Level them.
How much gas you got in that barn?
No, you can't burn down the cane fields.
This stuff's half dead anyway.
Yeah, it's the seed for next year.
It's not gonna happen. Fucking not.
See, you use what you need,
and you set up anywhere,
but one thing: I don't want
you talking to Sid.
I watch my son, you watch
the cane, that's the deal.
Good by me.
Fine.
Alright, hold still.
It's easy for things to get
infected in a farm...
so I fill it off.
Pussy.
I'm gonna be out here and
you're in the house,
we need a way to communicate.
There's a diner bell in the barn.
Ring the bell if someone's coming on here.
Diner bell. We need... buzzers,
walkies or something.
I don't know what
we've got, but I'll look.
Sid.
How's the math coming?
I want to help the man.
Help him with what?
I could help with my toys.
No. Let me turn to you.
I need you to stay away
from that man. Ok?
You just let him do his thing,
but you stick with me. Ok?
Is he not good?
Well, we're gonna see what he is.
Alright? But I need you to stick with me.
Give me that pop-ups.
Tell me if you hear her coming.
- What you're doing here?
- Communication.
But I need to make it stronger.
- How do we do that?
- Bigger battery.
Smart.
Do you kill people?
- Let's say I kill people.
- With your gun?
- Why, you want a gun like mine?
- Yeah.
What you gonna do with it.
Pole vaulting?
It's bigger than you.
Stop bad things from happening.
So hum... how long you and your mum
been out here on the farm?
- She's not.
- She's not what?
Sara doesn't know...
but I remember my real mom.
When I was a baby, I couldn't stop it.
Couldn't stop what?
I couldn't stop her from getting killed.
I saw it, but I couldn't stop it.
I was not strong enough.
You should... you should talk
to your mum about this.
She's not my mum.
She's a liar.
Spotted in coming out of
a sewer tunnel in the West End.
He's on the run.
He is heading to the
western tower street,
possibly to whore selling.
We have a visual.
You can't take that thing out
with a plough or something?
Listen, I found a...
In the barn I found some parts,
and I made a... a thing.
Here.
So if you see something, just press that.
When?
Last night, he woke me up.
Don't tell him, I told him I wouldn't.
You said you were his mom.
Yeah.
He told me you're not.
He said that?
Yeah...
- If he's not your son, who is he?
- He's my son.
I had Sid when I was 22...
but I didn't want to give
up my life in the city.
So I dropped him here, on the farm,
and my sister, when she saw
how I was living,
so she took him.
And my sister, she raised him.
She loved him.
He called her Mom.
- How did she get killed?
- Jesus Christ.
He remembers it.
You gonna have to talk to him about it.
I told you one thing,
I told you to stay away from my son.
- He asked about my gun.
- Stay out of it!
Stay the fuck away from my son!
Where does 56 go?
Good, you're smart.
21?
How long you cannot sleep?
I don't know... a little while.
It's a good question.
Where's the token going?
Good! 32.
We should help Joe watch.
Joe?
Cause he can't stay awake all the time.
- Ain't our business. Ok?
- He's keeping us safe.
Let's do this now. Okay?
You have 32 there,
I know you know this one.
No. Eight times three is what?
32.
- Eight times three is what?
- 32.
I want you to count three eights.
8, 16...
32.
Are you telling me you want a long time?
No.
Then why don't you put that were it lies?
A long time.
He's protecting us, cause you can't do it.
Ok, I told you to stay away from him.
I never did anything.
- Do you think I'm stupid?
- So.
- I told you...
- So!
You do what I tell you, Sid!
You can't tell me what to do,
cos you're not my mom.
You're not my mum, you're a liar.
You're going to get killed,
cos you won't stop lying.
- Sid, calm down...
- Liar, you're lying to me,
I hate you, you're a liar!
Come on, kill me, I hate you, liar!
I hate you, liar, you're lying to me...
- Calm down. Calm down!
- ... I hate you!
Liar!
You're not my mum, you're a liar!
Liar, liar!
I'm sorry.
It's OK, sweetie.
Holy shit.
How are you ma'am.
Hey, man.
What can I do for you?
Would you start by
accepting my apologies
this late visit, I hope I
not interrupt your dinner.
No, that's fine.
I've been walking into all the empty
farms around there in the hot sun,
I just...
take this one off the list,
- or I'd have to come back tomorrow
- What this is about?
You're alone here, madame?
My husband should be back
from the city anytime now.
Happy to hear it.
Can I trouble you for some water?
I'll get you some,
and you take the glass with you.
I'm sorry ma'am. My business today, is...
ticking off the list business,
it's gonna require me coming here.
If that's all right.
Will you tell me what this is about?
I will, yeah.
Can I come in?
Madame?
I am a sworn police officer,
and I'm looking for fugitives.
Have you seen anybody those past two days?
Vagrants?
Vagrants are always wandering around.
- That man?
- He is young? No.
We're looking for his father too,
similar look and build,
end fifties.
You may meet each of them together.
You recognize them?
- No.
- Keep it.
Your kids are with your husband?
- Yeah, just one.
- How old?
Ten.
I show you the barn, and then the house,
and then you can be on your way.
I took the liberty with your barn.
Apologies.
So... The house.
- 10, you said, your boy?
- Yeah.
And your husband?
I just got to check in, the Home Office.
You said the boy is the city
with his father. When is he getting back?
Can't tell you.
This Goddamn thing.
You never get the signal this far out.
Piece of shit.
Ok, here we go.
Is this man dangerous?
He shoots men down for a living.
He is a cold-blooded killer.
My boss says half of the city
is looking for him.
Half of the city then me, so...
And if you find him,
there's a hell of a prize.
A chunk of money like that.
You think of it.
- I will.
- Alright.
You show me upstairs?
There's drafts in the house.
My grand dad dug this tunnel when
the vagrants rixe got bad.
Nanna said cuz he was nuts.
Thank you Grand dad.
That wasn't the man?
No. It's funny, I know though,
his name's Jessie.
I like him, he's good.
He's gonna go away
once he didn't find me.
He won't harm your mum...
Sara.
Where is your mum?
Where's my mum?
she... she gave me up.
I was younger than you.
They were vagrants, and she was alone.
For a long time, I thought
she was stupid for getting
on that junction,
resigning, but now I see, she was...
so alone.
That's what she had.
And she sold me to a begging little gang,
I got away and I ran,
I went on this train,
I remember seeing there an empty car.
I saw myself over and over again,
killing those men who bought me.
and who got my mom on what she was on.
Finding them and tearing them apart. Saving my mom.
What did you do then?
A man in the city found me,
put a gun in my hand,
and gave me some things that was mine
It's just that men try to figure out
what they would do
to keep what's theirs.
Their take out.
This is the only kind of man there is.
I'm not going to let Sara get killed.
I think we're clear.
...
All working girls, yeah?
This whole block,
back-up all blocks over.
Hello Joe...
You wanna check those too, I can arrange.
I'm an arranger, stranger.
But if you don't see
what you want to see, no refunds.
What?
What happened?
That's pretty good.
In the city, young guys
would head on me by...
flying fucking quarters.
I wouldn't tell that I was TK, but...
I would keep their quarters down.
This one guy...
busted a vein, I saw, in his eye,
trying to get it high.
He's you.
Your loop.
You lied to me.
But I know you're not lying when you
said you're gonna kill this guy...
your own self.
You protected Sid from that Gat man.
- Come on...
- Yeah.
- Yeah...
- He saved your ass, didn't he?
He saved my ass, yeah.
He's a...
He's a good kid.
Yeah, he is.
You know when I came back,
after my sister died,
I remember seeing him,
for the first time in two years
just sitting on the porch,
I drove up, crying,
I had been in this...
party all night in the city,
when I called...
and so I was wearing this
ridiculous party dress,
my, ridiculous shit.
And I don't know if he...
if he even remembered me, but...
but he looked at me.
I abandoned him.
I abandoned my baby.
And I've seen so many men in the city,
This empty look in their
eyes, and just lost...
So whether he loves me back, or not,
as long as I'm there to raise him..
he's gonna be taken care of.
He's gonna be safe.
He's never gonna get lost.
- Hello Joe.
- Jessie.
Put this down, let her go.
Sarah, Jessie here is the best
shoot with the Gat that I know.
So when he lets you go, just sit down
on the couch, don't do anything stupid.
He's coming here, Jessie,
my loop is coming here.
I've got to take you in there.
I've got 948 bars of pure silver.
I close my loop, I get back with Abe,
whatever he gives me back,
I'll split with you.
Was that your plan?
Okay, take all of it.
Are you delusional?
You didn't ride with anyone.
As long as Abe has got one Gat man's down,
he gonna be hunting you
'till his dying day.
We're gonna go now.
I'm gonna get my truck,
and we're just gone...
I'm sorry.
The Rainmaker...
My God...
Sid. Sid!
Sid!
It's him!
What is he, some TK freak?
You knew.
- What are you doing with those guns?
- How did your sister die?
- What are you doing with those guns!
- How did your sister die!
How did she die,
is that what happened to her?
- No. No, no.
- Did he kill her like that?
No, listen, he was climbing
a bookshelf, okay,
and it... it fell back on him, and...
- he can get scared and explode...
- Jesus, fuck!
.. but one day he'll learn to control it.
Yeah, I know he will,
and imagine what he's gonna do!
But if he did good with it, though,
if he grew up, wouldn't it raise him?
If he grew up good?
He doesn't.
You stay away from him, Joe!
Sid! Sid, stay away from Joe, baby.
Won't you, baby?
Come here, it's okay.
It's okay, baby.
Now right now two things have happened.
My loop knows Sid
is the kid he's looking for,
and my gang knows I'm here.
That means that in 15 minutes
one or both of them
is coming down the highway.
Back-up the Gat man's truck,
take everything that fits and go,
driving North, away from the city.
Thank you.
I've got everyone here, all our men.
Arm them up, let's go.
I got him Abe. I got him!
Well, cheers...
Right, motherfuckers!
I got him!
He had a sweet on
this one particular whore, so
I checked her building...
They found Joe too,
they're on a farm on the east side.
That's why all the Gats came here,
the whole crew is armed
up to make up a sweep.
Joe.
Fuck Joe!
Save your bullets, I've got the loop!
Not such a fucker mellow,
I'll bring him up to see Abe.
Gats, shoot!
Shoot!
Holy shit.
Joe!
I used to put a gun in that kid's hand,
I guess it comes back around.
Like your Goddamn ties...
Take this truck, you take
your gold and go live your life.
Nobody's coming after you.
I've fixed it.
Are you gonna kill the boy,
is that how you fix it?
You're Goddamn right
I'm gonna kill that boy.
You've just got your life back.
My life!?
Your life!
Becoming you.
Goddammit! You've lost your fucking mind,
You let the boy live,
he will take everything you've got!
And everything I've got!
You've seen what he becomes.
I haven't seen that yet.
Okay baby, we're gone.
Put your seatbelt on.
- Stop.
- Tap down, baby, it's okay.
- Stop, please, he's gonna shoot us.
- Tap down, baby!
Stop. He's gonna
shoot us! Stop!
- Please, get...
- Stop! Stop, stop!
- Sid...
- I'm sorry.
It' okay. It's okay,
I'm gonna get you down.
Ok, we'll go and hide in the cane.
Go. Go!
Go.
No!
No, Sid, no...
Noooooon...
It's okay, baby...
It's okay...
I love you, calm down.
Good boy...
Mummy loves you.
I's okay...
Mom.
You did good, you did so good,
Good boy.
Okay, listen to me.
I need you to run into the fields.
No mom, no, I don't wanna leave you.
- It's okay.
- I don't want to leave you, Mom. No!
It's okay, baby. Go, Go!
Move! Move, Goddammit!
Move.
Then I saw it.
I saw a mum who would die for her son.
A man who would kill for his wife.
A boy angry and alone.
Lay down and frightened.
The bad path, I saw it.
and the path was a circle.
Round and round.
So I changed it.
Sid!
Where is Joe?
He had to go away, baby.
subtitle by
jcdr
resync by
A M I R
DVDRIP
...
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player