Previously on Mad Men...
Roger Sterling is a child.
Still I expect pragmatism from you...
We share that...
I just keep thinking about
what's going on here and I miss it.
I say we put it to a vote.
I say we step outside.
Allison and Faye Miller and
who knows how many more...
I'm going to be with
you until I die.
How's not your wife
dropping you off?
There was a time when she
wouldn't leave the house in a robe.
There's a point when you go from
going home on the 5:25 to the 7:05.
( theme music playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
( Tires screech )
( Crashes )
( Dramatic music plays )
( Chuckles )
( Phone ringing )
Man on film:
State highway patrol.
There has been an accident at
Tremble Road and the expressway.
( Water dripping )
Does it go like that all day?
I suppose, but I don't hear it.
( Sighs )
( Wrench grinding )
You're not ready at all?
We have time.
The first half of a football
match is just flirting.
Well, I'd like to get there,
grab a nice seat,
enjoy the chitchat.
If it's a matter of you
and I having a nice lunch,
perhaps a ride in the boats
in the park, hmm?
You don't even know
what's good for you.
Spending an afternoon in
the pub with our friends.
One: They're your friends,
and recent ones at that.
Two: I have no fond memories
of hours spent in pubs
watching football.
Three--
- You love football.
- No, that's my father.
And I hate this business
of bringing england
over in pieces.
It's strictly for the homesick.
But it's filled with
immigrants like us.
( Sighs )
How lovely your face becomes when
you tell me you need something.
I'd be happy if you'd just
pretend to have a good time.
Then pretend I shall.
( Cheering )
♪ God save our gracious queen ♪
♪ long live our noble queen ♪
♪ God save our queen... ♪
Now, I want both of you
to make a pledge
that this is the end
of football for some time.
We beat the bloody Jerries
for the world cup, darling.
That is the end of football.
I'll believe that
when I see it.
Is Lane this way about that?
Perhaps at one time.
But right now
he's been in the midst
of a messy divorce
with Great Britain.
I dare to say
my blood's running now.
Good day to be an Englishman.
I don't know if I caught it.
Are you an account man at the firm?
No, financial chief.
You should have one
give me a call.
Well, my name's on the door.
I don't find britain any more
moral than here nowadays.
The boys look like girls
and the girls,
they don't seem to be concerned
with manners, do they?
I find New York
better than London
because 50 miles away, things
are infinitely more wholesome.
You'll have your farmland.
Give it some time.
She wants to raise hogs.
( Laughs )
Just take the last booth.
Kenny?
Oh, hi.
What are you doing here?
Trying to get
ptomaine poisoning.
( Chuckles )
- I'll see you at the office.
- Unless you have plans.
Oh, no.
It's Cynthia's uncle.
He's trying to break into radio.
I'm gonna try and talk him out of it.
I'd love to meet him.
He's painfully shy.
I get it.
You want to be alone.
Do you mind?
Joan: Okay, now on
to new business.
- Roger?
- Nope.
- Pete?
- No.
- Mr. Cooper?
- No, dear.
- Don?
- Nope.
Very well, then.
If there are any addendums
for the minutes,
please give them
to me by 4:00.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
If I may.
I have a bit of new business.
- Taking leave again?
- Not at all.
I don't know if you're aware,
but England won the World Cup.
Cup of what?
Anyway, I've begun a bit of a
friendship with Edwin Baker,
senior vice president
of public relations
for Jaguar cars incorporated.
Completely unprovoked,
he made it clear
that since their impending
merger with BMC,
they're looking
for a new agency
to break them
into the American market.
Dinner is set.
- Yowza!
- Spectacular.
- Roger: I want one.
- So, Mr. Pryce,
- that's Jaguar, like the cat?
- Indeed.
Why are you smiling?
Jaguar, well, we'd probably
have to hire 10 people
who will be on
the payroll for months.
Are you sure we can afford it?
My lordy.
New business.
Not here, sir.
I suppose if you brought in
an account of this stature,
I might said
something different.
It's $3 million, tops.
It's a car and you know it.
You know, I'd be happy
to ride shotgun.
If nothing else, I could pick up the
check and make you look important.
I think that would make
you look important.
But, honestly, Lane,
if you want any of us along,
Cooper speaks British.
I believe Edwin and I
relate to one another
on matters both business
and personal.
Englishman to Englishman.
I love that car.
Should someone give
him a few pointers?
- That's a good idea.
- I'm terribly busy.
- Roger.
- I'd be glad to.
Oh, Don.
Just a minute.
Trudy dictated directions
to Clara for Saturday night.
I promise, no charades,
no bridge,
just good home cooking
and drinks.
This Saturday
I think we're going away.
I doubt that.
Trudy will only act
on a certainty.
Okay.
Thank you.
- ( Sighs ) Dawn, can you get Mrs. Draper?
- She's inside.
I'm almost done.
So, I want you to call your new
best friend Trudy Campbell
and tell her that we're
unavailable this weekend.
You already said
we were coming.
To who?
I don't know.
Trudy said you did.
Well, she got this far
by subterfuge.
She won't feel bad when
you pull the plug on it.
I like her.
I like her, too.
But Saturday night in the suburbs?
That's when you really want
to blow your brains out.
If you want to tell her,
you call her.
Hey, where's Stan and Ginsberg?
Why? Do you have something
you want to tell them?
No.
Listen,
about this morning--
- I thought we had a pact.
- It's not about the pact.
It has nothing to do with the pact.
The pact still stands.
Then why didn't you
introduce me?
I'm a copywriter.
I'm not gonna take your job.
I'd love a shred of privacy.
Just a shred.
You know?
Is that too much to ask?
( Sighs )
Okay, listen.
You know I write stories.
You're still doing that?
Well, I decided
to fly under the radar.
I have a nom de plume and, well,
I've had quite a bit of success
in a particular genre
and he's from Farrar Straus.
Wow, that's exciting.
I guess.
Cynthia's trying to talk
them into taking the best 20
and turning them
into a collection.
20?
When do you do this?
I started turning most
of my dinners into drinks.
And if I have only one, I'm in
pretty good shape when I get home.
So, what is it?
It's between fantasy
and science fiction.
Robots and planets and things.
There's whole magazines.
No, I mean what's
your pen name?
Fine.
It's Ben Hargrove.
Anyway, I could have
introduced you,
and that was wrong,
but I just...
I don't know.
Well, I wish
I felt more relieved.
It's probably not gonna happen.
And listen,
the pact still stands.
If I go anywhere,
you go with me.
Okay.
So that's some big news.
Are you here to put in
a good word for yourself?
No.
A little bird told med
you got an RFP from Jaguar.
And that is a very good sign.
Yes, I was just going over it.
Request for proposal.
Jaguar. Blah, blah.
"One, have you ever
been fired off an account?"
There are worse ones than that.
Would you take a little bit
of unsolicited advice?
It's not pride that's
keeping me from asking.
I certainly am aware that
you're skilled in this arena.
I was.
Now I guess I'm professor
emeritus of accounts.
Look, most people will tell you
it's hard to make a mistake.
I mean, you just lie.
But that won't
get you anywhere.
The beauty of this dinner
is that if you do it right,
you can actually have him
tell you all the answers.
In fact, I once got a guy from Dr.
Scholl's to fill it out for me.
( Chuckles ) There'll
be plenty of drinks.
Not for you.
You order a scotch, rocks and water.
You drink half of it
till it turns see-through.
- You get another.
- Very good.
And then, well, then it's
kind of like being on a date.
Flattery, I suppose.
Within reason.
But I find it's best
to smile and sit there
like you've got no place
to go and just let them talk.
Somewhere in the middle of the entree,
they'll throw out something revealing.
And you want to wait till
dessert to pounce on it.
You know, let them
know you've got
the same problem he has,
whatever it is.
And then you're in
a conspiracy.
The basis of
a "friendship."
Then you whip out the form.
What if I don't have
the same problem?
It'll probably
just be something like
he drinks too much, he gambles.
I once went on
a five-minute tear
about how my mother loved
my father more than me.
And I can assure you
that is impossible.
Very good, then.
And if, for some reason,
he's more reserved?
Just reverse it.
Feed him your own
personal morsel.
Oh, I see.
That's it.
Get your answers,
be nice to the waiter,
and don't let him
near the check.
Thank you very much.
Oh, and find out everything you can
about him before you get there.
- That I've done.
- And you still like him?
- I do.
- Let it show.
- ( Intercom buzzes )
- I finally got Mrs. Campbell on the line.
Trudy, I'm glad I got
a hold of you.
- I have some bad news.
- No, you don't.
We're building the whole
party around you.
You see, I'm afraid
we're not free.
Don, do you want to go down
your list of excuses
and I'll combat each one
individually?
Or should we just skip
to the end?
If you can't make it Saturday,
I will reschedule.
It's going to happen.
And I promise you'll have
a good time.
It's too bad your husband
can't close a deal like this.
We both know he's doing
just fine.
7:30.
( Gasps ) Who's hungry?
Are you okay?
I saw you getting
a little green in there.
Those movies are gruesome.
I think we should go
back to riding horses.
( Chuckles ) That must
have been something.
Why don't you
have a license yet?
I grew up in Manhattan.
Just wasn't necessary.
I like going down to the city.
There's so much to do.
Well, maybe you'll move
there when you get older.
Then you'll get married
and you'll move back here.
I'm not getting married
until after college...
If my parents still let me go.
What?
Didn't you hear
about the sniper
at the University
of Texas today?
Aren't you going to Ohio State?
It doesn't matter.
Just two weeks after
those nurses in Chicago--
They don't want me
out there by myself.
Don't let them scare you.
I don't know.
Things seem so random
all of a sudden.
And time feels like
it's speeding up.
It does,
doesn't it?
I remember when the summer seemed
as long as the school year.
I used to go every spring
to the botanical gardens.
And this year, look,
it's already August.
In the Bronx?
My family donated some of that.
- Really?
- Well, generations ago.
We should go some Sunday soon.
We'd be VIPs
Who's going to drive?
We'll take turns.
Give each other lessons.
- ( Door opens )
- Man: Okay, that's 15 minutes, everybody.
Back to the salt mines.
We should go back in.
Don't want to miss the mayhem.
What's Ken's wife's name?
I can't remember.
She sent me the nicest
thank-you card for the party.
Why don't you wear
the sport coat I got you?
It's the country.
You should slow down.
I'm timing this
for when we arrive.
I want to hit the doorbell
with my chin.
You know, this could be fun.
How's that work?
You don't think there's
any chance you could
have a conversation with
another couple as friends?
What about your actor friends?
I don't think
there was any business
or financial realities
discussed the whole time.
Don, I had to invite your
accountant to your birthday party.
Frank's been very
important to me, okay?
You're driving.
Now go change.
( Classical music playing )
Incredible, right?
We keep expecting to open the doors
and see a tiny orchestra in there.
- That would be amazing.
- ( Chuckles )
And it's a beautiful
piece of furniture.
It's seven feet long.
Wilt Chamberlain could
lie down in there.
Why would he want to do that?
The hostess would like you
to turn down the stereo
for fear of waking
a nonessential guest.
( Lowers volume )
I told her she's not allowed to
talk about the baby tonight.
( Knocking )
Terrific.
That's him.
- Welcome.
- I'm sorry we're late.
You know I can't
blame the directions.
- You have a lovely home.
- You haven't seen it.
But it is certainly graced by
the addition of the Cosgroves.
It's nice to see you, Don.
Well, hello, you.
I see a familiar red tin.
Brownies from
William Greenberg.
Well, hello and welcome.
You look lovely, Trudy.
We did it, didn't we?
We got them together.
Tweety, look what they brought.
Doesn't it make you homesick?
I'm sorry there are no bakeries
or Greenbergs in Cos Cob.
Can we put them in the icebox?
Could everyone try it my way?
I'm going to devil some eggs
if the girls want to help.
Megan, you want to take
Don's drink order?
Big and brown.
Trudy, I love your touch.
It's almost rustic.
Am I wrong?
That may take longer
than you like.
Ken just handed it to me.
Do you like the music?
I do.
You know, I've never lived
on the ground floor before.
And we don't share any walls,
so I can make it
as loud as I want.
But we're not gonna.
Trudy has ground rules.
No work talk, no baby talk.
And you get the big steak.
Excuse me?
Look,
I'm not gonna pretend it's not a
big deal to us that you came out.
Oh, come on.
We're long overdue.
I remember asking you
over to dinner
when we first got married.
That was another lifetime.
- Well, at least for me.
- ( Laughs )
Mmm, beef's brilliant,
but it would be difficult to
do those tomatoes one better.
Ever done any gardening?
- No.
- Well, I'm quite keen on it now.
Three years in north Africa,
scarcely a blade of grass,
living like a dog.
Yes.
I've heard men talk with dark
permanence about those years.
Not me.
Best days of my life.
Oh, well,
then I suppose
you must miss it.
You must have some melancholy.
No, it's just how
I associate with my youth.
What about your war?
I volunteered for combat
on numerous occasions,
but spent most of the war as a
supply assistant in Rosyth.
Well, everyone
played their part.
That was britain at its best.
Yes.
So I'm glad to hear that
America has been good for you.
And your wife
is pleased, I assume?
I'll be honest with you, Lane.
I haven't a complaint
in the world.
Well, that's too bad, isn't it?
( Laughs )
So the Coe family claims it was them.
Coes' Cob.
Which became through
yankee arrogance Cos Cob.
Of course, it also sounds a lot like
the Algonquin word for briefcase.
( Laughs )
Ken, where have you and--
Where have you two
made your home?
We're in Jackson
Heights, Queens.
It's very down to earth.
A lot of workers.
I keep telling them
to move out to the country.
Well, we both work in the city
and my parents
aren't like Trudy's.
Help from them comes with a
lot of strings attached.
It is beautiful out here.
The air is so fresh and all
the trees and the grass.
I grew up in rural Vermont.
Kids throwing their bikes on the
front lawn is not the country to me.
You miss the horse shit, huh?
( All laugh )
Don!
I grew up in the country,
too, and I don't miss walking
to an outhouse in
the middle of winter.
Well, it's more
civilized than that.
But there are a lot
of varmints.
You should bring
that rifle home.
You still have that?
There will be no gun in this house.
I never liked them.
And now with that Charles Whitmore.
Whitman.
They say he had a brain tumor.
He kept warning everyone.
Without a gun would he
be able to kill his wife
and mom and 20 other people?
I'm sorry.
It's the hostess' prerogative
to change the subject.
Trudy, it bears discussion.
One rifle for shooting
gophers is not the same
as a frustrated ex-marine
shooting at pregnant ladies.
You know, Kenny predicted it.
He wrote a story that
was exactly like that.
- Don't, Cynthia.
- Cynthia!
What?
Nothing, I just...
- Honey, they don't want to talk about that.
- Why not?
You know, if he wasn't a writer,
we never would have met.
- I didn't know that.
- I work in publishing.
My boss was rejecting him and I
thought it was all he could handle.
( Laughing )
What was the story?
- Forget it.
- No, we want to know.
It's called
"The Punishment Of X4."
There's this bridge
between these two planets
and thousands of humans
travel on it every day.
And so there's this robot;
he does maintenance on the bridge.
And one day, he removes a bolt
and the bridge collapses
and everyone dies.
There's more to it
than that, you know.
But it's just a story.
Why does he do it?
Because he's a robot.
Those people
tell him what to do
and he doesn't have the
power to make any decisions
except he can decide whether
that bolt's on or off.
Or he just hates commuters.
( All laugh )
How long have you been writing?
I started screwing around
in high school.
And by the time I got a job,
I thought it would go away.
And it mostly has.
No one grows awaiting
to be an advertising.
Oh, that's not true.
It's such an interesting profession to me..
What are you to it, Megan?
Megan came to
New York as an actress.
If trying to be an actress
is being an actress.
That's fascinating.
I could see it.
But I had been in a few
agencies on auditions
and it looked like a fun
place to get the bills paid.
And I saw what Don
and Peggy did
and I saw a future
for myself in it.
That's the truth.
Can I interest anyone
in dessert and coffee?
- Hot or iced?
- Yes to dessert.
Still having too much
fun for coffee.
People talk about how there's
so much crime in the city.
I was ripped off by the kid
who mows my lawn.
Yes, they used to take my beer
out of the fridge in the garage.
A fridge in the garage?
That's a good idea.
( Men shriek, laugh )
Damn it.
I'll get the toolbox.
I turned it on and it
just blew in my face.
Hold this.
Don, what are you doing?
Look, it's Superman.
- ( Baby crying )
- Oh, good lord.
( Applause )
What was wrong?
The supply was turned all the way up.
It forces the valve.
- But it stopped the leak.
- That was a coincidence.
Grab Don's shirt.
I'll throw it in the dryer.
Aren't we supposed to say
something about that baby?
- Look at her.
- What an angel.
I take no credit
for her at all.
- ( Baby cries )
- Cynthia: Aw!
I'm gonna close my eyes.
And when I open them
I want to see skyscrapers.
Admit it, you had a great time.
I'm too drunk for you to drive.
We should pull over
and both sober up.
( Unzips )
Let's make a baby.
No, that's impossible.
What, isn't that
how this works?
A baby gets you going?
Just pull over.
This brassiere is like Fort Knox.
The only reason
you're getting anywhere
is because Pete scared
the shit out of me
with his car
accident statistics
and because I can't believe
how much I loved watching
you fix that sink.
Pete: Because there
was a plane crash.
And it doesn't matter that
it's not one of Mohawk's.
We should stop
running ads for a week
and then just hope
that no one notices
that Mohawk has 10 planes
that are the same model.
Why? There's a plane crash
every day in Vietnam.
There were seven yesterday.
It's Braniff, for Christ's sake.
Let them eat their
award-winning work.
- ( Knocks )
- Ask Lane.
- Yes?
- Do what you want. It's your account.
Hey, Heathcliff.
How was your date?
Lane here got Lord Jaguar
to unravel the mysteries of the RFP.
Yes, about that...
Unfortunately, I was forced
to do the plan in reverse,
as you suggested.
I even offered that Rebecca
was unbalanced
in an effort to attempt
to lull him into confession,
but to no avail.
- Oh.
- What plan?
Anyway, I've primed him
for another dinner
when all should be revealed
and it's on the books.
That's not what
I told you to do.
Lane, I think Roger and I,
and probably Don,
should take your friend out to a
dinner which is strictly business.
Ask all the rough questions,
brag about you,
then allow you to swoop in,
his new best friend,
and shine the chrome.
I don't know if
that's necessary.
Roger, tell him that's
the way the plan always works.
Sure.
You wouldn't want to hit
a golf ball off the tee
when you could hit
it from the green.
We need you to stay a pure friend.
Practice your putting.
Very well, then.
That was generous.
Come on, Lane couldn't
close a car door.
- I mean inviting me along.
- I'm inviting you to dinner,
not the wedding night.
How are you?
I think I'm hungover.
What? Really?
Belinda and I were left
alone in the drugstore
and she opened up a bottle
of vanilla extract.
It did make the afternoon
go faster,
but now I have a headache.
Sounds like my office.
( Chuckles )
Well, now that you're sober,
I will remind you
that you promised
to find a Sunday
for the gardens.
What about church?
God's all over the gardens.
- Hi.
- Hey.
I missed a couple classes,
but I'm here from now on.
No, he's not the instructor.
He's Peter.
- Who are you?
- I'm Jenny Gunther.
- Chemistry.
- Right.
You're handsome, aren't you?
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
Your name is handsome?
No, my name is hanson,
but everybody calls me that.
( Clears throat )
So I got to be some kind of
weirdo that I don't remember you.
It was a big class.
There were a lot of girls.
- So what are you doing next year?
- Ohio State.
Billy Josephs and I were supposed
to join up, but my dad went ape.
He wouldn't let me
drive, either.
So I'm gonna follow through on that
track scholarship to Holy Cross.
I think a man getting out of a
Jaguar needs a cold shower.
That's it--
A singular message
repeated over and over again.
The Jaguar XKE is pornographic.
Is that enough of a flavor?
Gentlemen,
not that I don't appreciate
the all-hands-on-deck,
but I think the cause
of our friendship
would be best served
by us having a little fun.
Oh, fun.
Well, you know that I have every
intention of giving you this business.
I just wanted to make sure that
I enjoy the people I work with.
We'd love to show you
a good time.
I'm surprised Lane
didn't offer.
I don't think Mr. Pryce and I
have the same taste in this area.
We should go grab
a drink at the Carlyle.
It's a good place
to get into trouble.
You understand
I'm not visiting.
I reside here in New York.
Roger, I believe this is
your opportunity to shine.
You know what?
I have a friend
who's having a party
right around the corner.
Oh.
I like parties.
- ( Music playing )
- ( Laughing )
I said we're from out of town.
Now give me one attraction that isn't
in this room right in front of me.
What happened to your friend?
Because the last word I want to hear
out of his date's mouth is next.
Anastasia, he likes you.
Listen, honey.
I'm not gonna bore you
with compliments.
What about your friend?
Jesus, Don, even in this place
you're doing better than us.
Well, someone got lucky.
I think one of your sorority
sisters isn't very picky.
Come on, Don.
Work, work, work.
Do you think you could lift me?
That's what I thought.
You're one of those guys
who's stronger than he looks.
I want some rum, but I
think it's in my room.
( Laughs )
Easy, tiger.
I don't do this by the minute.
( Chuckles )
You think this
is gonna be easy?
I do.
I really do.
You any good at this or not?
Oh, honey.
You've had such a hard day.
Nope.
Um...
This is my first time.
I'm kind of nervous.
Nope.
You're my king.
Okay.
I suppose you know that officer
Logan says to say hello.
I'm not a cop.
Are you interested in
someone who's already busy?
Just waiting for my friends.
Well, if there's something
you can't find here,
a friend of mine
has an apartment.
Maybe more what
you're looking for
and he's walking distance.
That's the best
I've ever seen that done.
Does that happen to you a lot?
No. I grew up
in a place like this.
There's no other
place like this.
You're right.
It wasn't as nice.
We called it a whorehouse.
Oh, I see.
So, expert,
what do you think?
Should I get a TV in here?
No.
Jessica, I've got his drinks.
Well, gentlemen, I asked
for fun and I got it.
Unless you're going to give me
a pen that says Jaguar on it,
you should be reaching
for your house keys.
Good night.
Two more stops.
First one is the near corner of 72nd.
That went very well.
He seemed happy.
I'm sorry you
weren't feeling well.
I'm feeling fine.
So why do I feel like
I'm riding with a nun?
I didn't say anything.
I mean, you of all people.
You're right.
- Well, have a good night.
- I already did.
Good.
Boy, this is rich.
I can't believe I have to
explain I was doing my job
to a man who just pulled
his pants up on the world.
Pete, just go home,
take a shower, and forget this.
I suppose there are
no stern looks for Roger.
Roger is miserable.
I didn't think you were.
Have it all.
Wait till your honeymoon
is over.
Look, I'm just trying to tell
you because I am who I am
and I've been where I've been that you
don't get another chance at what you have.
Brave words for a man
on his second time 'round.
Yeah, and if I had
met her first,
I would have known
not to throw it away.
Now I need you
to take me to Cos Cob.
Driver: You got to pay
both ways, you know.
I'm aware of that.
( Shower running )
( Door opens )
You wanted to see me?
Yes, come in.
So, a little birdy told me
you've been hard at work
- writing stories.
- Oh?
Who'd have thunk
you were you by day
and Edgar Allan Poe by night?
It's nothing.
I only do it because my wife likes it.
Well, my wife likes fur, but you
don't see me growing a tail.
- ( Intercom buzzes )
- Time for the partners' meeting.
Coming!
You know, as an account man,
you already have a day job.
- And a night job.
- And I love it.
You knew to keep it a secret because
your attentions are divided.
I like to think we offer you
more than security here.
I understand.
Good.
And as a fellow unappreciated
author and a friend,
let me tell you,
when this job is good,
it satisfies every need.
Believe me, I remember.
- ( Intercom buzzes )
- Mrs. Pryce is on the phone.
I'm late for
the partners' meeting.
What?
Calm yourself.
Believe me, Nixon's
lying in wait.
So, I see everyone's here.
Johnson will stop the war
before the election.
You don't stop a war
before an election.
Mrs. Harris,
please excuse us.
Immediately!
Your activities last night
- have cost us this account.
- What?
Go ahead, tell him how you corrupted
my account and my friend.
Hold on.
What happened?
Edwin's wife,
her life destroyed,
called my wife
with gory details.
Why would he say anything?
Because he was caught with
chewing gum on his pubis.
( All laughing )
How dare you laugh at this?
What, did she just put it
there and forget about it?
- It was Edwin's idea.
- Impossible. He would never.
He didn't ask you because
he thinks you're a homo.
I can't believe
the hours I've put into
helping you become
the monster you've become.
I was doing my job.
It was my account!
Your account?
You have no idea
what you're doing.
In fact, as far as I can tell,
our need for you disappeared
the day after you fired us.
Mr. Campbell.
That'll be enough of that.
Mr. Campbell,
you and I are going
to address that insult.
- Are you kidding me?
- No.
You're a grimy little pimp.
As soon as I raise my hands,
I warn you, it shall
be too late to run.
( Chuckles nervously )
Fine.
You want to take
your teeth out?
Or do you want me
to knock them out?
I know cooler heads
should prevail,
but am I the only one
who wants to see this?
Come on.
Let's go.
( Grunts )
This is medieval.
- Hi, I'm sorry--
- Shh!
( Men grunting over intercom )
- Lane: You little devil.
- Lane and Pete are fighting.
( Crashes )
Pete: You want some more,
Mr. Toad?
( Panting )
- You all right?
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
Consider that
my last piece of advice.
( Panting )
You'll be fine.
I don't know about you
two, but I had Lane.
Reschedule the meeting.
- ( Knocking )
- I'm busy.
It's Joan.
What happened?
( Ice rattling )
What do I do here?
I mean, truly?
Something essential.
You could do it.
If they've tried
to make you feel
you're different
than them, you are.
That's a good way to be.
( Door opens )
I just seem to find no end
to my humiliation today.
- I'm sorry.
- About what?
Everyone in this office has wanted
to do that to Pete Campbell.
Did you hear?
Lane kicked the crap out of Pete.
- I can't believe he beat me to it.
- What did Pete do?
I don't know, but I know he
told Roger about my writing.
Why did you tell him?
Cynthia let it slip.
Hell, she bragged about it.
Well, you can't blame her.
I read the one in "Galaxy"
about the girl who lays eggs.
- Wow.
- Well, thanks.
But Ben Hargrove is dead.
I'm through with all
that fantasy stuff
oh. I'm sorry.
I'm gonna leave the
writing to the writers.
Come on.
- Where are you headed?
- I'm meeting Megan for lunch.
I'm not as virtuous as you,
so you just cut me loose?
What was I supposed to do?
Step in? Punch Lane?
Why were we even
having a fight at work?
This is an office.
We're supposed to be friends.
I have nothing, Don.
Kenny's voice: "The man with
the miniature orchestra,"
by Dave Algonquin.
"There were phrases of
Beethoven's 9th Symphony
that still made coe cry.
He always thought it had to do
with the circumstances
of the composition itself.
He imagined Beethoven
deaf and soul-sick,
his heart broken,
scribbling furiously
while death stood in the
doorway clipping his nails."
( Projector whirring )
Kenny's voice:
"Still, Coe thought,
it might have been living in the
country that was making him cry.
It was killing him
with its silence
and loneliness...
Making everything ordinary
too beautiful to bear."
( Water dripping )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
( Classical music playing )