Previously on Mad Men...
He is not your friend,
he is the enemy.
You let Don talk,
you should know better.
The guy's not a salesman.
- Why do we care what that guy wants?
- Because he's a client.
I don't want to live on
the Upper East side.
I saw us raising our kids in a place
with more different kinds of people.
I don't know what to say.
Say you're gonna be the first American
to complete a successful heart transplant.
I could come up and
stay there tonight, if you want.
We'll be fine.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Are you sure you don't want
me to order in some food?
- Chinese?
- I'm sorry this is taking so long.
It's a common mistake
to not ask questions
when you want something because
you're afraid of the answers.
So you want something?
I'm interested.
And considering the precedent
for small agencies,
this is how we might
take you public.
With one and a half
million shares outstanding
before the offering, we'd sell
400,000 additional shares
to the public at $9 a share.
- 12 a share.
- It's not an insult.
Our valuation of your company was
made after careful analysis.
Of papers you spent
20 minutes with?
I can't take this
to the rest of my partners,
but I can take it
to other underwriters.
I'll need these documents
for 24 hours.
These papers are spotless.
My compliments to the chef.
Shall we?
You don't think Cooper pushed that
poor banker too hard, do you?
We don't want to lose him.
Certainly not.
It's a marvel.
Everyone wants you, don't they?
Pete, no.
No, I believe our primary
hurdle has been cleared.
And our secondary one?
Don't worry about Don.
Even at nine a share,
your part of the company alone
will be worth nearly $1 million.
My goodness.
You're flushed.
I drank too fast.
I don't think Don
cares about money.
That may be true.
God bless him.
But he's tired of playing
in the bush leagues.
This capitalization
will double our size
and that will turn his head.
You want another?
No. I can hardly walk
and you know it.
I hope Clara reminded you
tomorrow's Mother's Day.
Thank you, I'm aware.
Ow.
Just wanted to make sure
you were still here.
I am, but not for long.
You don't even know
what time it is.
I do.
Because I already got up
and put on my face.
Is that what you do?
- I wondered.
- I have to go.
Daisy, you're a tease.
What more could I give you?
Look, the first-class lounge would
be a darker place without you,
but you're supposed to have
your ear to the ground.
I feel like you only call me
when you want to see me.
Am I going to see you tomorrow?
If there's a flight filled with P&G
executives headed back to Cincinnati.
- How about tonight?
- I have plans.
Some other boyfriend? The one
you give all the leads to?
With my mother.
It's Mother's Day.
Don't go.
I have to.
But my mother just died.
What are you doing?
You told me you wanted
me here Sunday morning.
I'm here.
Peter, don't.
So we'll just maintain every
other aspect of this marriage
except the one that matters.
You mean Tammy?
Will you stop holding
the axe over my neck?
So you'd rather I divorce you just
so you know where things stand?
You don't care that I want you.
I've taken note
of your efforts.
I'm going to get her.
Well...
you're gonna be sorry
when this is over.
You've given up on me
at exactly the wrong time.
I have big things coming.
You have no idea.
Well, I'll take note
of that, too.
_
Could you get that?
- Arnold. Come in.
- Hi.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Do you have any wrapping paper?
It's an emergency.
Good morning.
Sorry, this is
Megan's mother Marie.
We passed in the lobby.
I thought you were Megan.
Dr. Arnold Rosen
at your service.
- Enchanté.
- Are you French?
My kid's going to Paris.
Should I keep him home?
I am French,
but I live in Montreal.
And, yes, I believe so.
I assume this isn't
a medical emergency.
Mitchell--
that's my son--
he came home and surprised
her for Mother's Day.
- How long is he staying?
- Who knows?
I know he thinks a morning stroll
in Central Park is a gift,
but Sylvia's gonna
expect an actual gift.
Do you want my flowers?
I'm quite done with them.
Thank you, Mother.
You're a lifesaver.
He's a surgeon. He's working
on heart transplants.
Wealthy, talented,
handsome--
I would not leave them alone.
I'm more worried about you.
There's poop
on the stairs again.
Somebody's dog got in.
No, it's human.
I think it's from the tenant.
She wouldn't do that.
She's a junkie.
She doesn't care.
I want her out.
We can't do that.
How is your mother?
I got curtains.
She wants to come visit.
Ah!
Ow! Ow.
Jesus.
We have to hire a handyman.
Why?
It's a waste of money.
Because you have no idea
what you're doing.
Herb Rennet called. He's
canceling dinner tonight.
That's a relief.
We can still have dinner.
I'd love to discuss
some things with you.
Let's enjoy our reprieve.
Of course.
Psst.
Close the door.
Did he say your dinner
with Jaguar is off?
Yes, unless it was the
world's most boring dream.
Well, it's on,
but Pete's not invited.
Herb Rennet wants a word alone
to straighten things out.
Why can't you handle it?
This could be fatal.
You're going.
And my plan is to pack it with
spouses to limit the explosion.
Megan made plans
with her mother.
She thought I had
a business dinner.
Marie's in town?
Fantastic.
Bring her along.
That's perfect.
Tell her I insisted.
In attendance
I have Jim Cutler,
Frank Gleason, and Ted Chaough.
Sweetheart, this is a creative meeting.
What are you doing?
It's for the purposes
of the memorandum.
Well, Ted, some men love
women, some love memos.
I want to go over where we are
on Chevrolet again
and devote our final days
to overdoing it
on the artwork for
the top three campaigns.
I cannot look at these again.
I told you, they're very keen
on the rocket ship thing
with the astronaut anecdotes.
You told them
about the astronauts?
I had to.
It was too vague otherwise.
I don't want to draw
any more rockets
and I don't want to stare
at this work again.
We should have never
resigned Alfa Romeo.
What, is this mystery Chevy
gonna be in "The Graduate"?
Those things are
flying off the lot.
Frank, are you not
on board with this?
I love what you're doing.
I'm tired of rockets,
that's all.
Could you give us a moment?
We'll continue this later.
What is that, Shalimar?
What's gotten into you?
You're supposed to be
calming me down.
Ted, I've got cancer.
What?
In my pancreas.
I told Jim.
I thought he told you
and you didn't want
to embarrass me.
No.
Maybe it's more of
a financial issue to him,
but I'm glad he can
keep a secret.
Financial?
The minute I cash out,
I cash in.
You two have to buy me out.
You have cancer.
See, if we still had Alfa,
I wouldn't have to worry
about putting you
out of business.
First of all,
stop talking about money.
Second, we are going
to get Chevy
because you're going
to do your best work.
Third, you're going
to build a wing
at Sloan-Kettering
and beat this thing.
Aye, aye.
Will you tell Jim you told me?
He'll see it on your face.
Everybody loves astronauts.
I've got to go lie down.
Well, hello there.
How are things in Glocca Morra?
Hello. Can you hear me?
I love it when you whisper like that.
What are you wearing?
My uniform.
I have one
and his flight's delayed.
Who is he?
What's he do?
I'm not sure,
but he doesn't believe
my name's really Daisy.
Use that.
Shit.
Do you mind?
17, please.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but we love your show.
Oh, thank you.
Can we get an autograph?
I know you're not waving to me.
Makes the delay
worthwhile, doesn't it?
- Headed to Detroit?
- Eventually.
Should we try LaGuardia?
They already did.
Forget it.
This is why I like
to drive everywhere.
I'd live in my car if I could.
You know, with her
in the backseat navigating.
I'm Roger.
- What's your name?
- Mikey.
Well, Mikey, since we're
gonna be cell mates,
I'm going to ask the screw
for a couple of drinks.
Jim Beam.
I'll make her bring them over.
- Good idea.
- I'm full of 'em.
I want a glass of water
with an onion
and bring him
a double Jim Beam.
And get me on that flight.
_
This is my day off.
We had plans.
_
Well, you would rather spend the evening
laughing at Roger Sterling's jokes.
I should return home.
I've overstayed my welcome.
_
Well, I don't know
what's happened.
I knew something was wrong.
We have not had a fight.
He's so far away
that sometimes
when we're alone,
I feel like
I'm making conversation.
Darling, you have confounded
everyone's expectations.
And it is very hard
to stand next to someone
giving an autograph.
- He doesn't even care.
- Of course he does.
But he may think you belong more
to other people than to him.
_
I love coming into the city.
It's 25 minutes,
half hour give or take,
from Tenafly
depending on the traffic.
I always think I'm gonna
go to museums and stuff.
And there's some good ones.
You've probably seen them.
But I always end up at Saks.
And I come home
and Herb always says
the same thing.
How much damage
did you do, Peaches?
We always do some shopping.
My daughter is very generous.
She even invited me along
to this wonderful evening.
You get a hold of Silver Bells?
No. That doesn't mean
he's not coming.
I'm pretty much done waiting.
Perhaps we should go.
What?
No, I think
we're gonna order now.
Herb gets very peckish.
I skipped lunch.
Can I help you, Bert?
You've already done
all you can do.
Snapped this place into shape,
expanded our business
while keeping it lean.
Pending due diligence,
we're done...
at $11 a share.
Really?
I believe I would like a drink.
What do you drink?
Do you have any brandy?
No.
Spirits of elderflower?
No. I don't have
any laudanum either.
- Surprise me.
- Night, chief.
Bob, could you get Joan?
- And some ice.
- Absolutely.
When do we break the news?
Call the meeting for tomorrow.
Ahh.
So there she was in the garage
right among the-- you know,
there's an oil stain
that Herb's been meaning
to take care of--
there she is, our little puppy,
with a full litter.
_
You're right, Mother. They
must have been adorable.
There's one yellow
and one brown
and then three sort of mixed.
Each one at its own nipple.
I love puppies.
Not the way she does.
_
You know what?
Why don't we let the men
discuss the business they're
probably here to talk about
while we powder our noses?
Tall and tan
and young and lovely.
So why are we here, Herb?
Oh, it's nothing serious.
I just had an idea.
There's a kid who's been
writing fliers for me
at a few of my lots
and I'm really getting results.
He's got a good turn of phrase.
I think you'd appreciate it.
Is he looking for a job?
No, he's got a job.
I just thought that
it might help you and me
if he were to take a look
at some of your work,
even at the formative stages,
just to get his take on it.
What's his name?
Fawcett.
Chris Fawcett.
Here you go.
- What is this?
- It's the name of the guy
who's going to be handling
your account from now on.
You never fail
to overheat, do you?
You know the somersaults I'm
doing 'cause you're so touchy?
Really?
A man your size?
You know what?
Your whole company should
be taken to the woodshed.
First Campbell
gives me the sass.
Then Sterling,
he didn't even show up.
And you-- huh, yeah--
my friend,
you're gonna
be working for him.
And he could
teach you something
like knowing where
your bread is buttered.
Why don't you get this?
I want you to buy me
one last meal.
I'm tired of taking it
out of your account.
Okay.
And if you ever
see Sterling again,
tell him you screwed up
'cause I'm done
with all of youse.
Don't sit down.
Dinner's over.
Are you okay?
Never felt better in my life.
Nice meeting you.
See you soon.
My mother needs an aspirin.
I don't care.
- Hello?
- Marie.
It's Roger.
I'm so glad I got you.
If you are calling
to apologize, don't bother.
- It's too late. Good night.
- Hold on, hold on, don't hang up.
- Let me talk to Don.
- Did you call to talk to Don?
Yes, but I was hoping you were there.
You were next, I swear.
You dragged me out
and made me sit
with that disgusting man
with his disgusting wife.
She is the apple that goes
in the pig's mouth.
Marie, I swear I wouldn't
have missed it for the world.
It's just something came up,
something very important
that I need to talk
to Don about.
You are speaking slowly
so I will understand?
Forget... my... name.
Excuse me.
Is it possible for me
to pay for my friend?
Yes, but
it's too late for that.
What are you bugging him for?
Aren't I enough for you?
This is my friend. What
was your fake name again?
Curious George?
You're a riot.
Hello.
Good night.
Isn't that guy a client?
Is he gone?
Yes.
I have a high-level
accounts question.
A hypothetical.
So it doesn't involve
anybody in this room?
Let's say you caught your father-in-law
in a compromising position.
It's every Sunday night.
The guy can't hold his liquor.
Last night I was celebrating
at that party house up on Lex
and I saw my father-in-law
exit the bedroom
with the biggest,
blackest prostitute
you've ever seen.
Was there anyone else
from Vicks there?
Not that I saw.
But we spoke.
I mean, all I said
was hello, but--
Okay, look,
when I was in high school,
they had this picture come to the
only movie theater in Cabot.
It was called
"Making A Baby."
They invited women
and men separately,
but it was a delivery system
for some filthy stuff.
So at the matinee, I look over
and Mr. Miller my science
teacher is five seats away.
And he's not, you know, working
the slide rule or anything,
but we see each other for sure.
But we both knew that neither
of us should be there.
It was mutually
assured destruction.
So he's not going
to say anything?
He can't.
Mr. Cosgrove,
I have a phone call.
Give me a second.
It's why I don't worry
about the bomb.
It's urgent.
I have Hugh Hibbert
and John Echolls from Jaguar.
Why are they calling you?
Pick it up.
This is Ken.
Good morning.
Do you have any idea where Roger
has been for the last 24 hours?
- I don't.
- Draper!
What in the hell have you--
- What?
- You have done it again.
What did you say
to Herb Rennet last night?
Nothing that shouldn't have
been said last Christmas.
As usual, you have
acted impulsively
and harmed the company
irreparably.
- Pete, calm down.
- We'd already lost the account.
He was gonna bring in
some kid to write copy.
That's because you
screwed him last time.
You couldn't wait.
Pete, you've got to
understand when it's over.
Do you know that we had
a public offering underway?
And now it's ruined!
- What?
- You don't care about the company.
- You're already rich.
- Not here.
Inside.
- What is going on?
- Why the hell didn't I know about this?
- We're going public?
- Not anymore.
- When did that happen?
- I was going to tell you this morning.
I tried to last night, but you'd
rather have dinner with Herb Rennet.
Well, I have some good news
and some bad news.
- Where the hell have you been?
- Don fired Jaguar.
What?
Then I just have good news.
We're giving a presentation
this Friday on Chevy's
top secret new car.
- What?
- Friday?
Come on, you've been thinking
about Chevy your whole life.
- Are you serious?
- And I have this check for $10,000
because I close, Pete.
I close things.
Did I mention I was in Detroit
where my friend Mikey O'Brien--
look him up--
said he was looking for
something cutting-edge,
but none of the agencies
had it?
So he had a great idea.
Bring us in.
We're not afraid of a deadline.
Holy crap.
Chevy.
You want to go public?
How much better is it
when we have Chevy?
Don't act like you had a plan.
You're Tarzan
swinging from vine to vine.
Roger, I want to know everything.
Pete, go box up Jaguar.
Make sure they have
all their files today.
Joan, get the creatives
in my office.
Get them yourself.
Don't you feel
300 pounds lighter?
I don't.
Honestly, Don, if I could deal
with him, you could deal with him.
And what now?
I went through
all of that for nothing?
Joan, don't worry.
I will win this.
Just once
I would like to hear
you use the word "we."
Because we're all rooting
for you from the sidelines,
hoping that you'll decide whatever
you think is right for our lives.
In my office, all of you.
Should we go in there?
I don't care.
XP-887.
- So we get to name it?
- Possibly.
For now it's all
cloak-and-dagger.
They've got a room full
of R&D on this.
But it boils down
to Chevrolet's top brass
trying to build
the perfect car.
- They designed it with a computer.
- So they're scared.
They run another agency in
at the one-yard line.
They're terrified.
So who else is in it?
Well, the guest list limping in
is as follows--
Campbell-Ewald.
Chevy's right arm. They got
200 people in Detroit.
Dancer Fitzgerald Sample
and Cutler Gleason and Chaough.
Ha, fantastic. Two
steamships and a rowboat.
You had to write that down?
- There's no pictures.
- It's a GM car.
It's got four wheels
and an engine.
No, it's totally new.
I want you to go to the library
and get me everything
you can on Mustang.
- And Chevy.
- No, forget that.
They know there's been
nothing before Mustang
and nothing after it, but
they're hoping it's this.
No one and nothing
leaves my office.
How about that?
How 'bout it?
Are you okay?
I just wanted to watch "Hazel,"
but I can't get any reception.
I think you should go home.
I love how you work every account
like it's make or break.
I need some of that right now.
You've been working plenty.
I have a new way to go.
I'd show it to you, but it's top
secret and it may be terrible.
Maybe Frank's right.
We should have
never dumped Alfa.
It's one thing to want something,
it's another to need it.
This is your agency.
You're always going
to need something.
Don't let Frank Gleason
make you question it.
Well, it's Frank's agency,
too, Peggy.
And I've been counting on his
paintbrush and his negativity
to balance me out for 20 years.
Fine.
But I've spent a lot of time
working with pessimistic people
and I like the fact
that you're--
Do not say I'm nice.
I hate it when people
say I'm nice.
I was going to say strong.
I'm sorry.
I'm just grateful.
No, of course.
Good night, Peggy.
Yes.
Good night.
Hold that.
I got it.
You want to go celebrate?
I just quit my job.
What? Really?
I had a heart and a kid
who needed the heart
and now they're both dead.
I'm not gonna get
the opportunity.
I'm tired of fighting.
Well, you're fighting
God in a way.
Oh, bullshit.
You don't think
God's in Houston?
My hospital chickened out
and now some asshole down
there is taking my place
in history while I piss away
my life in New York City.
You can't think that way.
Fate hasn't chosen me.
Look...
I don't cut people open.
I don't believe in fate.
You make your own
opportunities.
You sure you don't want
to go for a drink?
I got work.
- How'd it go?
- I don't know.
I was gonna sleep on it,
but now I think I'm just
gonna shower and go back in.
I love you like this.
Desperate and scared?
Fearless.
And I want to do whatever I can
to make sure you do not fail.
Then you can jump
from the balcony
and fly to work like Superman.
Will there be anything else?
No, thank you, Daisy.
Actually, can you
get those lugs
from Dancer
bumped off the flight?
Roger, I told you,
I can't hurt the company.
They bought most of the seats.
Jesus, there's like
eight of them.
Surprised to see you here.
Taking your kid
to look at colleges?
No, taking him
to pick out a car.
Oh. When did they add
you guys to the mix?
When they saw your work.
I wish you the best of luck.
In fact,
maybe we shouldn't even go.
What are the billings
for Vicks?
Nine million? Someone's
gonna pick that up.
Any of you have a cough drop?
I know they don't.
Get him on the phone right now
or I'm coming over there.
I've got it, Clara.
Roger's calling
from the airport.
He says something happened
with Vick Chemical.
Tell my father-in-law
I am not joking.
Believe me, you do not
want me in your lobby.
Let me talk to Roger.
So it's true?
No, I'm gonna fix it.
Jesus, they don't need
to hear this right now.
Roger will handle it.
- Well?
- They're screwing with us.
Really?
Daisy's gonna lose
their luggage.
Well, apparently you
didn't get any of my calls.
So I came down here
to your lair.
Spare me the outrage, Pete.
I'm tired of it.
Tom, what are you doing?
I know we're both
emotional and vulnerable,
but I'm not the enemy here.
I'm an adult, as are you.
And if anything,
our relationship
has shown over
the last seven years
that I have
a very short memory.
Now, what can I do
to bring you back to reality
in this obviously
impulsive decision?
My daughter is a princess.
She could have had anyone.
I knew there was a reason
you never wanted children.
You have no business
being a father.
You just pressed
the button, Tom.
You just blew everything up.
Well, it makes me sick
thinking about the man I saw
being with my daughter
and my granddaughter.
Why don't you look
in the mirror?
You can walk out like a man
or I can have you thrown out
like the lowlife you are.
If I have as low character
as you say,
why would you
push me like this?
You'll do the right thing.
The paint fumes
are making me sick.
I got the windows open.
It'll be dry
in a couple of days.
And when am I gonna
be able to walk around
my apartment in bare feet?
Soon.
We're fixing it up.
In here, yes.
But out there?
Those kids are living
on our stoop
lighting firecrackers
and playing their music.
And you keep waving to them.
Look, the neighborhood
is changing.
We're a part of that.
I don't like change.
I want everything to stay
the way it was.
I don't think
you understand, babe.
Everything's getting better.
Johnson's gone.
The war is gonna end.
We're gonna have a new
president no matter what.
Maybe McCarthy.
Worst case, Kennedy.
I love Bobby Kennedy.
Fine.
If that's what you want.
I just want you to kiss me.
Damn it.
Hello to you, too.
What the hell
are you doing in Detroit?
My doctor recommended
an ocean voyage.
Can I get one of those?
I don't believe this.
I spent six weeks
on this pipe dream
and it's gonna be over
in two seconds.
Hell, I knew I was good,
but I didn't know
all I had to do was show up.
You don't know what this means?
It's not my job
to put you at ease,
but just because
they brought us in
at the last second
doesn't mean you're dead.
Me?
We're both dead.
I've had enough
psychological warfare today.
- Why don't you take a table?
- Think about it.
When it's two top 10 agencies
and me, I've got a chance.
Now that there's two
little guys, we're DOA.
I'm not worried.
I've got great work.
Of course you do. And mine's
even better, I guarantee.
You know how this works. They're
gonna take our creative
and give it to one
of the big boys.
Second place, tied with last.
Come on, you know I'm right.
So they want a name brand.
- We had a car.
- So did we.
It's not the same thing.
It's the size of the team.
It's opening an office
in Detroit.
This is General Motors.
They fight the war
with bodies on the ground.
I saw Dancer at the airport.
Looked like half my office.
This business is rigged.
Damn it.
That's what I said.
Sorry about that.
I'm tired of this crap.
I should just let Chevy buy
my brain and put it in a jar.
Can I get another?
Brain in a jar.
Put it on your tombstone.
"Here lies SCDP,
the little company
with the big ideas."
"CGC, giving away creative
one car at a time."
So what did you go with?
What, I show you mine,
you show me yours?
What's the difference
at this point?
You first.
Okay, but I've got to stand up.
This is a car for the young
and the young at heart.
Because today nobody knows
where they're headed,
but they're not afraid
of what's around the bend.
Power plus design
equals adventure.
Throw the map out the window
and hit the road, Jack.
Then I sing the song.
- That's good.
- No kidding.
Just music.
People's faces.
All kinds-- teenagers,
dads, moms.
Different expressions
of wonder.
What could this possibly be?
It's so new,
this combination of power,
technology, comfort, and price
that it's impossible
to imagine.
But not at Chevy.
The future
is something you haven't
even thought of yet.
You run that for a week,
then you finally show the car.
That's interesting.
Hooray.
So should we go home?
We--
that's interesting.
Why, you want to stay
just so Chevy
can put a feather in your cap?
I have a better idea.
No, you don't.
I just heard it.
This is why everyone hates you.
Think about it.
Both of us have the creative,
but neither of us
have an agency to match.
Why would I do that?
Because we're dead.
Even if I were to consider
that, Chevy calls the shots.
Hey, Lieutenant,
want to get into some trouble?
How would that even work?
Well, one of us, probably me,
will have to figure out
a way to make Chevy
think it was their idea
to combine our agencies.
And then the other one,
let's say it was you,
will have to figure out what the
hell we're going to present.
Well, we have partners.
Who aren't sitting in this bar.
Can I get another?
No, we're done.
We've got a long night.
♪ My eyes were on the sparrow ♪
♪ My feet were on the ground ♪
♪ I used to walk
the straight and narrow ♪
♪ Never fly around ♪
♪ Till one night at a party ♪
♪ I met you,
Baby Jane... ♪
I want to make it clear,
unless this works,
I'm against it.
I was just saying
the same thing.
Shall we?
After you.
You're not supposed to be
here till the weekend.
I don't like you surprising me.
Sit down, Trudy.
Did you know your father
pulled his business?
No.
And I don't care, Peter.
You understand that we were
going to be very rich,
but he's ruined that.
He's done everything for you.
He's a hypocrite, Trudy.
Don't you dare
criticize my father.
I guess it doesn't matter
that I caught him
in a Midtown whorehouse.
Just stop it right now.
It's true. With a 200-pound
Negro prostitute.
Ask him to his face.
You'll say anything
to hurt me, won't you?
He wanted it this way.
He left me no other choice.
You had lots of choices, Peter.
We're done.
Get your things.
Mr. Chaough
wants to see you.
- He's back?
- That's all I know.
So, how'd it go?
We got it.
We won Chevy.
What are you doing here?
We went in together.
What?
What are you talking about?
They wanted our ideas
and a big agency,
so we gave them both.
Just for Chevy?
No, we merged--
furniture, fixtures,
everything.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
I did this wrong once before,
so let me tell you
how great it's going to be
and you can decide
if you want to come along.
You are the copy chief
at one of the top 25
ad agencies in the country.
You're not even 30.
I'm jealous.
I just bought an apartment.
Congratulations.
Are we moving?
We are, and we'd like you
to write the press release.
For what?
We don't have a name yet,
but make it sound
like the agency
you want to work for.
Who do I give it to?
Give it to Ted.
New York City,
May 17, 1968.
For immediate release.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com