Previously on Mad Men...
I hope you left us something.
You will be here only
when I tell you to be here.
We're done, Peter.
Have a happy birthday.
How old are you gonna be?
Forty.
So when you're forty,
how old will I be?
You'll be dead.
My boss made a call.
You told Mayor Lindsay.
We have to be careful.
We can't fall in love.
( theme music playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Woman:
1,290 square feet.
Let's call it 13
with the balcony.
One and a half bathrooms.
That means it's a full bath
and a powder room.
Two bedrooms, 11th floor,
one parking spot
with an option for a second.
And at $28,000,
I do believe that was
everything on your list.
It's a little farther east
than I wanted.
In fact, it's about
as far east as you could go.
You can see the highway
from the corner.
You can see the river.
And who needs Central Park
when you can smell the ocean
and the Hungarian bakeries?
Believe me, when they finish
the Second Avenue subway,
this apartment
will quadruple in value.
- ( doorbell rings )
- Oh, that's Barbara.
You let me do the talking.
Sorry I'm late.
It's quite a hike
between First and York.
It's got to be longer
than a normal block.
I don't think so.
We just got started.
What do you think?
I think no one's gonna catch
that doorman napping.
I left your name.
It's got a doorman.
I was telling Peggy that an offer
is coming in at asking price.
We'd have to beat it.
So it's in your best interest
to be decisive
and take this property
seriously.
Well, okay,
but it's not my decision.
Ginny, we are taking
this seriously.
- What Abe means is--
- I'm more her trusted advisor.
An interested party.
Oh. I see.
I, uh, misunderstood.
I'm going to flush
that toilet again.
She didn't know
I wasn't the buyer?
So all this time
she was just being rude.
( laughs ) Forget about her.
Is it too far east?
Betty:
Dinner.
Bobby, Sally, let's go.
( elevator bell dings )
Look at you two.
Heading to the track?
( laughs )
- Where are you going?
- DC, if Jonesy can find a cab.
- Hope you're not in a rush.
- We have a car coming.
6:30?
We should have done that.
We're not going
to miss the train.
Where are you going?
They said DC.
I mean, why are you going?
Arnie was invited last minute
to give a keynote address.
Did you have to tell him
it was last minute?
I guess the point is somebody
more important fell out.
It's a very
distinguished group.
And you must have been
at least as important.
Either way, it sounds like a good
excuse for a weekend in Washington.
Yes. Come Monday morning,
it'll all be a dream.
We should really go away.
Looks like you're going
somewhere fun now.
We are.
Megan's up for an award.
Good for you.
Maybe tomorrow
you'll be calling the producers
and asking for a raise.
No, it's for advertising.
The Ad Club of New York.
- Paul Newman's coming.
- My goodness.
You're really good
at everything.
I was just a name on the team.
There's the car.
Well, break a leg.
You, too.
Oh, and, Don...
we're going to DC.
( laughs )
Hey, Pop, I--
I'm sorry.
Am I interrupting something?
We were waiting for you.
Look, miss, whatever he told
you we were interested in,
- we're not.
- See how funny he is?
Now, don't be rude.
This is Beverly Farber.
She is Chaim Farber's daughter.
I'm-- our dads,
they play chess together.
Oh, uh...
well, I...
it's nice to meet you.
And now that you're home
from a busy day
on Madison Avenue,
I think you should go out
and have some dinner.
What?
Maybe we should
do this another time.
Nonsense. There's no
time like the present.
You both should have some fun.
She's a schoolteacher.
She works all the time.
I need to shave,
change my clothes, prepare.
I mean, look at her.
She had a jump on me.
( laughs ) I did.
I was led to believe
that you knew about this.
- Why did you tell her that?
- What's the difference?
Look at her. I'm obviously
doing you a disservice.
At least we're close
to the kitchen.
It's not fair that all the
big agencies are up front.
Closer to their trophies.
But at least we're gonna
eat before them.
Oh, I see Peggy back there.
We should go say hello.
- I'm gonna wait for the group.
- You can't avoid her forever.
I'm not.
Tell her that no matter what,
her laxative radio spot
is the sentimental favorite.
Megan:
Hello, stranger.
I was hoping I'd see you.
You know, other than on TV.
- You don't watch.
- My mother and sister do.
Really?
Do they hate me?
Oh, just a minute.
Megan, I want you
to meet Jim Cutler.
He's the president of CGC.
This is Megan Draper.
She's also a finalist.
You must be Don's wife.
When I started out,
they didn't make
copywriters like you.
Good luck.
He's the head of accounts.
He's like Roger
with bad breath.
So he knows who you are.
It must be going well.
If I survive tonight.
CGC has no other finalists.
Other-- they have none.
I only came because
it seemed important to Don.
I bet it is. We're the
only finalists from SCDP
and neither of us
work there anymore.
My work was for beans
and they aren't even
a client anymore.
I don't want
to talk about this.
I want to talk
about my apartment.
I made an offer today. I think
we're gonna be neighbors.
- 84th and York.
- You're buying a place?
Well, I paid off my debts
and helped out my mother
and it turns out I still
have this tax problem.
Don't apologize, Peggy.
You deserve it.
Thank you.
I should get back.
I have to walk all the
way down to the front.
You're terrible.
Joan: These are the worst
seats in the room.
- Don Draper, this is Randall Walsh.
- A pleasure to meet you.
Randy here is in insurance and he wants
to come in for an official visit.
Look, man, it's not like we're not
supposed to talk about business here.
You want a presentation
right now?
I don't think we'll interrupt the
proceedings, wherever they are.
- I just thought you two should meet.
- We've already met.
In fact, I'm pretty sure we've
had this meeting already, too.
- And it went well.
- So where's our check?
- He's solid.
- Okay, Randy.
Go get back in your cage.
- What was that?
- Don't worry about it.
Have no fear. They're
gonna fire off a cannon
- when the atrocities begin.
- ( laughter )
Hello all.
You remember my wife Nan.
Hello, everyone.
Good luck.
I told you, Nan, Peggy's
the only one competing.
Well, I didn't know
what else to say.
So you probably figured out
by now that you didn't win.
- Ted. - But it doesn't matter,
because next year you will.
- Ted.
- And the year after. Just a second, honey.
- Hey, man, sorry.
- Oh, I'm in your seat.
Nan, you wanted
to see Paul Newman.
Here he is.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Emcee: Ladies and gentlemen,
we would like to welcome you
to the Advertising Club
of New York's
Fourth Annual ANDY Awards for
Excellence in Advertising.
( applause )
So you like kids?
Excuse me?
I was asking because
you're a teacher,
but I realize how that could
sound like something else.
I'm a student teacher.
I'm getting my master's
at Hunter.
And, yes, I like kids.
Some kids.
I just really can't believe he
brought you to the apartment.
Stop saying that. You
don't know where I live.
Well, it's kind of early
to find out, isn't it?
Yes, I suppose it is.
I don't know
what you're expecting.
I mean, a couple of alter kockers
arrange a little meeting like this,
it sounds very old world.
But it doesn't feel like it.
I mean, you're a sexy girl
and you smell great.
You don't need to be set up.
And I sure as hell
didn't arrange this.
I'm sure my father told you
what a Lothario I am,
but I'm not.
I'm very anxious about it.
I've never had sex,
not even once.
( laughs ) Okay.
What am I doing? I ordered
soup, I just said that.
Michael...
I'm just doing a favor
for my parents.
Tonight will not be the night.
And I saw a picture of you
and, honestly,
you're very handsome.
And I'm obviously very shallow.
- I am?
- You must have heard that before.
So...
do you make a lot
of money teaching?
( laughs ) No.
Emcee: Ladies and
gentlemen, Paul Newman.
Newman: Good evening.
I am Paul Newman.
The Advertising Club
of New York
has been kind enough to let me
say a few words here tonight.
And I want to make one thing
clear from the very start.
- I need binoculars.
- Shh.
Newman: I'm not here
because I'm an actor.
We invited him
because he's an actor.
Newman: I'm here because I've got six
kids and I'm worried about their future.
That's not an actor,
that's a speck.
Gene McCarthy stood up
to Lyndon Johnson
before Bobby Kennedy.
The others backed into
the election
with their fingers to the wind,
thinking of their own career
when the nation
was in critical need of a hero.
I know Bobby Kennedy,
but I'm supporting
Gene McCarthy
for President
of the United States.
( applause )
Man:
Mr. Newman, sir.
Do you know, Mr. Newman, sir, that
Martin Luther King is dead?
- What have you to say?
- ( crowd murmuring )
No, that can't be.
Who the hell said that?
Woman:
How awful.
Emcee: If I could have your
attention for a moment, please.
A moment of your attention.
Not wanting to interrupt
the festivities,
we hoped to keep this news
until the end of the event.
As it stands,
let's take 10 minutes
to talk out this terrible event
and then resume the program.
What do you think happened?
- What do you think?
- Come on.
I guess Puerto Rico.
But who has time?
Your father says you've even
written some billboards.
That must be exciting.
You'd think so, but they
usually change it so much
by the time they put it up there, it just
makes you angry every time you walk by.
- ( laughs )
- Radio: ...in Memphis, Tennessee,
after being shot in the face
by an unknown assailant
on the balcony in front of a
downtown hotel a short while ago.
( plate shatters ) Associated Press
says Assistant Police Chief
Henry Lux of Memphis
confirmed Dr. King's death.
- Reverend Dr. King, winner
of the Nobel Peace Prize... - Oh, my God.
- ...was 39 years old.
- They had to do it.
He was in Memphis
to lead demonstrations
in sympathy
with a prolonged strike
by municipal garbage men,
most of them Negro.
Police at last report
were still looking
for a young white male
who was seen running
from the scene of the shooting
and reportedly dropped
the weapon in flight.
What are you doing in here?
Thought you'd be by the set.
- She won't let us watch. - Because who
knows what they're going to show?
You don't have to go.
Betty, they're gonna
burn down the city.
Everything's fine.
I have to go help the mayor.
Please be careful.
- And call me.
- Man on radio: We repeat,
Dr. Martin Luther King, America's
nonviolent civil rights...
What is taking so long?
There are other people here
who need to make calls.
They shot him in the face
in Memphis.
Do they know who?
Come on, they didn't catch
him yet, but you know who.
Listen, Jimmy says they can get me a
photographer if I can get uptown.
No, it's not a good idea.
It's the "New York Times."
- And what?
- It's a huge story.
( sirens wailing )
- Don't do anything stupid.
- Peggy, it's too late.
I'm going to Harlem
in a tuxedo.
I can't believe this.
Abe just went uptown for work.
I'm sick and I don't even know
how I'm gonna get home.
We'll give you a ride.
I'm tired of waiting for a phone.
I'm going home.
What are we doing? They're
really still having the awards?
What else are we gonna do?
Look, I'm sure
it's hard to sleep.
What is that?
What are you doing?
I didn't do it.
It peeled off.
Why are you
destroying this house?
( sighs ) You can't do this.
I didn't do anything.
I don't want
to talk about it now.
Please just go to sleep.
( door closes )
...the Civil Rights
Movement
has been shot to death
in Memphis, Tennessee.
Police have issued
an all-points bulletin...
It's me.
Oh.
How are you?
Not good.
I don't know why
I'm so surprised.
It's shameful.
Listen, I...
( sirens wailing )
I don't want you
and Tammy to be alone.
I could come out and sleep
there tonight if you want.
No, I--
we'll be fine.
Well, I want to see Tammy.
Is she all right?
She doesn't know
what's going on.
No, of course.
I'll see you on Saturday.
No, I'll just tell my parents
you couldn't get out
of the city.
Or I'll just cancel it
altogether.
Trudy.
What?
I don't want you to be worried.
Okay.
Man on TV: In a nationwide
television address,
President Johnson
expressed the nation's shock.
Good night, Peter.
Good night.
Johnson:
...of Dr. Martin Luther King.
I ask every citizen
to reject the blind violence
that has struck
Dr. King,
who lived by nonviolence.
Pop, wake up.
What time is it?
What are you doing
home so early?
We cut it short.
Martin Luther King got killed.
( sirens wailing )
Reporter:
...try and cool things down.
In Boston,
according to police reports,
a large crowd of Negroes
stoned six police cruisers
near a Negro housing project
in the Roxbury section.
And there was a clash between
police and young Negroes
in Raleigh's main
downtown streets tonight.
The latest report of trouble
comes from Washington, DC,
where stores along
a six-block area
were broken into
late this evening.
(French) - I don't agree with you, Papa.
- President Johnson went on nationwide
television to express his shock
and personal grief at the tragedy.
( speaking French ) _
_
...looking subdued and grim
at the thought
of what this act
could mean in a country
already taut
with racial tension.
He said he applauded
the escalation of decay.
So sick of that
Marxist bullshit.
So far it's only
looting in Harlem,
but a lot of places
are on fire.
Well, it's raining.
Do you think
your secretary is okay?
Sylvia and Arnold are in DC.
My father just hides
behind his intellect.
He doesn't want
to feel any emotions.
Let's watch inside.
Maybe we can fall asleep.
( TV turns off )
_
( phones ringing )
- ( knocks )
- Am I disturbing you?
No. I'm not gonna judge you
if you want a drink.
The man knew how to talk.
I don't know why, but I
thought that would save him.
I thought it would solve
the whole thing.
Oh, I don't know if he
just wants to hold hands,
but my insurance friend
from last night, he called.
He wants to come in
at 3:00.
I'll have Caroline remind you
since you're on your own.
Could you get the door?
Yes, actually, I'm trying
to reach Dr. Rosen.
No, I'm not a patient.
I just know that
he's in Washington and--
well, I was concerned.
I'm his neighbor.
Oh, well, if you do reach him,
just say...
actually, no message.
I'll try later.
( radio playing )
Oh, you're here.
I'm sorry. There's no
reception out there.
No, I just-- I didn't
expect you to come in.
I kept calling
and no one answered.
We went out
to my aunt's in Newark.
Why would you do that?
My mother wanted
to be with her sister.
Abe said it could
have been a lot worse.
I'm so sorry.
I knew it was going to happen.
He knew it was going to happen.
But it's not gonna
stop anything.
And these fools
running in the streets--
it's exactly
what he didn't want.
You should go home.
In fact, none of us
should be working.
Thank you.
Is this really what happened?
You didn't tell me anything.
They got it right,
except that it was terrifying.
Walking into that angry,
crazy crowd
and Lindsay smiling like he was
going to a pancake breakfast.
The only lives His Honor seemed
worried about protecting
were the photographers'.
- But it worked.
- I'll tell you what worked.
Cutting deals with all
the militants last year.
Well, I'm glad you were there.
Me, too.
And I got to go back in.
I want you to eat
something first.
- ( phone ringing )
- Clara.
Have you seen Scarlett?
Where's my girl?
They must all be
watching TV somewhere.
- Not in my office.
- I barely slept last night.
I just thought working
might take my mind off things.
Good luck. Been on the
phone all morning.
They're worried about
last night, obviously,
but they're worried about tonight,
they're worried about the weekend.
- Who?
- The clients.
They won't take make-goods.
They want money back.
- That's disgusting.
- I don't know.
It's enough
of this crap already.
All these special broadcasts
preempting the prime-time schedule.
"Bewitched," Merv, Dean Martin.
You know they might
cancel the Stanley Cup?
How dare you?
This cannot be made good.
It's shameful.
It's a shameful, shameful day!
Don't you scream at me.
You don't think I'm upset
about that man being shot?
Only because it's
costing you, you pig!
It's costing all of us.
And when's it gonna stop?
No one will be happy
until they turn the most beautiful
city in the world into a shit hole.
- Gentlemen, stop it. Stop it this minute.
- In a second, Bert.
Did you know we were in the
presence of a bona fide racist?
That's the latest thing, isn't it?
Everybody's a racist.
Gentlemen!
I urge you to shake hands in the
spirit of erasing these remarks.
I'm sorry.
I suppose that my comments
were inappropriate.
I mistook this for a workday.
Don't worry. I'm sure you
can make your money back
on some Movie of the Week
next fall
about the death of a great man.
That is not what I meant.
Let me put this
in terms you'll understand.
That man had a wife
and four children.
( doors slam )
( knocks )
I'm sorry I'm late.
Would you like coffee?
Dawn, I'm just glad
you're okay.
Joan was trying to reach you.
The phone was out
for a little bit last night
and, well, it took
some time to get here.
I don't think
you should work today.
I couldn't reach you. I assumed
you weren't coming in.
My mother told me I should.
Well, Mr. Cooper just
announced that out of respect
we're going to close
the office early.
- Oh.
- That's probably a good idea.
- Mr. Sterling still wants to have the
3:00 meeting. - Are we closed or not?
Stan and Ginsberg will also be joining.
Do you want to cancel it?
- If you're gonna stay, I'll stay.
- No, you go.
I'd really rather
be here today.
Okay.
We're all so sorry.
Do you want anything?
No.
( phone rings )
- Hello?
- Peggy Olson, please.
- This is Peggy.
- Oh.
I was about to send over your
offer and it occurred to me--
Oh, my offer. I completely
forgot about that.
- You haven't sent it?
- No, I haven't.
Well, no one's gonna want
to look at that today.
May I speak?
I thought the same thing,
but then I realized
there's trouble 10 blocks away.
They're probably
on pins and needles.
So am I. Do I want
to live up there?
Get ahold of yourself.
The other buyer never came in.
Why don't we come in
at 5,000 under asking
and give them 24 hours
to respond?
We'll let the TV news
do the rest.
- I don't know.
- This is the only apartment for you.
You don't want to be
kicking yourself next week.
And, of course, I'll wait
until tomorrow to present.
Good girl.
Randall Walsh,
you remember Don.
This is Stan Rizzo
and Michael Ginsberg.
Randall, would you
like a drink?
Never. I really don't
even want to talk.
I was trying to communicate without
words, but it's not working.
Randy, it never works.
Randall has an idea and the ad
director won't take a chance.
You're in the property
insurance business.
I'll bet you're about
to get hit pretty hard.
Forget about that.
This is about
a no bullshit approach
to why I got
into this business.
People say they care.
I really care.
We're waiting for you, Randall.
All I see when I close my eyes
is our name
and a Molotov cocktail
being lit with a match.
And then a coupon
at the bottom.
The ad sales guy
didn't like that?
I know what it looks like--
fearmongering.
But this is the opposite.
This is a coded message
that came to me
when I was visited
by the spirit
of Dr. King last night.
He said that I should question
the whole property thing, man.
It makes you happy, right?
( stifled laugh )
No, I think it was
his end will always
be in poor taste.
'Cause you'd rather
not think about it.
But there is a tear,
and in that tear
are all the tears in the world,
all the animals crying.
You're right-- I don't
want to think about it.
What Don's saying is
despite what we believe
to be good intentions,
you're allowing
the emotions of the day,
and whatever else you got in your
system, to influence your judgment.
Are you forgetting
what Tecumseh said?
Heya howa howa hoya.
- Heya howa howa.
- I had forgotten that.
We'll think about it.
This is an opportunity.
The heavens
are telling us to change.
You talked
to Dr. King's ghost?
Make sure Randy
doesn't get lost.
- I had to wait around for that?
- I don't know.
He was very emotional.
He talked me off a roof once.
I kind of owed him.
You want a drink?
I just want to go home.
Someone's gonna do
that idea, you know.
Not us.
Reporter: Three deaths
have been reported
in the Washington
rioting so far.
There are no details yet on the
circumstances surrounding them.
More than 350 persons have
been treated for injuries.
Among them, several policemen and firemen.
( phone ringing )
Firefighting was hampered
if for no other reason
by the sheer volume
of the alarms.
But still, some persons
were injured and...
Megan: It's Betty. You're supposed
to pick up the kids.
Oh, shit.
Got it.
Hello.
I knew you would forget.
You really want them down here?
I know you don't. You get out of
every opportunity to see them.
You don't even know
how strange they're acting.
The news is very upsetting.
I'm sure it has nothing
to do with the fact
that their father
forgot about them.
You want me to come up
there and get them,
drive right through
everything after dark?
Well, of course,
Henry thinks it's fine,
but he's not as concerned
about their safety as you are.
Well, Henry would know.
I guarantee you'd go
to Canada on your knees
to pick up your girlfriend.
I don't believe this.
I'm going to get the kids.
...relatively little interference
during the afternoon.
Really?
They called in the troops
in Washington,
but Henry says we're fine here.
She's a piece of work.
Looting spread to the downtown
shopping section of the city
and as darkness fell,
arrests increased.
( sirens wailing )
You finished with that?
You can walk me to work.
I'm already at work.
Since when are you
going in on Saturday?
Since I don't want to be
in front of the TV set.
Good as new.
This?
This is a mess.
You can't sew, you can't
cook, you can't clean.
You don't think there's a reason
you have all these flaws?
You need a girl.
But maybe you don't like 'em.
I like girls, Dad.
If that was true, you'd be
in bed with her right now.
I don't think
anybody's in the mood.
It's quite the opposite.
Now's the time
when a man and a woman
need to be together the most.
In a catastrophe.
In the flood, the animals
went two by two.
You, you're gonna get on
the ark with your father.
I can find my own girls, okay?
Okay.
I'll bring you a sandwich.
( TV playing )
( sighs )
I'm glad you finally slept.
What's going on?
We're going to a vigil
in the park.
- You're not supposed to be watching TV.
- I'm not.
You are, and Mom
said you can't.
Sally, stop it.
Troy and Bridget called.
They're gonna meet us there.
We'll be back
in a couple of hours.
I don't feel well.
You go on ahead.
I'll watch him.
Come on.
Look, I just can't sit around
in the apartment anymore.
I feel like
I have to do something.
I understand.
I knew you wouldn't go.
You want some aspirin?
Hey.
Turn it off.
( TV turns off )
Tell me exactly
what your mother said.
I'm not allowed
to watch TV for a week.
Dr. Zaius:
Man has no understanding.
He can be taught a few
simple tricks, nothing more.
Dr. Zira: I'm afraid
I must disagree.
According to
my experiments--
Dr. Zira,
I must caution you.
I guess your stomach
is feeling better.
Why are you being punished?
I don't know.
Come on.
Because the wallpaper
didn't line up.
...the simian nature
from a study of man
is sheer nonsense,
because man is a nuisance.
He eats up his food supplies
in the forest...
You maniacs!
You blew it up!
Oh, damn you!
God damn you all to hell!
The humans blew up New York?
All of America.
So he came back to here?
In the future.
Jesus.
You want to see it again?
Can we?
- ( typewriter clacking )
- ( phone ringing )
I need another half hour.
Oh, yeah.
Just a minute.
It's for you.
It's the real estate agent.
- Hello, Ginny.
- Well, we didn't get it.
Wh-- what happened?
Someone came in
a little bit higher.
But you know what?
It wasn't meant to be.
( sighs ) How much higher?
It was still under asking, Peggy.
It wasn't meant to be.
There's no other way to think about it.
Try, try again.
( hangs up )
Someone else got the apartment.
What are you gonna do?
- That's it?
- What do you want me to say?
That you give a damn.
Peggy, this is
an emotional story.
Stop being such a martyr. You're
having the time of your life.
- Why are you so mad?
- Because I'm alone in this.
That's not cool.
I don't mean financially.
I mean, don't you care
where we live?
Look, I don't feel right
expressing an opinion.
Now is your chance.
I don't want to live
on the Upper East Side.
Fine. Why?
I don't know.
I saw us raising
our kids in a place
with more different
kinds of people.
This photographer
trailing me the other night,
he lives in the West 80s.
Isn't it dangerous?
No, it's more rundown.
But that's why it's so cheap.
Get some lumber, a coat of paint--
people are doing it.
I didn't know
you felt that way.
About the Upper East Side.
I do.
I'm sorry.
I just felt it wasn't my money.
How much of a say do I have?
You're in my life.
You're a part of my life.
Peggy, I've got to finish this.
( typewriter clacking )
- Did you see this movie?
- Not yet.
Do you get to see it for free?
- I do.
- It's really good.
- We're seeing it again.
- You enjoy yourself.
Everybody likes to go to the
movies when they're sad.
I was looking for you.
You left the TV on.
I don't feel right
turning it off,
but I don't want to watch it.
He doesn't even want
me to come in.
Everything has settled down.
For the time being.
No, I think this
is the end of it.
Good.
Betty, I hope you know you'll
never have to worry about money.
Why would you bring that up?
Nothing.
I just keep asking myself,
- "What am I doing?"
- About what?
I keep thinking about
walking through Harlem,
Lindsay a few paces ahead,
grinning like he always does,
the rest of us
following behind.
- Wasn't that frightening?
- It was exhilarating.
But what was the cost
of avoiding that riot?
Police corruption,
disrespect for authority,
negotiating with hoodlums.
You can't say that
to the mayor.
He's never been more popular.
It's just, Betty,
I keep thinking I would
do it differently.
I want to do it differently.
And, well, they approached me
like they always do
when somebody dies
and they offered me a seat
in the state senate.
Do you want to run?
Run?
It's a Republican seat.
It's basically unopposed.
- You'd have to quit the mayor's office.
- He'll understand.
You think I'm the first guy
sick of being in a flank?
I feel like I've been asking you
to do this since I met you.
Well, I finally heard you.
It's a stepping stone
to state attorney general.
- And--
- And who knows what else?
Easy, partner.
This is what
I've wanted for you.
Us.
I can't wait
for people to meet you.
You know?
Really meet you.
Everyone's in bed.
Gene finally
climbed in with Sally.
( sighs )
I felt better, but now I don't.
- Why?
- Because who knows what you're feeling?
I didn't know
what to say to her
except, "I'd tell you
to ask your father,
but he's at the movies."
I should have said,
"He's just drunk."
You're better with them.
You don't understand.
I do.
You don't have Marx,
you've got a bottle.
Is this what you really
want to be to them
when they need you?
No.
( sighs )
I don't think I ever wanted to
be the man who loves children.
But from the moment
they're born...
that baby comes out
and you act proud and excited
and hand out cigars...
but you don't feel anything.
Especially if you had
a difficult childhood.
You want to love them,
but you don't.
And the fact that you're...
faking that feeling
makes you wonder
if your own father
had the same problem.
Then one day they get older...
and you see them
do something...
and you feel...
that feeling
that you were
pretending to have.
And it feels like your
heart is going to explode.
That was faster
than I expected.
Are the things calmer out there?
Well, then...
have a good night.
Hey.
- You need to go to sleep.
- I can't.
So why can't you sleep?
I'm scared.
Don't make me sorry for
taking you to the movies.
No.
I just keep thinking...
what if somebody shoots Henry?
No one's gonna do that.
- But they could.
- But they won't.
Henry's not that important.
Go to sleep.
( sirens wailing )
( "Love is Blue" playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com