Previously on Mad Men...
Heinz beans.
Something's never changed.
Oh, it's clever.
We're going to lose
Jaguar unless
an arrangement is made, and
it involves you and her.
You look radiant, Joan.
You must have heard some terrible
things about me from Don Draper.
Now, why would you want to
play for the other team?
It's not a game.
You don't get another chance
at what you have.
I have it all.
( theme music playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Here we go.
The one with the fur.
You know, I might just take you
up on those theater tickets.
- You must see "Hair."
- Oh, you like that?
- Who doesn't?
- What is it?
Oh, it's just filled
with profanity,
marijuana smoking,
and simulated sexual acts.
Simulated?
And a few songs.
The two holiday
chairmanships that remain
are the 4th of July
block party,
which really consists of
calling the fire department,
or the Labor Day
Soap Box Derby,
which consists
of calling the hospital.
- ( laughs )
- Which one do you do?
Our family has claimed
the Easter egg hunt.
Do you dress as a bunny?
Maybe a little cottontail?
( laughs ) It's very wholesome.
Mm-hmm.
( laughs )
I'd like to surprise Doug
for his birthday.
Maybe you could get me
the tickets in secret.
Arrangements could be made.
Just pick a date
and ring me up.
I have to warn you,
I'm from a small town
and all of my forays into
Manhattan have been a disaster.
We'll make a deal.
Brave your way to Grand Central
and I'll hand off the tickets
and throw in a hot dog.
You have another one of those?
But you've already
seen "Hair."
Maybe I want to see it again.
Oh, there you are.
Gentlemen, it's been
a pleasure.
Thank you both
for your hospitality.
- Thank you again.
- It was lovely.
Consider what I said
about the pool.
That is the end
of the welcome wagon.
We'll basically have to move to get
someone to make dinner for us.
What was that about the pool?
He's insistent we all
go skinny-dipping.
Ha! Let him get
his own pool.
Turn it off.
( turns up TV )
I need to put it in the
mail today and the tailor.
Sylvia, sweetheart--
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Morning.
- Honey.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll swing by
the bank at lunch.
( sighs )
I give her cash every month,
but I think she's secretly
sending it all to our kid.
( chuckles ) You don't
have to explain anything.
You're lucky your wife works.
She doesn't earn much.
Not yet.
I forgot my cigarettes.
You got to stop that nonsense.
Listen, don't worry about dinner Wednesday.
We'll have money by then.
( chuckles )
Looking forward to it.
( doors open )
( car horns honking )
I knew it'd be you.
"I've Got Five Dollars"
playing in background
( woman laughing )
It wasn't all bad.
I got me some memories.
And the boy.
Don't know what it is yet.
I mean Dick here.
Well, hello there.
This is Mack. He's with
me, so he's your uncle.
We thank the Lord for
opening your rooms to us.
All I said was, "My sister's
coming with her boy."
Mack's the one that brung ya.
I'd do the same for mine.
And, of course,
Ernestine told you
we could always use
a little help around here.
Let's get you off your feet.
Dick, you help Mack
with the bags.
You keep your eyes down and
mind your own business here.
Good-looking kid.
He yours?
Not that I know.
Little boy, find your own sins.
Stay away from Mack's.
( laughs )
Afternoon, Charlotte.
Hey, kid, you were raised
on a farm, am I right?
Yes, sir.
Well, I'm the rooster
around here, understand?
You help all the hens?
And I'll bring on the day.
I feel bad.
You should.
I have to go to work.
You get to sleep.
No, about dinner.
I thought there was no smoking.
I just found out
the maid smokes.
She doesn't sleep
in here, does she?
You don't mind sitting
across the table
from your wife and my husband?
I don't think about it.
They're both good company.
They are.
I suppose that has
nothing to do with this.
This didn't happen.
Just in here.
You're right.
( news playing on radio )
I only said yes because
Arnold wants to impress you.
Megan keeps asking.
- She likes you.
- And I like her.
It's 9:00.
I have to go.
You love to go.
Well, it's nice to know
that no matter what
we got something done today.
You found it in the cookie jar.
I have money,
I just never have money.
Mr. Mathis and Mr. Gifford
are waiting outside.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because they don't
want to come in.
Look, Phyllis,
I've had their job.
I know. And you've
had my job, too.
So you know it wouldn't hurt
if you were to act like--
if you were as encouraging
to them as you are to me.
Why don't you just get me
whatever book you read
and save me
these little lectures?
More coffee?
She's ready for you.
Have a seat.
- No, don't.
- What's wrong with them?
The strategy is Clearasil
stops blemishes
that keep you from having fun.
That means no one
should be having fun.
Okay.
So we'll just start over.
Just a minute.
I don't want you to think
that just because
I have high standards
that means I'm not happy
with you.
Especially, you know,
the way you are.
The way you are
has nothing to do
with the fact
that the work needs work.
Thank you, Coach.
We'll try our best.
There you go.
( door closes )
Please, dear,
don't linger in the hallway.
Your coat?
Can I get you something to eat?
I think I have some peanuts
and some cheese crackers.
No, thank you.
Perhaps something to drink?
I have bourbon, vodka,
gin, champagne.
I shouldn't.
I started on the train.
( laughs ) What kind
of music do you like?
None for me.
Is the temperature okay?
Yes.
Hmm.
It's been known to get hot.
I'm fine.
That's a pretty shade
of lipstick.
Thank you.
I'm glad you came.
Come with me.
DDB managed to get me
on the 50-yard line
for the Giants game
last November.
If we'd done it,
the Steelers would have won.
- ( laughs )
- We'd do anything to make you happy.
I'm not unhappy with DDB.
No notes.
When I presented the numbers
for my division,
Timmy came up to me and said,
"How the hell did you do that?"
So I figured he's in town,
why not take him
to the horse's mouth?
The past few years,
I've overseen ketchup
to great success.
But how long before
we're old news?
And, hell, when I saw baked beans
have a sales spike like that...
Raymond has demanded
our best work.
So then the question is
what can we do for you?
What can we do for ketchup?
Let me know.
A pleasure to meet you, Timmy.
This isn't an official visit.
I'm just dropping by.
Ken, Don and I have a little beans
housekeeping, if you don't mind.
I'd love to walk you out.
Raymond, we're grateful
for this opportunity
and consider it
quite a vote of confidence.
It is, but I don't want you
to waste your time.
Well, then if nothing else,
we appreciate the introduction.
I'm not winking here.
There is to be
no further communication
with Timmy or his division.
I'm sorry, Raymond. Did we
do something to upset you?
You guys are doing
a bang-up job.
And now that polished Polack
wants the same.
I'll take that drink.
No one's paid attention to me
in nine years at the company.
They gave me a suicide mission.
Vinegar, sauces,
and baked beans.
And then in my moment
of triumph, he comes up to me
and he didn't say,
"How did you do that?"
He said,
Smug bastard.
I taught him
everything he knows.
- We understand, Raymond.
- No, forget it.
I know ketchup's
the gold standard,
but after all we've been through,
I'm sure I don't need to tell you
that if you so much as send
him a ham at Christmas,
well, I'd rather retire
than watch that guy
screw my girlfriend.
- Let me walk you out.
- No.
If he lingered at all,
I'm gonna pretend I'm on
my way to the men's room.
I'm sorry.
What a waste of time.
I don't know.
We met Timmy.
- He's certainly going places.
- Raymond's so weak.
But he brought his business here
when we were barely standing.
It's Heinz Ketchup, Don.
It's the Coca-Cola
of condiments.
I know.
But sometimes you've got to dance
with the one that brung ya.
I'm afraid that's the end
of your toilet paper.
This place could really use
a woman's touch.
You think so?
I might come to town Friday.
There's always
a sale at Macy's.
We'll see.
Okay, I'll call you.
If I let the phone ring once and
hang up, then you'll know it's me.
Don't do that.
Well, I'm going to park my car
in front of the driveway
instead of in the driveway.
Then you'll know
I'm thinking of you.
That's sweet.
I really have to get back.
Can you move it along a little?
You told me you were
washing these by hand.
- No wonder the elastic is shot.
- I forgot.
And you forgot you left
the vacuum on the terrace.
I was changing the bag.
And you forgot not to use
S.O.S on the Teflon.
I mean, I leave
for work every day
and I wonder what you're
going to ruin in my house.
I'm so sorry,
Mrs. Draper.
( sighs )
I don't know how to do
this, but you're fired.
I'll get my things.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
I am. I walked in on it and
then I didn't want to pretend.
( crying )
Are you okay, honey?
No.
Come on.
Let's go upstairs.
I don't wanna go
up until she's gone.
Let her alone
with your silverware?
So, after weeks, I finally showed him
the picture of my mother...
but that's not enough, because
her name has been changed in the will.
That is quite a story line.
Well, you asked.
- It's meaty, isn't it?
- It is.
I just wish watching TV
during the day
didn't make me feel so guilty.
I had a miscarriage.
All right.
I will watch.
( chuckles )
No, in real life.
Two days ago.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't
burden you with this.
No, you obviously need to talk.
I was sloppy
in Hawaii--
the time difference, vacation.
Now I feel so guilty.
May I?
What do you have
to feel guilty about?
What did Don say?
I didn't tell him.
It's been a hard
couple of weeks.
Oh.
I don't know why.
I mean, I do.
You were raised
the same way I was.
I keep hearing
Sister Eugenie in my head.
I'm such a horrible person.
You're not a horrible person.
No, I am.
I mean,
to be pregnant now
at this moment?
I didn't know
what I wanted to do
and I was so relieved that I
didn't have to do anything.
I see.
Has this ever happened to you?
About a year after
I had Mitchell.
So I certainly understand
some of what you're feeling.
But the rest of it,
no.
I'm sorry.
Really?
Because I was raised
the same way,
so I would never even
consider that my decision.
You really believe that?
I do.
And I think you do, too,
or you wouldn't feel this way.
I just feel so shitty.
I'm sorry I brought it up.
( door opens )
Hello.
- Sylvia's here.
- I see that.
Hello.
I should be going.
You don't have to rush off.
- Have a drink.
- No, I'll leave you two alone.
- I fired the maid today.
- Good riddance.
Good night, both of you.
See you tomorrow.
- Excuse me?
- For dinner.
Oh, of course.
Yes.
( door closes )
So send her in.
Sorry to bother you,
but this was on my desk.
Is it new?
There's usually a memo
for everything around here.
- What is it?
- It's Quest.
Feminine hygiene powder.
- Did I miss a meeting?
- "Proof points--
has baking soda, makes you
nicer if you're stinky,
kills overly
critical bacteria."
( laughs )
"Target-- professional
women and other Olsons."
Just give it to me.
Calm down.
I think this is somebody's
idea of a joke.
Of course, when you want them
to be funny they're useless.
Hello, gorgeous.
Hello, Herb.
Did you get
all gussied up for me?
No.
I had no idea you'd be
darkening my doorway.
When are you gonna
come out to the lot?
I told you, I'll let you have a
Jaguar for as long as you like.
I take the bus.
I know there's a part of you
that's glad to see me.
And I know there's a part of
you you haven't seen in years.
Herb!
There you are.
How are you today?
Toodle-oo.
Dawn on intercom: Mrs. Harris
is here to see you.
He's here.
Thank you.
- Who are you?
- I'm Bob Benson.
We've met before.
I'm part of the team.
Doesn't the elevator
go up to this floor?
( door opens )
Herb.
What brings you by?
I had some thoughts,
the complexity of which
could not be expressed
over a telephone.
What is it you want?
Well, you guys are gonna
make some fancy-schmancy
Michelangelo TV spot
and the dealers
are gonna foot most of
the bill for running it.
That's how it works.
Well, I'm the only guy actually
out there selling hamburgers
and I want people to know there's
a hamburger store in Englewood,
not England or in your mind.
I don't want another thing with some
shmuck sitting on his lawn mower
fantasizing that he's gonna win
the Grand Prix driving a Jaguar.
I need foot traffic.
Get 'em in the door
so I can move metal.
Well, you, along with
the factory guys,
have already signed off on
the work as well as the buy.
I just think there should
be retail radio as well.
You know? "Does your
car sound like this?"
Voom voom! "Does your
wife sound like this?"
"Ooh, I love your car."
And then you say
the phone number twice.
Wonderful.
We'd love to increase
the exposure of the campaign.
How much more
would you like to buy?
There's no increase.
Just adjust the proportions.
I think we should spend
60% of the money
on local dealership ads
instead of national.
Herb, that would really take a
bite out of the national campaign.
Well, if you say so.
Unfortunately,
it's not up to me,
so I am suggesting
that you recommend
this plan to all of us.
Why don't you recommend it?
It's your idea.
Because it's an idea
you had yourself.
And Lord knows
you're so damn persuasive.
We understand, Herb.
See how easy that was, Bob?
Bob, why don't you
show me the sights?
You must be like a kid
in a candy store around here.
- You can't shake his hand?
- He didn't seem interested.
In fact, the only thing he seemed interested
in was gutting our national campaign.
You do realize that defeats
the purpose of having Jaguar?
So he's demanding
and unreasonable.
How does that make him different from the
other people who walk through that door?
I wish you would handle the clients
as well as you're handling me.
( door shuts )
- ( phone line ringing )
- Stan: Jimmy's Condom Warehouse
where the rubber meets the road.
Jimmy speaking.
( laughs ) You want a drink?
No, thank you.
I'm quite comfortable.
How was your day, honey?
Okay.
Okay?
What happened to Shangri-La?
Chaough quit crapping out
snow cones?
Everyone hates me here.
Well, that was bound to happen.
You worked for me
and you like me.
- I worked with you.
- I was tough but fair.
Oh, speaking of people
who hate you,
Raymond J. Beans came in today
and pulled a real boner.
Go on.
He brought in
the head of ketchup.
He's obsessed with that man.
Yeah, he should be.
I met him.
So Raymond makes
the introduction
and then, according to Ken, ketchup
leaves, but Raymond lingers
and he says he's gonna
kill the account and himself
if they even talk
to ketchup again.
Why'd he bring him in?
Because he's Raymond.
He's a fraidycat.
And-- here's the part
that's gonna make you happy--
Kenny spent two weeks
telling everybody
how he was getting ketchup.
( laughing )
Okay, Tuesday morning
is perfect.
What? Oh, yep.
We'll have your wig
ready then, ma'am.
You're allowed to make
personal calls after 5:00,
especially if they
make you laugh.
My friend Stan was
telling me a funny story
- about one of our old clients.
- What happened?
Oh, it's complicated, but basically
the guy from Heinz Baked Beans
hates the guy at Heinz Ketchup.
Of course he does.
Well, surprisingly,
beans brought ketchup in
for a meeting at the agency
and everyone got excited,
and then unsurprisingly
he sent ketchup out of the room
and told everyone
it was just for show.
So he's unhappy?
He's not going anywhere.
Probably misses you.
( laughs ) No.
I assure you, he doesn't.
There's nothing like things going
badly when you leave, is there?
Sorry I'm late.
3rd Avenue was a parking lot.
I'm not feeling well.
That's not where it hurts.
Oh.
Did you cancel?
No, I thought I'd feel better
by the time you got home.
We're supposed to be there
in 15 minutes.
They're probably already there.
I know, but I don't
want to pretend
like I'm having a good time
and it's too late to cancel.
- They'll survive.
- I want you to go.
I want you to have fun.
Okay.
But you go right to bed.
Yes, sir.
( TV playing )
Brenda:
Go away!
Somebody help me!
- ( turns TV off )
- What on earth is that?
- ( pounding on door )
- Somebody, please!
Somebody help!
- Oh, my goodness!
- What happened to you?
Doug: Hey, Campbell,
she's your problem now.
I'm sorry. I didn't
know where else to go.
- He was chasing me.
- Close the door.
Hold this to your nose.
What the hell happened?
( crying ) I'm so embarrassed.
We had a terrible fight.
- I'm going to call the authorities.
- No, please.
Well, then I'm taking you
to the hospital.
- I'll be fine.
- No, what do you think you're doing?
You're not going back there.
Peter, go to Tammy's bathroom.
There's some cotton wool.
I'll be right back.
I hope you haven't
been waiting long.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I was late, too.
They already gave us
a hard time.
- Where's your wife? - She sends her
regrets. She wasn't feeling well.
- That's too bad.
- You look lovely.
Let's get you a drink.
We'll get the waiter
to do the whole show again.
I'm afraid there's only
going to be three of us.
- Don?
- Old-fashioned, please.
Subito.
Well, the North Koreans
really took that ship.
And the Vietcong, did you see
them storming the embassy?
I haven't followed it today.
- We got it back.
- Still...
these two little pissant countries
handing our head to us.
Well, I don't know
about the ship,
but from what I've read, the embassy was
an ambush that broke the cease-fire.
We gave them peace
for their sacred holiday.
Next thing we know,
they cut us to ribbons.
Reminds me of Cuba.
No one took
Fidel Castro seriously.
We thought he was Señor Wences.
Turns out he was
George Washington.
And they say surgeons
are arrogant.
Who says that?
You know we're losing the war.
Wouldn't know it
from looking around here.
Yeah, it's something, right?
- You are Dr. Rosen?
- You see this service?
Yes. We'd like to hear
the spiel again.
Uh, scusi.
There is a telephone call.
( groans ) Really?
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna take this as an
opportunity to powder my nose.
( line ringing )
There's no answer.
Is there anyone else?
Family?
My sister's back in Oneonta.
My mother's in Boca Raton.
Well, you can't go home.
We should find a hotel.
Let's try some ice.
What did you say to him?
Hello? Yes.
Do you have any
vacancies this evening?
Take me to the city.
I want to be with you.
Absolutely not.
Very good.
Thank you.
The Old Greenwich has rooms.
- Can you take me there?
- We'll get you a taxi.
Nonsense.
I'll drive you.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I'll run you over.
Brenda, dear, let's go.
It's best this way.
Emergency averted?
Unfortunately, no.
Sylvia and you
are having dinner.
- This is silly.
- We can do this another time.
I'm not taking my foot out of
the door of this restaurant.
Order for four
or they'll punish me.
Good luck.
What are you having?
I don't know
that I'm that hungry.
You want another glass of wine?
Should we get a bottle?
You're drinking something else.
I don't want you to have wine
if you don't drink wine.
I'm not gonna drink
a whole bottle, obviously.
I don't know
how obvious that is.
Another glass is fine.
So what looks good here?
Depends what you want.
Well, I'm hungry,
I'm in a good mood,
and I'd like some guidance on the
Italian menu from my favorite Italian.
I didn't cook it, so I can't
speak to its quality.
You think I'd like
eggplant rollatinis?
For the lovely signora?
- We're not ready yet.
- Yes, we are.
Can she have
another glass of wine
and could you give us a minute?
Certo.
What's wrong?
How could I possibly know
what you like to eat?
I thought you were
looking forward to this.
I don't know what we're doing.
We're having dinner together.
And I'm sorry, but I guess
it was a stupid idea to think
we could spend time together
outside of your maid's room.
Just because they cleared
their place settings
doesn't mean we're alone.
Is that what's bothering you?
That everything
worked out perfectly?
And you enjoy how foolish
they both look.
Now I understand.
You want to feel shitty
right up until the point
where I take your dress off.
Because I'm going to do that.
You want to skip dinner?
Fine. But don't pretend.
"Casta Diva - Norma
1st Act" playing
And what if she had come?
The evening would be
just the same,
only it would be
someone else's dress?
What are you talking about?
Weren't you the one who told
me you were drifting apart?
Isn't that what this was about?
I want you.
- I want you all the time.
- ( moans )
But if you've suddenly decided you
want something more than that,
well, then,
that's news, isn't it?
So, have you decided?
I don't know.
Have you?
He'll have the steak diavolo
and I'll have the branzino.
Anything to start?
No. We're in a bit of a hurry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I have no right to be jealous.
This is just us here tonight.
We have to be careful.
We can't fall in love.
It won't be so French anymore.
( moaning )
( gasps )
Hi, this is Johnny Carson.
As you know,
this is the usual starting time
for "The Tonight Show."
And tonight my guest is the New Orleans
district attorney Mr. Jim Garrison,
who is with us to discuss,
as he puts it,
some new and vital information
concerning the Kennedy assassination.
But because of the critical
war situation in Vietnam,
especially around Saigon,
NBC for the next 15 minutes
is going to bring you a special
news program via satellite.
So stay with us.
We'll return in 15 minutes
with our guest
Mr. Garrison.
( door opens )
Did you have fun?
Arnold had an emergency,
so Sylvia and I
had to eat enough
to keep him
in good graces there.
Are you feeling better?
I need to talk to you.
What's wrong?
Um...
Well, I had a miscarriage
a few days ago.
Are you okay?
Did you go to the doctor?
Yes.
How far along were you?
Six weeks.
I wish you would have told me.
I guess I didn't know
how you'd feel.
I didn't know what you'd want.
Megan, you have to know
I'd want what you want.
Is that what you want?
Of course it is.
But I don't know that it's even
the right time to have
a conversation about it.
And I guess that's why
I didn't tell you.
But I should have.
Yes, you should have.
Do you want to have
that conversation?
Whatever you want.
Now I can go to sleep.
Good morning.
- Where's Tammy?
- Leticia took her to the park.
Oh.
Well, I'm off.
Couldn't you just pretend?
I let you have that apartment.
Somehow I thought
that there was some dignity
in granting permission.
All I wanted was
for you to be discreet.
She lives on our block!
Trudy, don't jump
to conclusions.
There's no way
for me to escape.
To not be an object of pity
while you get to do
whatever you feel like.
I have never said no to you.
That is not true.
What are we doing out here?
We're done, Peter.
This is over.
You want a divorce?
I refuse to be a failure.
I don't care
what you want anymore.
This is how it's going to work.
You will be here only when
I tell you to be here.
I'm drawing a 50-mile
radius around this house
and if you so much as open your fly
to urinate, I will destroy you.
Do you understand?
You know what?
You're going to go
to bed alone tonight
and you're going to realize you
don't know anything for sure.
I'll live with that.
( door slams )
- Good morning.
So far this is all we have,
but I want you to find out
everything you can on Heinz Ketchup.
What?
And this is not a joke.
No.
I can't do that.
Why not?
It's a little bit of a secret,
but it turns out
they're taking meetings.
I told you that secret
and I shouldn't have.
Look, everybody's gonna know.
We just know a little sooner.
My friend told me that
in confidence.
He's not your friend.
- He's the enemy.
- Well, he doesn't know that.
Maybe you need a friend
more than you need a job.
I didn't know that.
I'm in advertising.
It's not that.
It's just that it was
a private conversation.
What are you, his priest?
This is how wars are won.
Your friend's mistake
was underestimating you.
I hope ketchup makes the same
mistake so you can blow their mind.
Herb: So, correct me
if I'm wrong, Pete.
I certainly will.
You're suggesting
that we forego
this sparkling
national ad campaign
in favor of hard-driving sales
ads at the local dealer level?
Not exactly. We will still
have a national presence
with the sophisticated work that
Don presented and you loved,
but we will increase
sales with a surgical
and financial focus
on local media.
Well, that sounds good to me. Of
course, I'm a little bit biased.
Why would we do that?
We feel it's best to have a
plan that creates customers,
not just aficionados.
Don, are you really in favor
of throwing
our emphasis into radio?
Well, it's hard to argue
with a more direct appeal
to customers.
I mean, we can artsy up
the image of Jaguar,
make it look romantic
and stylish,
but isn't it better
to tell people
who are actually
in the market for a car
that a Jaguar is available?
I think
it's an exciting new angle
to use direct sales
on a luxury vehicle.
I mean, forget about radio.
How about a mailer
or a circular
in the Sunday paper?
I don't know if that's
what we had in mind.
So this is your recommendation?
I think it's better to
think about someone
in New Jersey
driving in their current car
and hearing that
right around the corner
there's a Jaguar to buy
at a low, low price.
I bet the numbers would support
that don't they, Harry?
That...
is really a statistics game.
You know what?
I will have to double-check.
Look, why are you
limiting yourself?
Wouldn't you rather
cast a wide net
so you can sell Jaguar
to the average guy?
You know, truck drivers,
housewives.
John: I was under the impression
from the work you showed us
that this would be
a more elegant approach
that made the Jaguar seem rare
because, let's face it,
the gentleman who buys our car
needs to be of some means.
I am 100% positive
that this approach moves cars.
And not just Jaguars. This is
proven to move all kinds of cars.
Hell, even used cars.
Am I wrong, Herb?
No, he's right.
It moves cars.
Gentlemen, we appreciate
the recommendation,
but we believe we should
stay with the proposal
as first discussed.
And as persuasive
as these arguments were,
that is how we will
continue to proceed.
Let's not be too hasty.
Maybe we should listen to them.
At least give it some thought.
Herb's right.
We still believe this is our
best chance for success.
Fellas, this is gonna work.
I'm sorry, but this is
our final decision.
Thank you very much.
What the hell was that?
Herb, we couldn't
have pushed any harder.
You pushed,
then you let Don talk.
You should know better.
The guy's not a salesman.
That was the deftest
self-immolation I've ever seen.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I didn't know you were
capable of being that bad.
- What was that in there?
- I wasn't feeling well.
Something about that guy
makes me sick.
Don't be cute. I still
have his spit in my hair.
Why can't you
just follow the rules?
I did. I did exactly
what he asked for.
Not in spirit. You know damn
well that is not what he wanted.
Why do we care
what that guy wants?
- Because he's a client.
- Our client.
And so we just keep
saying yes no matter what
because we didn't say no
to begin with?
You know what this is?
It's Munich.
You guys are always
talking about Munich.
What the hell
does that mean anyway?
It means we gave the Germans
whatever they wanted
to make them happy, but it
just made them want more.
Well, who the hell won the war?
As my mother used to say,
your options were
dishonor or war.
You chose dishonor,
you might still get war.
That was Churchill.
- ( vacuum humming )
- ( knocks )
First one in, last one out.
I don't know how you do it.
Me either.
Well, it can't be that bad when
you're doing something that you love.
I'm glad it looks
like that to you.
I spent a year in finance
watching identical men
in identical suits
sneak drinks out
of a desk drawer
while counting
other people's money.
What house?
My family's been at
Brown Brothers Harriman
for three generations.
You make this
look a lot better.
It's all about what it
looks like, isn't it?
I'm going down to the deli.
Can I get you something?
No, thank you.
Bob.
My wife asked me
and I seem to have forgotten.
Could you pick me up
some toilet paper?
I got it, chief.
( sighs )
( knocking lightly )
- Good evening.
- ( TV playing )
He's home. You can't knock
on the door like that.
I was taking the trash out
and you left it open.
Tomorrow morning.
"Just a Gigolo"
playing in background
( people laughing )
( indistinct conversation )
You're a dirty little spy.
I dropped a penny.
You got your own room.
That's how things
work around here.
♪ If you admire me ♪
♪ Hire me ♪
♪ A gigolo ♪
♪ Who knew a better day ♪
♪ Just a gigolo ♪
♪ Everywhere I go ♪
♪ People know the part
I'm playing ♪
♪ Paid for every dance ♪
♪ Selling each romance ♪
♪ Every night
some heart betraying ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ There will come a day ♪
♪ Youth will pass away ♪
♪ Then what will they say
about me? ♪
♪ When the end comes, I know ♪
♪ They'll say just a gigolo ♪
♪ As life goes on ♪
♪ Without me ♪