Previously on Mad Men...
Heaven's a little morbid.
I didn't get to Heaven.
Something terrible
has to happen.
I'm sorry my accomplishments
happen in broad daylight
and I can't be given
the same rewards.
I'm sorry, but your
name escapes me.
I'm Bob Benson.
I'm upstairs, in Accounts.
You know,
but just in the outfield.
What did they say?
It's just like last time, no.
We cannot go on like this.
This is what Chevy
is paying us for.
It's not our clock,
it's theirs.
So what's another weekend?
( theme music playing )
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
This convention instructs the
Democratic National Committee
that it shall
include in the call
for the 1972 convention
the following addition
to section one--
quote, it is the further
understanding...
Megan: Should I pack
your swim trunks?
What?
( sighs )
They're supposed
to be debating the war.
They can debate it all they want,
they just can't come out against it.
Then no one will vote
for Humphrey.
Over Nixon?
Well, they can't have the whole
convention without talking about the war.
30 seconds after prime time,
they'll start the debate.
( TV off )
Cops have been hassling
protesters all day.
Also not in prime time.
You're so cynical.
Come over here.
Come with me.
We'll go back to Disneyland.
From what I remember, something
amazing happened there.
- I made the biggest mistake of my life.
- That's true.
You know I'd come if I could.
You'll have fun.
Just stay away from actresses.
Do they have them out there?
I hate actresses.
( chuckles )
Kenny said that this time
he went to a floor
in the Chevy building
he'd never been to before.
He said it was
like "Get Smart."
Just a bunch of doors
in procession.
And he met the man he believes to be
the source of our current torture.
- What's his name? - Same as the
rest of them-- Jack something.
Apparently
his feelings were hurt
because we haven't
kissed his ring.
Well, I'd be happy to go
there and help soften him up.
- If anyone's going, I'm going.
- But you can't
because you're going to Los Angeles for--
what again?
I'm going to pay them
a visit immediately.
We don't want to miss our flight.
Are we going?
Right after
the partners' meeting.
Oh.
Are we done here?
Sweetheart, could you step out?
This morning I received
an envelope addressed to
Sterling Gleason and Pryce.
- From who?
- It doesn't matter.
They don't know our name because
we don't know our name.
Aren't we SCDPCGC?
Not officially.
Well, I'm tired
of the conversation
that goes along
with my business card.
I know that no one has observed the
memo that requested specifically
that all seven letters be used
when answering the phone.
Sterling Cooper Draper Pryce Cutler
Gleason and Chaough? It's a mouthful.
SCDPCGC is a mouthful.
But CGCSCDP is not.
- I don't agree.
- We've each lost a partner.
Why don't we each
lose a letter?
SCDC.
- What do the Cs stand for?
- Not Campbell.
Cooper and Cutler.
Pardon me?
Well, SCDCC sounds like a
stutter and looks like a typo.
Very well, if it puts
this to rest,
I will gladly withdraw my name
along with the other deceased
parties in this conversation.
Bert, don't be a martyr.
Want to throw away
both of these brands?
Just leave it alone. We'll
get a bigger front door.
Well, of course you like it.
You're at the front.
- I'm at the end.
Well, I move to table this.
You have fun in Detroit.
And you have fun
with Manischewitz.
Any special instructions?
Yeah, the guy in charge, just
pick an eye and stick with it.
Very well, but it's my belief
that any further delay
in choosing our name
will take it out of our hands
and leave it up to the world.
You know Sunkist is still
only doing print work?
I'm cutting you off.
- You're two ahead of me.
- No, from work.
Come on.
We're executives.
Leave the drudgery
to Ted Chaough
and the rest of the underlings.
Did you prepare at all?
Sunkist, Carnation,
the avocado people.
My biggest job
in these meetings
is to keep them from saying
"golly" too many times.
Carnation has 27 million
in billings.
I don't think the guy in charge
ties his pants with a rope.
I didn't say that. But I guarantee
they all have a certain regard
for two gentlemen
from the big city.
You mean they won't trust us?
I mean they don't
trust themselves.
I don't know if you realize it,
but we are big New York admen
from an agency with seven
letters in its name.
That means under
no circumstances
are you to trot out that drawl
you do when you've had too many.
Be slick. Be glib.
Be you.
Well, I'm usually informed.
We're conquistadors.
I'm Vasco da Gama and
you're some other Mexican.
We're gonna land there, buy whatever
they've got for the beads in our pockets.
Our biggest challenge
is to not get syphilis.
Cathy.
Another round.
And send one to the pilot.
( sighs )
Man on radio:
...hours of acrimonious debate,
the Democratic National
Convention has rejected a plank
advanced by Democratic doves
calling for an unconditional
end to all bombing
of North Vietnam.
What's going on?
They delayed till noon
and then they rejected it.
- Rejected what?
- The peace plank.
Chance to have a platform
against the war.
Uh-huh. Then let me
clarify my question.
What's going on with
the work for Manischewitz?
Because you're for the war.
You know there's 200
body bags every week.
Figure out how to get
into that business yet?
( chuckles )
I refuse to be distracted
by events in which I have no
actual stake or participation.
How could you say that?
Because he doesn't
have any sons.
I served in the Air Force.
Did you?
You're disgusting,
you know that?
This whole thing works because
people like you look the other way.
- Ginsberg.
- My politics are private.
But that presentation isn't.
Now, are you gonna hide your
dawdling behind your outrage?
You'll have your work
and you know it.
You can go in there and take
credit for it like you always do.
Be friendly and charming after you've
stuck your fascist boot on my neck.
So I'm a fascist because
I gave you a deadline?
No, you're a fascist
because you love business
and you hate everything
else-- freedom, blacks, Jews.
This is my stop.
I hate hypocrites.
Like hippies who cash checks from
Dow Chemical and General Motors.
You rooting for the Soviets
in Prague, too, you Nazi?
Michael, what are you doing?
That man is your boss.
Why are you always down here?
Go back upstairs!
You're a truncheon, Cutler.
Thanks for making that worse.
Hello, Ted.
- You busy?
- Extremely.
I think you know
I'm a man without regrets,
but I do believe
we fired the wrong people
and I'd like to remedy
that immediately.
Jim, I think you're upset.
No, because I have a solution.
I think we should remove
the rest of their people
while Sterling, Draper,
and Crane are in California.
Just lock the gates and leave
Pete Campbell as the doorman.
- What happened?
- Do I need cause?
How about failure
to complete tasks
coupled with gross
insubordination?
Maybe part of it is you
keep seeing this agency
as our people and their people.
Well, how about your people
and my people?
Do I have permission
to clean out creative,
starting with
Mr. Ginsberg?
Jim, he's lightning
in a bottle.
You have to start holding
hands, starting with his.
Because I'll be in
Detroit tomorrow
and you're taking him
to Manischewitz.
Sterling's client
and Draper's boy.
I'm the world's
most expensive babysitter.
That's the spirit.
I suppose I wouldn't be a
good friend if I didn't ask--
is Kate pulling
her weight around there?
She arranged this.
She did.
Well, Kate told me that
you're the kind of woman
who won't just tell me
what I want to hear.
I hope she didn't make
any promises.
My wife always says
I'm the kind of man
who doesn't like
to ask for directions.
My new job has me
face-to-face with ad agencies.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Kate said you were divorced.
I am.
I forgot.
( laughs ) What does that say?
( sighs )
Anyway, what should
I look for in an agency?
Oh, well, a good agency
should tell you.
Go ahead.
Me?
( laughs )
That's why I'm here.
Yes.
Of course.
Well, I suppose we don't
just lean on
stylish creative,
or market research.
We listen to the client.
Doesn't everybody do that?
Despite your modesty,
you already know
that the way to get invited
into people's homes
is through their TV sets.
Media placement is part
science, part courage.
Anyone can tell you not to run
makeup ads during football.
The trick is finding
your customers
in places you hadn't
thought to look.
Harry Crane is a wizard.
They use a computer
the size of this restaurant.
And what is your job there?
I'm in charge
of thinking of things
before people
know they need them.
- I've got this.
- Come on.
Please, this is what
I get paid to do.
I was just coming to see you.
But you're not going anywhere.
I was, but then you appeared.
At the risk of playing defense,
I only interfered
because I hate disrespect.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
- Neither do I.
- Hmm.
I believe in you, Bob.
But you're untested.
Manischewitz,
tomorrow afternoon--
think you can handle
the parties involved?
Michael Ginsberg
or the clients?
I don't see much
difference, do you?
I think I can
keep the volume down.
Excellent.
I welcome this chance to shine.
( film flapping )
- Are you on a deadline?
- No, do you need me?
I need a drink.
Okay.
I had this lunch
my friend Kate set up
and I think
it's a potential client.
- I know he is.
- Who is he?
The new head
of marketing at Avon.
( laughs )
I thought it was a date, but
it turned out to be better.
- I love Avon.
- Of course.
And you'd be perfect for it.
It's just-- I don't know
what to do with it.
He's leaving town tomorrow.
So set a meeting.
I know I have to,
but Don's not here
and I don't want to get
kicked off the diving board.
We'll take it to Ted.
- He'll know what to do.
- What did I just say?
He's not like that.
And what do I ask for?
I don't know.
You'll be the account man
if that's what you want.
Trust me,
he loves new business.
He doesn't care where it comes from.
Let's go.
- I told you I wanted a rental car.
- They insisted.
- Ted, do you have a minute?
- Just barely.
Well, it's kind of urgent.
Joan has a solid lead.
He's leaving tomorrow.
We need to set a meeting.
Good for you. Get Pete
Campbell down here.
- Who is it?
- It's Avon Cosmetics.
- It's Moira. Can you send him down
immediately? - Very groovy.
The new head of marketing, he's a
friend of a very close friend of mine
and I just wanted
to introduce him to Peggy.
- Peggy'd be perfect for it.
- You rang?
Pete, as head
of new business--
Since when?
I don't want that.
Joan has a lead
for Avon Cosmetics.
Peggy's creative. He's leaving
town tomorrow. Reel him in.
Moira:
Fly safe.
Avon Cosmetics.
That's Fortune 500.
What's his name?
Andy Hayes.
My friend Kate just moved there from
Mary Kay and she sent him my way.
Tell me everything you can about him and
set lunch tomorrow for Peggy and me.
I should be there.
Joan, this is how
things get botched.
First, account man
and creative.
Then if all goes well,
next trip
he visits the office
and you show him around.
I think he'll be expecting me.
Shouldn't Joan
make the introductions?
I don't understand
what the problem is.
You're going to make the call
and tell him how important I
am and how exciting Peggy is.
And then we're going to tell
him how essential you are.
Don't worry.
You'll get all the credit.
Clara.
Are you coming?
Hey, I let you sit up front.
Sorry about that.
You need a hand?
What?
There's no one
from GM in Los Angeles?
Get rid of that car.
And get us something
with a roof.
Don't want to show up to a
meeting with bugs in my teeth.
So, you want to take
a dip in the pool
or should I
just wait in the bar?
- Both have attractive scenery.
- Where's the bellman?
Mañana, Don.
Everything's mañana here.
I'm gonna take a shower. You can
wait in the bar if you want.
I'm gonna get room service.
We're gonna go
to the Sunset Strip,
watch a girl dance in a cage.
That you heard?
Save your strength
for tomorrow.
Going to a party in the hills.
- It's very hip.
- Beverly Hills?
No, the hills. And
it's movies, not TV.
My friend in development at CBS says
it's going to be crawling with moguls.
- Jesus, it's hot here.
- It's a dry heat.
It's a dry heave.
Come on, Don, let's go to the Strip
right now and get some dinner.
No, I'm gonna turn in.
Tried to sleep on the plane, but
somebody wouldn't stop talking.
Don't worry, I got this.
TV anchor: This is on tape since again
we're not able to cover it live.
The tape you're about
to see was made
about 30 to 40 minutes ago.
( people shouting )
( horns honking )
( people screaming )
It was supposed to be a
nonviolent demonstration today.
And one will never know
what it was
that made it become violent.
( phone ringing ) This is directly
in front of what advertises itself
as the world's largest
and friendliest hotel.
Where at this hour
people stand around
and sit in their rooms
with handkerchiefs...
- Hello.
- Are you watching this?
Yeah.
It's hard to believe
no one got killed.
That the only measure?
Can you imagine a policeman
cracking your skull?
It would change
your whole life.
Honey, they're throwing rocks.
They're prepared for trouble.
Reporter: In some
places, plainclothesmen
are helping make the arrests.
On the bright side, Conrad Hilton is
probably in that hotel right now.
Don't make jokes.
Megan, you can't even vote.
But I live here.
I'm sorry.
I want you to be careful.
This could easily start a riot.
Don't worry.
I'm not going anywhere.
Really?
You can if you want to.
I miss you.
Go for a swim.
It always makes you
feel better.
( people chanting )
The whole world is watching.
Reporter: There's a break
in the arrests now...
We should hang up.
This is costing a fortune.
Try and get some sleep.
You, too.
Bye.
( chuckles )
( sighs )
So you came after all.
Pete couldn't make it.
What? How the hell are
we supposed to do this?
Don't worry about it.
Coffee, please.
I didn't know Ted was going
to handle it that way.
Well, he did.
And Pete's not coming...
because he wasn't invited.
- You can't do that.
- I did it.
If you want to leave, go ahead.
I hope I didn't keep you waiting,
but I was trying to check out.
See, if you were a client,
you could have left your key
at the desk and we would
have attended to that.
Andy Hayes, Peggy Olson.
She's the dynamite
in our creative department.
I don't know about that.
Tomato juice
and coffee, please.
I didn't want you to leave New
York without meeting Peggy.
Her expertise has been honed
by her work on Clearasil,
Pond's Cold Cream, and most
relevant, Belle Jolie lipsticks.
I almost worked there.
Do you remember
"Mark your man"?
I do.
I grew up in an Avon home.
Our lady was Gladys Bowman.
She was very elegant.
My mother would vacuum
the drapes before she came.
Then my sister and I would
fight over the catalogue.
- In fact--
- In fact, all women
have some kind of personal
connection to Avon.
But that doesn't turn into
advertising, now, does it?
Why don't you tell us
your biggest challenge?
We're here to listen. It's just
hard to hide our enthusiasm.
It's true.
Well, they don't
bring in a new guy
unless they're expanding
or sales are flat.
I'm afraid it's the latter.
Women are working.
They're not home.
And hippies don't wear
makeup at all.
I'm not sure if we should
try to be "groovier"
or nostalgic.
We're somewhere
in between right now.
That's about it.
Peggy?
Yes, Joan?
What do you think
of your current work?
Besides the fact
that it's not working?
It's okay.
We didn't do it.
I don't know how
to describe it.
Would you say it's
unintentionally old-fashioned?
Yes.
Yes, I would.
I'm sure you've thought
of this already,
but Joan and I were saying
how convenient it would be
to have the Avon lady come to
the office maybe during lunch.
Well, they're not resistant to
trying that, just to advertising it.
There's no doorbell
in an office.
I only saw a little bit
of it on the morning news,
but I'm sorry I missed
Humphrey's acceptance speech.
I assume he was
high-voiced and desperate.
You're the exception. Early numbers
look like over 80 million people.
Look, we all hated what we saw,
but the Democrats are dead.
It's over.
Not just now, maybe forever.
- ( laughs )
- ( door opens )
As you were.
Nobody get up.
Nonsense, Jack.
Great to see you finally.
Roger Sterling, Don Draper.
George was just laughing that these
riots gave Nixon the election.
I don't think that's
anything to smile about.
And although this boardroom
has been the site
of many casual
political conversations
among better men than us,
this is a business meeting.
You're right, Jack.
Last night was disgusting,
seeing those long-haired
fools shame this country.
You think Richard Nixon
is going to fix that?
I think he's a patriot.
Dutch Reagan is a patriot.
Nixon is an opportunist.
Now why don't you gentlemen
tell us how it's possible
to devote your energies
to our nutritious
and delicious Instant Breakfast
and Life Cereal
at the same time?
Well, Jack,
your powdered milk
and dairy products
have had a long, successful
relationship with breakfast cereal.
There's no reason
to give that up.
And as far as we can tell,
Instant Breakfast has
a different target-- adults.
They don't eat cereal.
They eat bacon and eggs.
And this is healthier,
easier, and instant.
And what if we were to say we
find the conflict unresolvable?
I'm sorry to interrupt, but we
discussed this over the phone.
This is about a whole different level
of exposure for your products.
All of them. You should
be in game shows.
You should have a presence
on Saturday morning.
Where we'll sit right next
to one of your cereal ads?
- Don?
- Look, Jack, George,
I'm sure you know that we would
do anything to make this work.
We believe that strongly
in Carnation.
We believe in the wholesomeness
of both your intentions
and your products.
To be frank,
we've worked with
New York firms before.
We come in in the
morning, try to get you,
everyone's at lunch.
And when people
are at lunch around here,
that's just the time
we get a message from you.
And with it comes an attitude
as if to say we're not
working hard out here.
I can assure you, it is
very much to the contrary.
Look, we're sorry your
last girlfriend hurt you.
We're in your office right now.
Tell us what you have in mind.
What is going on? I just handed
you the business of your life.
What is going on?
You just threw it away.
Morning, ladies.
- Morning.
Stop that.
What exactly
are you planning to do?
Are you trying
to intimidate me?
No, that's always
been impossible
because that would require
respect for me or what I do.
I know you want this,
and now you can't have it.
You could've,
but now you can't.
It's mine. And I've
been doing account work
in one form or another
since the day I started.
But you're not in
that department.
I never said that to you
when you stopped filing
and started writing copy.
Yes, you did.
Every day.
And it was worse
because you made me feel
like I couldn't do it.
I know you can do this.
So why do you think
I should give it away?
I worked my way up.
You were so brave,
letting Don carry you
to the deep end of the pool.
I never slept with him.
Congratulations. You
really are just like them.
I'm sorry, but I never thought I
would be in the position to say,
"Joan, you've made
a mistake."
I have to do it myself, Peggy.
This is the only way
I could do it.
Because all that matters now is who
has a relationship with that client.
Who is the client
going to call?
Well, I am sick to my stomach
thinking about what you're going
to say when they find out.
I'll be fine.
Man on record:
Gentlemen, after all,
this business of selling
narrows down to one thing.
Just one thing.
Seeing the people.
( phone rings ) Show me any
man of ordinary ability
who will go out
and earnestly tell...
Benson here.
( doorknob rattling )
- Ginzo, you have a visitor.
- Where is he?
Michael?
- What's wrong?
- I feel sick.
I got diarrhea.
My mouth is dry.
I didn't sleep last night. I
don't want to go. I'm not going.
Oh, sure.
You'll talk to him?
I love you, you know that.
You're a mother hen.
- Michael, you look fine.
- Stop calling me Michael.
We have to go.
It's a very important meeting.
And I don't say
that to scare you,
I say that to inspire you.
I'm not scared.
I'm a thug.
I'm a pig.
I'm part of the problem.
"Now I am become Death.
Destroyer of worlds."
Come on, buddy.
You're not Death.
You got a little stage fright.
Maybe you smoked
too many funny cigarettes.
I never touch that stuff.
It makes you crazy.
I know what you're feeling
and it's fear.
But not fear of failure,
fear of opportunity.
I can't watch this.
Look, you can't put yourself in the
right place at the right time.
You got to be in the right
place all the time.
Listen, man, I can't turn off
the transmissions to do harm.
They're beaming them
right into my head.
Damn it, there is
no harm in this!
Manischewitz are good people.
They're your people.
And they sell wine for religious
ceremonies of all faiths.
Now pull yourself together
and be the man that I admire.
( sighs )
Tell me the truth.
Are you a homo?
There's that sense of humor.
I would like
to have her for lunch.
Well, don't have
Harry Crane set it up.
He got us very high up
with three major companies.
You forgot because Chevy
fell in your lap,
but big accounts require
a golf and dining offensive.
When are we gonna do that?
Next time.
Harry, what did I say
about that car?
( "Harper Valley P.T.A." playing )
Well, Cindy, these are
my friends Don and Roger.
A pleasure.
There's tacos
and booze outside.
If you want a joint, try the
candy dish on the coffee table.
Or make a friend.
You look familiar.
You'll have to do
better than that.
As you can tell, there's
a different protocol.
I look forward
to figuring it out.
Just let me make introductions.
They don't take business cards.
Who is that?
I know him.
Earl Rice from Kodak.
He's their studio rep.
I don't think he was there when you were.
I know he never goes east.
No, not him.
Isn't that Danny?
Jesus, he is everywhere.
It's Daniel J. Siegel now.
( chuckles ) Danny Siegel?
Producer. And that's Irwin Fields.
He's at Paramount.
What's he doing here?
Probably trying to buy
one of Danny's movies.
Not him.
Roger, Don. Where've
you been all my life?
Come on.
This will be fun.
Daniel, my man.
Did we interrupt?
It'll keep, man.
Danny. What are you
up to these days?
Taking care of business.
That was Irwin Fields.
And this is just Lotus.
She's from Sacramento.
So how do you know Stephen?
Oh, I've known
Stephen a long time.
Whereas Danny we've only
known for a very short time.
( laughs )
I know these lugs back
from my days in advertising.
More like a day, wasn't it?
Hey, it wasn't my bag.
I had to quit.
You didn't quit.
You were fired.
( laughs )
Harry, why don't you
introduce me to the bar?
Actually, Danny and I
used to be related.
Daniel.
His ex-wife
is still my cousin.
You'd like her.
She's about your age.
There are small differences.
Tiny things you'd notice.
( chuckles )
Stephen.
I was just telling Lotus
here how I'm finally
making a picture
with a major studio.
We're gonna do
"Alice in Wonderland."
And Stephen over there
works for Ben Kalmenson,
president of Warner Brothers,
who's also here somewhere.
He took over from Jack Warner.
You know what, Lotus?
I'm gonna introduce you.
Nice rapping with you, Rog.
So most of the pictures don't
have a lot of score right now.
They like pop songs. You know,
kids want to hear a hit.
I think ads are going
that way, too.
What kind of ads you do?
Well, we represent
Chevrolet, Mohawk Airlines.
- Where are they?
- The northeast.
Samsonite luggage.
Life Cereal.
Well, if times get tough,
I'm gonna look you up, Donny.
I dig jingles and I hear
the bread's out of sight.
Don, there you are.
Ben Kalmenson's leaving.
I think he's heading to a party in the canyon.
Should we follow him?
- You know Ben?
- Do you?
( "Rag Ahir Bhairav" plays )
I was looking for the restroom.
Well, there's an extra nipple
here when you come back.
It can wait.
Take off your shoes.
Do you like hashish?
I don't know yet.
Man: Hey Man, are you the
guy who came in a taxi?
You don't talk much, do you?
In fact, I'm wondering if
you're hearing a word I say.
Are you tripping?
I've done it five times.
So if you're trying
to see through me,
just know that
I am this handsome
and this rich.
Don't worry
about your hang-ups.
Lotus, let's split.
( laughs ) Together?
She's gonna crash
in my guesthouse.
- Until her audition?
- It's up to her, man.
I'm sure it is.
Lotus, honey,
there's no reason
to start at the bottom.
Yeah, maybe he can help
your dream come true
of having your lips
on the side of a bus.
What are you gonna do when you fail here?
Keep going west?
Japan's a long walk
for those little legs.
Lotus, let's go.
You're lucky
I hate violence, man.
Really? I love it.
You know, I was a boxer.
There's nothing like
finding that magic spot
that'll drop a man
to his knees.
You know, unless he's
already starting there.
- ( groans )
- ( Lotus giggles )
Hated to do that.
( groans )
Mmm.
( "Found Love" playing )
I'm really thirsty.
There's a pool full of
water out there, Don.
I told you, that's not my name.
There you are.
Honey, I--
you're here.
Is that your old lady?
It's cool.
It's California.
Everybody shares.
What are you doing here?
I thought I'd surprise you.
How did you find me?
But I live here.
I quit my job.
I couldn't bear to be apart.
And I want to have enough love
for my other surprise.
Really?
What do you think it is?
A second chance.
Come with me.
Everybody's looking for you.
I heard you were here.
Are you in
the movie business, too?
I'm not pitching
for the Dodgers.
What happened?
I'm not at liberty
to discuss that.
My wife thinks I'm MIA,
but I'm actually dead.
How come you didn't
get your arm back?
Dying doesn't make you whole.
You should see
what you look like.
Roger:
Man overboard!
( muffled screaming )
( coughing )
He's fine.
Everybody back away.
( coughs )
( panting )
- Is it real? - They took me to breakfast
on the way to the airport
and told me Jack signed off.
And he's high enough at Chevy
he doesn't have to run it
by the whole outfit and--
- ( intercom buzzes )
- Moira: Bob Benson to see you both.
They finally let me
see the car.
They had clay models.
It's not a dog.
I don't mean to interrupt.
- But that's what you're doing.
- Come on in, Bob.
I just got off the phone
with Manischewitz.
Apparently they're
putting us in review.
- What happened?
- They barely listened to the presentation.
It was a courtesy. They haven't
liked the work for months.
Shit!
Weren't you there?
Well, I thought it was
high time we embraced Bob.
He was going to go.
I talked him out of it.
Roger Sterling let you
watch his dog and it ran away.
Bob, we appreciate you
handling this like a man.
And as a reward,
Ted and I want you to familiarize
yourself with Chevy.
We just found out
we're moving to the next step.
We're going to need
more than Ken in Detroit.
That's music to my ears.
Welcome aboard.
They shouldn't have
gone to California.
We're going to bring in Avon.
They gave us Chevy.
Throw in losing
Sterling's account,
I think we have
a lot of good news.
They're not gonna think that.
You're splitting this place
and not in half.
We'll give them something
to take their mind off it.
What do we have?
( coughs )
You caught a cold
in California.
I don't know what happened.
I usually feel
better out there.
You've got to stop
talking in the past.
You know what I learned?
New York is the center
of the universe.
We could send
a landing craft out there,
but they don't understand
what we do.
Or they understand it
thoroughly.
My shrink says
the job of your life
is to know yourself.
Sooner or later, you'll start
to love who you are.
And apparently
I'm a curious child
with a full head of hair
and a thriving business.
And you're a terrible swimmer.
( chuckles )
- ( knocking )
- Come in.
Mr. Campbell wants to see you
in the conference room.
Oh.
And what is it regarding?
Avon sent over a box
of samples to the girls
and Diane opened it, not me.
I'll be right in.
Everyone out!
She'll be right in.
This shouldn't be in here.
What the hell is this?
I guess Avon's serious.
Oh, they're serious.
When the hell did you have
a "productive breakfast"?
You and Peggy ditched me.
Peggy didn't know.
There was some confusion
and then it was too late
and I thought since
I mixed things up--
There was no confusion.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- I bet you are.
Were you coming in here to
celebrate what a fool I am?
You upset the girls. They
have nothing to do with this.
So, you opening up
your own agency?
Ted assigned her.
Isn't the point
that Avon's happy?
Oh, I bet you're
making him very happy.
Because it's better
than being screwed by you.
We'll see what Ted
has to say about this.
Let me handle Ted.
It's too late for that.
- Ask her. - Did you meet with
Avon and not invite Pete?
It was very
last-minute.
Peggy, this doesn't
concern you.
Pete:
This is unacceptable
and I'd like to know what you
have to say for yourself.
- Does this color look good on me?
- Shh!
What would you like
for me to say?
Joan, you of all people
can't plead ignorance.
She's going to say something
about her client
and her connection.
And, honestly, I take
no issue with that.
But what we have here is a breach of the
fundamental rules of this business.
An account executive
signs business
and they send their junior
to maintain it.
To maintain their boss's
relationship.
The entire thing falls apart
if I send you
to the store to get cake
and you eat it on the way home.
Did you really try
to squeeze him out?
Pete: You have nothing
to say for yourself?
It's a revolt.
- Excuse me.
- Meredith, not now.
"Joan, Andrew Hayes from Avon
is on the phone
for you."
Oh, it just gets better.
What are you waiting for?
Go take it.
- Pete: That's it?
- Possession is nine-tenths of the law.
Only where there is no law.
Pete! We're all
working together.
All agency business
is your business.
Thank you.
You better hope
he really calls.
( door closes )
Welcome back.
How was your trip?
If you don't mind,
this is urgent.
Aren't you glad you
didn't go straight home?
I have to tell you that in your
absence, things have become quite dire.
- ( intercom buzzes )
- Dawn: Mr. Draper, the partners are here.
Come in.
Welcome back.
How was California?
It was a series of busts
and not the kind I like.
Well, we have a bit
of news concerning the firm.
- We should get Joan.
- No.
- Anyone else?
- No, thank you.
My visit to Detroit
was a success.
They finally signed off
on the strategy.
Even showed me
a model of the car.
That's a relief.
Good work.
Also, Joan's at the five-yard
line with Avon Cosmetics.
Joan?
Well, well, well.
While the cat's away...
Unfortunately, Manischewitz
has put us in review.
Ah, it's been coming
for months.
But that's not what
we're here to talk about.
We thought long and hard about what it's
gonna take to make this agency stable.
I'd like to offer what we believe
to be a deferential solution.
They want to call the agency
Sterling Cooper & Partners.
Well, we know you like it.
It would depend on Don, Jim,
and me all sharing the blow.
You're willing to do that?
It's the only thing that's
equally offensive to all.
SC ampersand P.
I can swallow it if you can.
I don't think
I should weigh in on this.
Good.
Then it's settled.
I'll get the art
department on a logo.
- Nice work.
- I had nothing to do with it.
Have a good weekend.
You have no problems with this?
Pete, we're in the same
boat and I'm fine with it.
Trust me, that name
is a consolation prize.
It's a gravestone
to our resistance.
You have no idea
what's going on out there.
This is not
the same business anymore.
If you don't like it, maybe it's
time to get out of the business.
Dawn, could you get
my wife on the phone?
What are you doing?
Working.
Give me that.
Hey.
( "Piece of my Heart" playing )
♪ Come on, come on ♪
♪ Didn't I make you feel ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Like you
were the only man? ♪
♪ Yeah, didn't I give you ♪
♪ Nearly everything
that a woman possibly can? ♪
♪ Honey, you know I did ♪
♪ And each time
I tell myself that I ♪
♪ Well, I think
I've had enough ♪
♪ But I'm gonna show you... ♪