Previously on Mad Men...
I've seen that look,
and he is in love with you too.
Nothing can happen.
We are going to
get Ocean Spray.
So you need to stop
chasing Sunkist.
Oh, God...
You make me sick!
Sally!
We want you to familiarize
yourself with Chevy.
That is music to my ears.
When there's true love,
it doesn't matter who it is.
I don't know where you've gone,
something has to change.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
I was waiting up.
I didn't want to wake you.
- Don.
- What?
I don't know what's going on,
but you have to pull back on
the throttle a little, honey.
Don, turn off the range.
Sorry, I forgot about them.
It's fine.
I want to make you
a real breakfast.
You look terrible.
So do you.
Just stay home today.
Can you do that for me?
Please try and sleep it off.
You want to quit
in front of Kenny?
He hasn't fired a shot.
Whatever you fellas want.
Kenny, you need
to discharge that weapon
before Ray turns us
into the Bataan Death March.
You see that tree over there?
Pretend it's Ralph Nerer
and let's go get a drink.
Wait!
Oh, shit.
In recent years,
crime in this country
has grown nine times
as fast as population.
At the current rate, the
crimes of violence in America
will double by 1972.
We cannot accept that kind
of future for America.
We owe it to the decent
and law-abiding citizens
of America to take
the offensive
against the criminal forces
that threaten their peace
and their security
and to rebuild respect
for law across this country.
I pledge to you,
the wave of crime
is not going to be the wave
of the future in America.
_
I suppose I'm supposed
to believe
that you didn't know
that she wasn't me
when you took her to the
boathouse and you had your way.
I'm talking to you.
Don't you dare ignore me.
A lot of people
laugh at the idea
of a girl playing the tuba.
- Hello?
- It's me.
Your girl said you were home.
I am.
If you're too sick to talk,
it can wait.
I can talk.
It concerns Sally.
What about her?
She's not coming
this weekend either.
Oh.
That's too bad.
Although you should tell her
if she does come,
I'm gonna be working
all weekend.
Why would I tell her that?
It could have been being
held hostage by that burglar
or the fight she had with
her friend after Model UN,
but she says she's not
going again.
What do you want me
to do about it?
I don't know that it's a
good thing or a bad thing,
but she wants to go away
to a boarding school.
I'll pay for all of it.
She has to get in, of course.
How much does that cost?
Eleanor, Henry's daughter,
went there and I think
she'll interview well.
She has good manners
with everyone but me.
She'll get in.
I don't know, Don.
It is Miss Porter's.
Jackie Kennedy went there.
You mean
Jacqueline Kennedy Onassis.
What kind of medicine
are you taking for this cold?
Formula 44.
Yeah, I bet.
Jackie did well twice.
So did you.
- I'm going to go.
- Betts...
will you tell her that Megan...
that we both miss her?
Of course.
Cranberry, Cran-Apple,
Grape-Berry,
that would be Cran-Prune.
Don't let the name fool you.
They're all delicious,
my friend.
Is that the line?
They are one dried
and one fresh fruit
for a new generation.
You want to use Vaughn Meader?
I thought they buried
that guy with JFK.
No, there was this old salt
who took us around the plant.
He had a heavy accent
and a red shirt.
Ted called him Rose Kennedy.
During all this levity,
did you mention that Cran-Prune
sounds like a glass of diarrhea?
When we agreed
to take the blends,
we agreed to take the names.
It's got less pucker
than the Cranberry,
but it's heavier
than the Cran-Apple.
That means
Cran-Apple is light.
Light.
- And Cranberry is...
- Sour?
- Bitter?
- Makes your teeth feel weird?
It's tart.
That's all they keep
saying about the berries.
Yes, they do.
You know, I hate to say this
again, but I got to take a leak.
Great idea.
Peggy.
You want to get some chowdah?
Thought you had to pee.
No, just wanted to see
if I could get him
to respond to an idea
that wasn't hers.
You look better.
Hello?
I can barely hear you.
Oh, hello, Harry.
What?
Listen, I wouldn't
bother you at home.
Obviously I'm on the Coast,
but I've got good news.
You finally found a hooker who
will take traveler's checks?
Why did I tell you that?
I got a packet at the desk and
then a phone call from Sunkist.
I told you to drop that.
Well, Jeffrey, the fat one,
he finally got a look
at the media plan
and suddenly
they're interested in TV.
They've called a meeting with
Sanford, who I think is a decider.
Don't do that.
Don, they're talking about two and
a half times the print budget.
We can't.
- Why not?
- Because we have a conflict.
Ted has Ocean Spray.
You should have
told them we withdrew.
Adios, Harry.
I really didn't want
you to work today.
Harry is such
a pain in the ass.
Let's get out of here.
That was really, really scary.
It was disturbing.
Hello.
Oh, hello.
That was quite a film.
It was terrifying, wasn't it?
Well, we were, um...
you know we're doing the St.
Joseph's spot based on it
and Peggy and I had an argument
about whether there was
a Japanese in the end.
You know, when Mia Farrow
walks in and sees the baby
and the devil worshippers
are there.
- There was.
- I know.
So you'd both already seen it?
Yeah.
But obviously she
remembered it better.
She wants a Japanese in the ad.
They always have a camera.
We're going to grab a bite.
Have you eaten?
I should get going.
I have a date.
Yes, well,
don't let us keep you.
So, Don, I see
you're feeling better.
I had to get him
out of the house.
We can still go eat.
I am supposed to throw
around a football.
- I should go.
- After you.
Oh, my God.
I would never live
in an apartment that old.
There's so many buildings
like that in Montreal.
It's creepy.
Don?
What?
I'm gonna have nightmares.
You know who's not gonna sleep?
Why are you
so interested in this?
You're not interested?
Honestly, I'm more
troubled by the idea
of using "Rosemary's Baby"
for a children's aspirin ad.
Why were they going
to the movies at 5:00?
They didn't think
anybody would be there.
You've been on a soap too long.
I don't know.
I guess.
What time is it in California?
Three hours earlier.
I need to make a phone call.
Okay.
What happened?
Come in.
What the hell happened?
I'm fine.
Well, obviously not.
I thought you were in Detroit.
I was.
I told them that
Cynthia was pregnant
and they took me out to
celebrate and they shot me.
- What?
- It's not funny.
Chevy is killing me.
I hate Detroit.
I hate cars.
I hate guns.
I don't even want
to look at a steak anymore.
The only way
to get through this
is to keep reminding yourself
it's a great account.
I'm gonna be a father.
- I'm gonna have a family.
- Pull yourself together.
Anyone here would trade
places with you in a second.
Did I tell you that
on the way to the hospital,
they tried to stop for lunch?
They're fat yahoos in cheap suits.
I'm done.
Are you entertaining this idea?
You'll be laughed out of this building
and then out of advertising in general.
It'd be a difficult transition.
Chevy won't like it,
but I think they're feeling
pretty guilty right now.
Well, if it's in your power...
and you're willing to give up
what goes with it,
I would gladly take your place.
What about your family?
Trudy and I are separated.
I only see Tammy
every other weekend.
She won't know the difference.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Yes, it's unfortunate.
I don't know what to say.
Say you'll back me up
and I'll be there for you.
Congratulations on the baby.
Thank you.
Is he ready?
- Morning.
- Hello.
We have what we think is some
pretty spectacular news.
Crane called from Los Angeles.
Sunkist finally looked
at the media plan
and enthusiastically embraced
a television campaign
to the tune of $8 million.
Great Caesar's ghost.
They don't care that we're
a month into Ocean Spray?
Harry said we'd resign.
Apparently they were excited
by the spike in color TVs.
Don told them that
was the secret. Color.
- When did you tell them that?
- When we were out there.
But they wouldn't
leave Harry alone.
You upset, Ted? It's almost
three times the business.
No, I just...
well, I'm dreading
making the call.
Well, I'll call Ocean Spray.
And the rest of our clients?
Someone has to let them know to
look out for a knife in their back.
You want to turn it down?
Absolutely not.
Don't be an idiot, Ted.
Stay out of this, Jim.
Forget about giving
someone your word,
which obviously doesn't
mean anything to you...
how does it look?
The right hand doesn't know
what the left hand is doing.
You're right.
We should work more together.
We have to. That's the
message from this.
Then it's agreed
that we have a more
coherent approach
to new business.
That means no more
surprises, Don.
You're right.
I apologize.
But it's a great account.
Can we celebrate now?
I think Peggy should be on it.
She has, you know,
juice experience now.
That makes sense.
What are you doing?
Getting ready to do
a little hunting.
What's going on?
Mr. Cooper wants to see you.
Let's find out.
That's a .22. It's not good for
anything but squirrels, you know.
Would you ever leave New
York, Annie Oakley?
- Hello, Pete.
- Hello, Bob.
Kenny, how are you feeling?
Better than I am right now.
Have a seat.
Well, shiver me timbers.
I'd laugh, but it hurts
like a son of a bitch.
For obvious reasons, Ken is
withdrawing from handling Chevy.
You sure you want to do this?
I'm positive.
Kenny, you know,
I once had a client
cup my wife's breast.
Lee Garner, Jr.
made me hold his balls.
Well, I'm not resigning Chevy.
I just can't be on the
ground there anymore.
Pete and I have
already discussed it,
and I will stay on the business in New York.
They'll want that.
I'd be lying if I said
I wasn't reluctant.
But I know Ken would do
the same for me.
Crocodile tears.
How quaint.
Look, I know
everyone's worried,
but Bob's going to be a big
help with the transition.
Anything I can do.
In all deference to the weeks
Bob spent trying
to develop ties with Chevy,
I think it's best
if I bring in my own team.
That's a dumb idea.
Any continuity
preserves the belief
that service has not changed.
It's nothing about Bob
in particular,
but isn't it better
to create the belief
that service has improved?
Pete, you're going to need to know
where the landmines are buried.
I'd listen to the cyclops, Pete.
I think maybe I'm keeping you
from discussing this freely.
I understand Pete's objections,
but I will do
whatever is decided.
Pete, there's nothing
to discuss.
I like Bob, Chevy likes Bob.
And if you don't like Bob,
we can find someone who does.
Of course.
By the way, thank you,
all of you, for having
this trust in me.
Is there a problem?
I don't want to work with you.
I don't want to stay
in a hotel with you.
- You're sick.
- Why would you say that?
So you didn't profess
your love to me?
Only my admiration,
which is waning quickly.
This is not about my own interests.
I care about Chevy.
You should watch
what you say to people.
Is that right?
Congratulations.
Can you believe this guy?
- So?
- So what?
Can I have one?
Are you anxious?
I expect you to sail
through this interview.
Jeez, I wasn't nervous
about it a minute ago.
I hope it doesn't ruin it
that I'm excited for you.
When I was in 10th grade,
my friend Annie left--
To go to Rosemary Hall.
I know, you told me.
Did I tell you
she hated her mother?
Good for her.
Is it about getting
away from boys?
If I say yes,
will you stop asking?
I'm proposing some reasons because
you aren't being very forthcoming.
Sally, I can turn
this car around.
I want to be a grown-up, but I know
how important my education is.
Oh.
Well, congratulations.
You log a few months on that,
you can work anywhere.
I'm not looking anymore.
So what is this?
That old joke
"Hell, I'm telling everyone"?
No, I'm calling on behalf
of a young account man
whom we love, but can't promote
because Draper doesn't like him.
So you're looking
for an account man?
You know you can't work here.
I'll be frank.
I got to get this kid
out of here
and he's not going
to call you himself.
I'd love to present
some concrete options to him
when I push him out the door.
I just need leads.
He doesn't have
to land anything.
He must be pretty good
if he's in your way.
He's eager to please.
Handsome.
His name is Bob Benson.
He has a blue blood connection
to Brown Brothers Harriman.
Beloit, Wharton. I'll send
over his personnel file.
And I'll send over a bill.
Make it an even grand.
Cash.
No, no, no, no.
_
- What going on in there?
- Someone's having a good time.
You do realize this is the best
picture these people will ever take?
We were thinking about putting
this old man in a wig
because he looks
so much like Ruth Gordon.
- Fill me in.
- That's a great idea.
The conceit is that it's shot
from the baby's point of view.
No, no, let's do
the ad for him.
Joan, come here.
Can I do it from here?
No.
So, Don, you are
the camera and the baby.
We might have the end of the basinet
right at the front of the frame.
Maybe see some kicking
toes under a blanket.
Should I get down
a little lower?
No, that's fine.
Okay, it's dark.
Fish-eye lens,
you're the baby.
Just, "Whaa!
Whaa!"
- You do that.
- Whaa! Whaa! Whaa!
Okay.
So there's a crowd.
Eight or nine people.
It's the whole coven. And there's
a crazy little old lady.
What you need
is a mustard plaster.
And then there's
this wrinkled old man.
You need a compress.
And then a Jewish
neighbor lady.
How about a bowl
of chicken soup?
Anyway, there's one
more of those, maybe.
Then they all start
crowding in on you.
And the Japanese
takes a picture
and the flash turns it white.
Then you see the beautiful,
radiant young mother.
You don't need anyone's
help but St. Joseph's.
Usually with things like this, it
depends on you knowing the movie.
But I think this
works on its own.
I told you it was good.
That's a lot of people.
You need to feel
the conspiracy.
You want me to come to casting?
Sure, but I'm just gonna watch.
It was all her.
Casting's on the West Side.
You should go.
That's a lot of people.
I didn't want to dampen
the enthusiasm,
but the approved budget
is $15,000.
There's at least $35,000
in residuals alone here.
What did
St. Joseph's say?
They haven't seen
the new budget.
So who's paying for casting?
We are.
But Ted seems confident
they'll be good for it.
So he wants to spring it on
them at the pre-pro meeting
after we're 10 grand
out of pocket?
I don't know, Don.
I don't tell him what to do.
And Diplomacy Club.
I don't know if she told
you in the interview,
but Henry thinks she can
be an ambassador one day.
It's heartwarming to see
such a proud mother.
Well, Sally going away
is going to be difficult,
but, of course, I wanted it
for myself way back when.
And in this day and age,
it's overwhelming
to raise a young girl,
let alone be one.
Beautifully put.
Now, Sally,
during your overnight
and tomorrow in class,
I want you to keep in mind, and
I'm sure your mother would agree,
this is as much for you
to find out about us
as it is for us
to find out about you.
Carla, could you fetch Millicent
Turner from study hall?
You have fun.
I'll be back
in the morning around--
2:30 would be perfect.
Thank you again.
Mr. Campbell, your
mother is here to see you.
What are you
doing here, Mother?
Josephine, you have
my phone number.
This doesn't concern her.
I'm here for my passport.
I'm planning a voyage.
And I spoke to Manolo.
I forbade you to see him.
Well, he's very upset
about the way
you're treating
his friend Bob Benson.
That Spanish fly.
Why are you still
in contact with him?
- I ran into him.
- Where?
I don't remember.
Tell Manolo that I almost
threw you down the steps
when you brought up his friend.
Peter, I am still your mother.
I don't have your passport.
I'm sure it's expired
like everything else you own.
Josephine!
You're endangering
your position.
So, this used to be
the living room.
And, of course, you have to walk
through my room to get to her room,
but we switch over
at Christmas.
I'd rather have
my own room, too.
Oh, hello.
You must be Sally.
I'm Mandy.
Move over.
Sally's family lives
in Rye and Manhattan.
Let me guess, dad's remarried,
mom's fat and sad.
No, they're both remarried,
but my dad's wife is my age.
Well, I'd like
to feel sorry for you,
but things are about
to get worse.
Don't you like it here?
You're not allowed
to talk anymore.
Our opinion is crucial
to your acceptance.
And I can't believe
no one told you
that you were supposed
to look after us.
You didn't bring a bottle
or some cigarettes at least?
I probably have some money.
You think we need money?
You should call your mother.
Tell her that you're useless.
I can get you
anything you want.
She keeps talking.
Now what do we want?
How was casting?
It was interrupted by a phone
call from St. Joseph's.
Did you send over a budget?
Yes, but relax.
I talked to them.
I played the bad guy.
They'll be fine.
No, they won't be.
They called me
at casting to stop it.
Now I have to turn
a no into a yes.
You were gonna have
to do that anyway.
I couldn't even tell Peggy.
Did you tell her
how expensive it was?
It's great work
and you know it.
St. Joseph's has been doing
the same ad for 20 years.
They're bread and butter.
Why did you pick them to push?
They kept asking me for their
"plop plop fizz fizz."
And all of a sudden
she comes up with this.
She can smell the Clio, Don.
Remember your first big ad?
She has her heart set on it.
It's okay, Ted.
I get it.
You're right.
They're coming in tomorrow.
Just back me up on this?
Of course.
I've got to go
over that budget.
Yeah, she stayed skinny,
but her breath smelled
like vomit all the time.
I think it's time for
you girls to go to bed.
You hemmed your skirt.
My friend Sandy used a stapler.
Then by the time she went home,
her legs were all scratched.
Stand still.
Sally, you there?
Hello.
That was pretty fast.
Hey.
I'm Mandy
and this is Millicent.
Hold on, do you
have a rope for him?
Millicent, go get him.
Go around the front.
Nice digs.
I'm Glen, by the way.
Did you have trouble
finding us?
Rolo's driven by before.
Then I just looked for Snoopy.
Do you want a cigarette?
No, but I wouldn't
mind a drink.
Rolo brought
something to smoke.
How you been?
How are you folks?
Can we drink it straight?
I know how to make
a Tom Collins.
- She's too much.
- She's okay.
I don't think anyone saw us,
but we should keep it quiet.
I'm Rolo, by the way.
Nice digs.
What about the proctor?
The housemother's
a booze fiend.
I'll save some for her.
I want to get stoned.
I need a surface.
Here's looking up
your old address.
Hello?
Look at the two of us,
burning the midnight oil.
Something wrong? Did the
messenger find you okay?
I'm gonna need more than this kid
Bob Benson's personnel record.
Might as well
be written in steam.
What do you mean?
I don't even know
if the name is real.
I don't know where he went to
college, but it wasn't Beloit.
I tried a buddy at Wharton,
he said maybe he's just
telling people Wharton,
so he's gonna check the whole
University of Pennsylvania.
But it's tough when I don't know
if he's really 28 years old.
The most interesting is the
Brown Brothers Harriman job.
You told me that.
I got that from him.
Well, I have a friend there.
Turns out they all
remember Bobby.
He's from West Virginia.
Parents are brother
and sister or something.
He was a manservant
for three years
to a senior vice president.
He took him to
Europe on the Queen Elizabeth.
Are you kidding me?
He had three references,
two nonworking numbers at K&E
and a live one at Cunningham.
They said he just
disappeared one day
with an electric pencil sharpener
and the Christmas card list.
So what does that mean?
Mostly that his only
job opportunity
was someplace dumb enough
not to ask any questions,
and so far,
that's just you guys.
I'd offer to return the money,
but I would file this
under valuable information.
Yes, of course.
I've never seen
anything like this before.
I have.
You can do that
in bed, you know.
Since seventh grade.
The Ro is from Ronnie
and the Lo is from Lowell.
So they just started
calling me Rolo.
And 'cause he rolls
a lot of joints.
Should I roll another?
Your friend bogarted the last
one and she didn't get any.
I'm really drunk.
You think Millicent's okay?
She always freaks out.
What if she runs
screaming down the hallway
and she thinks
her hair is on fire
and she's screaming, "Boy on the floor!
Boy on the floor"?
Do you two know each other?
I think so, but who knows?
I was reincarnated.
I came back as a fish.
You should read my diary.
Come on.
Ahem.
Nice shot.
I've got good hands.
Do you play basketball?
I've been with lots of girls.
I know what I'm doing.
What kind of music do you like?
I don't want to talk anymore.
What's going on, Sally?
You called us.
You made us drive
all the way over here.
Suddenly you don't want
to fool around?
Are you frigid?
Glen. Glen, come out.
Hey, come on.
You've got to relax.
What do you want?
He won't leave me alone.
What the hell, Rolo? I told
you she's like my sister.
I think you're
full of shit, man.
You just wanted the good one.
What is going on?
He tried to force me.
What?
Damn it, Rolo.
She's a lying little tease.
That's bullshit.
Keep it down.
Get off me, Bishop.
Are you suicidal?
I'm your ride home.
He'll be fine.
I got to go.
I don't want to hitch.
Are you all right?
- Nice meeting you.
- You, too.
I'm sorry.
Keep in touch.
How do you know him?
We grew up together.
You like trouble, don't you?
Good morning.
Are you joining us?
Ted wanted more firepower.
I thought I'd pitch in.
I don't understand
what happened.
Residuals. Can't let
them sneak up on you.
It'll be fine.
We always win this one.
Well, I see
everything's in order,
including our cookies
from Ferrara's.
Byron, you remember
Peggy Olson.
- Mr. Poole, nice to see you again.
- Byron.
And Don Draper, of course,
our other creative director.
Yes, and I'm sorry
about the phone call,
but it was a bit of a surprise.
But you're here and we are
going to set you at ease.
Now Ted and Peggy will take you
through the creative process
that resulted
in this ingenious spot.
I know what it is. I bought
it the day I heard it.
I just paid a lot less for it.
Well, as a concept
becomes more developed,
expenses can mount.
We want to do this right.
The cost is still a fraction of the
business we believe it will generate.
Ted, with all due respect,
it's not your job
to promise sales.
It's your job to deliver work
for the budget agreed to.
It turned out to be
more people than we thought.
That's why we sent
the budget over.
We didn't want there
to be any surprises.
But this is worth the money.
But this is a surprise.
We agreed to 15,000
and it's 50.
You said specifically
that you wanted
something contemporary
with a sense of humor,
something that wouldn't
make young parents
feel like old people.
This does that and more.
That's not a reason.
Well, it should be.
We have enough of a history that
you should trust my judgment.
No, I want a reason.
I'm entitled.
You know the raft of shit I
caught when this budget came in?
Mr. Plough called me.
Uh, I hate to interrupt.
I think, Byron, I know
what you want to hear.
And it has nothing to do
with the shooting days
or the cast
because you've had
a long and fruitful
creative relationship together.
I think, and correct me
if I'm wrong,
that when you say
you want a reason,
you want to know why
we would push you like this.
It would help.
Well, the truth is
that I don't think
Ted wants to say.
'Cause it's, well,
it's a little bit personal.
In fact, it's very personal.
I'm not sure
I know what you mean.
Yes, you do.
Are you okay, Ted?
I, uh...
It's okay.
Tell him, Ted.
You don't want to say anything?
All right.
I'll tell him.
It's hard for Ted to say,
but this was
Frank Gleason's last idea.
Really?
Yes.
I'm afraid we've gotten
a little sentimental.
Damn. You should
have told me that.
I guess I was--
I don't know.
I, uh...
the factor didn't seem
relevant except to us.
I, um...
didn't want to lean on that.
Frank was a hell of a guy.
Best I can do is 25.
I don't care if you make these
characters out of cardboard
or turn them into cartoons,
you got to reduce the cast.
- That's all you get.
- I understand.
I'll show you out.
You should come to
Piping Rock this Sunday.
Get in a few holes
before all the grass dies.
We'll see.
Was that really necessary?
Leave us alone.
What was that?
That was the best I could do.
Do you want me
to tell him the truth?
What are you talking about?
You're not thinking
with your head.
That was your solution?
Try and embarrass me?
You're embarrassing yourself.
I know your little girl
has beautiful eyes,
but that doesn't mean
you give her everything.
That has nothing to do with it.
Come on, we've all been there.
I mean, not with Peggy.
Don't say that about her.
Ted, you're kidding yourself.
Everybody sees it.
Just ask your secretary.
Your judgment is impaired.
You're not thinking
with your head.
Good morning, Bob.
How you doing, boss?
I thought for certain you would
have brought me a coffee today.
You want me to go get one?
I've always wondered how
you were so expertly servile.
But now I know. It used
to be your profession.
What do you want?
Well, for one thing,
I wanted you to stop smiling.
You got it.
I've been awake all night
wondering what you do
when you're found out.
This must have happened before.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
- Who hired you?
- You did.
When?
I met with Ken.
You walked in,
complimented my tie
and walked out.
It was the best day of my life.
Well, your fraud
is irrefutable.
Can I have a day's head start?
Can you give me that at least
after all I've done for you?
You've done more for
me than I've done for you.
Spectacular.
You don't respond well
to gratitude.
So you're just going to run?
I don't believe you.
It terrifies me what
you could do in a day.
No, Bob, you're going to get
the benefit of the fact
that I've been here before.
I don't know how
people like you do it.
You're certainly
better at it than I am
at whatever I do.
But I would like to think
that I have learned
not to tangle with
your kind of animal.
I don't understand.
Where you are and who you are
is not my concern.
I surrender.
So what does that mean to me?
I want you to graciously
accept my apologies.
Work alongside me,
but not too closely.
Again, I don't understand.
Yes, you do.
I'm off-limits.
And please, can you find a way
to get your friend
out of my mother's life?
You know she's demented.
Manolo doesn't like women.
Make sure.
Sally.
What?
So you got what you wanted
and now you think
you can be rude.
Fine.
I'm not going to tell you
what Mrs. Beresford said
to me when you were
saying good-bye.
She talked to you?
She said you were
curious and bright
and received glowing reports
from all concerned.
But?
She said a girl like you
coming from this family
will have plenty of choices
and she hopes you choose them.
Oh.
Now get me a cigarette
and give me some details.
You want one, don't you?
Go ahead.
I'd rather have you do it in
front of me than behind my back.
I'm sure your father
has given you a beer.
My father has never
given me anything.
Did you tell him
that I need to see him?
- He went home.
- When?
Right after I told him
you needed to see him.
I know what you did,
I just don't know
why you did it.
Calm down.
You want to offer me a drink?
Pretend like you're
helping a little more?
Close the door.
Oh, of course.
You deserve privacy.
Look, there's still enough money for the ad.
We'll make it work.
Stop hiding behind the ad.
I know what you did.
I saved both of you.
How do you think it looks?
You hate that he is a good man.
He's not that virtuous.
He's just in love with you.
Well, you killed him.
You killed the ad.
You killed everything.
You can stop now.
I'm just looking out
for the agency.
You're a monster.
♪ My, my ♪
♪ The clock in the sky
is pounding away ♪
♪ There's so much to say ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
♪ A face, a voice ♪
♪ An overdub has no choice ♪
♪ And it cannot rejoice ♪