I don't know anything about you.
Previously on Mad Men...
I'm so sorry...
but you can't do this.
But I'm his father.
Find a way to get your
friend out of my mother's life.
Manolo doesn't like women.
There's this opportunity...
I guess you should have
Brooks talk to me about it.
Daddy!
Tell him, Ted.
I'm not sure I know
what you mean.
Crane called from Los Angeles.
Sunkist finally embraced
a television campaign
of $8 million.
It's a great account.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
- Morning.
- Don.
Can I have a moment?
I know you're deciding
who's gonna be on Sunkist,
so I wanted to volunteer.
You want to go?
You know that's a demotion.
You're gonna be in one
room with one account.
Thought about that, but rather than
just being a satellite office,
I was thinking I could
turn it into a little agency.
Los Angeles is not what
you see in the movies.
It's like Detroit
with palm trees.
So it's the frontier.
I don't even need
running water.
Just let me set up
the homestead.
You think you're asking
for a promotion,
but if you fail there,
you'll be out of advertising
because no one
takes it seriously.
All I'm saying is that
I think it'd be exciting
to build one desk
into a real business.
That's not the way I saw it.
That's not the way you saw me.
And you're gonna change that.
I've always felt you learn more from
disappointment than you do from success.
Well, I suppose I'm
becoming a very wise man.
- Hello, Daddy.
- How you doing, sweetie?
Oh? Wow.
He did get my good side.
He made it for
his generous Pop Pop.
Why don't we take you to lunch?
Come on, honey, I've taken
up enough of Dad's time.
I wanted to say thank you,
but obviously that
would be premature.
It's time to take a breather.
It's prudent investing,
it's not personal.
No, it is personal.
I'm your daughter.
What do I have to do to get on the
list of girls you give money to?
- Honey.
- Don't be a brat.
Brooks won't say it, but you're
taking food out of our mouths.
Don't even bother
to come to Thanksgiving.
The table will be empty.
Stop it.
I'll buy a turkey.
Sir, she doesn't mean it.
Mr. Cosgrove is here.
Send him in.
Name a chocolate.
What, like Hershey's?
Kenny, there's a reason
I'm standing here.
Hershey's Chocolate sent an RFP
out to the top 30 agencies
and all anyone seems to care about
is that we're in the top 30.
Because Hershey's
isn't serious.
They don't advertise.
They never have.
Mars bills at 10 million.
We think Hershey's is asking for
someone to talk them into that.
- What did Ted say? - He said his
plate is full and yours isn't.
But if you want to take the lead
on this, I think he'll follow.
I love Hershey's.
Get me in a room.
I'll get you what they sent me.
How's the Motor City?
I found a deli, but the
airport's like Calcutta.
Should be easier once I get an
apartment and stop commuting.
It's a hell of an account.
Don't I know it.
You're back in one piece.
Oh, one bigger piece.
I'm putting on weight.
- No one can see it.
- What's that?
- It's a racehorse.
- It's for Kevin.
Don't do that. He's just
gonna want a real one.
We'll see.
They just gave Bob one.
Well, you know what
they say about Detroit.
It's all fun and games till
they shoot you in the face.
Aren't we going to have dinner?
Eventually.
I'm worried.
Now they sent a letter.
Sally has to call them.
I'll talk to her
at Thanksgiving.
I told you,
we just have the boys.
Miss Porter's doesn't have
Thanksgiving vacation.
I read the letter.
The next step is a subpoena.
Okay.
Hello.
You can have one.
Then we're having dinner.
Sounds like a plan.
_
Could you get
Bob Benson for me?
Bob Benson's here to see you.
Really?
Send him in.
Were you circling my office?
- I don't understand.
- Sit down.
It occurred to me that you haven't
had a performance review.
Yes, I did. Didn't
Mr. Cutler tell you--
I don't give a shit.
You have a hand on
every rung, don't you?
I don't think I know
what you're talking about.
What are you doing
buying presents for that kid?
Leading that woman on? That's
another man's kid. You know that?
I assure you, I'm not
involved with Joan.
We're just buddies.
Joan's known for
having a lot of buddies.
They go fishing together.
What does this have to do
with my performance?
I'm asking the questions here.
I see what you're up to.
Look, I know that you're
concerned with your career
and Chevy's counting on you
being a family man,
but playing with
Mrs. Harris' feelings
is not the right way
to go about it.
- You're right.
- Damn it, Bob, I better not be.
I'm keeping an eye on you.
I appreciate your candor.
I'm looking forward to having
you out in Detroit, Bob.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
This is Sally Draper speaking.
It's Daddy.
What do you want?
I wanted to wish you
a happy Thanksgiving.
Okay.
I have to go.
Also, I'm calling
because--
well, I know it's unpleasant,
but you have to give a statement
regarding the burglar.
You need to make arrangements to
be out of classes December 1st.
My calendar is full.
Honey, you have to.
It's the law.
Well, I wouldn't want
to do anything immoral.
You know what?
Why don't you just
tell them what I saw?
Hello?
I've got it, Moira.
I have a personal plea.
Is this about Hershey again?
No, the folks from
Sheraton are in the lobby.
Royal Hawaiian.
We can't find Draper.
Again?
You don't have to listen,
but I have to say it.
We're all brothers in Christ.
That's His gift to us.
We're talking about a fellowship
far more powerful than drink.
Can you keep it down?
I'm trying to drink.
What's your occupation,
young man?
Staying out
of people's business.
You're not doing
a very good job of it.
I didn't mean to engage you.
But you did.
'Cause something's
on your mind.
You need to talk.
I don't.
What if I told you
that Jesus could offer you
not only eternal life,
but freedom from pain
in this life?
I'm doing just fine.
Nixon's the president.
Everything's back
where Jesus wants it.
He doesn't work that way.
'Cause He's mysterious.
He offer the same deal
to Kennedy?
Martin Luther King?
Vietnam, for Christ's sake?
Studies show Jesus
had a bad year.
Well, I'm afraid there's not one
true believer in that list.
What the hell did you just say?
I told you before to get
out and not come back.
- Be on your way.
- This is a house of sin.
You can't keep these girls
from the righteous path.
- They belong to the Lord.
- You're wrong on that.
You love the Bible 'cause you
can't get your dick hard.
Repentance is your salvation.
I'd tell you to go to hell, but
I never want to see you again.
The only unpardonable sin
is to believe God
cannot forgive you.
Excuse me.
Hey.
- I shouldn't be in here.
- You're right.
You punched a minister.
You should be in Rikers.
Sleep it off.
Absolutely not.
You'll have candy
at the theater.
- Oh, hello, Peggy.
- Hello.
Good night.
Come on, boys.
Let's go.
Clara, I'm going to give
my keys to the subletter.
Did you get me a room
at the Roosevelt?
Yes, and you just got
this telegram.
Open it.
Let's see.
"Need to inform you,
mother lost at--"
Oh, my goodness.
She fell off a ship!
What?
Get Bud on the phone.
_
I assume this has something
to do with last night.
Yes.
Megan, I--
Come over here.
Where were you?
I spent the night in jail.
Why are you laughing?
Because I realized
it's gotten out of control.
I've gotten out of control.
Sorry you had to
find out that way.
But I realized
something else, too.
I don't want
to be here anymore.
- It'll get easier.
- No.
I want to move to California.
What?
I don't want you to
give up your career.
I don't want you to think that.
I just can't be
in New York anymore.
I want to move to LA.
I don't--
I don't know what to say.
There have been all these
opportunities in Hollywood,
but I never even considered it
because I thought it
would make you go crazy.
But-- I mean,
wouldn't it?
What would you do out there?
Sunkist wants us
to have someone local.
It could be like
having my own shop.
A small team, a desk,
windows, some sunlight,
the ocean.
You'd throw
everything away here?
No.
It's an opportunity
to build one desk
into an agency.
We'd be homesteaders.
Really, Don?
What about the kids?
I'm sure they'd trade weekends
for a whole summer in LA.
We were happy there.
We could be happy again.
Is that a yes?
This was to be
a junior position.
Look, I'm the search party
and I decided we were
thinking too small.
Well, I think we can spare you.
I apologize for Sheraton, Ted.
That won't happen again.
That's my recommendation.
Of course I welcome
a vote on the matter.
How is it every decision
made in this place
is subject to 10 opinions
unless it's him?
What if we need him here?
It's California, not the moon.
There are telephones
and airplanes.
You're already doing
the heavy lifting.
This is good for you, Ted.
Honestly, I have
bigger problems than this.
Dawn, could you bring me
a carton of cigarettes?
You didn't think ahead.
You let her go and yet
you still need something.
- She's not going anywhere.
- But you are.
California, here you come.
You probably dictated
the memo right to her
and had no idea
she'd be affected.
Hold on a second.
I was gonna talk to you.
Really? Why?
You don't owe me anything.
I can probably get you
out there eventually.
To work for you?
No, I'd rather stay here.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna have that
sandwich on my desk.
I need to get to it
before you do.
Are you kidding me?
They got married?
What the hell was he
even doing there?
You should really get going.
You tell those Panamanian criminals they
should put Manolo under house arrest.
Or ship's arrest
or whatever it's called.
Fine, the brig.
Do whatever it takes.
- What's wrong?
- Get me Bob Benson this minute.
He was waiting for you. You're
late for your flight to Detroit.
Hold that.
- How are you?
- Not great, Bob.
- What's wrong?
Don't play dumb.
You don't know that your boyfriend
Manolo kidnapped my mother,
married her at gunpoint,
then threw her off a ship?!
Slow down.
I know you're exaggerating
and you're being hostile.
If you want to run,
I'd do it now.
Because you're
an accessory to murder.
I will never, ever let this go.
Manny wouldn't hurt a fly.
Even if he thought it was rich?
I swear I knew
nothing about this.
Ignorance will not be
a very good defense.
Get your own cab.
I'm leaving a little early
because I have plans.
I hope that's okay.
Yes, of course, dear.
Chanel No. 5?
It's all I wear.
Vixen by night.
I'm very excited
to see the scale model.
And I'm even more excited
to go to the London Chop House.
Bob loves it.
Well, unfortunately
Bob's not feeling well.
Pete, have you seen
this beauty?
No, not in the flesh.
That's a Camaro Z28.
Am I wrong?
No, you are not.
I like a man with
gasoline in his veins.
- You've got to try it.
- We can't do that in here.
I did.
Last week.
Shit, it's our floor. We can
do whatever the hell we want.
Keys are under the visor.
Go to town.
Bobby, you like to get
into trouble, don't you?
It's standard.
So is the solid-lifter
302 V-8.
Listen to that music.
That's good enough for me.
Ah, take it out.
Come on, boys, back up.
You looking for first?
It's written right on there.
I got it, Bob.
Jesus, you can't drive a stick?
We'll pay for that.
What are you doing here?
Waiting for you.
I told your neighbors
I was a cop.
You should go home
before they kill you.
I need to talk to you.
How was your date?
Is that why you're here?
I just want to know.
You didn't bring him home.
It was terrible, okay?
He works in finance
and ate with his hands.
Not that it's any
of your business.
I don't know what we're doing.
You don't know?
Why don't you have
your wife drop by again?
- I'd love that.
- She came in with the kids.
Why did she give me that
look on the way out?
Did you tell her something?
Do you two talk about me?
I don't know why
women do anything.
Why did you parade your ass
in front of my door
on your way out
to see another man?
I'm following your lead, Ted.
You let Don terrify you into
ignoring me and now you're here.
Because I don't want
anyone else to have you.
You should go.
Peggy, I'm going
to leave my wife.
Don't say that.
I'm not that girl.
I love you.
Hello?
I just got off the phone
with Miss Porter's.
Sally's been suspended.
What did she do?
She bought beer
using the name "Beth Francis"
with a false ID she'd made.
Kids do things, Betty. At least
they didn't kick her out.
Henry's already in Albany.
I'm supposed
to join him tomorrow.
I know you're picking
the boys up Thanksgiving Day,
but could you go
get her tomorrow?
They're holding her
in the infirmary, I think.
I don't want to have this
conversation with my mother-in-law.
I can't, Betty.
I have a big meeting.
She was drunk.
And she got other girls drunk.
I've done everything
I can think to do,
everything my own mother did,
and it doesn't matter.
The good is not
beating the bad.
She obviously needs
more than I can give her.
Birdie, this isn't your fault.
Don, she's from a broken home.
Pauline doesn't need to know.
I'll come get them
Thanksgiving morning
and then I'll come get her.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Is everything okay?
No.
Is there anything I can do?
Let's go to Hawaii.
For work?
For Christmas.
We'll come back with tans.
You should probably go home.
I don't want to.
I can say I worked
late on Hershey.
Don't you always
go home, though?
I don't want to sneak around.
I promise we won't have to.
I don't want a scandal.
I can wait.
Go.
No, you should go.
Oh, good, you're home.
Yeah, I didn't want
to wake you.
Come to bed.
Okay.
Oh, sweetheart,
you're working too hard.
What are you doing back?
- You haven't heard?
- Heard what?
I need a place to live.
I spoke with the GM
personnel department.
No, here in New York.
I'm done in Detroit and the
tenant's already moved in.
Oh.
Your brother's been trying
desperately to reach you.
Did they find her?
Well, let him know I'm back.
I'm gonna be gone
for a couple of hours.
Roger needs me to go to
the bank before the holiday.
You want someone on his desk?
I'm not sure he's coming in.
- I'm worried about him.
- What's wrong?
For one thing, Margaret and the
son-in-law are bleeding him dry.
Trust me, he loves it.
Well, he's forlorn.
I'd invite him to my place
for Thanksgiving,
but Ralph stopped drinking and you
know little Ralphie's spastic.
I think both
are too much for him.
Mr. Draper.
Mr. Chaough's here
to see you.
Send him in.
- I need to talk to you.
- I was thinking the same thing.
You should come to Hershey's
since I'm going to California.
That's not why I'm here.
Do you want something?
No, thank you.
I don't know how to say this,
but I want to go to California.
Really?
We can't both go.
I know.
I want you to stay here.
You put all that energy and
optimism back into the business
and let me go out there.
I'm the one who needs
to start over.
With Peggy?
No, with my family.
I don't understand.
Yes, you do.
It's my only chance, Don.
I've got kids.
I can't throw this away.
I can't--
I can't go on like this.
I'm sorry, Ted.
I wish I could help you.
I don't know what
I brought out in you,
but I know there's a
good man in there.
I need you to help me
put 3,000 miles
between me and her
or my life is over.
I didn't make
my decision lightly.
I need it, too.
And, frankly, they're writing
my wife off her show.
It's too late, Ted.
It will go away.
Will you have a drink
before the meeting?
My father was-- you can't
stop cold like that.
Every agency you're going to
meet with feels qualified
to advertise the Hershey bar
because the product itself
is one of the most successful
billboards of all time.
And its relationship
with America
is so overwhelmingly positive
that everyone in this room
has their own story to tell.
It could be rations
in the heat of battle
or in the movie theater
on a first date.
But most of them
are from childhood.
Mine was my father
taking me to the drugstore
after I'd mowed the lawn
and telling me I could
have anything I wanted.
Anything at all.
And there was a lot.
But I picked a Hershey bar.
The wrapper looked like
what was inside.
And as I ripped it open,
my father tousled my hair
and forever
his love and the chocolate
were tied together.
That's the story
we're going to tell.
Hershey's is the currency
of affection.
It's the childhood
symbol of love.
Well, weren't you
a lucky little boy?
Our company excels
in television
and we'll tell you exactly when
and where to tell those stories.
Sweet tales of childhood.
I suppose
we'd start with yours.
You can't just have that.
You got to pay us first.
And that's what's so exciting.
I'm sorry, I have to say this
'cause I don't know
if I'll ever see you again.
What?
I was an orphan.
I grew up in Pennsylvania...
in a whorehouse.
I read about Milton Hershey
and his school
in "Coronet" magazine
or some other crap
the girls left by the toilet.
And I read that some orphans
had a different life there.
I could picture it.
I dreamt of it--
of being wanted.
Because the woman
who was forced to raise me
would look at me every day
like she hoped
I would disappear.
Closest I got to feeling wanted
was from a girl
who made me go through
her john's pockets
while they screwed.
If I collected more than a dollar,
she'd buy me a Hershey bar.
And I would eat it alone
in my room
with great ceremony...
feeling like a normal kid.
It said "Sweet" on the package.
It was the only
sweet thing in my life.
Do you want to advertise that?
If I had my way,
you would never advertise.
You shouldn't have
someone like me
telling that boy
what a Hershey bar is.
He already knows.
Don's being modest.
But it's just this kind
of theater
that makes our work
so different.
Well, that's quite a story.
It was a pleasure meeting you.
We'd love to have a meal,
stop you from going to some
of these other meetings.
Ted...?
- It was a pleasure.
- Yes.
You're going to California.
Are you sure?
I want you to.
Thank you.
Dawn, get my things.
You know, you shit
the bed in there.
- I don't care.
- Was any of that true?
Yes.
I have to go home.
Happy Thanksgiving, sweetheart.
You, too,
Mr. Draper.
It occurred during the
Roaring 20s dinner dance,
so your mother likely went
missing over the promenade.
It's the only way she wouldn't
have hit a deck below.
No, where was the boat?
Oh, somewhere off
the coast of Martinique.
Did they check the beaches?
First of all,
there are a lot of sharks.
Dear Lord.
As I said, there's no impetus for
either government to investigate
and the SS Sunset Princess
in contacting you
has fulfilled its obligation.
It's 1968.
Surely you're not telling me
there's still some
international oceanic limbo
where murder is smiled upon.
I have a private investigator
prepared to board the ship
and locate your mother's
husband-- well, nurse--
Manolo Colón,
alias Marcus Constantine.
We also have wheels
we can grease in Panama.
No stone unturned,
no expense spared.
Ahem, let's say we want
the very best of everything.
What are the expenses?
To bring your mother's
killer to justice?
- Ballpark.
- It may take time.
Now that Manolo's aware of her limited
financial resources, he may bolt.
Alvin, I have another
call coming in.
Can we continue this later?
When you think about it,
it won't bring her back.
She's in the water
with Father.
She loved the sea.
I didn't want to disturb you.
What happened?
I don't even know
how to say this.
Did you tell Nan?
Did you confess?
I told you to wait.
No, that's--
I'm going to California.
You can stay here
and have your life
and your career
and let this be the past.
I can't believe Don did this.
I knew he wasn't going.
He knows it's Siberia.
- I can undo this.
- No, Peggy.
He gave up his spot for me.
Don?
I wanted this so much,
but I have a family.
The world out there...
I have to hold onto them
or I'll get lost in the chaos.
Oh.
You have to listen to me.
I love you that deeply.
I can't be around you.
And I can't ruin
all those lives.
Get out.
Just get out.
Someday you'll be glad
I made this decision.
Well, aren't you lucky
to have decisions?
Dawn just called. She said
there's a partners' meeting
tomorrow about California.
Attendance is mandatory.
9:00.
You have a meeting
on Thanksgiving.
They must really
want us out of here fast.
Honey.
You have to sit down.
Why?
Because something came up.
And it's not
just Sally, it's--
It's what?
I'm sorry, but we can't
go to California right now.
No, Don, that's--
that's not possible
because I already told Mel
and Jeff Hunter's got me a
bunch of meetings out there
- and the train is leaving the station.
- The agency decided that--
Fuck the agency.
I quit my job.
Megan.
You know what?
I don't even know why we're
fighting for this anymore.
I don't know what it is.
We don't have any kids.
You want to be alone
with your liquor
and your ex-wife
and your screwed-up kids.
Don't say that.
I love them to death.
I used to feel pity for them,
but now I realize
we're all in the same boat.
I know you're upset.
But I'm gonna be out there
all the time with you.
We'll be bicoastal.
Megan, I love you.
I can't do this.
I can't be here right now.
They'll deliver the lowboy
and the china closet
next Friday.
I couldn't take any more
and I already look like
the Beverly Hillbillies
with the chair
tied to the roof.
I don't want your
mother's things, Peter.
Well, Bud's not
getting everything.
And I'm not moving everything
to California with me.
It's fine.
I'll manage.
When are you leaving
for your parents'?
When Tammy finishes her nap.
When are you leaving
for Los Angeles?
Soon as I can.
I'd invite you, but I think it's
best you're alone right now.
- Don't be cruel.
- No.
It's going to take you a moment
to realize where you are.
You're free.
Free of her.
You're free of them.
You're free of everything.
It's not the way I wanted it.
Now you know that.
Can I go in and say goodbye?
I won't wake her.
I was told 9:00.
Right on time.
Impressive.
Don, we need to have
a serious conversation.
Where would you like to do it?
Is this about the Hershey
meeting yesterday?
Because I can explain.
Well, unfortunately,
that meeting
and most of your questionable
behavior is beyond explanation.
Should I sit down?
Yes.
I'm not going to defend myself.
I've tolerated plenty
from every one of you.
Don, there's no need
for defense.
This isn't a trial.
The verdict has been reached.
So what time
did this meeting start?
We think it's best
for you and the firm
if you take some
time off and regroup.
- How much time?
- A few months.
But the holidays are coming.
That'll take up most of it.
Did you tell Ted?
'Cause he can't go to California if
there's no one here to run New York.
Ted feels confident he can
oversee Peggy from LA.
He knows it's temporary.
I want a return date.
We can't give you that.
You all agree with this?
Try and see it from our side.
- Good morning.
- Hello, Don.
You're early.
Sorry about that, old chum.
This is Lou Avery
from Dancer Fitzgerald.
We've met.
Going down?
What's that?
We couldn't send it back.
- Hey.
- What?
Happy holidays.
What's he doing here?
I'm inviting you
into Kevin's life,
not mine.
Okay.
Hi, Bob.
Mom, Roger's here.
Gail got her hair done for you.
Hello, little man.
- You ready for some turkey?
- Yes.
Here, let me get it for you.
I thought you left.
No, I've got too much to do.
And you thought
you'd do it in here?
It's where everything is.
See you Monday.
Did they name it "Hershey"
because of the chocolate
or is the chocolate
named after the city?
There was a man named Hershey.
He made enough chocolate
to build a town.
Why are we stopping?
This is a bad neighborhood.
Come on.
This is where I grew up.
♪ Rows and flows
of angel hair ♪
♪ And ice cream castles
in the air ♪
♪ And feather canyons
everywhere ♪
♪ I've looked
at clouds that way ♪
♪ But now they only
block the sun... ♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com