Haley, hurry up!
You don't have much time, and
I made chocolate chip pancakes.
Mom, I'm not 12.
Dibs on hers.
Honey, you excited
about your first day?
You know what? I really am.
There's something
about going to work
that makes you feel like you're...
I don't know, worth something.
No offense, mom.
Listen... I wanna
give you some advice.
Do it fast.She's gonna be late.
Work hard.
Keep your eye on the ball.
Stay focused.
Never... Check it out!
Cam in overalls!
Mitchell sent me the same text!
Why "Look what you've done"?
Oh, because Cam is helping me out
with that baseball field,
and Mitchell hates it
when he gets all farmed up.
His turn-offs are farm, Fizbo,
And, worst of all, Farmbo.
Howdy, life pardner!
Well, I gotta go.
Don't wanna be late for my first--
Oh, my god! Why didn't
you guys tell me the time?!
So what do you think?
Can we turn this into a baseball field?
Oh, yeah. No problem.
You know, back on the farm,
I once turned an acre of corn
into a snowflake-shaped maze.
It'd still be there if
our neighbor Billy Bob Sheinberg
hadn't seen it from his crop duster
and said it looked like a swastika.
So how good's Luke's team anyway?
Well, you may have
seen them on youtube
under "Boy stuck in batting helmet"
or "Pitcher beans self."
But a few of them went through
puberty early this year, so...
They say it's because
of hormones in our milk.
But whatever it is,
they really jacked up.
Luke and Manny's team tied
for the final spot in the playoffs,
but since nobody was expecting it,
all the fields were booked.
The other team wanted
to settle with a coin flip.
We said "Rock paper scissors."
That's when talks broke down.
So what do you do
when you can't find a field?
You build one.
And we got the last laugh,
'cause guess what I found there?
Rocks, paper, and scissors.
- I see home plate up here.
- Mm-hmm.
I see pitcher's mound in here,
And I see little boys' dreams
coming true everywhere.
I found a dead snake!
It's perfect.
Not dead! Not dead!
I'm gonna be mother of the year.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Synced by YYeTs, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
And this is our dining room,
where we eat.
And this is our kitchen,
where we also eat.
Who are you talking to?
It looks like you lost your tour.
Or your mind.
The baby.
Shorty's girlfriend
Darlene send it to me.
She said it's for prenatal bonding.
I love it.
We took a tour of the house.
We took a look at all my shoes.
Come on, Jay.
Say something to the baby.
Darlene's an idiot.
Oh, yeah, beautiful.
Your first words to our baby--
"Darlene is an idiot."
This is stupid.
The baby's only 2 inches away.
He doesn't need
speakers blasting at him.
Like in restaurants nowadays
where you can't
even hear yourself think.
Ah, you're gonna do whatever
you want. Why do I bother?
Get used to that.
Sometimes you just gotta let him go.
Then he eats some sherbet
and falls asleep.
Okay, I'll chalk the field
with this bad boy.
And while you're doing that,
I will get the bases.
We make such a good team.
Why does your friend
have a chalker?
Oh, he used it
to propose to a skywriter.
Oh, ma'am? Ma'am,
do you need help with that?
Oh, yes. Please.
Is this your house?
I'm moving in with my son.
He's rich.
Phone by the toilet rich.
All right, so have
you lived here a long time?
I moved here in '62
to be an actress.
I had one line in a "Rockford files."
"He went out the back.,"
Who went out the back?
That was you.
Well, you're all set here.
You're not interested
in the place, are you?
- Oh, no, thank you.
- Yes-- yes, we are.
Yes. Yes, we are.
- Come on.
- Okay.
You gotta keep your eyes open.
It's not natural when a ball
is hurtling at your face.
Will you choke up a little?
Probably when they play
the national anthem.
No, move your hands up the bat.
"When they play
the national anthem."
I had a perfect record--
22 games, and I hadn't played
a single inning.
Then the McCoy twins' grandma dies,
and suddenly I'm starting
at right field.
What does that even mean?
Is it the same as stage right?
All right, ready?
Nice and easy.
I haven't even thrown it yet.
Then it's your fault.
I'm doing my part.
Forget it. We need
to do something different.
Let's change your stance.
Try leaning in.
Further.
Now close your eyes.
Ah! Perfect! You think
you can do that every time?
What, get hit on purpose?
If you wanna get
on base and be a hero.
Some men are born into greatness.
Others have it
chucked at their face.
Yes!
Okay, Mrs. Brooks,
thank you very much.
We'll be in touch very soon.
Say it one more time.
He went out the back.
- Oh, love it! Love it!
- Brava! Brava!
Bye-bye!
What do you think, Phil?
Well, I have to admit,
it's a steal.
Yes! Yes! I told you!
And you said Gil Thorpe
makes a killing flipping houses.
Yeah, he brags
about it all the time.
Every time he makes a sale,
he calls himself "Flipper"
And walks around making
this dolphin sound. Like...
How does he do it?
I hate him so much.
Okay, look, if the four of us
go in on this together,
we can minimize the risk.
Or if none of us do it,
we can eliminate the risk altogether
because none of you know
anything about flipping houses.
Okay, well, we already
have it figured out.
I'm gonna be the designer...
Because I know
about colors and shapes.
Yeah, so does Lily.
I'm gonna be the contractor.
And I'm gonna be the astronaut.
Oh, this is fun. Phil, you go.
Mitchell, I am serious.
I have overseen lots
of projects in our home.
I oversaw the remodel
of our bathroom.
Under budget. Right, Phil?
Yeah. I was a little disappointed
we didn't go for
the butt-washing toilet,
but otherwise...
You can wash
your own butt for free.
Well, that's not the same, is it?
This is all fun to talk about.
It is, but I don't think
that you understand
what-- what this
could really entail. And--
Okay, there it is. Mitchell just
said "No," so we're done.
Surprise, surprise.
Listen, we'll talk
about this at home, okay?
Don't give up.
Phil, you think
it's a good idea, right?
Totally.
Yes. And you know
we can handle it, right?
I think you guys
can handle anything.
And you go talk to him.
You're a professional.
He respects you.
Okay. Give us some space.
I'll go talk him into it.
- All right.
- All right?
- Okay.
Listen...
there's no way
we're letting them do this.
I know, right?
They are not equipped
to take this on.
We might as well
flush all our savings
down my boring old toilet.
Oh, you are really
bitter about that.
It's the one thing I asked for.
Don't sit on your sunglasses.
Sorry, guys.
Whoops. Just to be clear, though.
Under no circumstances
are we letting them do this?
I am totally with you.
Okay, you stay here.
I'll go break the bad news.
Sorry, guys.
Not gonna happen.
- Yeah, well, maybe if--
- I would drop it.
It's not worth the fight.
Come on, Claire.
The faster we leave,
the less it's gonna hurt.
Hop in. Yep.
Why does it have to be like this?
I don't know. He's your brother.
Buckled up? Good.
No! No! No, no,
I see what you're doing!
He doesn't want this either!
- Little radio?
- Sure.
Phil! Claire!
Come on!
It's such a shame
because I know we would do
a great job on that house.
- Totally. - If Gil Thorpe
can do it, I can do it, right?
Please!
Please. Gil Thorpe
has decades of experience
and infallible instincts.
As much as we'd all like
to believe otherwise,
I did not marry Gil Thorpe.
Can you imagine that?
God, we'd sell a lot of houses.
Oh! Great.
- Mitchell.
- Oh, you know what, Claire?
You gotta cool down or
you're just gonna make this worse.
Why don't you go get the coffees?
And I'll deal with him.
Well, okay,
what are you gonna say to him?
I'm just gonna
talk to him man-to-man.
Right.
Okay.
Hello?
Claire, Phil doesn't want
the house either, all right?
He's letting me take the fall.
He's a liar.
And a clever one.
Ugh! How long do you think
you can keep this from her?
All right? I'm gonna
talk to her eventually.
Well, as long as
we're swapping stories,
Maybe I'll tell Cam
what happened to the sweater
he knit for you.
I can't.
I can't! I can't!
I can't do it! I can't take
this stupid thing anymore!
It was stolen out of the car.
Do you understand me?
Got it.
That is low.
I know. Don't be mad at me.
That said, I suggest
you lose this number.
I'm not proud of what I did,
but I'm not comfortable
squashing people's dreams.
I am a cheerleader.
I'm the guy on top
of the pyramid shouting,
"Go, dreams, go!"
You know what's not a cheer?
"Two, four, six, eight,
you are going to fail at this
and lose everything
we've worked for, Claire!
Hush, little baby,
don't say a word.
Papa's going to buy you
a mockingbird.
And if that mockingbird won't sing,
papa's gonna buy you
a diamond ring.
Papa'd buy ten diamond rings
to get that mockingbird
to shut the hell up.
But I wasn't gonna tell Gloria
she was a terrible singer.
That's just taking
a bath with a toaster.
Still, the thought of
that poor little thing stuck
in there like a hostage,
listening to that racket
days on end...
I just couldn't take it.
And if that billy goat won't push,
papa's gonna get every le--
I'll tell you what papa's gonna do.
He's gonna take a turn on that mic.
- Oh! Really?
- Yeah, I've been thinking,
if it's a chance to bond,
I should take it.
Ay, Jay, that's great.
I think that the sound of my voice
shouldn't be the only thing
that the baby should hear.
Same page.
Breaker, breaker, big Jay.
Baby, what's your 20? Over.
Ay, that's so cute.
You sound like
Smokey and the Bandito.
Go on. Go on.
Hi, kid.
This is your dad Jay Pritchett.
Uh, we're all pretty
excited to meet you.
Just a heads-up--
I might be a few years older
than you're expecting.
But on the plus side,
we're very comfortable.
What's that? Nothin'?
Tough womb.
What are you doing in there?
You sleepin'?
Are you sleeping?
- Ah! Ah! Ah!
- *Are you--
Ah! Still daddy's turn.
Dumb-- dumb rock!
- Are you cryin'?
- No.
No. I just can't get
this rock to budge.
Okay, what did we learn
from "A League of Their Own"?
No crying in baseball.
No. That Madonna's
a lousy actress,
and so are you.
What's really going on?
Okay.
You know, over the last
couple of months,
I've applied for, like,
five different jobs.
- I didn't know that.
- No. I didn't tell anyone,
because I didn't get them, Cam.
I went to college, you know?
And... I just wanna be able
to contribute to my kids' education.
And I wanna be able
to buy my husband a present...
with my own money.
Hey, you're preaching
to the choir director.
It's actually why
I became a choir director.
You became a part-time teacher
in a public school for money?
I make more than you do.
I mean, before parking. But...
Look, I'm sorry Mitchell
killed our house dream.
You know, now especially that I know
you wanted to use the money
for such noble reasons.
Yeah.
And also...
there was this pair of boots.
There's always a pair of boots.
Mitchell, do you know
what I've realized?
That some thoughts
are better left unexpressed?
No. That in this relationship,
I'm the gas pedal,
and you're the brakes.
Okay, wait.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
Last week, you said that
you were the painting
and I was the frame.
That's if we were artwork.
This is if we were a car.
I know what part
you'd be if we were a horse.
- Excuse me?
- Hmm?
Claire and I bring you
this great opportunity,
And you stop it cold.
I guess that's what brakes do.
You know what brakes also do?
They keep you
from driving off cliffs.
Maybe they're not cliffs.
Maybe they're ramps,
ready to launch us into new,
exciting vistas.
I am not the only one against
this whole house thing.
Phil doesn't want it either.
You keep saying that,
but I find that very,
very hard to believe.
Phil supports Claire.
Phil is a cheerleader.
Why can't you be more like Phil?
And then it hit me.
I could be exactly like Phil.
I could pretend to be on board,
forcing the cheerleader
to be the bad guy.
I know it's underhanded,
but that's the way I throw.
- Mitchell?
- You-- you know what?
You've convinced me.
If-- if you and Claire
and especially Phil
are into this,
then I'm on board.
- What? Seriously?!
- Yes! 100%.
In fact, why don't you
call Claire and Phil
right now and tell them?
Okay. It was
the ramp thing, wasn't it?
You know, I felt
really good about it.
What?
Are you serious?
That's fantastic!
Oh! I gotta tell Phil.
I'll call you right back.
What's-- what's up?
Mitchell changed his mind.
He's all for it.
We're flipping a house!
- Yeah.
- Yeah!
Well, hello, Phil.
To what do I owe this pleasure?
Cut the crap.
You wanna play chicken?
Chicken's my middle name.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm just being supportive
of my partner and my sister,
both of whom I love very much.
How do you sleep at night?
Soundly, knowing
you'll do the right thing.
So how about it, Phil?
You gonna stop this train?
'Cause these brakes are out.
Oh. And I suggest
you lose this number.
Mitchell?
Mitchell?!
Yeah, I was pretty ticked off
that Mitchell double-crossed
my double-cross.
And then he stopped
taking my calls,
And so I sent him the following
carefully worded text...
"U suck."
I could tell Phil felt pretty hurt
and betrayed, so I responded.
"How r u gonna cheerlead
your way out of this one, Buffy?"
"We both know this
house thing is a disaster."
"Then say something, or I will.
I don't care if you tell Cam..."
"I threw out
that hideous sweater?!"
I spent months knitting
that hideous sweater.
- Yeah.
- W-- how are we seeing this?
They're using the
group text from yesterday.
They have no idea these
are even coming to me.
Okay.
Oh. Here's another one.
"We need to shut
this house thing down
without them knowing it's us"?!
Oh! Well...
"2 late."
No, that-- that's bad.
Claire, I am so sorry.
I know I should've been
more honest with you, but I--
No, Phil.
You know what really kills me?
Is you didn't believe in me,
and you believe in everything!
You know, I knew
that sweater wasn't stolen.
And here I pick blue yarn
to match your eyes,
but I should've picked
black to match your heart.
Although you look
amazing in black. Damn you.
Come on.
"...Leaving 17 dead and
thousands without power."
Ay, Jay, please!
It's bad that the baby listens
to such terrible things.
He's heard worse.
Jay, do you know a good
1-hour dry cleaner?
And I don't mean
the "Must be in by 10:00,
only on weekdays,
you need a coupon" kind.
I mean a hard 1-hour.
This conversation feels
like a hard one hour.
And what do you need it
cleaned for? It's spotless.
There's mustard here
from Reuben's reuben.
That's what happens when
you put a narcissist
in charge of snack day.
Okay, it's my turn again.
Baby, it's your mother again.
- I'm--
- Gloria?
Why don't we give him a break?
He probably needs a minute
because he just learned
about a deadly tornado.
Okay, stop calling him a he.
What if he's a she,
and you're making her upset?
I told you. That's just
the shorthand I'm using.
- Don't jump down my throat
every time I'm - Ay, yes,
- because you always
- What are you doing?
Do you really want
your unborn baby
to hear you fighting like this?
Studies show it's unhealthy
for a fetus to be exposed
to a stressful environment.
Studies? You're 13.
Read a comic book.
What time does your game start?
I have to be there
at 3:00 for hitting practice.
Batting practice.
Not for me.
Jay, I don't want our baby to think
that it's coming into
an unhappy home.
Let's promise that we're
never ever going to fight
in front of him.
No fighting in front of the baby.
Okay, good.
Twinkle, twinkle
little lamb
Gloria, stop it! Stop it.
No more singing.
Why?
Because you stink.
You're a terrible singer.
Come on. Let's get some lunch.
How dare do you say that I am...
I know! Ay, no, no, no.
No fighting in front of the baby.
We just made a deal.
Yeah, but that's not fair
because I am always
in front of the baby!
Gloria, you're as close
to perfect as woman gets.
Nothing wrong with
one tiny, little flaw.
Yours is when you start to sing,
is sounds like something got stuck
in the vacuum cleaner.
That's-- you're just--
No, no, no.
That is just your stupid,
stupid opinion, Jay.
But I am very angry at you,
and I am gonna make a list
of all the things that
I am going to scream at you
as soon as this baby's out of me.
I didn't think it
all the way through.
Oh, hello, Mitch.
Uh, you got Claire flowers?
Yes. I had a little bit
of a rough night.
Yeah, you and me both.
Daddy slept in my room last night.
- Here, give me some of those.
- What? No.
- You got me into this.
- Hey, stop! You're breaking them!
I need-- I'm not going
to Cam empty-handed!
Phil, let go of the...
Hold still!
Claire and Cam did all this?
A week ago, that was all junk.
It's amazing.
I mean, there's that
little bump in the middle.
But other than that...
Even if one of those boys
had hit five home runs,
the biggest star
on that field was Claire.
That's the funny thing
about marriage.
You fall in love with this...
extraordinary person,
and over time, they
begin to seem ordinary.
I think it's all the nagging.
Wow. This...
this is incredible.
You literally saw
a diamond in the rough.
Yeah, but I take on
a lot of projects
no one else is willing to.
I deserve that.
I was an idiot for doubting you.
Please, honey, forgive me.
How could I not,
when you give me
this bouquet of crumpled flowers?
- Mitchell did that!
- Mitchell again?
Ask Lily!
- Hey, Cam.
- Hey.
Here you-- Okay. Well...
Oh, wow. Broken and mangled...
Just like my heart.
Cam, I'm sorry
for not supporting you.
- What about the sweater?
- That's unforgivable.
I mean, you put all
that time and work into it,
and I just toss it
out the car window.
Tossed it out the car window?!
I'm forgetting how much you knew.
You know what, guys?
Honestly, I...
I think we should do it.
I think we should go for the house.
- Really?
- Okay, but careful, honey.
Don't say something
if you don't mean it.
No, I do mean it.
I think you two will do a fantastic job.
You know, I do, too.
I'm on board.
On board for what?
Oh, well, the four of us,
uh, might go in on a house.
Claire and I fix it up and flip it.
That's the worst idea I ever heard.
You guys know nothing
about construction.
You'll make all sorts of mistakes,
you'll turn on each other,
you'll stop talking,
and suddenly I'm doing
two dinners a week instead of one
because you can't be
in the same room.
Family and business doesn't mix.
Ah, you're gonna do whatever
you want. Why do I bother?
Is he right?
Y-you know dad.
I mean, he's a pessimist.
I want us to get that house.
I do. But I don't want us to fight.
We're not gonna fight.
Of course not.
Probably.
I don't know. Will we?
Maybe we just take
a beat and think about it.
Yeah. I-I guess that couldn't hurt.
Yeah.
You guys mean the world to us.
I don't want to jeopardize
that over a house.
- We feel the same way.
- I know.
- I just wanna say I know we'd do
a good job, though. - Hello?
- And I feel so--
- It's Mrs. Brooks, the lady with the house.
Actually, it's good that you called.
What?
What happened?
Gil Thorpe just made her an offer.
- We did it!
- We bought a house.
It's gonna be... great!
What could go wrong? Nothing.
Sometimes I don't understand people.
They do crazy things
for the dumbest reasons.
I'm going to march out there
and swing as hard as I can.
And if every
sports movie is correct,
I'm going to smack that ball,
and everyone will chant
my name as I round the bases.
By the way,
it is always counterclockwise,
or do I get to choose?
I don't think it's gonna matter.
They convince themselves
it'll all work out...
Please rise for the national anthem.
I'm gonna show you who can sing.
Gloria.
Oh, this is gonna be rough.
Despite all the evidence
to the contrary.
Oh say can you see?
By the dawn's early light?
Which I guess isn't so bad.
And the rocket's red glare!
All I'm saying is,
I hope to god you don't have
your mother's singing voice.
But, man, I hope you get
her self-confidence.
Try to get some sleep.
I'll talk to you in the morning.
2 outs, bottom of the sixth.
Tied at 4.
This is it, folks.
The whole game comes down to this.
Manny Delgado 0 for 3 on the day.
Gloria, your thoughts?
I think he's going
to hit the home run.
Please, God, give me one.
Manny, stand up straight!
But bend your knees.
Widen your stance!
Would you please let me just--
Take your base!
- You did it! You got it, Manny!
- I did it?
No, no, no, no!
Not that way! Go this way!
Oh, why do I bother?
He's gonna do what he wants.
Manny! Manny! Manny!
Synced by YYeTs, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player