Family fun meeting
by the front door, stat!
"Stat" means right now!
Ugh. What is it?
Ignore her. She's been
in a bad mood all day.
And Luke isn't home yet.
I'm right here.
Where were you?
This house still holds its secrets.
You're probably wondering
why I called you all here.
- Nope.
- Well, stop your wondering...
We're not wondering.
And behold.... this wonder!
- Oh, my God!
- Wow.
I sold a home to the one
and only Pete Johnson.
There's only one Pete Johnson?
Only one who's
California's top R.V. dealer.
There's 835 others.
Nightmare of a deal to paper.
Well, and this was
his way of saying...
- Thank you.
- Of course.
He paid a commission, too, right?
Yes. And he told me I could
take Jolene out anytime.
Yeah, I named her!
Let's take this dirty girl
for a spin up the coast!
- Yes! - Awesome!
- Pretty sweet, huh?
- Yeah!
- Huh.
I can see where this is going.
This summer-- you, me, the kids,
- Yellowstone National Park.
- Mm.
And that's just the Verona,
he offered me an Amalfi.
An Amalfi, Claire!
That makes the Umbria
look like a Portofino!
Well, they should've
called it the Roman,
'cause that's what
we're about to be doin'.
I'm really not following you.
Ten days on the road
with those kids?
Winnebag-no.
I hate it when Phil does this.
Now I have to be the bad guy
who comes in and
squelches his brilliant idea.
I said no.
Get it out of my house.
Fine.
Come on, Jolene.
Fortunately, this time,
I don't have to be
the wet blanket,
because even on just
a short spin up the coast,
Phil will see what I see
every day--
the transformation that happens
when our kids are locked
in a moving metal box...
The kraken that is unleashed.
I love my kids very,
very much.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Synced by YYeTs, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
- You're poking me.
- Yeah, well, I know, sweetie.
But I don't get
these pins just right,
your bun could fall out
during your routine,
and it could mess you up.
Okay, let's test it out.
All right.
Jump.
Good. Spin.
Now give me Beyonce.
Okay, I've done everything
I can do. It's up to you now.
We have a gymnast in our family.
Yeah, Lily goes
to gymnastics class.
In one short year,
I've seen her blossom
from a little girl
who couldn't do a somersault...
Into one who... kind of can.
Yeah, and by that standard,
we also have a black belt,
art prodigy, and prima ballerina
in our family, so...
You know, what we
don't have in our family
is two loving, supportive fathers.
I'm just saying, she's 5, you know?
And you never let her forget it.
- Excuse me, is that your little girl
out there? - It is.
- And you did her hair?
- I did.
Do you mind helping
my Julie with hers?
Oh. Oh, do you guys
own a convertible?
- No.
- Oh, no judgment.
Yeah, I'll get to work
right when Lily's done.
Not bad. That little leap
at the end-- that's new.
Wow. She's getting really good.
Mm. You better bring your "A" game.
Oh, my God. Cam, look.
Lily's in second place. 9.2.
I told you she's a gymnast.
With scores like that,
she's gonna make pre-team.
- Are you serious?
- Mm-hmm.
Pre-team? She could make pre--
What's pre-team?
Claire!
Phil!
Haley!
Luke!
Alex!
Gloria, we've been through
the roster three times.
They're not home.
But their cars are here.
Where could they be?
Who knows what these people do?
But my backpack is in there, Jay,
- my poem for my poetry reading.
- Calm down.
Didn't you back it up
on your computer?
What kind of man writes
poetry on a computer?
You could've ended
that sentence after "poetry."
Come in.
And no questions.
My backpack wasn't upstairs.
What's that?
Postcard from a friend
of Claire's-- Rachel.
"Living it up in Club Med Cozumel."
Looks like that marriage
went down the drain.
In other shocking news,
Phil subscribes
to a trampoline magazine.
Going through other people's mail--
keeping it classy, Jay.
Mom, my backpack
isn't in Luke's room.
I don't see it in here, either.
I don't think
it would fit in there.
Ay, this was open when I came in.
I was just looking
for an aspirin.
I thought that
I heard some noises.
So you were snooping?
Oh, so now it's snooping,
wanting to know
more about your family
by looking through
their personal things?
Not just now.
Since the invention of things.
Is that one of Claire's brownies?
No, they're delicious.
Must be Cam's.
- Oh, no.
- Don't worry. There's more.
No! That's where my backpack is.
Cam drove me and Luke home.
I must've left it in his car.
Why are you so scattered lately?
Aw, he's just nervous because
of his poetry reading tonight.
But don't worry, papi.
I am going to be
there to support you.
I don't want my mom there.
I'm exploring some darker themes
I'm not sure she's ready for,
poems like "The umbilical noose,"
"A jail called mom,"
"Smother nature."
She'll just find some way
to make it all about her.
And a toasty 75 degrees
for daughter Haley.
You see, the Verona boasts
individualized climate zones, Claire.
I could literally transport
a polar bear and an orchid
and not make two trips.
Dad, I'm freezing.
It's, like,1 degree back here.
Six minutes in, and it begins.
Here.
Take the blanket from the bed.
Thanks, kitten.
Dad, can you change the music?
Can I?
Oh, no. Oh, no,
that's just getting louder.
This isn't good.
It's not good at all.
Actually, it's kind of perfect.
Right?
The big windows,
the classical music.
It's like we're in a movie.
Turn it up, handsome.
You got it!
Obviously, the novelty of the situation
was delaying the inevitable.
But I didn't want to get halfway
into a trip to Yellowstone
before Phil discovered
what malevolent hellspawn
we have for children...
Whom I love very much.
Alex, honey,
that's a cute sweater.
Doesn't Haley have one like that?
Oh, it actually is hers.
- I took it from her closet before we left.
- Really?
Ooh. Sorry, girls.
Didn't mean to start a whole thing.
I am so sick of you always
looking better in my clothes.
- When did that happen?
- You're okay with this?
Oh, yeah. She can wear
whatever she wants
after I've had it for six months.
- Oh.
- Or I get it automatically
if you buy anything
that looks like it.
This just feels right.
Huh, team?
Matter of fact,
I was thinking we could all drive up
to Yellowstone this summer.
But I say,
let's take this beeyotch
ocean to ocean!
- That'd be cool!
- Awesome!
We're doing it!
Phil, the road!
I don't know what
button I just pressed,
but that was amazing.
My backpack's definitely
not in there.
Well, they're not
picking up their phone.
He must've brought it inside.
Sorry, kid, looks like
you're out of luck.
Come!
Don't they have a burglar alarm?
Ay, please.
Okay, everybody,
split up and search.
Jay, you look in the bedroom.
I'm not looking in their bedroom.
Fine. Mom, I don't think
my backpack is in Cam's bag.
I was just closing it for him.
I... heard a noise.
Looks like the guys
threw a little party.
I noticed. They brought out
the guest soaps.
How long have you been in here?
Hey.
This is that bottle of wine
I bought Phil when
he started his company.
And Claire's lipstick is
on many of these wineglasses.
Pictionary.
They had game night?
But we always go to game night.
Son of a bitch.
They snubbed us.
Found it!
There must've been a dozen players.
Pepper was here.
But Pepper loves me.
Okay, she's all set.
I defy you to find a tighter bun
in this gymnasium.
Lot of different ways
you could've said that.
Oh, and good luck
on your floor routine, sweetie.
Not that you need it.
That's Abby.
- Mm-hmm.
- She's the best in class.
- Oh.
- She's our competition.
I've never wanted
to beat a kid so badly.
Are you not hearing these?
No? Okay.
Oh, Lily's on the beam.
I'm nervous about her dismount.
You said that she could
stick the landing, right?
Yeah, as long as she breathes,
relies on her training,
and stays in the zone.
We are talking about
her stepping off a 6-inch beam.
And not falling. Right.
I have to admit.
Seeing Lily do so well
brought out something in me.
The pride of being
a parent of a child
who wasn't just
participating but thriving.
Okay, here comes her dismount.
Stick it Lily. Stick it!
She stuck it!
- Mm!
- She stuck it!
9.4.
If no one beat my daughter's
score on the beam,
she would make pre-team.
She'd be one of the elite.
Funny thing, pride.
They say it goeth before the...
Fall. Fall.
- Fall.
- Mitchell, I can hear you...
- What?
- Rooting for a little girl to fall.
If I can hear you,
other people can hear you.
Yes!
I don't know why I said that.
I don't-- I'm sorry.
Yeah, he didn't mean it.
- I didn't mean it.
- No, um, he just got caught up.
And, uh, you know, we all know
competition makes people
do crazy things. So...
Look at this! Her bun fell apart
during the floor exercise.
Her hair got in her eyes
and she couldn't even finish!
You did it on purpose!
- No!
- Daddies!
I'm in first place.
- Yay.
- That's great.
Did you offend them?
Me? They love me.
Can we go now?
I have a poetry reading tonight.
And speaking of that,
- are you sure you guys really want--
- It makes no sense.
We're always the life
of every party.
Maybe they didn't invite you
because you're a couple of snoops?
Okay, Mr. Goody two-shoes.
A trait normal parents would value.
Jay, I think you're right about him.
He's been too good
lately for a teenager.
It's not normal.
I am afraid that
the world is going to--
- Oh, hell, no. This is too far.
- Ay.
Look at this.
Is that supposed to be...
That's us.
Not only do we get blown off,
now they're making fun of us.
Well, I'm just gonna
leave them a little message.
As far as I'm concerned,
they can all...
Horse mouth!
That's a good one!
No, "horse mouth"
is not an expression.
You can't get this?
Look. Donkey.
That's not a donkey.
Look at the ears.
Okay. Donkey mouth!
That's a terrible guess.
That's a terrible drawing!
- Hello? - We weren't invited
because you stink at this game.
At least I can draw!
Excuse me.
Just need a signature.
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
Here we go.
There. Thank you.
Yep.
That's not a signature.
You drew a cat.
Thank you.
Perfect freaking harmony.
That's when it hit me.
Maybe it's not the cold
confines of a moving vehicle
that brings out
the worst in my kids.
Maybe I bring out
the worst in them
when there's no fun-lovin'
Phil around to neutralize my toxins.
I was in a full shame spiral.
Aah! A bee!
And then something
wonderful happened.
I got it!
- Ow! You idiot!
- Kill it!
No, don't!
Haven't you heard
of colony collapse?
Bees are endangered!
Okay, guys, stand still.
They can't see you
if you're not moving.
- It's coming near me!
- Aah!
- Do I look like a bee?!
No, that was an accident!
Well, so is this!
Everyone remain calm!
I'll just open up
the double-tilt Swiss skylight
and the airflow will pull
- the bee out of--
- Aah! There's another bee now!
We must be near its cave!
Oh, my God!
There's so much stupid in here!
All right, I'm pulling
this thing over.
Those are the wipers.
Claire, say something!
Kids, stop, please.
Hey, there are daily
flights to Yellowstone.
Aah! You ripped my sweater!
My sweater, which you
shouldn't even be wearing!
- Aah! Get off of my sweater!
- Short layover in Salt Lake.
Are you really not
gonna do anything?
Oh, Phil, you must have known
this was gonna happen.
I know that tone.
You're making a point.
It's better that you find out
who they are now
than when you're halfway
across the country.
Well, I guess I'm just a naive boob
who thought we liked each other!
Obviously, it was too much to ask
to think that we could take
one magnificent trip
in a tricked-out,
state-of-the-art R.V.
to see the sun
dancing off the Pacific.
What a huge ask!
I can't stand the way
everyone's starting at us.
Yeah, I know.
It's the way we look at people
who walk with their pet birds.
There she is!
Hey, good luck on your balance
beam routine, sweetie.
- You're gonna do great.
- I'll never beat Lily.
Of course you will,
because you're a superstar!
And your daughter's a genius.
I am such a fan. Such a fan.
- Okay, now you're overcompensating.
- I have to!
You saw what a monster
I was out there.
This-- this is the exact thing
I always hated in my dad,
that ugly macho
testosterone drive to win,
and today it has flowered in me.
- Well...
- No, this ends today, Cam.
I am not passing this on to Lily.
Well, it's not all on you.
You know,
I'm beginning to think maybe
I did sabotage Abby's hair.
I didn't spray.
I didn't Beyonce.
I basically built
a ticking time bun.
Well...
Are you okay?
No.
- My hair hurts.
- I'll fix it.
We should find Lily.
Did you see what
your daughter just did?
Uh... Lily, did you pull
the pins out of Julie's hair?
Yeah, she fell.
- Oh.
- Okay, um...
I-- Could I get everyone's
attention for just a moment?
We consider what
our daughter just did
to be an embarrassment
to the sport of gymnastics.
I assure you,
she did not learn this from us.
And as far as we are concerned,
that is a sign of weakness...
Not the way a winner behaves,
but the way...
- A loser behaves.
Come on, Lily. Let's get
your grips and tiger paws.
- You're going to a time-out.
- Yeah. A nice long one.
I made pre-team, and my daddies
get to watch from outside.
- No closer than 100 feet.
- But we're appealing.
- Yay!
- Yay, Lily!
Kill the chicken!
Chicken fingers!
- Pigeon man!
- "Pigeon man." "Pigeon man"!
You see, Tony, it's not me.
Would you invite her
to game night?
I'm gonna go now.
They're kinda sticklers about
the next-day delivery thing.
- Bird in the hand!
- There you go.
Any slower, she'd be
the U.S. mail, am I right?
That's gonna kill
at the warehouse.
You see?
You are the problem.
Except you cheated.
I saw you look at the paper.
I knew it.
You're no better.
All the screaming and bullying.
The question isn't why
you two weren't invited.
It's why you're ever invited.
And by the way,
this isn't even about you.
"Treasure... chest."
Now can we clean this place up and go?
Funny story.
My mom and Jay were invited.
Cam gave me
the invitation at school,
and I forgot about it.
But how could I tell them
right after I'd shamed them?
I had to cover my tracks.
It's true, Jay. I cheated.
I cheat a little bit every time that
we come to the game night.
I think Mitch saw me the last time,
and that's why they don't want
to play with us anymore.
But why would you do that?
I don't know!
Maybe because
I don't want you to think
that I am not smart.
I would never think that.
And besides, it's my fault, anyway.
The kid is right.
I'm too competitive.
Lost a game of Yahtzee once.
The dice are still on the wall.
Yeah, but at least
you're not a cheater.
I feel like such a donkey mouth.
Guys, there's something
you should know.
It's Trivial Pursuit night
at mom's church.
I hate for you to miss
my poetry reading,
but maybe you could
head down there,
work on your sportsmanship,
and you will feel better
about yourselves.
Are you sure you're going
to be okay without me there?
Yes, mother. Mother.
I'll be in the car.
I get this damn competitive
streak from my old man.
It's a miracle I didn't
pass it down to Mitchell.
I love that we can
blame our parents.
My mother was the biggest
cheater I've ever known.
And she used to snoop on
everything that we did.
Ay. Jay, look at this.
Our invitation.
They must have forgot
to give it to us.
No. I checked this bag
when we got here,
- and it wasn't there.
- Why are you always--
You know I have a problem.
This was Manny.
He forgot to give it to us,
and then he came and
tried to sneak it in there.
Why wouldn't he just tell us?
Maybe because he doesn't
want us to go to the reading.
That's why he was talking about
the church and the game.
He was working us.
Guess he's not too much
of a goody two-shoes.
No. He's a lying,
scheming little sneak.
That's my son.
Our son.
I've never seen dad
freak out like that before.
I feel terrible.
Oh, it's partly my fault.
I goaded you guys into
a fight to prove a point.
Why do I always have to win?
How did I get this way?
That you?
Yeah.
- You?
- Yep.
How many kids in yours?
Felt like 30.
I got four.
But I'm thinking of emancipating
two of them early.
Tell me one of you
has cigarettes or a flask.
Sorry, buddy.
I've been through every state--
depressed, catatonic, Arkansas.
I considered faking my own death
in Bryce Canyon National Park.
Have you been?
Not to be missed.
I'm gonna miss it.
I'm missing every bit of it.
I'm not spending another second
in that rolling asylum.
Poor guy. How long you been
on the road? Couple weeks?
Couple days?
Dad's in the middle
of a super sad dude hug.
We really disappointed him.
Yeah, maybe we should
just suck it up
and go to jellystone this summer.
Wait. That's why
dad got this thing?
I-I can't go
on a trip this summer.
- Why?
- I've...
- I've got stuff.
- Huh? No. What stuff?
- I don't want to talk about it.
- Luke.
Summer school.
I'm failing pre-algebra.
- Why didn't you say something?
- I don't know.
I feel stupid.
You know what it's like
to follow her?
All the teachers look at me
and think that I'm some
kind of irrational remainder.
- Did I use that right?
- No.
Dang it.
But why didn't you ask me?
I would've tutored you.
I tried, but you were
always off in your room
or some corner
of the house on the phone.
Yeah, who have you been
talking to so much lately?
- Aaron?
- Who's Aaron?
Actually, it's two boys--
Aaron and Alex.
- Oh, two boys.
- A boy named Alex likes you?
Yeah, I know. It's weird.
But my friend Andi with an "I"--
She's a girl--
- also liked Alex.
- The boy?
Yes, the boy. I don't refer
to myself in the third person.
- I thought Aaron was the third person.
- No.
Anyway, I thought I was cool
juggling two boys at once,
but...
They both ended up
dumping me on the same day.
Sweetie, that's awful.
How did I not know
this was happening?
You've been really busy lately,
like with flipping that house.
And plus I didn't really
want to talk about it,
- because it's kind of embarrassing.
- Oh...
Not as embarrassing as failing
a class that starts with "pre."
- Baby...
- You guys wanna feel better?
I auditioned to be a
Laker girl this morning.
- What? You did?
- No way.
I took all those dance classes
when I was younger,
and, I don't know.
I've been trying to figure out
what I want to do with my life,
so I saw online that
there were open tryouts,
- so I went down there.
- And?
I'm the new head Laker girl, mom.
It was a disaster.
I was the worst one there.
I couldn't even get
through my routine.
- Oh...
- You have a routine?
Pat, Heath, you guys have given me
the courage to go back in there,
stand up to my wife,
and tell her
she was right all along.
Happy trails, Phil.
Heath?
I might just stay here a while.
Phil. Phil, I have
to show you something.
Don't gloat. I get it.
I keep trying to push
this family closer together,
- but they need their space.
- No, no, no. We have too much space.
Being in trapped in one room
has forced us
to actually talk to one another,
and I have found out some
incredible things about our kids.
Wait. Incredible good?
You tell me.
Oh, my God.
- Dream come true! I don't even
need context! - Yeah!
What is this?!
- So our trip's back on?
- We're in if Jolene's in.
- Come on. Do it!
- Yeah!
Oh! Why can't I get this?
You just gotta focus.
Clear your mind.
Loosen up. Get in the zone.
You know this.
Okay, we're gonna walk
through this together,
step by step.
Five, six, seven, eight...
One, two, three, four,
- five and six, seven and eight...
- 56.1 plus or minus 8.25.
- That's the first one.
- One, two, three, four,
- five, six, two, five--
- Okay, number 2-- x plus 2 over 4
- equals 3 plus 3-- minus--
- Damn it, Alex, do you mind?
We're doing something
important here!
Oh. OK.
Once more.
- Like nobody's watching.
- x plus 2...
Synced by YYeTs, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player