Okay, let's see...
Oh, could you grab me
an extra virgin...
- I think one's enough for the sacrifice.
- Olive oil, Phil.
Come on. That's funny.
Oh, it's funnier than your
freestyle "sandwich rap."
Girl, you crazy.
I'm mad fun to shop with.
♪ Trapped in between
two whole wheat slices. ♪
♪ Pastrami and Swiss
are my only vices. ♪
Sweetie, my shoe.
Come on. Jesus. God.
Hello.
Hi.
Oh, roadblock.
- Beep beep!
- Pardon me.
- Oh!
- Are you okay?
Actually, not okay.
Not okay.
Honey, did you pull
from the bottom again?
So after hors d'oeuvres,
we'll bring everyone in
here to share the news.
We're having the family
over tomorrow night
to tell them we're planning
on adopting a new baby.
Yes, and we both agreed
to--to go a little more low-key
with the announcement this time.
♪ Let's hear ... ♪
Okay, just to be clear,
this is low-key?
It's a banner
and just some light musical
accompaniment, Mitchell.
I don't have a lower key.
Besides, this is a happy occasion.
Am I right, Lily?
Aren't you excited to
get a new baby brother?
No! I hate the baby!
We are having a slight issue
getting Lily on board
with the adoption.
"I hate the baby."
"No new baby."
"I wanna make the baby dead."
I thought we weren't
gonna share that one.
I-I-I just hope
that the problem is
she hasn't spent much time
with any babies.
So we thought it would
be a great idea
to show her how much fun
it'll be to have one around.
Oh, he is so cute!
Yeah, and he never cries.
Literally never.
It's actually a little weird.
Oh, no, that's not weird.
My sister was born with
a full set of teeth.
- Yeah, that never happened.
- Oh.
No? Really?
You should've seen her crib.
It looked like beavers lived there.
Oh, is this Lily?
Oh, yes, it is. Hey, honey.
Say hi to the baby.
- My Daddy!
- Oh!
Okay, so that's
one problem solved.
Sync by YYeTs.net | Corrected by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
Bye! See you soon!
Or never.
Cam, I'm a little freaked
out about what Lily did.
Oh, please. She barely touched him,
and he went from zero to big crybaby.
We're talking about bringing
another child into this house.
How's that gonna work with Lily
being so possessive of you?
Why am I hearing an accusatory tone?
Oh, come on. You have to admit
that you do coddle her.
I will not apologize for
loving our daughter.
I'm not criticizing.
I'm not only criticizing,
but we did talk about giving
Lily a little more independence.
Yeah, which is why we
put her in preschool.
Yes, but you can't bear
to leave her there.
You always pick her up early.
That is ridiculous.
Okay. Okay.
Lily, honey,
did daddy pick you up early
from preschool today?
No.
Case closed.
We didn't go.
Case opened.
We went shopping.
That's enough.
We bought matchy hats.
You are going to your room.
You're both going to her room.
Do we spend a lot
of time together? Yes.
Do we have a special bond?
Absolutely.
But do I coddle her more than
any other loving parent?
Mm-hmm.
It's possible.
And for Lily's sake, I should
probably work on that.
No, you calm down!
This is how I talk when somebody
accuses my Manny of stealing.
- Who is that?
- It's the principal.
He's saying that Manny
stole some girl's locket.
What, do you think that all
Colombians are criminals
because a Colombian necktie
is a symbol of violence
all over the world?
No, no, I'm not threatening you.
Okay. Apology accepted.
No, I didn't mean anything
about the necktie.
I just--
I was trying to make a point.
Could you "L"
A little less "O L"?
Don't you see what
I'm trying to do here?
Die alone?
Girls, dinner!
You know, why does Luke
get his own room,
and I still have to share with you?
I can't take it anymore.
Me either, even if it is
just for one more year...
When I leave for college.
It is one more year or when
you leave for college?
Because those happen to
be two different things.
So I hear this little voice
coming from the cans
and it's like...
"Help! I fell in the peaches!"
That's Mom!
- Hilarious!
- So hilarious.
I'm like, "Claire?"
You might wanna tell
them that it was you
who pushed me into the
peaches in the first place.
This again? I wasn't even near you.
Yes, you were!
You knocked me with the cart.
It was completely your fault.
Well, let's just agree to disagree.
No. I-I disagree to disagree.
Then you agree.
No. No, I don't,
because I'm right.
Okay, Claire.
You're right.
As usual.
No, I am right.
Like always.
Stop it. When I am wrong,
I admit it.
Which is never.
Fine. Fine.
Aah!
You're a little jumpy tonight,
Manny. Anything wrong?
No. Well, I'm just gonna--
Have a seat, kid.
You know, maybe it's me,
but I thought you were kinda
squirrelly tonight, you know,
before when your mom was on
the phone with the principal.
Almost like you wanted
to say something...
But you just couldn't.
Anything you wanna say now, Manny?
No. I have nothing to say.
You sure about that?
Think real hard.
Could I get a glass of water?
That girl's locket--
you took it, didn't you?
Um...
- Didn't you?
- Yes. Yes, I took it.
- I didn't mean to.
- I don't wanna hear any excuses.
You're gonna tell your mom,
and you're gonna set this right.
Do you understand?
All right, get out of here.
Just one more thing.
You're not, um...
You're not wearing
that locket, are you?
No. Of course not.
It's a girl's.
Why would I want to wear it?
It's no reason.
Mom, hurry up!
I don't want to be late for school.
You didn't tell her, did you?
What's the hurry this morning?
Okay, what's with the looks?
- It's like a silent
movie in here. - Okay.
I was walking behind this girl
Alicia, who's moving away,
and I was working up the
courage to get her new address
so I can write her.
I express myself a lot
better on paper than--
Tick-tock, kid.
Well, she dropped her
locket, and I picked it up,
but she kept walking, and I...
You stole the locket.
After I told the principal
that you could have never
done something like that,
and I threaten him with
the Colombian necktie!
Manny, why?
Don't worry. It wasn't 'cause
he wanted to wear it.
I thought I could keep it as
something to remember her by.
But then you were yelling
at Mr. Vickers,
and I-I was just too
scared to tell you.
Go to the car.
- I'm really sorry.
- Go.
Why would he do
something like that?
It's bad enough that he's
the boy with the pan flute
and the puffy shirts
and--and the poems.
Now he's the jewelry thief.
Might be an upgrade.
Ay, Jay, this is not funny.
Those things stick to you.
My cousin Rosa Marina--
when she was 14, she stole
something, and after that,
everybody thinks of her as
the girl who steals cars.
She stole a car?
Cars.
But after she got that label,
what else could she do?
Listen, you can't
control what kids think,
but you can make sure
he learns from this.
You take him to
the principal's office,
he owns up to it,
he never does it again.
Okay. Okay.
But what was he thinking?
This is not even real gold.
No way, Haley! It was my idea!
I'm taking this room!
Over my dead body!
This is going to be my room,
and there's nothing
you can do about it!
Seriously?
What are you guys
fighting about?
Okay, so we both think
that this would make a
totally awesome bedroom.
But only one of us can have it.
Don't you think it should be me?
Oh, so not. It should be me.
Right, Luke?
Why do you guys
wanna move into the attic?
Oh, you mean "the penthouse"?
With all the privacy of being
on its very own floor?
It is kinda cool.
I'm not an idiot.
I knew what they were up to,
but I've been wanting
to move for a while.
There's a line of ants
going to a trick-or-treat
bag in my closet,
and I don't want
to still be there
when they get tired of candy.
Good morning, princess.
Good morning, Lily.
Very adorable, Mitchell,
but I'm having
kind of a rough morning,
Daddy, up.
I'm sorry, Lily,
those days are over.
Now here's your lunch.
Go get your bag.
We will be leaving shortly.
Cam, you don't have to
ice her out completely.
Do you think I'm enjoying this?
But I need her to detach from
me before the new thing comes
or who knows what
she'll do to it.
Why are you saying "thing"
instead of "baby"?
Kill the new baby.
Oh. Um, look,
I-I-I know this is hard,
but I really appreciate
what you're doing.
And believe me,
I take no pleasure in seeing
you suffer like this.
I take a little pleasure.
No, but there--there are
very few parenting issues
where I come out on top.
You know, I'm distant.
I work too much.
My French braiding is "sloppy."
Finally, you know, something
that isn't my fault.
Ready.
Okay.
Could you please just go
put her in her car seat
while I compose myself?
All right, you know what, Cam?
Why don't I just take Lily to
preschool on my way to work?
I think that would be best.
Let me just whip up a smoothie
for you before you go.
I push the buttons, Daddy.
You certainly do.
What do you think the
principal's going to do to me?
I am a first-time offender.
Oh, great. Now I'm tardy.
Strike two.
Manny, think of this
in a positive way,
- like it is your "ha ha" moment.
- What does that mean?
That means that one day,
you're gonna laugh about it.
Ah, I should've just given
that stupid necklace
back to Alicia
when she was standing
right next to her locker.
This is the worst day of my life,
- till tomorrow...
- Oh.
- And every day after that.
Come on, Mom.
Let's get this over with.
- Wait.
- What?
Which one did you say that
it was her locker? This one?
Mm-hmm. The one that
smells like rose oil.
Mom?
Keep the lookout.
Now promise me that
you will never, ever do
anything dishonest again.
I promise.
Okay, because that's not
the way I raised you.
- Don't tell Jay anything, okay?
- Mnh-mnh.
- Hi, Lily.
- All right, Lily.
- Hi.
- Have fun, sweetheart.
Bye.
She is so sweet.
Oh, thanks. Well, you
should've seen her yesterday.
Yeah, she pushed a baby
off of Cam's lap.
- Huh.
- I know. I know.
She is so possessive of him,
but, you know,
Cam's really working on trying
not to coddle her so much,
- So... - Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
I'm not really sure
it's about coddling.
Sounds more like
a sharing issue.
You know, we've noticed Lily
has a hard time with that.
- Really?
- I wouldn't worry.
Kids usually pick that
habit up from other kids,
except the ones that pick
it up from their parents.
We have a few of those in here.
Of course, I can't share
those names with you...
Until I get a glass
of wine in my hand.
Oh. Oh, miss Elaine.
I have been told
that I might have
the teensiest issue
with sharing.
But is that something Lily
would even pick up on?
My chicken.
My pillow.
Ow! Mmm.
Daddy's pen.
Okay, it's possible.
And I suppose for Lily's sake,
I-I should work on that...
Privately, because right now
we really need to get Cam's
coddling problem under control.
What's going on?
Moving into the attic.
Give me a day or two to get
settled, then I'll have you up.
When did all this happen?
Depends on who you ask.
My plan's been in motion
for three weeks.
Honey, this is a terrible idea.
You're gonna hate it up there.
Mom, stay out of this.
Yeah. We all have our own rooms now.
Everybody wins.
Well, don't get too
comfortable in there, girls.
Luke, it's cold,
and it's scary up there.
You're gonna be back in your
own room by tomorrow night.
I don't know, Claire.
It's got a lot of potential.
This is a lot nicer
than the attic I lived
in when we met.
One night, if that.
Trust me on this.
Oh, yes, because
you're always right.
Sweetheart,
I would love to be wrong.
I just don't live with the
right people for that.
Let it go, kids.
She's not gonna budge.
- Kept me up all night with the--
- Phil, you did push me!
Your word against mine.
Guess it's one of those
things we'll just never know,
like what really happened
to the "Titanic."
It hit an iceberg.
- Maybe.
- Mm, there's no maybe.
Oh, you're right, Claire.
Again.
Surprise, surprise.
Okay, I-I will see you
over at Uncle Mitchell's.
I'm gonna skip this meeting
of the "Pile on Claire club".
Guess I pushed her
into that pile, too.
I spend half my life
waiting on you.
How many times do you have
to change your outfit?
Sorry, Jay.
Too many choices is a prison.
Just drive before
he rethinks the pants.
- What's wrong with my pants?!
- Go. Go. Go.
So, Manny, how'd it go
with the principal today?
It was terrible, but he was
brave, and now it's over.
- Right, Manny?
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm. So d-- - What'd they give you?
Detention? Suspension?
No, just a warning because
it was first offense.
- So how was work?
- Great.
Just a warning, huh?
Like she said.
So I ask about work,
and you change the subject.
Are you trying to hide something?
No, I just wanna make sure he's okay.
You okay?
'Cause, I mean, it looks like
you're sweatin' bullets
back there, kid.
Stop grilling him.
First the principal, now you.
This poor boy has been
screamed at all day.
- Well, not to mention--
- Quiet! I've got this.
- Where is Lily?
-Um, she's getting dressed.
All by herself?
- Cam is encouraging her to
be more independent. - Oh.
And there she is!
- Ah! Ah!
- Doesn't she look beautiful?
- Mnh.
- Mm-hmm.
She looks like she
was dipped in glue
and dragged through a flea market.
- Hey there!
- Hi!
- Hey, hey.
- Hi! Hi!
- Hi, guys. Come on in.
- How's it going?
Hey, do you guy
have any old furniture?
I'm moving into the attic.
- The attic?
- Hey, at least it's big.
Grandpa said you used
to live in the closet.
Oh. Okay.
Well, you know what?
Yeah, we'll absolutely find
you something for sure. Okay?
My Daddy!
Lily, no!
I-I'm sorry, Luke.
This isn't over.
Oh, my God. Mitchell,
she's getting worse.
I have turned her into a pushy,
little, entitled monster
on her way to a rap sheet and
a bracelet on her ankle.
Oh, she has a bracelet
on her ankle.
Cam.
Cam, Cam,
This--this might not be
entirely your fault.
No, it is.
I spoke with Lily's teacher,
and she thinks that--that she may
have a problem with sharing,
which she might have gotten from--
You. You don't like to share.
No, I do it to make
a point sometimes.
Like, if you want the chicken,
then order the chicken.
Wait, when did you talk
to Lily's teacher?
Uh, today, when I--when I
dropped her off at school.
And you let me suffer all day?
All right, look, we--we can't
do this with everybody here.
- Can we please just get
through the evening? - Yes,
but we are not making the
announcement tonight
because that is a joyful thing,
and I am not feeling
very joyful right now.
Well, I share your feeling.
Just so you know, I'm on to you.
You never took Manny
to the principal.
Okay, play it like that,
but I know Manny.
He has more of a conscience
than you have.
He's not gonna be able
to live with this.
You'd be surprised what
people can live with, Jay.
Hi, miss Lily.
How's my big girl doing?
Good.
Can you tell me
how old you are now?
Three.
That's four. This is three.
Okay, show me again.
How old are you?
- Three.
- No! That many is four.
This many is three.
Don't argue, Lily.
You'll never win.
Really, Phil?
Okay, I-I was gonna wait
until we got home for this,
but now I think it's something
everyone's gonna enjoy.
Guys, everybody, come
on down to the TV room.
I've got something
really special to share.
Okay, how's everybody on drinks?
If this is Alex's graduation
again, just leave me the bottle.
I'm good, Cam.
Okay, everybody.
Showtime.
Oh, my gosh.
It's us at the market.
How did you-- uh-huh.
Yeah, it's security camera footage.
I don't understand.
What are we watching?
It ain't "The Godfather,"
I can tell you that much.
Okay, look, I fell
yesterday at the market,
and Phil and I have been
having a little disagreement
as to what happened. Just watch.
Okay, right here.
I stop to fix my shoe,
and then Phil--
right there. Okay.
He makes way for this
very attractive woman,
whom he conveniently leaves out
of his retelling of the story.
Now right here, Phil backs up,
pushes his butt into the cart,
pushes me into the cans!
- Do you see that?!
- Oh!
It's all his fault, just like I said!
I was right!
Suck it!
- When did you get this--
- Oh, my God.
That's why you wanted
to come separately.
You went to all that trouble
just to prove you were right?
It really wasn't that much trouble.
I just went to the store, found
your friend Jordan the bag boy,
who got me the manager.
He gave me the address of the
off-site security office.
I filled out some paperwork.
Sally faxed it to corporate.
Three minutes later, I'm buying
pack of DVDs and burning a copy.
Cake.
It's like a sickness.
What? None of you believed
me, so I got proof.
You should all be
sucking it right now.
Hey, please stop with the
"sucking it," Claire.
The children!
Yes, children are
very impressionable.
You'll never know
what they'll pick up.
Okay, Cam, I'm sorry that
I blamed it on you, okay?
But we both need to look
at our actions.
I mean, if we're thinking
about adopting another baby,
then we need to--
You guys...
you're adopting another kid?
- No! No, no! You're-- wait!
- Congratulations!
We're thinking about it.
It's not...
♪ Oh, let's give the boy oh, wow. ♪
What the hell's happening here?
Is that from "Footloose"?
Really, Mitchell?
You couldn't even share
telling your family!
Fine. Fine.
But why are you upset?
This is such good news.
No, we're a little on edge
because Lily has been acting out
like she doesn't want
a sibling, and--
Yeah, because Mitchell
taught her to hate sharing.
And/or because Cam wears
her like a fanny pack.
Oh, stop blaming each other.
No kid wants a sibling.
I mean, Claire hated you so much
she stuck you in a dryer
when you were two.
You put me in the dryer?
I did, but it wasn't
'cause I hated you.
My friend Marci said
that it wouldn't run with a kid
inside it, and I knew it would.
I was right.
Good governor.
It's been going on
since you were five?
- Oh, my God. It is a sickness.
- Yeah.
What would make me have that
need at such a young age?
How long was I in that dryer?
Because I--
is this why I'm afraid of tumbling?
I had to quit gymnastics, Claire!
- A childhood without tumbling?
- Ohh.
You knew this and just
stood by and did nothing?!
Okay, okay.
What's done is done!
All you can do is learn
from your mistakes.
And in that spirit,
I would like to propose a toast...
to Manny.
This week, he did something
he wasn't supposed to do,
- like we all do--
- Like we all do!
- Salud to Manny!
- Uh, not yet.
But Manny stood up like a man.
He admitted he was wrong
and he took his licks,
and I'm damn proud of him.
Ah, now we clink!
No, we clink when I say we clink.
So Manny made a mistake, but he
didn't take the easy way out.
He's got guts, he's got integrity.
As far as I'm concerned,
he's the best little b--
Okay, stop! Stop!
I didn't do any of that.
Mom broke into the locker and
threw the necklace inside,
and then we ran away like cowards.
- I'm sorry, Jay! I'm sorry!
- I knew it!
I was right! I was right!
Ohh.
- Who is it?
- Oh!
Hi, honey. It's just me.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm great.
So, how you liking your new digs?
- I know you told me that I'd be cold...
- Mm-hmm.
- And scared...
-  Mm-hmm.
But I'm not.
No, I can see that.
I was--I was wrong.
- You were.
- Yeah.
Well, you're gonna
hate this then, honey,
but I'm gonna need you
to go back down and sleep
in your old room.
I just--I'm worried if you
get something so cool
this early in your life,
you're not gonna have anything
to look forward to later.
I-I have to go now?
You can spend the night
tonight here if you want.
Oh! No, if it's so
important to you,
I'll go now.
You should come, too.
Something sleeps over there.
Wait for me. Wait.
Wait for me! Wait for me.
Sync by YYeTs.net | Corrected by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net