Honey!
- What is all this?
- Hey!
Hey mom! I'm trying to write
a stupid college essay question
- and I really don't even know where to
start. - OK, what's the question? Tell me.
"What's the biggest obstacle
you ever had to overcome?"
Didn't my 3rd Grade teacher said
I had like ADD or something?
Oh, no honey.
She said you couldn't ***.
She put it that way because she
also knew you couldn't S-P-E-O-L
Wait, slow down.
Sweetheart.
What's this?
We talked about this last week.
I said I'm building Luke a treehouse,
you said fine.
You know? Sometimes I think
you just turn me out.
I never told her.
She just would have said "no."
I don't remember
agreeing to this, Phil.
This is like the time you
backed down the driveway
with a hang glider
sticking out of the car.
If you'd let me keep that,
those geese would have
followed me to the wetlands.
- You would have died.
- A hero.
So we spread out a nice blanket,
opened up a bottle of vino,
and watched the sun
set over the water.
It was majestic.
- Mm.
- Majestic.
Why? Why we never have the picnic?
Who wants to sit on a blanket?
There's no back support.
It's majestic.
Last week, Shorty took me
to see the Cirque du soleil--
It's like a circus, but classy.
So if you like elephants,
don't hold your breath.
She's so cute.
Jay hates the crowds,
the beach, the rainbows.
Rainbows?
It's just colors in the sky.
Do we have to pull over
every time and take a picture?
Shame.
There's an expression in Italian, Jay--
Dammi la tua mano e corriamo
uniti per tutta la vita.
"Give me your hand and we
will run together our whole lives."
Jay also hates running.
Modern Family 3x07 Treehouse
Sync & Corrected By Ali's Ultimately
Here you go.
Oh, thank you.
- And here you go.
- Oh. What is this?
You said to knock your socks off.
Oh, well, look.
It's already working!
Well, two more of those,
and you won't be wearing
any underwear either.
- Oh! Look...
- Cam, down. Down.
- Maybe later.
- Oh, okay, maybe... maybe later.
Did you hear that?
Waitress is flirting with me.
No, no. She's not flirting with you.
She's-- she's trolling for tips, okay?
She totally knows you're gay.
How would she know I'm gay?
Uh, maybe it's the way
you ordered a drink-a-doodle-doo.
Cam has this crazy theory
that if he were straight...
And Julia Roberts were single...
- They'd be dating.
- It's not crazy.
I met her once
at an A.I.D.S. walk,
and our chemistry was palpable.
No, you handed her
a bottle of water.
And her fingers lingered.
Because you wouldn't let go.
I could totally pick up
any woman in here.
If by that, you mean
lift her off the ground,
then yes, I'll give you that.
I for sure could be a womanizer.
Or you could be someone
who just stepped out
of a machine called the womanizer.
Okay, you know what? That's it.
Pick anyone in here.
If I can get their number,
you do the laundry for a month.
If I fail, I'll do it.
Okay. I hate doing laundry.
So, um...
No, um...
Oh, okay. Right here.
Her.
Okay, great.
Great. Just get rid of my flair...
Whoa. Where did Cam go?
I don't know. Where is he?
Dinner was absolutely wonderful.
Amazing.
Hey, you know what?
Why don't you guys come
salsa dancing with us tomorrow night?
Oh, yeah! That would be great!
It sounds like so much fun.
I love salsa dancing.
Jay, let's go salsa dancing
with them. Look.
Why not?
I just bought that
pay-per-view fight.
I tell you what-- we'll compromise.
We'll watch the fight.
We'll eat salsa.
Who needs him?
Come dancing with us.
Ay, no, I wouldn't want to--
No, no! You'd be doing me a favor.
Shorty never wants to stop,
and I could use a break.
You hear that Jay?
I never stop.
All I hear is she could use a break.
Hey! Oh, my God! How are you?
Hey. Hey!
Wow. Look at you.
You look fantastic.
Thank you. So do you.
How long has it been?
- It feels like forever.
- Yeah.
Um, when is the last time
we saw each other?
Oh, let's see.
I think it was at Dave's thing.
You know what? I'm sorry.
I don't know if you've heard.
I was in a terrible car accident,
and ever since the coma,
I have a really hard time
placing names and faces.
So who are you again?
Oh, my God. I am so sorry.
It was just a clever way
to try to approach you.
We don't know each other.
I've never been in a coma.
But you so deserved that.
That was the worst pick-up ever.
Oh, my God!
That was genius! And mean!
Now I know why
we're old fake friends.
Oh. Can I buy you a drink?
Yeah. I'm Katie.
Cameron.
If she were a hot guy,
I would never
have been that smooth.
It's ironic.
Like the gift of the vagi.
There you go.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
- You, too. Bye!
- Bye!
Wham, bam, thank you, Cam.
Seriously? You got her number?
Sure did.
And all my shirts get ironed,
and their seams
should appear straight,
just like their owner.
Should you be using
screws instead of nails?
America was built with nails, son.
So was that gazebo you built
for our 4th of July party.
I'm telling you, you are
gonna love this bad boy.
You know what can't climb trees?
Raccoons?
Worries.
Raccoons can and will get up here,
so don't leave any food,
or they'll get
territorial and attack.
Are you sure this is a good idea?
Are you kidding me?
You're gonna have so much fun
hanging out up here
with your buddies.
Trust me, when you get older,
it all changes.
- Why?
- Well, life gets in the way.
Did I just say
"wife gets in the way"?
'Cause sometimes I do that.
Nope, you're good.
And you have lots of friends.
Yeah, I have work friends,
and your mom and I
have couples friends,
and there are my college friends,
but they're scattered
all over the country.
It's not the same
as just shouting out
to your neighborhood buddies,
"Hey, fellas! I'm up here
in the tree house!" Uhh!
Fix that... board.
I can't do this.
Why are you so frustrated?
Because I've never had
any obstacles to overcome.
Oh, honey, that's not true.
Really? Name one.
Well...
You're lactose-intolerant.
Oh, "dear college,
cheese makes me gassy.
See you in September."
Sweetie, you're not really
starting your essays
"dear college," are you?
What difference does it make?
I've lived a boring,
sheltered, pathetic life.
I am sorry we have
made things too easy
and comfortable for you.
Oh, you should be!
It is all your fault!
You have shielded me
from everything interesting
and dangerous!
You are blaming me
because I kept you
from getting hurt?
Gaby's mom's a hoarder.
That essay practically writes itself.
Maybe it is our fault.
But did you ever consider
there's a reason?
What are you talking about?
There's a reason why
we were so easy on you.
I don't understand.
Oh, honey, you're old enough now.
Old enough for what?
The truth.
Okay, come on.
Gotta show you somethin'.
We're gonna go for a ride.
Mom, just tell me.
You are my mom, right?
Oh, hey.
I'm a bad man.
Oh, no. What did you eat?
Mitchell, remember
the girl I met last night?
How can I forget her?
She's super famous for having
the world's worst gay-dar.
How could I be so cavalier
with her emotions?
You know, we had a real connection.
She gave me her number,
and right now she's probably
sitting by the phone
waiting for me to call.
I don't think you understand
how charmed she was by me.
Oh, my God. Where did you
get all this self-confidence?
I won cutest baby
at the 1974 Jasper county fair.
People at the time
said I could go gerber.
You know what? I'm calling her.
What?
No, I can't carry this around.
I have to come clean
so she can move on with her life.
This is crazy. She is not waiting--
Hi. Katie. It's Cam.
First ring.
I was hoping I would call, too.
Oh, smooth.
So listen, I forgot to mention
something last night,
and I'm--I'm actually not really
quite sure how to say this.
I'm a gay guy.
Um, it's actually
somewhat delicate.
As am I, on account of the gay.
No, no, I had a great time
with you, too, Katie.
It's--well, it's just that--
- I don't dig the ladies.
- No, no. And I want you to sit--
I want you to have a seat
on a chaise lounge.
Hey, you wanna go out
and grab some dinner
before the fight tonight?
No, thank you.
Wanna eat at home?
I'll grill some steaks,
open a bottle of wine.
Whatever you want,
because I'm not going to be here.
She's going salsa dancing
without me.
Ay, Manny, I told you,
it's a 21 and over club.
A forbidden dance floor.
Only makes me want it more.
Wait a second. You're going dancing
with Shorty and Darlene?
Yes, because even though
he's old like you,
he still likes to have fun.
We like to have fun.
Last week I took you to dinner,
went to the boat show,
got some sherbet?
And we were home
by 8:30 with no boat.
What do you want from me?
I don't like dancing.
- I don't like sherbet.
- Yeah, right.
How about coconut?
Who doesn't like the coconut, hmm?
Who?
And anyways, I'm going
dancing with or without you.
Fine. I hope you have
a good time with Shorty.
I don't need Shorty!
I won't have any problem
finding a partner on my own!
Wow. Way to rub it in, mom.
How'd it go, heartbreaker?
That is one classy lady...
- Which is why I couldn't tell her.
- What?
Well... I just couldn't
do it on the phone.
She seemed so excited
to hear from me,
and I'm very bad
at disappointing people, Mitchell.
Not all people.
Mama was right when she said
my charm was like a wild stallion--
if not properly bridled,
it'll bust down a barn.
Okay, you wanna get rid
of your girlfriend?
Tell her that story.
Maybe I will when she comes over.
She's coming over.
Are you serious?
She said she was in the area
running errands.
What was I supposed to say,
"don't come over"?
Well, I guess I could
have said that,
but it's too late now,
plus I wanna break it to her gently.
So come on.
Help me un-gay this place.
You know what?
I'll make it less gay by half.
Oh, these flowers should go, too.
You mean the ones
underneath the portrait
of you cuddling another man?
Oh, good catch.
Aw.
Manny.
What's up, big guy?
How hard is it to learn
this salsa dancing stuff?
Not hard at all.
It's about tapping
into your emotion,
your passion,
and your inner fire.
Crap!
I stink at dancing.
First dance at our wedding,
Gloria was all graceful
and gorgeous,
and I was all big and clunky.
Like that scene from
"Beauty and the beast."
Actually, that was the song.
Manny picked it.
He didn't like me back then.
Back straight. Okay.
Do as I do.
Other leg.
Okay, stop marching.
You're dancing,
not invading Poland.
Hello, hi!
I'm looking for Jay Pritchett.
He's about 6'2", tough guy,
wrestles with homophobia...
The hell are you doing here?
Uh, I had to get out of the house.
Cam needed a little alone time
with his new girlfriend.
- Don't ask.
- Don't tell.
What's going on here?
He's learning to dance,
but he's just so tense.
- It's not working out.
- 'Cause you're not letting go.
I'm trying. Don't you think
I want to be all smooth
and make your mom
happy out there?
But I just can't do it, that's all.
Jay, I'm not giving up on you.
Okay. Hey, Manny,
would you give us a second?
Thanks.
Dad, look, I-I know this is weird,
but you and I are a lot alike.
We're self-conscious, okay?
So, um, here. Just...
The hell is this?
It's just something that
some people take at clubs
to, you know, loosen up.
You take this?
A gay man who hates dancing
lives in a sad and
lonely little world.
This just melts your inhibitions,
and--and you can dance all night,
plus it gives you a raging--
I don't wanna--
I don't like this at all.
Just hold on to it.
Just in case.
Come on. It's fine.
Jay, I wanna show you something.
A farmer in New Zealand
taught a pig to dance.
Oh.
See how he keeps his snout up?
Yep. This is it.
This is what?
This.
I-I can't do this.
I can't get out of the car.
I'm sorry. I'm too embarrassed.
Would you just tell me
what's going on?
Okay. I-I want you to go read
what's carved in that tree.
Mom, you're freaking me out.
Just do it. Do it, Haley.
Have fun getting home!
There's your obstacle!
What?! Are you kidding me?!
Oh! Son of a...
Brisket!
Why does that keep happening?
Maybe I need a nail gun.
Okay, that's it! I'm out!
What do you mean, you're out?
Where are you going?
Dad, no offense,
but I've seen you
with a glue gun.
I think a nail is gonna be harder
to get out of my hair.
No, don't go!
I'm doing this for you!
Are you, dad?
Are you?
The kid made me
think with that one.
Who was I really doing this for?
Sometimes I just say,
"are you, dad? Are you?"
Because he gets real quiet
and doesn't notice
when I walk away.
It's weird, because I feel
so comfortable around you already.
You know, last night
when I got home,
I just started thinking
about all of the fun things
that we could do together, you know?
Yeah.
I don't wanna scare you off,
but my sister's getting married
in a couple of weeks,
and I so don't wanna go
to that thing alone.
Maybe you could be my date?
Katie, you're an amazing woman.
You're smart, you're beautiful,
and how fun is that handbag?
This is gonna come
as a little bit of a shock.
I'm fairly gay.
I don't know why I said that.
I'm--I'm totally gay.
Just gay.
You're telling me you're gay?
Yeah.
Why?
I was born that way.
I mean, you know, it's just--
No, why are you telling me?
I mean, I know you're gay.
It's obvious.
Well, it's not that--
it's not that obvious.
Well, yeah.
The way you talk
and walk and dress
and your theatrical
hand gestures--
I do not have theatrical
hand gestures.
Okay, maybe I am
moderately... expressive.
But why would you
give me your number?
Oh, because I want a gay friend--
someone I can dish with,
give me guy advice,
and I can shop with--
those are totally
offensive stereotypes.
We could go see Julia Roberts
movies together.
I know her, and she's as nice
as she seems on screen.
- Shut up. Really? Is she?
- She is, yeah.
Wait, what--so you were
pretending to be straight,
and hitting on me?
I was just a stupid bar bet.
My boyfriend-- oh, he's here...
Bet me that I couldn't get
a beautiful woman's number.
And as a proud gay man,
I know it shouldn't matter,
but I-I just wish everyone
could find me attractive.
Oh. But now
he's gonna get to gloat,
and I guess I deserve it.
Hi... hi.
How's-- how's it going?
Hello.
This is Katie, and, uh,
it turns out, well...
No, actually.
It doesn't turn out well.
Because I thought I finally
met a nice, funny guy,
who is also hot!
And now he's telling me he's gay?!
He's, like, the least gay person
I have ever met
in my entire life!
And I thought he was the one!
And I even told
my mom about him!
You better cherish him!
Wow.
Are you sure you're gay?
- No.
- Cam.
Yes.
Yes. Look...
You're gonna find somebody,
because you're
an amazing girl, Katie.
You're the whole package.
I just prefer somebody
who has one.
Okay.
Oh... my... God!
That was a lot of girl tongue!
I think I need
a drink-a-doodle-doo.
What was that?
Hello, Haley.
How was your day?
I have no money, no cell phone...
You're welcome.
What?!
I listened to you.
I stopped coddling you,
and look--
you overcame an obstacle.
Oh! Yeah! I did!
I grew up normal
despite my crazy mom!
Well, that sounds like
the beginning of a great essay.
"Dear college..."
Oh, honey, if you get stuck,
let me know,
and I'll make you
sleep out in the yard.
You're psychotic!
Use spell check!
Aah!
Don't just sit there!
Get out here!
I'm good, I'm good.
Okay!
Hola! You're looking so good!
How long has it been?
We don't know each other.
Go away.
Fair enough.
Hola!
You're looking so good.
How long has it been?
What was wrong with that guy?
Yeah, I would have
danced with him.
He's got nice shoulders.
Aw, you know,
salsa is so intimate and sensual
that it feels wrong to do it
with somebody else
that is not Jay.
Aw. You know, Darlene
feels the same way.
If I wasn't here, she's be
holding up the wall.
Yeah. A wall of men.
You know, I think I should go home
to my loving husband
and pull him close and tell him
that I danced with 20 men.
He's not home.
He's in a dicey neighborhood
worried about his car.
Yay! Hey!
Jay!
What, are we gonna kiss or dance?
Let's dance!
I'm dead set against drugs.
"Just say no" and all that stuff.
But I thought,
just this once for Gloria.
And if I was gonna make
a complete ass of myself,
I didn't wanna remember it.
The big drug I gave him-- baby aspirin.
Orange-flavored.
He could have chewed it.
Home come you never
surprise me like that?
I do surprise you.
No, you don't.
You never surprise me...
That's gonna be
a hell of a tree house.
Oh, thanks. I'm trying.
It's for my son, but
he's kind of lost interest.
It's kind of like my daughter
with the dog.
Which is why I'm the one
out here doing this.
Did you just move in?
Lived here eight years.
You?
- 12.
- Huh.
Huh.
You know, me and my friends,
we, uh, we built a
tree house when I was a kid.
We spent hours in that thing.
Loved it.
Me, too.
You need any help?
Yes, a lot.
But I-I don't wanna bother you.
Only thing that bothers me
is that drunken Amish roof
you got up there.
Do you even have a level?
I did, but I might
have gotten frustrated
and thrown it into your yard.
Let me find it. I'll be right over.
Thanks.
I'm Phil, by the way.
I'm Andre.
Nice to meet you, Phil.
Nice to meet you, Andre.
So I guess I was wrong
when I said once you get older,
it's harder to make new friends.
Honey! The dude in the tree is cool!
Andre, it turns out,
is an orthopedic surgeon,
handy with tools, and
a great guy to hang out with.
Plus he's a badass black man
that gives me extra street cred.
That's his joke.
He's my brotha from
a different motha.
- What was that?
- Different--
- That's not it.
- What is it?
It's "brother from another mother."
Brotha from anotha motha--
Slow down. Slow it down.
Brotha from another motha.
Forget it. Don't-- just don't say it.
Forget it.
Sync & Corrected By Ali's Ultimately
www.tvsubtitles.net