Ooh! Individual frittatas!
What a treat.
You're a lucky man, Phil.
- I'm always saying, I'm...
- Phil.
- Sorry.
- You left the milk out again.
Oh. Mmm.
I may have to take
one of these little guys home.
Claire, did you ever find
that tupperware I lent you?
Sweetie, for the hundredth time,
I gave it back to you, remember?
I remember you
telling me a hundred times,
yet my pea soup is in baggies.
Did you check your car?
In the...
Trunk.
Because that's where
you found that thing
that you thought that
you gave me long time ago,
- the... the...
- Pizza cutter.
Good, give me another one.
- Yes, I was wrong that time. I--
- It's a piece of plastic.
You're ruining brunch.
Don't sweat it, Cam.
I forget things all the time.
Like I can never
remember the name
of that weather guy
that I liked. Uh...
- Thunder something.
- Stormy...
Flash stormy?
Ah, whatever the hell it is.
- I don't know.
- Mm, just eat your eggs, Jay.
Yeah, just eat your eggs, Jay.
- Oh, ho ho ho!
- Grandpa got told!
Look at them.
They all think Lily's so great.
The novelty will wear off.
We used to be the cute ones.
Now she gets all the attention.
We need to take her down.
And I should remember his name, too,
because your mom and I
got in a big fight over him.
She was using the convertible,
and I told her,
"put the top up because it's supposed
to rain tonight, according to..."
P-p-p-partly Mccloudy?
Whatever the hell his name is.
Anyway...
She didn't.
Ruined the car.
Well, not to be the one that
always come to mom's defense...
What? It was 20 years ago.
- What, you think he's gonna ground you?
- It was you?
Yes. Yes, I left the top down,
and I let mom take the fall.
And then they got divorced.
- 12 years later.
- I'm just saying.
Ugh. You're ruining brunch.
Relax. It was years ago.
There's a statute of limitation
on this stuff.
In that case, I should
probably let you know
I let the top down
to let out the cigarette smoke.
Not-- not mine. Not mine.
My-- my bad friend Eleanor.
Eleanor being her boyfriend Allen.
Statute of limitations.
Oh, relax, it's okay.
Remember when I told you
that I couldn't get to
your figure skating semifinal
because I was stuck at work?
Yeah.
Well, by "stuck" I meant "drunk,"
and by "work" I meant "the golf course."
- Wow. Dad!
- Oh, no. I got one. I got one.
Remember that time
we went golfing together,
- and you got a hole-in-one?
- Yeah?
You never got a hole-in-one.
I got bored and
I kicked it in the hole.
This is fun. Here's a corker.
They didn't used to label babies
as carefully in hospitals,
- so for two days--
- Not now, Phil.
What do you mean, you--
you kicked the ball in the hole?
What, was it, like, on the edge?
Yeah, it was on the edge of that, uh...
- What?
- That--that sandy thing.
Gee, it's sure gonna be fun
to face my friends today.
Well, you don't have to tell them.
They call me "ace," Mitch.
I haven't paid for a lemonade
down there in 20 years.
- You're mad at me?
- Mm.
Great, daddy.
You ruined brunch.
You did!
This ends today.
Synced by YYeTs, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
A little help here?
You can't expect me to focus
when Miranda Cornell lives
right down your street.
She's like a dream wrapped
in a wish poured into jeggings.
Yeah, yeah, that's nice and all,
but we got a trap to set.
Are you sure
this is going to work?
Trust me.
We'll use these cookies as bait.
Lily's crazy for them.
Asian metabolism.
When she grabs them
with her grubby little hands,
off goes the trap.
Boom-- Big puddle of milk.
She'll get in so much trouble.
My mom hates messes.
I'm familiar with Claire.
Lock...
and loaded.
Mmm! These cookies are so good...
And so easy to reach.
Lily!
- Oh, my God! Cam!
- Oh! Ohh!
What happened? Are you okay?
Oh! That milk... fell,
and I must have slipped in it!
Did I leave that out again?
I'm so sorry!
Oh! My back! Ooh! My back!
Can I give you a Swedish massage,
accent optional?
Oh! Oh, no,
I just need to lie down.
Come on. Let's just
get you over to the sofa.
Do you think it would be offensive
if I asked our daughter
to walk on my back?
I'd say so. I just offered
to give you a massage.
Oh, no! You broke Beatrice.
Now she can't feed the dolphins.
What is she talking about?
Oh, it's a "My sweet companion" doll.
They all have
these elaborate backstories.
Beatrice works with
blind dolphins and models.
There are blind models?
That's so sad.
They cannot see how pretty they are.
Okay. Hold on. Here we go.
- Give me some. Give me some. Give me some.
- Oh!
Let me buy Lily a new doll.
It's my fault Cam fell.
No, no need.
Uh, the My sweet companion store
actually has a hospital
with an on-call doctor.
Well, I can go. I'm taking the girls
to the mall anyway.
Oh, that'd be great. Yeah.
And don't worry.
She has medical insurance.
Yeah, and I think we've met
our deductible for the year,
so you should be good.
Yeah.
Do you know what
a doll is in my village?
An apple on a fork.
I never really got dolls.
Does that make me weird?
It's on the list.
You're not weird.
You just kind of skipped
the little girl stage.
And jumped to the "I dare you
to ring her doorbell" stage.
The only stage you're ever going
to jump on has a pole on it.
Hey, at least I have the body--
Okay! Okay!
We're gonna have to settle
this dispute in court--
the food court.
The honorable Judge Cinnabon presiding.
The food court? That place smells
like the inside
of Luke's bicycle helmet.
- I like the food court.
- Me, too.
Don't worry, girls.
We're not gonna deprive ourselves
just 'cause of Haley's
aversion to food--
Oh. Oh, Haley's "aversion."
I thought you said...
Never mind.
Okay, so after you have
turned on the monitor
and selected your input,
you can change the channel
with this guy.
But if you need to change the volume--
You know what? I think I'm fine.
Why don't you just go ahead?
I know this sounds
really confusing,
but there's actually a very
simple way to remember it.
Input 1 is the cable box
- cable box, ca--
- I think I'm just gonna take a nap.
Okay. I'm going to yoga.
Ay! That sounds like so much fun.
Oh, you should go with her, Gloria!
Oh, we should definitely
do that sometime.
I would love it. Bye!
Do you see how she gives me
the cold shoulders?
I don't even know why I try.
- Ay. Sorry.
- Oh, well, that's just Claire, you know?
She's a Pritchett.
You gotta break through those walls.
The sooner the better.
You really think so?
Yeah. Why don't you go? Now.
Forge that friendship!
Okay, I go. I have
my gym bag in the car.
Feel better!
Okay, thank you!
I'm just gonna lie here...
Some ice on my back!
I knew for a fact Claire
never returned my tupperware,
I just needed a few minutes
alone to find it.
And when I did,
I'd never have
to hear them snicker again,
"Oh, silly Cam" or "forgetful Cam,"
because revenge
is a dish best served cold.
And even better, two days later
out of 24-ounce microwave-friendly
burp-sealed pak-n-stor.
Oh, hey! I thought you
were going to the pharmacy.
- I forgot my phone.
- Oh.
I think I'm just upset about
this stupid thing with my dad.
Well, sweetie,
I'd love to hear about it
when you come back with
my heating pad from the pharmacy,
because I hurt my back, remember?
I mean, did he overreact or what?
It's just a game, right?
Well, unless there's
something more to it.
Maybe you should go talk to him.
- Yeah.
- Huh?
Oh, I should have just
kept my mouth shut.
I mean, it was such a great day.
After he thought he got
that hole-in-one,
he took us out to dinner.
He bought me my first beer.
Well, there you go.
He's probably hurt
because you marred a very special
father-son experience.
- You think?
- Ya marred it.
But you can fix it.
He's down at the club right now.
Go, Mitchell!
Un-mar that memory!
You know what?
I'm gonna do it.
- Ow.
- Sorry.
Don't worry. I'll be back soon.
Okay! I'll miss you!
Call first.
What were you thinking
saying that in front of him?
I'm sorry. It slipped out.
Besides, I figured he knew.
Mom knows.
Only because she
dragged it out of Dylan.
And she promised not to tell dad
until I left for college,
which means he might
have never found out.
Stop panicking.
We don't even know for sure
he heard what I said.
Okay. Beatrice is with the nurse.
They'll call us.
Shouldn't be too long.
We can just wait
until she's married.
Until she's... ready.
Which, apparently,
everyone is these days.
Funny, I used to think it'd be years
until everyone was ready,
but I guess I was wrong.
Wrong and naive.
Surprise!
Oh! Gloria. My God.
I came to do yoga with you.
I wasn't expecting to see you here.
Yeah, that's why I say "surprise!"
Oh, yeah. This is awful,
because I was just thinking
I might have to bail on yoga.
I have the worst headache
all of a sudden.
Oh, but yoga is good for that, Claire.
For the meditation, for the mmm...
Yeah, yeah. It's just right now
I wanna go lie down
in a dark room and breathe.
That sounds like yoga.
I... I realize that.
Yes.
- But still, I-I... should go.
- Come on.
I'm not gonna do
the class by myself.
Okay, so let's go
and get massages.
Or there's a nail salon there.
Ooh, I would love to do that
some other time,
I really would. But right now
I need to get home and lie down.
You understand, right?
- Of course.
- Okay.
You go!
And lie.
- You're better!
- Oh!
Barely. Barely, yeah.
I was just getting something
cold for my back.
Gravy? Well, if it can save
your mom's turkey,
it can save anything.
I thought you were going
to see your friend Miranda.
This one chickened out.
For someone who says
he likes girls so much,
he sure is afraid of them.
It's a dance, Luke.
Chicken dance.
Well, since you're back,
what if I give you 20 bucks,
and you guys...
Go wash my car?
Is that 20 bucks for each of us,
or both of us?
Both.
That's what I thought.
Uh-oh, check it out.
Ace is drooling over
his plaque again.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't smell you idiots come in.
Listen, I've been thinking,
maybe it's time
we retire the name "Ace."
You mean the name you
had printed on your golf cap?
- And his robe.
- You know, guys, about that--
remember how mad he got when
I yanked that cap off his head
and put it on?
You got to earn that!
Yeah, yeah, well, I'm just glad
one of those cheap hair plugs
didn't get caught in it.
Hey, for the millionth time,
they're not plugs.
So what, your hair just came back
when you turned 50?
- Unlike your wife.
- Hey, that was a blessing.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be taking out
Natalie Hobbes tonight.
Taking her out or doing her taxes?
So I'm trying to find
a way to come clean
about the hole-in-one,
when it occurs to me...
Why?
One idiot lies about his sex life,
the other dumbbell has a Ferrari
"in the shop" for years,
and moron number three
is a Hollywood stunt car driver
who gets sick when he rides
backwards in the golf cart.
So you ladies ready
to tee off or what?
- Yeah, just gotta settle up our tab.
- I took care of it.
You said you were
going to the restroom.
Ah! Can't trust a word
out of this guy's mouth.
20 years we've been falling for this.
I-I'm sorry to interrupt,
- but my dad never lied to you guys.
- Mitchell...
No, he didn't even know until today
- that he never made the hole-in-one.
- Okay.
But the fact that
he couldn't live with himself
when he found out,
and he raced down here
to confess to you,
that just shows
the kind of man he is.
He is a hole-in-one kind of man.
You never got a hole-in-one?
I didn't tell them.
So this is the gang.
Introduce me.
- Ahh.
- Score!
It's not like me and Miranda
are perfectly suited.
For one thing, she likes bad boys.
That's just not me.
I'm gonna turn on some music.
I'm sorry.
I can't unlearn how to treat a lady.
But where does that leave me?
Waiting till I'm 40 when
she looks me up on Facebook
after a failed first marriage?
Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm sick of hearing you
whine about Miranda!
- It's time to make her notice you!
- But we can't!
We got a full tank of gas,
and she's right down the block.
Now buckle up!
- Are you crazy?
- You tell me.
Lily, what is this?
Don't you rather have
a chemistry set or flash cards?
She's pretty.
No. No, she's dirty.
Look. Look at the dirt.
Let me wipe her off.
Fix that.
One of her breeds
is coming loose. Come here.
Fix that right up.
So I've completed the examination,
she did really well.
What's the prognosis?
We can fix most of her arm,
but she'll never regain
full mobility in her shoulder joint,
because they don't make
that part anymore.
Well, that's pretty good, right?
I mean, she'll look exactly the same.
No one will know.
I'll know.
I'm just saying I liked her
the way she was.
She was such a sweet little doll.
I'm sorry, doctor.
I'm having trouble
adjusting to all this.
Uh, dad, she's still
a sweet little doll.
No, she's broken.
No, she's just changed a little.
It happens. Dolls grow up.
Well, actually--
- Uh, could you...
- Yeah. Sure.
I actually have to go
give a little girl
some pretty bad news.
So, Haley...
The thing is...
Fact-- Haley's almost 18.
Fact-- I am the cool dad.
Haley, I understand
that sex is a part of life.
I can't say that
I'm thrilled to hear this,
but I'm sure you're being safe,
and I hope that you'll feel free
to talk to me about this anytime.
We should...
We should probably get Beatrice,
like, a-a cast or something,
and we can all sign it. Yeah?
Uh, yeah. Sure.
Fact-- I blew it.
This repair's probably
gonna take a little while.
Why don't you run up
to the food court
and grab us a table?
I'll get Alex and Lily.
Okay.
Do you want the counter or a booth?
Whatever seems right to you.
I trust you.
I have a cool dad.
Okay. Your turn.
Unh-unh! No way!
Do you wanna get
her attention, or not?
That was amazing!
Did you see the look
on Miranda's face?
No. But you did good, Thelma.
Please stop calling me that.
I hate that movie.
What movie?
Uh-oh! Dead end!
You gotta make a u-ey.
I don't know how to do that.
She pretended to have a headache, Cam.
She doesn't want
to spend time with me.
Maybe she just wanted to be alone.
Why?
Because some people
really value their privacy,
and you have to respect that.
I have to go.
Hola, Claire!
Gloria, you've gotta stop doing that!
Were you going back
to the yoga class without me?
No, that is not why I came back.
I don't understand you.
Why you don't want
to spend time with me?
Everybody wants
to spend time with me!
Even the lady that did my nails
wants to take me to pilates.
I didn't come back here to do yoga.
I don't do yoga. It's a cover, okay?
Look...
I know that from the outside,
it seems like I have
everything together.
No, not really.
My point is that my life
can be very stressful.
And I have found a way
to cope with that stress.
And it's my little secret.
And I'm not proud of it.
- Hey, Claire. See you inside.
- Hey!
Is that what you do?
No. No!
Okay. You're coming with me.
Come in.
But listen to me. Gloria...
It has to stay between us.
This is my sacred space.
It's just such a great release.
- Thank you for not judging me.
- Why would I?
If anything,
it makes me like you more.
- Mm.
- So how often do you come here?
Not that often. No.
Hey.
Maybe a little often.
That's so sad.
I live with four teenagers.
You live with two adults.
- You have no idea...
- No, no, no. It's so sad
that you come here so often
and that's the best
that you can shoot.
And that's with pretty nails.
But improper stance. I...
- Practice more.
- Okay.
Here you go, Ace...
I mean... what is your real name?
Jay.
- Dad, I--
- I told you, forget about it.
All right.
I-I just want you to know
I get why you're upset, okay?
That--that day
you got the hole-in-one,
it meant a lot to you.
And... I... I marred it.
But it meant a lot to me, too.
We had a steak dinner,
you gave me my first beer,
and, uh...
It was one of the greatest days
we ever spent together.
And it wasn't about some
meaningless hole-in-one,
it was about us.
No. It was about a hole-in-one.
Yes. Yes. A-a little bit, maybe.
But mostly, it was
about how we bonded.
I thought I hit a ball
straight from the tee
really, really far
into a tiny hole.
Okay.
Well, when will I learn?
And it wasn't your first beer, anyway.
Yes, it was, dad, but I wouldn't
expect you to remember.
It was your 14th birthday.
You asked me for a sip of mine.
Your mom yelled at you
in front of all your friends,
said you were just a baby.
You ran outside in tears...
Which, unfortunately,
supported your mom's argument.
Anyway, I came out
with a couple of beers.
We drank 'em on the porch
watching the storm clouds coming in.
I had completely
forgotten about that.
You know, you're--
you're unbelievable.
- Just when I peg you as some--
- Storm Stevens! That's it!
Give me something.
I'm gonna write it right here.
- Before I forget. "Storm Stevens."
- Stevens.
What were we just
talking about? Just now?
- No?
- Mnh-mnh.
Come on, Lily.
Let's see if Beatrice is ready.
Hey, dad?
I know I'm way too old for this,
but do you think
I could get this doll?
Her name's Genevieve,
and she's developing
a vaccine for...
Yes, you can get the doll.
You can get
as many dolls as you want.
It's $200.
Or one is fine.
I know you're here.
Hello.
I have a bad feeling about this.
What if one of your neighbors saw us?
Maybe we should just confess.
We will...
In 20 years.
Huh?
You heard grandpa.
There's a statute of limitations,
which is a good thing
because we still need
to take Lily down.
Nah, let her be the cute one.
We don't need that anymore.
We're bad boys now.
Yeah. I like that.
Bad boys.
Your mom!
Oh, my God.
Cam!
Um, this had a lid?
I'll see you guys later.
I'm going to Abby's.
Bye, honey. Have fun.
Have fun, you! With Abby!
We've confirmed Abby's
a real person and a female?
Yes, sweetie. We met her.
Honey, we can't treat
Haley differently
just because we both know
what we know about her.
I know. I just need time.
So Dylan told you?
Why didn't he tell me?
He and I used to share everything.
You're upset about a lot of things.
Okay, I won't obsess over it.
I just wanna ask you one thing.
How long have you known?
Three months.
So this giant thing
happened to our first born,
and you kept me in the dark
about it for three whole months?
I'm sorry. I just wasn't sure how you'd--
Okay.
Thank you.
Synced by YYeTs, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net