Please, please, please, please.
Okay, what is this?
We're making sure I'm tall enough
to ride all the rides
at Disneyland.
Without having
to spike up my hair.
Buddy...
We are good to go.
Sweet!
I have been waiting
for this day
ever since the doctor pointed
to the ultrasound of
your mom's womb and said,
"either that's a fifth limb,
or you got a boy."
Okay, no. Gross.
All right...
I want everybody
to eat a lot at home
because "the happiest
place on earth"
is also home to the most
expensive churro on Earth.
Come on. This is gonna be awesome.
Who doesn't love
a day at Disneyland?
Can't you and mom
go without me?
You're the kid.
I think we need you to get in.
Well, it couldn't come
on a worst day.
The technology sector is tanking.
We're doing a stock market
project in school,
and today's the last day.
We all get a thousand
fake dollars to invest,
and as the market
closed yesterday,
I'm in the lead.
I may not be the tallest
or the most athletic,
but someday
I will be the richest,
which is good because
the ladies love that,
and I've grown accustomed
to a certain lifestyle.
Do you really wants girls who
only want you for your money?
I'd like to have that option.
Manny, put the stock away
and put your ears on.
Mom, I don't think you have
to wear one of these.
Be a kid! Put them on!
Really? Those shoes?
What?
Do you know how much walking
you have to do at Disneyland?
Why do you think they have
so many fat people on scooters?
I like wearing the high heels.
I'm fine.
It's just like that jacket
you refuse to bring
when I say, "take a jacket."
"Don't tell me what to do!
I'm fine!"
Huh? And you're not fine.
You're cold and shivering,
and I look like the jerk who
won't give his wife a jacket,
so I do, and then
I'm cold and shivering,
and I brought a jacket.
Are you done with your
boring jacket story?
Because we're going to hit traffic.
Tell you one thing.
I'm not gonna give you my shoes.
Ah! That must be Ethan.
Who's Ethan?
Didn't I tell you?
My friend Bethenny's nephew
is coming with us today.
He moved to town
to go to college.
He's very nice, very smart,
big hockey player.
I know what you're doing.
Really? She was so subtle.
Haley has a thing for bad boys,
which was so me.
Clearly.
So if she's going to be
leaving the nest soon,
we'd prefer it was not
on the back of a motorcycle.
My college roommate
had a motorcycle.
Man, I had some good times
on the back of that thing.
I can't believe you did this.
I'm not gonna babysit Bethenny's nephew.
Alex can have him.
Okay, I don't need your rejects.
Hi. Hi, Ethan!
I'm so glad you could make it.
Thanks for inviting me.
Sure.
Hi. I'm Al--
My 14-year-old sister.
Ethan, was it?
Yeah.
Synced by YYeTs, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
And that's my grandpa
and his wife Gloria
and her son Manny.
Wow. You guys have a big family.
Big family.
She likes him!
Yeah, who wouldn't?
Where'd you find him,
a Tommy Hilfiger catalog?
He got a 2200 on his S.A.T.s.
And those eyes...
Okay, did you get him
for Haley or for you?
Mitchell.
You know, I haven't been here
since dad brought us
when we were kids.
Ohh, yeah. Remember?
You cried in the Abraham Lincoln thing.
Hey, he's a great president,
and it was the first
robot I ever saw.
When Claire and Mitchell were young,
their mom and I were gonna
take them to Disneyland.
But that morning, Dede and I
got in this huge fight
over something or other--
surprise, surprise--
and I ended up taking
them on my own.
Claire's biggest fear
was running into the evil queen.
My biggest fear was
that I married her.
Okay, people over 46 inches,
first stop-- Indiana Jones!
Have fun on the teacups, Lily.
Okay, let's do this.
Oh, okay, wait just
a second here, everybody.
All right.
Is that a leash?
No, it's a child safety tether.
This way, sweetie.
It-- it's a leash.
Don't-- don't judge us.
Go on.
We have a runner.
Lily is going through a phase--
at least... Oh, we hope it's a phase.
She bolts every chance she gets.
Lily!
So we had no choice
to put her on a child safety tether.
It's a leash.
And we did have a choice.
Lily, sweetie, don't pull.
Lily, heel!
Dad.
If I'd had known you guys
were gonna do this,
I'd have brought Stella.
It was Cam's idea.
So much for the united front.
I'll have you know, despite
all your jokes, Lily enjoys it.
Okay, sweetie, you're not helping.
You're not helping.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
You guys, is that Dylan?
What?
Oh, jeez.
Dylan?!
Oh. Hey!
Uh, what are you... I didn't
even know you were in town.
Either did I...
Know you were in town.
This town. Anaheim.
I thought you were still in Wyoming.
I was, uh...
But, um...
Oh, shoot.
You know, I, uh, gotta meet up
with some friends
and I'm... really late.
It was nice to see you, Haley,
and everybody.
Hi.
And dude I don't know.
I'm Ethan.
It's nice to meet you.
And polite dude I don't know.
Did Haley used to date
that guy or something?
Yep. You date her, that's
the club you're joining.
Of course he would
still look amazing.
Does he? I hadn't noticed.
Did you know that Ethan
plays the trumpet?
No great surprise
with those lips of his, huh?
Coo-coo-ca-choo, Mrs. Robinson.
Okay, buddy, moment of truth.
Yes!
- This is gonna be so awesome!
- Yeah!
In 45 minutes,
this is gonna be so awesome!
Yeah!
Look, Reuben,
I have some underperformers
I have to unload,
and I don't have access
to a computer.
Log in as moneydelgado--
Manny!
By all means, Reuben,
go get a popsicle
while the Nikkei closes.
I wanna be a pauper.
Mom, my stocks just took a dive.
Your phone is about
to take a dive.
Come on! Where do we want to go next?
Oh! Ethan and I want
to try the haunted mansion.
There is no you and Ethan.
Let's go to the jungle cruise.
It's right there.
Why? Tired of walking
in those heels?
No. You tired of being
with a hot wife?
Well, well, well.
What do you know?
Another caring parent
with a child safety tether.
See? We're not the only
people who use them.
Hi! Aren't they adorable?
Oh, and look at your cutie!
Oh, well, yes.
She just wanted to say hi.
Oh. Sorry.
They're a little feisty today.
Oh! No problem.
She's friendly.
Rex, gentle.
Oh, his-- his name's Rex, huh?
Yeah.
Oh, okay. Lily, no, sweetie.
Lily, um...
Oh. Sorry. He-- he just gets excited.
Oh, yeah, no-- oh, no problem.
Lily, stop moving, sweetie.
Stop moving.
Okay, you got this.
Okay. Okay. Good girl! Good girl!
Sorry.
You know what the fight
with Dede was about?
I taped a football game over
an episode of "Dallas."
Who bails on a family trip
to Disneyland
over something like that?
Ironically, Dallas
was playing in the game.
And I remember pointing
that out to her,
and then I remember
a video cassette flying at my head.
You do not play the cello.
I do. Even geekier-- I'm good.
Okay, answer me this--
I will answer you this.
Why do people carry cellos around?
You know, people aren't expected
to lug a piano around.
What's the cutoff?
I know, right?
Like, go where the cello is.
Oh, look at this.
I think I've inadvertently
set up my 14-year-old
with a college boy.
The boy was your doing?
Yes. Yes, and he was perfect,
and Haley was into him until,
of course, we ran into Dylan.
I mean, come on, dad.
What are the odds of that happening?
It's a small world.
Yes, it is.
- You see what I did there?
- I did.
- 'Cause it's a ride.
- I got it. Got it, dad. I got it.
It's so frustrating because...
I know I can't run
Haley's like for her,
but if she would let me,
I would be so good at it.
Right, 'cause parents always know
what's best for their kids.
You remember that nice
girl at the office
I tried to fix Mitch up with?
No offense, dad,
but I think I probably have
a better sense of what
my kids need than you did.
I think it's cute you think that.
Mom!
It was so awesome!
The jeep was jerking around...
And--and there was a lot
of sharp turns and big drops.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
It just kept going.
Wow. You okay?
Great. Why wouldn't I be?
Because you're kinda leaning on me.
Well, isn't that
what a marriage is?
Ohh. Oh, Alex, stop touching him.
Oh. You look like hell.
I'm feeling a little dizzy.
I think that ride
did something to me.
The fluid in your
inner ear is thickening.
That's what happens
when you get old.
It is?
Yeah, you can't take the motion.
I gotta pop a dramamine
to get in my swivel chair.
That is not it.
I'm king of the roller coasters.
I think I just put
too big of a whipped cream smile
on my pancake this morning.
You guys wanna
go on Matterhorn?
Luke, I think me and your dad
are gonna sit this one out,
maybe get one them big pickles.
No! You're gonna have to eat
that pickle on your own, Jay.
I still got a few good years left.
Luke, wait up!
I'll race you there!
I'm good. I'm good.
Okay, everybody's looking at us.
I haven't been judged by this many people
since I forgot my canvas
bags at whole foods.
Yeah, well, maybe they're staring
because we have what they want.
Whoa! Oh, a pet daughter.
'Cause that...
You know, I don't care
what people think.
If I thought it would keep
my daughter safe,
I would have a kangaroo pouch
sewn into my midriff.
That's gonna work out really
well for you as a single parent.
Okay, we just got a glare
from Mr. Socks-with-sandals.
All right, that's it.
Lily, I'm gonna take off this leash.
I think it's a mistake.
But I don't want you to run away,
'cause that would be
very, very unsafe,
and if we lost you,
you'd be very scared,
and we'd be very sad. Okay?
Okay.
All right.
See, Cam? You treat her
like a human being
and she acts like one.
Chip 'n Dale!
Oh, great. Now she's chasing squirrels.
Lily!
Honey, come on!
Lily! Lily!
Hey! How was Splash Mountain?
It was great! Maybe we go again.
No, thanks.
There was no reception in there.
You know how many bars I had?
Zip-a-Dee-doo-dah.
Reuben, talk to me!
Must be nice to get out
of those shoes for a minute.
I don't know what you talking about.
Nothing. I'm just making conversation.
Hey. Check it out.
I bought one of those
souvenir photos
with you and Manny on the ride.
Boy, it looks like
you're having a good time.
Wait a minute.
What's that in your hand?
Are those shoes?
I'm not even sure
that that is us, Jay.
Why are you walking
around in pain?
Just admit the shoes
were a bad idea.
I am not in pain.
I just didn't want my favorite
walking shoes to get wet there.
Okay, my bad.
Well, we've gotta meet
everybody in Tomorrowland,
so we'd better get movin'
'cause it's all the way
on the other side of the park.
I'm fine.
You just try to keep up with us.
I can't take this.
Dad, throw your hands up! It's fun!
Oh, yeah, it is fun!
Reuben, if you heard about
that stock at a birthday party,
it's already too late.
Gloria!
Gloria, sit down for a second.
I'm fine, Jay.
Please?
Look...
You may not be in pain...
Okay.
But I'm in pain just
thinking you're in pain.
So humor me for one minute.
What are those?
There wasn't a big selection
at the Bibbidi Bobbidi boutique.
Are you crazy?
I cannot walk around
in public with these...
things.
They're so yellow and so ugly.
And... and they're so softy
and so comfortable.
Jay, what is this?
Thank you for going
shopping for me.
Thank you for worrying
about my feet.
Thank you for giving me
your jacket when I'm cold.
You're such a good man, Jay.
Thank you. Mmm.
I didn't expect you to be so...
So nice.
Why are you so surprised?
Now please don't go all Latin
on me when I say this.
Is it possible
you get angry from time to time
because you're always wearing...
uncomfortable shoes?
Maybe.
Can you get me a couple of more?
Maybe they have purple?
Whatever you want, honey.
All I'm saying is,
it seemed like you
were pretty into Ethan
until Dylan showed up.
Don't get me wrong.
Ethan's nice, but he's no Dylan.
Maybe that's a good thing?
Why? Because Dylan's a free spirit?
He's too edgy for you?
He plays by his own rules?
Oh, my God.
What?
I beg of you to turn around
and experience with me
the greatest moment of my life.
Your rebel boyfriend's a Dapper Dan.
Maybe that's not him.
Dylan!
Uh, uh, sorry.
Sorry. Um...
It certainly seems like him.
Oh, my God. He looked like
those old pictures of dad
from High School.
So anyway, I've really been
into street art lately.
Oh, there's a really great exhibit downtown.
I'll take you.
Oh, on what, your razor scooter?
Mom wants you.
I-I-I...
Ethan! I've been looking
all over for you!
I remember I was on
Pirates of the Caribbean,
and this whole fight with
Dede was really eating at me.
And there was this angry
animatronic wench
with a rolling pin, chasing
some poor pirate around.
They were on a track,
running in circles,
so he could never
get away from her.
And I remember thinking,
I can't save you, buddy,
but I'm getting off this ride.
And-- and we were
going around a corner,
and I was screaming
and I swallowed a bug.
Oh, being tail is everything
that I dreamed it would be.
What should we do next?
Sit down.
Where we gonna sit down?
The ground. Here,
this is good right here. Oh!
Are you okay, dad?
No, I'm not okay.
I hate to tell you this,
but these rides are killing me.
B-but you're
the king of roller coasters.
I know!
Something happens
when you get older.
Guess you can't take it.
One of my favorite
things in the world
is doing stupid
fun stuff with you,
like pogo stick basketball
or trying to get a swing to go
all the way around.
Next time, we should sit
on a fire extinguisher.
Yes, or a bottle of coke
and some mentos.
Honestly, though,
the way I'm feeling right now,
I don't know if there's
gonna be a next time.
Dad, we can always
find cool stuff to do.
Even if you're old
and in a wheelchair,
I'll take you to the mall
and push you as fast
as you wanna go.
Really? You'd do that?
Heck, yeah.
And we'll pop some wheelies, too.
That sounds fun.
And I'll take you to the top
of a huge hill and just let go.
Okay, we'll nail down
the specifics later,
but that... that's really nice.
So do you still wanna talk or--
No, go. Ride Space Mountain.
Uh, at the end,
when they take a picture,
do something hilarious
for both of us.
You're gonna die.
When you see it,
not 'cause you're old.
Lily! Lily, stop!
Dad! Dad, grab her!
Hey, I gotcha, you little monkey!
Thank you.
Hey, Cam, I got her.
We're in Fantasyland.
Where are you?
Okay, it's Toontown, not Toonton.
You've been watching too much PBS.
Thank you.
All right, honey, come here.
I don't like this thing.
Yeah?
Well, I don't like running
like a crazy person
through Downton Disney--
Downtown Disney.
I don't know what to do.
Well, the leash is not the answer.
You want my help?
Yes, please!
'Cause I can fix this for you
in about two minutes.
Come on, baby girl.
Come with me.
We'll be right back.
Okay.
Where we going?
Oh, this way?
Manny, you don't sound very happy
for a kid that is flying
an elephant.
I lost to Durkas. It's not fair.
He wanted to buy IBM because
he thought it was funny to say.
Well, I'm glad that you lost.
Fake money has changed you.
Where is the Manny that used
to stop to smell the roses?
He took a bath
on a solar start-up in San Jose.
You have been so busy burying
your face in your phone
that you barely said
hello to your family,
you gave Winnie the Pooh
the cold shoulder,
and you haven't even noticed
that pretty girl
in the blue elephant
that has been smiling at you.
Not my type, but
still it's nice to be noticed.
You see what happens
when you're not burying
your head in business?
You're right.
I'll try to be more present.
What the heck's on your feet?
They're slippers!
They're like pillows.
Attagirl.
You're welcome.
Look. Your dad got her
baby high heels,
which we said we were
never gonna let her wear.
I love 'em.
You look gorgeous, sweetie.
Oh, my gosh. You felt
people judged us before?
Wait till they meet little Miss Anaheim.
Who cares? Look at her.
She can barely move.
Thank you, dad.
You know what? She's got pretty
good gams for a 3-year-old.
Cheese!
Got it. Thanks, Little John.
Thank you!
Ooh, they have corn dogs.
We gotta get one before we go back.
They are legendary.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Haley!
It's me. Dylan.
I'm in the bear suit.
I borrowed it to talk to you.
Why are you dancing like that?
This is what Little John does.
Maybe.
I don't know what movie
this dude is from.
I'm not even supposed
to be talking to you.
Well, I'm not talking to you.
No, you can talk.
I know, but I'm mad.
You came back to town
and didn't even call me.
I was embarrassed.
I lost my job at the dude ranch,
and I wanted to get
my act together first.
But the four dweebs on a bike act?
Hey, the Dapper Dans
are a main street tradition
since 1959.
Hey, what's going on?
Nothing.
I still love her, Ethan.
Okay, how do you know my name?
It's Dylan.
Look, I don't wanna harsh your day,
but I never stopped
loving Haley and I never will!
I-is this some sort of joke?
Do I look like I'm joking?
Dylan, let's not do this now.
It has to be now.
I've got a parade at 3:00.
Hey, seriously, dude, back off.
Okay, that was my face.
And you're the one
who needs to back off.
You...
Okay. This thing's kinda heavy.
I can't get up.
Ethan? Ethan, what is going on?
What are you doing?
Uh, hi, Mrs. Dunphy.
Help me up.
No.
If I could get up, I would-- uhh!
Come on, Lily sweetie.
Keep up, honey.
Come on. Phil, you don't look
like you're doing very well.
Maybe because I officially
became an old man
back there at Thunder Mountain.
Oh, my goodness.
You are burning up.
You might have the flu.
A bunch of guys
at work had the flu,
and we all drink orange juice
out of the same carton.
We should get cups.
Luke, did you hear that?!
I have the flu!
Oh, gosh, no.
Glad we didn't share that pickle.
Hey, everybody.
Oh, hey, hey, guys.
Where's Ethan?
Oh, he's staying.
He ran into some friends.
But Dylan got fired, so...
don't freak out.
We have to give him a ride home.
And we're back together.
Yay.
Hey, no one goes home
till we hit the Lincoln thing.
Yawn.
Don't even try to fight it.
Yeah, he made us go
when we were kids.
Come on, people! It's a robotic president!
What's not to love?
A robotic president?
So my plan was,
drive Claire and Mitchell home,
put them to bed,
pour myself a big
tumbler of scotch,
and tell Dede it was over.
But on the way out,
we made one last stop.
If destruction be our lot,
we ourselves
must be its author and finisher.
As a nation of free men,
we must live through all times...
I don't know what happened.
Maybe it's what robot Lincoln
said about a man's duty
or keeping the union together.
Maybe I just chickened out.
But I realized that
staying with my kids
was more important
than leaving my wife.
Now that's not the right
decision for everyone,
but it was the right
decision for me.
And in that faith,
let us, to the end,
dare to do our duty
as we understand it.
So I stuck it out until
they were grown...
Jay, you want to join me
in the jacuzzi?
And the universe rewarded me.
Here we go!
Hey, dad, roller coast fist bump.
What was that?
Is this gonna be so awesome!
Close your eyes.
It makes it more fun.
Oh, yeah. That is more fun.
Synced by YYeTs, corrected by gloriabg
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net