We have to tell him.
I hope he's okay.
Walt, our elderly
next door neighbor, died.
He and Luke were pretty close,
so we have to tell him.
I'm a little nervous about it.
I think we should
break it to him slowly.
Like how?
Well, first we'd say,
"Luke, your friend Walt has a cold.
You shouldn't go over there."
Next day... "bad news.
Walt's in the hospital,"
but he's still cracking jokes
with the nurses."
Next day... "they're
trying an experimental drug."
Fingers crossed."
Next day... "his body rebelled.
He's in a coma."
Next day...
he rallies, next day... coma,
next day... coma, next day... coma,
next day... eye flutter...
Stop. Just stop. Stop. Oh.
Oh, Luke, we have
some bad news for you.
It's about Walt.
I'm afraid...
He passed away.
Um, it happened yesterday.
He finished writing
an angry letter
to the postmaster general,
and he just fell asleep.
Okay.
It was very peaceful.
Not the letter.
That was full of threats, but...
It's okay to be sad, honey.
You two were really good friends.
It must be quite a shock
to hear that...
Walt's dead.
Um, so do you
wanna talk about it or...
I'm okay.
Can I get back to my video game?
It's paused.
Oh, um, sure.
Yeah, buddy.
Come here.
How weird was that?
I know. Crazy weird.
It's like he had
no feelings at all.
I'm more worried about
the one you showed.
What's with all the smiling?
What are you talking about?
That grin.
"Walt's dead."
You looked like the joker.
I didn't smile.
You did. It's like
a weird coping mechanism.
You did the same thing when
you told him his hamster died.
I don't know what
you thought you saw, Phil,
but our child just got
some terrible news
and had absolutely no reaction.
Doesn't that concern you?
Yeah. He probably just
needs time to process it.
Hmm. Do you think?
Yeah, honey.
Death is a profound thing
to deal with at any age.
We all manage it differently.
Some people lock up their feelings.
Others...
reach out for comfort,
finding some way to reaffirm
their connection to life...
- You're joking.
- Oh.
www.SUBTITULOS.es
-DIFUNDE LA PALABRA-
Hola, Haley.
Gloria, I was driving by
and saw this outside your door,
so here.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Hey, so since I'm already here,
my friend was gonna have
a pool party tonight,
but he got sick.
Could we have it here?
Mm. Good thing
that you saw this paper
or if not, you would have
never been able to ask.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, but Jay and I are going
to Mitch and Cam's
for dinner tonight.
I'm just thinking out loud here.
What if I get a chaperone
that my parents approve of?
Would it be okay then?
Well, I guess so.
You know, it would be good for Manny
to have a little bit of fun.
Do you mind if he stays
here for the party?
Mind? The plan depended on him.
I don't suppose
you've thought of a chaperone?
Of course not, mom,
because it's going to be a wild party
and I'm trying to get away
with something, as usual.
Yes, I thought of a chaperone...
my Uncle who already
said he would do it.
But if that's gonna be a problem,
- I think I should just call everybody...
- Sorry.
Sorry. Sorry. It's fine.
And thank you, Uncle Manny.
Can you help a little bit?
This... if I... if I push down,
does that...
Yeah, that's helping.
That's helping.
No, it's not helping.
It's 'cause it's stuck.
I can't believe
I got 'em this stuck.
I've built beds my whole life...
bunk beds, dog beds, cow beds.
Okay, I'm calling you on cow beds.
Oh, that's my dad!
Okay. He can help.
He's built a boat, a dock, a lake...
Uh, he did not build a lake.
Okay, from now on, just stop
after you say the second thing.
So the cabin door swings open.
Damned if there wasn't
a lady pilot in there.
Yeah, well,
I hate to admit it,
but it throws me, too.
I do prefer a man.
Are we gonna have
this conversation again?
- Hey, Merle.
- Hey. How are you?
- Yeah, ooh.
- Okay. Nice to see you.
All right, let me grab that for you.
No. No. I got it.
I will take that beer you were
about to offer me, though.
Oh, yeah. Coming right up.
And you know where everything is.
Go have a seat.
Oh, I missed a call from my dad.
Oh, let me guess.
Is he calling to cancel?
What's his excuse this time?
You know, that's a really
mean thing to assume, Cam.
I really wish you'd give
my dad a break for once.
Oh, please.
You know Jay doesn't like my dad.
He thinks he's some
bumpkin from the sticks.
Well, I will have you know
that Merle Stonewall Tucker
is one of the most respected farmers
in all of Hell's Hollow, Missouri.
Okay, you're not hearing yourself.
My dad likes him just fine.
Come on.
- Hello?
- Hey, dad. It's me.
Mitch.
I'm sick.
I gotta cancel tonight.
Yeah. Yeah, 6:00.
We're really looking forward to it.
What are you doing?
I just said I can't come.
I don't know.
Let me ask.
My dad wants to know
red or white?
Um, uh, red.
Red. And I'm sorry.
Okay.
Yeah, Cam says red.
Okay. Yeah, he's...
he's so happy...
Knock it off, old man.
You are not sick.
Why do you always do this?
Okay, look, between you and me,
Mervis kind of bugs me.
Okay, first of all, it's Merle.
Mervis isn't a name.
Mervis is a sound.
And second of all, he's...
he's my partner's father.
Okay? You're coming.
Okay, dad, why don't you settle in?
We don't have plans until dinner
tonight with Jay and Gloria.
I-I don't like that guy.
What? That's...
you like everybody.
Not Jay.
The guy rubs me the wrong way.
Every time I try
to do something nice,
he makes this cranky face, like...
Okay. Well, you know what?
I'm gonna chalk this up to jet lag
for you because
it's not like you at all.
Okay, you have to make an effort.
It's my partner's father.
Now give me the growl
that means "okay."
Good.
Did you know Walt had a daughter
he was completely estranged from?
His lawyer said she wouldn't
even honor his last request
to toss his dog tags in the ocean.
Can you imagine?
Phil, do we really have
to go through this again?
I told you, I would
do everything possible
to make sure that your skeleton
ends up in a science class
at a women's college.
No, it's just sad.
That's half of what would
keep me going in my old age...
remembering all
the good times with the kids.
Teaching Luke to ride his bike,
Haley at the father-daughter dance...
Taking Alex for her first pony ride.
You never took Alex
on a pony ride.
- Oh, right. That was just me.
- Mm-hmm.
But Alex and I went, um,
Oh, no. That was Haley.
Mm-hmm.
Phil, look. It's Luke.
He's going into Walt's house.
Oh, he's saying good-bye.
He just needed a little time.
It's so sweet and so sad.
He's so much more sensitive
than I ever thought.
They had a special bond.
I wouldn't be surprised
if one day he wrote a book
like "Tuesdays with Morrie."
I never read it.
Did that guy steal Morrie's TV?
Now setting a course for adventure!
Beep. Boop. Beep. Bop.
Boop. Boop. Boop.
I've had great experiences
with all my kids,
but I... I might have
fallen behind a bit with Alex.
My fault completely.
Adventure?
We are throwing dog tags
into an already polluted ocean
where they will probably
choke an otter.
80% my fault.
Honey, we're bringing
closure to a man's life.
We'll hike up
to the scenic overlook,
where apparently,
Walt proposed to his wife,
wait for the light to be just right,
say a few words.
Share some memories.
That's kind of poetic.
Kind of navajo.
Now you're getting it.
We'll be sending him off
with a level of dignity,
that if we're lucky,
someday we'll experience, too.
It's called...
Hey. What do you got there?
Walt's old TV?
He said I could take
one thing after he died.
I wish he would've said two things.
I would've taken that phone
with the big buttons.
I bet you guys had
some really good times
watching this thing, right?
No. I just wanted a TV in my room.
You know, Luke,
there might be a nicer way
to honor Walt's memory.
What do you mean?
Well, I mean,
you guys liked to garden.
We could, uh, we could
take one of his flowers
and plant it in our yard,
and then every spring, when...
There we go.
Sweetie, how are you feeling?
You sad? Angry?
Confused? Frustrated?
You know you can talk to me.
I know, but I can't see through you.
Could you scootch?
No. No. You know, this is not okay.
It's going back.
What?
He said I could pick one thing.
This isn't picking.
It's looting, and it's going back.
You are so mean.
When Walt used to look
through those binoculars
and say, "your dad's one lucky man,"
he was wrong.
Hi, Haley.
Hi. Stef, Sam, this is Manny.
What's up, dude?
Kitchen's over there
and pool's in the back.
So where are your parents?
They're not coming.
I was told there'd be a chaperone.
There is. It's you.
My parents are totally fine with it.
Well, exits,
fire extinguisher, burn kit.
Okay, let's have some fun.
I believe I was clear
the bedrooms were off-limits.
Young lady, I don't think
you're ready up here
for what you're planning
to do up there.
Ugh. Not on my watch.
Oh, this was a delicious meal, Mitchell.
I wish my wife
could cook a roast like this.
You got a good one there, son.
Oh, well, I'm very lucky,
just like you and mama.
Never had a bad patch.
Except the winter of '85.
Remember that?
Oh, I spent several nights
in the cow bed then.
Oh, here. Let me help you.
No, no, no. You sit... sit down.
- Let... lets us guys catch up
here a little bit. - Yeah.
I'll tell you why
I don't like that guy...
and I could never
say this to Mitch...
he treats my son like
the wife in the relationship.
Always has.
Before we get to dessert,
I've got some presents here.
- Oh!
- Oh, you didn't need to, dad.
Love it!
- Oh, Merle, thank you so much.
- Oh!
Look at this. Oh.
So elegant, huh?
Oh, this is so sweet.
I think I might cry.
Don't.
Dad, I really gotta get home.
I know. I know.
You gotta do homework.
But you can't expect me
to see a sign that says,
"world's greatest milk shake... 50 miles,"
and not drive to it.
Sorry, sweetie.
Machine's broken.
I just wanted a special day
with my daughter,
you know, like
"the time we gave an old man
a dramatic sendoff at the beach,"
or... or "the time
we drove 100 miles"
for the world's greatest milk shake."
Call us when it happens, Francine.
Oh, it could be
before you get home.
I'm a week past
my due date as it is.
What can I do for you?
"The time we delivered a baby."
We were the only ones there,
and she was so close,
the sound of a pin dropping
could induce labor.
Okay!
What looks good?
Well, um...
Bam!
Wh-whoa!
Kids love to destroy things.
Not Manny. He's always been
a little bit too serious.
I would make the buildings,
and he would inspect them.
And if they weren't up to code,
ay, ay, ay, the paperwork.
I remember Cam, one time,
rolled a tractor tire right
through a chicken coop.
He was 3 at the time.
I remember Mitchell, one time,
karate-chopped
a plate glass window.
Got 17 stitches.
Ah, yes. I love that story.
Which one of the Charlie's Angels
he was being again?
- That's not important.
- I think it was Farrah.
Yeah, the thing I remember is,
when Mitchell told that story,
how... how he giggled
all the way through.
I'm sure he wasn't giggling.
Oh, yeah, he...
he was giggling, all right.
No, see, Mitchell
has a booming laugh.
It's Cameron, actually...
has the high laugh.
You know...
No, I think Mitch has
a higher laugh than...
it's...
No, it's...
Listen to them.
Best of friends.
Oh, man.
I'm sorry I doubted Jay.
He's been lovely.
Oh, well, confession time...
he kinda didn't want to come.
Well, you're gonna laugh
because my dad was kinda
hoping he wouldn't.
Wha?
Oh. They just needed to get
to know one another better.
I am so glad that we did this.
Yeah, me, too.
Oh, that's so funny.
Wh-what did your dad
not like about my dad?
Oh, well, you know Jay.
He's a Teddy bear,
but sometimes he can kinda
come off as a tough guy.
Yeah, that's true.
As an actual tough guy,
you can kinda see how that
would rub my dad the wrong way.
Oh, it's... I-I could see that,
but, you know,
my dad's actually
pretty tough himself, so...
Oh, yeah, city tough,
you know, not farm tough.
Uh-huh. You mean cities,
where there are gangs,
as to opposed to farms,
where there are ducks?
Oh, boy.
It's really jammed in there.
Yeah. Why don't you
hop on in there, dad?
My dad's got it.
All right, let's see here.
Hang on, Merle.
- Wait. Here. Huh? Hold.
- Yeah, that's good.
Oh. It's coming.
We got it. We got it.
- Oh, there you go.
- There you go.
Cam, why don't you go get us
a couple of cold ones?
We'll finish this job up in here.
Sure thing, dad. You earned it.
Yeah. Good helping there, Merle.
Okay.
Wow. It's hot in here.
It's, like, 80 degrees.
He did that so
the Meals on Wheels lady
had to take off her sweater.
How do we turn on
the lights in here?
Of course.
So, Luke, now that we're here,
you wanna take a minute and
say what Walt meant to you?
Nope.
Luke, you are going through
something huge in your life,
and I'm concerned that
you're not processing it
in a normal, healthy way.
I'm sad. I'm so very sad.
No, I don't just wanna hear
what you think I wanna hear.
- I want you to really tell me...
- Hi.
It's Kim with Meals on Wheels.
Oh. Hi, Luke. Where's Walt?
It is like a sauna in here.
How does he stand it?
Walt! I'm waiting for my hug!
I have some sad news about Walt.
He's dead.
What?
He died last night.
Are you joking?
No.
He had a heart attack.
A man died.
You're... you're smiling.
I'm not smiling.
You are, mom.
It's kinda creepy.
Well, hello? Walt?
What's going on?
Something happen to Walt?
Well, I'm sure you can imagine.
He sick?
He's in the hospital?
Oh, my God. Just tell me.
Mm! Okay.
He is... dead.
- He is?
- Yeah, he's dead.
What are you doing
with your mouth?
Nothing. She's smiling.
She thinks it's funny.
I don't. I don't think it's funny.
- I'm not smiling.
- I'm not leaving this with you.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I just found out my face does this.
Wow, mom. That was so wrong.
Well, it's... it's called
a coping mechanism, Luke.
Some people repress their feelings
and some people just smile.
But d... it doesn't matter.
Just put the TV in the den.
Let's get out of here.
It doesn't go in the den.
It goes right here.
I can see it from my room.
Sometimes I'd wake up
in the middle of the night
and look down here.
If the TV was on,
I knew he was up,
and I don't know,
I guess I'm gonna miss that.
Yeah. That's...
Yeah.
Is that any better?
Yeah, it still feels just,
you know, a little wobbly.
Oh! Oh, my God.
Okay, no, no, no.
That's... that's fine.
Thank you. Thank you.
Okay, it's "go" time.
Oh, hey, doc.
It's okay. It's just a cramp.
Can I get you guys anything else?
Please, no.
He's already made me eat
the world's greatest
everything on the menu.
Dad, why are you acting like this?
Is this about Walt dying?
No. It's about what he didn't do
when he was alive...
have a special bond
with his daughter.
I don't want to be that kind of dad.
I want to be Eugene Cernan.
Who's Eugene cernan?
"Apollo 17" astronaut,
last man on the moon,
coolest dad of all time.
When he was leaving the moon,
he reached down
and wrote his daughter's initials
into the lunar surface.
Since there's no atmosphere...
There'll be there forever.
Wow. So every time she looks in the sky,
she knows there's a message
just for her.
Exactly. That's why dads
everywhere hate Eugene Cernan.
Oh, no.
Okay, "hate's" a strong word.
It's just...
I'm trying to make...
Oh. Oh, boy.
Honey. Okay.
I really wanna help, but
you know when someone yawns,
it makes you yawn?
You're not gonna yawn, are you?
I already yawned a little in my mouth.
Oh, God.
Jay, I want to thank you
for helping me do this.
I know Cam appreciates
not having to do it all on his own.
What? What's that face?
You really wanna know?
Sure.
Sometimes I think you treat my son
like the woman
in their relationship.
- What?
- Like those watches.
Cam's was all big and manly.
The other one
looked like something
Grace Kelly would wear.
Well, that's just because
Mitch has a more slender wrist
than Cam does. That's all.
It's skinny, not slender.
And you're honestly telling me
you don't cast Mitch
in the more ladylike role?
Are you saying Cam
is the wife in this deal?
I don't think about it that way.
It's not like it was in our day.
Husband went out to work.
Wife stayed home with the kids.
That sounds like
a clever way of saying "yes."
Fine.
They're both equal.
Neither one is the wife.
Yeah. Yeah.
I know that in my head.
It's just that it makes me
feel a tiny bit better
to think that the person
he's spending his life with
is a tiny bit of a woman.
I get it.
Every time I start to feel
comfortable with this thing,
some new part comes up
I gotta wrap my head around.
Yeah, I guess we got no choice.
Yep. We got two sons,
and they're gay for each other.
I'll take it slow on the way home.
Don't worry.
Canceling course for adventure.
Beep. Boop. Beep. Bop. Mm.
You know what I'll never forget?
The time my dad
spent the entire day
trying to create
a special memory for me.
Or when a pregnant lady
slipped in my vomit.
Hang on.
I wanna do one thing before we go.
Hey, you on your way home?
Just about.
How's everything there?
Actually, it's pretty great.
I can't wait to see you.
Me, too.
Okay.
Let's hit it.
I don't know.
I feel like maybe we should get
some food on the way home.
Don't.
Maybe a nice tuna melt.
Stop it.
I did what I could, mom.
It was a nightmare.
I can't tell you how many times
I turned off the bathroom light.
Haley!
Oh, crap.
Listen, Gloria.
Okay, everything I told you
technically was not...
You lied to me
so that you could have a party
without supervision!
Oh, I had plenty of supervision.
He was running around all night
with his coasters and vacuum
and his "make good choices" speech.
Good. Somebody
needed to be responsible.
Thank you.
Not you.
You take rules too seriously.
I'm in trouble?
You are 13.
You're not supposed
to be vacuuming the party.
You're supposed to be
enjoying the party.
Exactly.
A party that you shouldn't
have been having!
It seems like you're sending
mixed signals here.
Yeah, maybe I should get
my friends and just leave.
No, you're in trouble,
little young lady.
You're having this party!
What? They've been using
glassware by the pool,
putting feet on the furniture,
and begging girls
to kiss each other.
Yes! All the things that you
should have been doing!
Yeah, all those things are fine.
Go. Have fun and go crazy.
But he's gonna ruin my party.
Two birds with one bullet.
www.SUBTITULOS.es
-DIFUNDE LA PALABRA-
www.tvsubtitles.net