We're beginning our initial
descent into Jackson Hole, Wyoming.
Thank you for flying United.
Reckon we'll be landing soon.
Phil, honey, you promised--
not till we got there.
This year, we're going
to a dude ranch
with the whole family.
Mm-hmm. The family.
What if Dylan buys his own ticket?
We'll be sleeping in separate cabins.
What if Dylan and I share a horse?
Mm, I hate landing.
We'll get through this.
Wow! Oh, my goodness.
What are you doing?
I want my ears to pop.
Try putting a little Rouge on 'em.
Nobody gets me.
Wow. Isn't this beautiful,
little cowgirl?
You hate her sparkly outfit,
don't you?
No, I told you, it's fine.
I just didn't like you
wearing a matching one.
So we haven't told the family yet,
but we've decided to
adopt a baby boy.
From America this time.
You might say
we're "buying domestic."
In private...
You might say that in private.
Our adoption attorney told us
it would be a good idea
to make a photo book to
show prospective moms.
Ues, but he thought that Cam's
version was a little too "artsy,"
so we've decided to take
a few rugged shots at the ranch
to, you know, balance it out.
I don't think it need
balancing out.
Really?
It's called "Production value."
Sync by YYeTs.net | Corrected by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
Horse.
Look, Jay! So beautiful!
Your ears haven't
popped yet, huh?
I'm like the horse whisperer.
But something is making
this one skittish.
Whoa. Look at the mountains.
They're amazing.
I've never been this far
from home before
now I've never been this far.
Where's a cliff
when you need one?
Look, kids!
A real life cowboy!
Oh. Come see. Come see.
- Uh-oh.
- What's he doing?
Oh, my.
My name is Hank.
Here at the Lost Creek Ranch,
you're gonna ride, you're gonna
rope, and you're gonna shoot.
You're gonna see a sky
so full of stars,
it'll put your city lights to shame.
And when it's all done,
you might just encounter
a piece of yourselves you
never knew was there.
Are there any questions?
Uh, do we book spa
treatments through you or...
I like you, kid.
I'm gonna call you "Hollywood."
That wasn't an answer.
And who's this cactus flower?
What?
That's my wife Gloria.
Well, she's "Cactus Flower" now,
old-timer.
These, uh, these nicknames--
are they set in stone?
Okey dokey.
You ready, gunslinger?
I heard word of trouble
in these parts.
Pull!
That oughta fix it, eh, Jay?
You got a piece of it.
I've been practicing like crazy,
all my cowboy skills--
shootin', ropin'.
pancake eatin'.
Why? Because sometimes
I feel like Jay doesn't
respect me as a man.
It's just that when you say,
"Phil is my son-in-law,"
it sounds like you're saying,
"Phyllis, my son-in-law."
- That's ridiculous.
- Okay, who's your son-in-law?
Phyllis.
I'm not asking for a hug.
I just want to get that
look of newfound respect,
like...
Or...
Or... mm.
Yeah.
Check it out.
Two birds, one leg.
Pull it!
Not bad, eh, Old-timer?
Uh, see, slappy only
had three fingers.
What?
He only had three fingers.
Who's next?
Oh, me. Me.
Oh, this is good. This is good.
Tres macho.
No smile. Don't smile. Good.
You ready?
Wait. Do I say "pull"?
Sorry. Sorry.
Mitchell, why don't you
go find Manny at the spa?
Wouldn't that be more fun?
Yeah.
I realized that if
I was gonna raise a boy,
I needed to butch up my life.
You know, I wanted to
be able to teach my son
all the things that
my Dad taught Claire.
Hey, Hollywood.
I don't love that.
Wanna see something?
Oh, my gosh.
Is that a firecracker?
Shh!
Now I just need to find the
perfect thing to blow up.
Is that thing even legal?
Not here. It's from Germany.
If they had this during the war,
right now we'd all be
knee-deep in strudel.
Watch it!
What you doing, eh? You readin'?
Trying to.
I'm not so good at it either.
- I'm not surprised.
- That was a joke.
I'm Jimmy Scrivano.
You want to see
me do a cannonball?
I'd rather see you
get hit by one, but...
Ha. Good one, gorgeous.
Jay! Is this like the lobster?!
Do I get to pick one for dinner?
Because this one
looks very tender.
Look alive, Old-timer.
One of your calves is getting away.
Hey, something's wrong with
my horse. She's veering left.
When this happened to my
Uncle, it was a stroke.
Oh, there's nothing
wrong with Buttercup.
You just gotta let her
know who's boss!
Beautiful form, Cactus Flower!
Beautiful!
You look like a dadgum conquistadora!
She's deaf, but I can hear ya.
Why are you riding that way?
I'm afraid that cow over
there might bite me.
Oh, yes, he's gonna
come up and bite you
because your leg looks so
desirable with those--
are those canvas?
Okay, Phil, ease that one
back over towards me.
- Got it.
- Ease him back this way.
Hey! Piece of cake, huh, Jay?
- Huh?
- Ease that one over to Bossy.
Which one's Bossy?
- That's my nickname for your wife.
- Hilarious.
Go, Mom! Whoo!
Yeah, Mom! You rock!
Oh, I wish I had a rock.
Hey. It wouldn't kill you
to be nice to Dylan.
It might.
But, honey, I don't know why
you always stick up for him.
Haley can do so much better.
Because I know what it's
like to fall for a girl
whose dad thinks
I'm not good enough.
All right, you're right.
I can make more of an effort.
That's the woman I love.
We taking a little break over here?
Laying some pipe?
- No. Sorry. I was just talking to Bossy.
- Uh-huh.
- Phil!
- I'm sorry.
Jay, look! I got this one!
I got this one!
She's veering left again.
When we get back,
I'm gonna see
if she can track
a pencil with her eyes.
Okay, Lily, I'm going to
push you one more time.
Now don't kick me, okay?
Aah! Oh! Lily!
I said don't kick me. Okay?
You know it's your own
fault that's happening.
Why don't you try
standing behind her?
You are an idiot.
Oh, really? I ain't the one
getting kicked.
- Why are you following me?
- Why are you fighting me here, gorgeous?
This works.
I really, really don't appreciate
you calling me "gorgeous."
I just want to enjoy
time with my family,
so if you don't mind-- mm!
Not a problem.
See you around, sunshine.
You kissed a boy!
No, the boy kissed me.
Okay, Lily?
The boy kissed me.
♪ I rode a horse for
the first time today ♪
♪ wasn't surprised
when it went... neigh ♪
Okay. Hey, Dylan.
Hey, Mrs. Dunphy.
I was wondering if we
could have a little chat.
Oh. You want me to go home.
No, no. It's the--
the opposite of that.
I want you to go home?
No, I, um, I want you to know
how glad I am that you're here.
Really?
'Cause sometimes I just get
this vibe you don't like me.
Oh. Dylan, no. I'm sorry.
I-I like you.
I-I like you a lot. I just...
It's complicated because
Haley's my daughter.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa.
You are totally a hot mom,
but I can't do this.
Oh, my God. Okay, we--
there's--no, no.
I merely meant that I'm sorry
if I made you feel unwelcome.
Whew! That would
have been awkward.
So awkward.
You know, but for the record,
Mrs. Dunphy...
Yes?
- If Haley wasn't my girlfriend...
- Yeah.
- And Mr. Dunphy was out
of the picture...   - Mm-hmm.
I would be honored
to share your bed
and raise Luke, Alex,
and Haley as my own.
Okay.
Good talk.
♪ She'll be running
down the mountain ♪
♪ she'll be running down the
Mountain when she come.s ♪
the song ended two minutes ago.
Well, I'll tell you what.
She could play Evita.
Really? You notice
the crickets left?
Anyone want more water?
Oh, Dad, I'll take one.
Heads up.
- Oh!
- Oh, my gosh.
Oh. It was--it was dark.
I-I couldn't see it. Thank you.
So did you set off
the firecracker yet?
When I do, you won't have to ask.
First, all the
electronics will go out,
then comes the heat flash.
Afterwards, the living
will envy the dead.
And yet I'm the one
on the "No-fly" list.
You know what? Maybe next time
I'll just catch it
and then hand it to you.
Oh, okay. Yeah, let's do that.
You--you do everything,
and I'll do nothing.
Something on your mind?
This isn't the right
place to talk about it.
Okay.
I-I'm s--
I'm not sure if we should
have another baby.
What? Are you serious?
I think that we might be
rushing into this.
Rushing into--
we've been working--
Everybody, it's me, Dylan.
I just wanted to thank you all
for bringing me on this trip
and making me feel
like one of the family,
uh, especially Bossy.
So I can't think of a better time
to ask something of
the woman that I love.
Okay.
No, no.
Haley Gwendolyn Dunphy,
will you do me the honors of
being my lawfully wedded--
No. No, no, no, no, no.
No proposals.
Not now. Not gonna happen.
She's a child, so...
- Mom!
- You're still in high school!
- I meant after she graduates.
- Not then. Not now.
Not ever. Seriously, what are
you two gonna live off of?
The--the--the royalties
from the horsey song?
- Put it back in your pocket.
- Would you stop it?
- No, I won't. I won't.
- No, it's okay.
I guess I'll just turn in.
Just so you know,
there's a fan in my cabin
- that sounds like someone crying.
- Oh.
Dylan, wait! I hate you!
Oh, come on. Haley,
get back here!
Phil, anything?
I think you said it all, Claire.
You want me to rope her?
I can, you know.
For what it's worth,
my second wife
was in high school.
Sweetie, here. Here we go.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
- Gone.
- It's gone! It's over there!
It's not back there.
- We counted to three.
- Yes.
Hey.
Where have you been?
I-I slept on the couch
in the lodge.
I know you didn't want to
have a big fight last night.
Well, I'm ready now.
Cam, I'm sorry.
Look, what if I can't do
the father-son stuff?
The hunting, the--the sports,
the Three Stooges?
You know what happens in real life
when someone gets hit in
the head with a ladder?
They go to the hospital
and they get an MRI.
Never see that scene.
I think you're overthinking this.
You know, I love sports,
I love the Stooges.
We've got this covered.
No. No, you--
you got it covered,
but I'm just stuck on the sidelines,
pretending to understand
the rules, and...
You know, my dad was a
rough-and-tumble guy,
and I just--
I could never relate to him.
And I don't know.
I just don't think I could handle
disappointing...
two generations.
I think you're more masculine
than you give yourself credit for.
Who puts a birdhouse
next to a porch?
Claire, I know
that you're worried
that Dylan is gonna
break Haley's heart,
but I see in his eyes that he's
gonna stick with her forever.
No matter what, he's always
going to be with her.
On your deathbed--
Okay. All right.
I can't take this anymore.
I'm gonna go find her.
No. You push too hard, you
chase her right into his arms,
you'll end up with
a boob for a son-in-law.
Believe me, you don't want that.
What's that supposed to mean?
- What?
- Hey, have you guys seen Dylan?
- No. No. Why?
- I'm not talking to you.
He said he was going out
for a walk last night,
and no one's seen him since.
Sweetheart, I'm sure he's fine.
Maybe after last night,
he just went home.
Doubt it. He left his luggage.
We have to do something.
If he doesn't eat five times
a day, he gets spacey.
What would that even look like?
We'll find him. Hank?
We got a situation here!
What seems to be the trouble?
We need to talk.
What?
You stole my first kiss.
What are you talkin' about?
I had it all planned out.
It was supposed to be special,
someone with a high GPA
and a bright future,
not a Mario brother.
Fine. You know what?
I don't even want your kiss.
Here, you can have it back.
There. Now we're even.
Well, keep it.
I don't-- I don't want it anymore.
What am I doing?
Okay, people.
Looks like we have a walker.
Right now he is facing
treacherous terrain,
sudden drops, mountain lions,
hungry bears, oh, and wolverines.
That is, if the hypothermia
didn't already get him.
Why did we come here again?
So our best bet is to split up.
You two are gonna take
the North hiking trail.
- Can I go with my Dad instead?
- Negative.
I need Buffalo Phil and Old-timer...
To check the Snake River.
Buffalo Phil--
worth the wait.
Me and Cactus Flower will
ride on up to Destiny Ridge.
Maybe I should ride
up there with her.
Negatory. That trail is
for advanced riders only.
We don't need another dead body.
"Another"?
Let's go! Move 'em out.
Phil, help me saddle
my horse, will ya?
Well, look who's suddenly
needed by his father-in-law.
Phyllis.
Phil...
is.
Hey, Uncle Mitch. Whatcha doing?
Oh, hey.
Just--just thinkin'.
You know, I've been
meaning to tell you,
you're a super fun Uncle.
And I'm saying this as a boy.
Uncle Cameron sent you
over here, didn't he?
What? That's hilarious.
No, I love how you and
me can joke like this.
Okay, Luke, look, I don't
know how much Cam told you,
but I don't think
this is a problem
that you can help me with. It's...
Okay, good.
I've got my own problem.
What? What's that?
Can you keep a secret?
I kept a pretty big one
for 22 years, so...
I've got this new firecracker,
and I can't decide what to blow up.
Oh, Luke, that's dangerous.
I know. That's what's fun about it.
I don't get boys.
What is so great about
destroying things?
It turns stuff into
flying chunks of stuff.
Okay, no. No,
g-give it to me. Come on.
Fine.
I take it back.
You're not that fun.
All right, hey, look, um,
we'll do it together, all right?
You just made the best
decision of your life.
Okay. Come on.
Damn it!
Buttercup! What the hell's
wrong with this horse?
Jay.
I want to talk to you about
that son-in-law crack
you made at breakfast.
- Oh, I didn't mean anything by that.
- I think you did.
I get that I wasn't your first
choice to marry Claire,
but it's been 18 years, and
there hasn't been a day
when I wasn't a loyal
husband to your daughter
and a great dad to your grandkids.
So if we've still got a problem,
now it's your problem.
Phil, wait up.
Let me ask you something,
man to man.
Okay.
You notice anything
funny about the...
Hank character and, uh...
Gloria? Yeah,
he's hitting on her. Why?
I knew it.
Where are you going?
Destiny Ridge.
Buttercup, ha!
Buttercup, hiya!
Seriously?
Okay. Okay, it's clear.
- After this, we're gonna have
some angry birds. -Yeah.
It's gonna be "Bye bye Birdie."
It's a big musical from the '60s.
No. Forget it. What you said.
Okay.
Okay, go.
That's it?
I'm sorry, buddy.
- I brought that thing all
the way from-- whoa! - Whoa!
Cam, I did a boy thing!
I blew up the birdhouse!
You should have seen it.
It was so awesome.
That's great!
Yeah. I think I can do this.
I mean, maybe not everything
and maybe not right away, and
- not the three stooges...
- No.
I do. I want a son.
I'm sorry I panicked.
Oh, that's great.
Now maybe we can go back to
taking pictures for the book.
Yes! Pictures of me
blowing up stuff!
Okay, I see we've overcorrected.
I know you think
I'm the mean mom
who wouldn't let you marry
your boyfriend,
but someday you're
gonna realize,
I-I did what had to be done.
No, you didn't.
I was never gonna marry Dylan.
I told him no.
Oh, you did? Thank God.
But it was my proposal
to turn down.
You know, you keep telling
me to act like an adult,
but then you don't
even give me a chance.
Oh. You sort of got me there.
But, sweetheart, I don't
expect you to understand this.
I certainly didn't
when I was your age.
I look at you as my baby,
and I always will.
It's--it's just what moms do.
I'm not a baby anymore!
Okay? And I am never
gonna see Dylan again!
Dylan!
What?!
Where are you?!
Wyoming!
You're okay!
I had the craziest night.
When you rejected me,
I felt lost and scared.
And then I went out on a walk,
and I felt a whole different
kind of lost and scared.
And then I fell
asleep in the stable.
And when I woke up, I met
this woman named Jake
who's strong like a man.
Then we had this long talk,
and he/she hired me.
Uh, what--
what do you mean, she hired you?
I work here now.
S-so you're staying?
Yeah. What about us?
It could never work.
We're from two different worlds.
You're a high school student,
and I'm a ranch hand.
I'm just--I'm so glad you're okay.
I really am.
I am. Thanks. But we're
not supposed to fraternize
with the guests.
Right.
Dylan!
You got a voice like a
meadowlark, don't ya?
Dylan!
Yeah, I sure am worried
about that kid.
Dylan!
He ain't down there.
Oh, come on now. You come up
here for the cowboy experience.
You're looking at him.
Do I look like the kind of woman
that would cheat on her husband?
Yes.
Really?
Hey! I think you better
move away from that woman.
Only we touch our women
when they don't want us to.
Easy. Easy there, friend-o.
I wasn't hitting on this filly.
This is all part of the package.
If I didn't play the bad guy,
he wouldn't get to ride
up and be the big hero.
He doesn't need you
to make him a hero.
He's a hero every day.
Why don't you do us all a favor?
Get back on your horse,
ride down to the lodge and tell 'em--
- Can you keep him still?
I'm trying to make a point. - I am.
Okay. Okay, I'm gone.
Ma'am.
Wait. Wait.
There's something
I wanna say to you.
I will only be checking
"somewhat satisfied"
on our comment card. Jeez.
I mean, he was great
with the kids.
I looked it up.
The distance between our
houses is 2,443 miles.
Yeah, but, you know,
on some maps,
it's like--pfft! This big.
God, you're stupid.
All in all, it was a great vacation.
We may have lost a man...
But out there on the range,
under that great big sky,
we found a part of ourselves
we never knew was there,
just like the horny
cowboy said we would.
No.
Fine.
Sync by YYeTs.net | Corrected by Alice
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net