Clive Bixby.
What a sexy surprise.
Quick question--
Hmm?
Did it hurt when you fell from heaven?
Because you--Uh...
I'm gonna come in again.
We are watching baby Joe
on Valentine's day
so my dad and Gloria can...
make love.
Ew. Don't.
Oh.
The point is, we are
celebrating a day early.
So they can finally be intimate.
You've...
more than made that point.
I'm just saying it's a long wait
after giving birth.
Six weeks.
Ugh.
I couldn't keep my hands
off this one for that long.
(both chuckle)
I can only imagine
what Jay's going through.
Voila.
(gasps)
Square knot. Impressive.
I can make any kind of knot.
It's like I have a sailor in my mouth.
I should check on the kids.
Haley took 'em to a movie.
She's not even gonna answer.
I know, but, sweetie,
I have a good reason to worry.
Luke had that nasty nosebleed
this morning,
and Alex, as usual, fainted.
She's fine,
and dunphy men get nosebleeds.
I told you this when we
got married. It was in my vows.
I'm still a little unclear as to
why you put them in your vows--
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Just finish that drink, pretty lady.
We got a big night ahead of us.
Okay.
First, we have a date with romance.
A threesome, if you will.
Oh.
From here, we move on
to an old-Fashioned blimpnic.
Now is that the one
where the man has to
face out at the woman...
it's a picnic on a blimp.
Hmm.
Champagne, cheese,
and this beautiful city beneath us.
That actually sounds really romantic.
After that, we swap
our earplugs for some earmuffs,
and take a few moonlit turns
around the local ice rink.
Oh.
From there, it's a quick trip
back to the hotel,
where...
I'm spinning.
Well, I wouldn't start with that,
But, uh, we--we can
work our way up to it.
No. I'm feeling really weird.
Catch that, clive?
Just tell me what you want.
(thud) Juliana?
Claire?
One of you needs to answer me.
♪♪♪
Blood pressure's still good.
I think I can send you home.
Great. So it was probably just
low BLOOD sugar or something?
See, honey? I told you
it was nothing to worry about.
Well, it's not nothing.
You did have a small heart episode.
Dr. Coben,
this may have been my fault.
I think I was being...
too sexy.
Yeah, I don't think that's an issue.
You sure about that?
Um, doctor, you're not saying
that I had a heart attack
or something, right?
Not at all. What you have
is a very minor arrhythmia,
known as Wolff-Parkinson-White
syndrome.
It's hereditary, so you're off the hook.
Oh, yeah. My mom has that.
We'll treat it with medication
and have you back in a couple of days.
In the meantime, just take it easy.
Okay. Thank you!
I guess we should tell your dad
we can't watch the baby tomorrow.
No. No.
I don't want everyone
to know about this.
They're just gonna get worried
and--And make a bigger deal
of it than it is.
Sweetheart, promise me?
I promise. I know
it's not that big a deal.
This is a huge deal...
for which I'm partly responsible,
in spite of what Claire's
lesbian doctor says.
Hey, honey, I was just reading
about this Wolff-White thing.
It's not that serious.
You're gonna be fine.
(Claire) I know.
Who's ready to hit the ice?
What?
Come on.
Somebody promised me a moonlit skate.
But didn't the doctor say
you needed to take it easy?
Oh, that's just one of those
things they have to say,
like, "you can't drink
when you're pregnant."
(chuckles) (laughs)
Come on.
We're not gonna seriously
blow off valentine's day, are we?
No. I just thought
why... Ice things down
when we could heat things up?
Oh, I like
where this is going.
Right?
Yes.
Yeah?
Ye--No!
Honey, I know what you're doing.
You're treating me like a patient,
and you promised
that you wouldn't.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
I just had a better idea.
What?
Side-By-Side
couples massage.
Oh.
Just you, me,
and a couple cambodian guys
to work us over good.
Specific.
(door closes)
What is that?
You think the kids are home?
(indistinct conversations)
That sounds like more than our three.
(pop music playing) Oh.
Oh, they think we're not home,
and they're having a party.
I'm killing them.
No, no, no.
"a" --it's my turn
to kill them.
"B" --you need to order up
those massages.
Mm-hmm.
It's under
"Best number one U.S.A.
Coca-Cola good time massage."
What the hell is going on?!
Dad? What are you doing home?
So This is how it is?
We're gone for a minute,
and you guys throw a party?
No!
Just texted mom we're having
a good time at the movies.
It works every t--aah!
So This is a regular thing?
No!
You know the drill.
Coolers our b--Aah--Ack!
Enough! Turn off the music!
(music stops)
Everybody who I did not create,
get out of my house right now!
I don't want to get upset.
I've been through enough tonight.
What happened?
I'm not supposed
to tell you.
When you say it like that,
we make it worse in our head.
Fine. It's no big deal.
Your mother had to go to the hospital.
Oh, my god!
What?!
That is so much worse
than it would be in our heads!
She's fine.
She just passed out a little.
Something to do with her heart.
Like a heart attack?!
Mom had a heart attack?!
Mom almost died
of a heart attack?!
no!
She had a little episode,
probably triggered by me.
She just needs to rest.
For once, let's not think
about ourselves.
(crunches)
(Claire) Phil, everything okay?
(mouth full)
fine! I'm coming!
(scoffs)
Just act like
everything's normal.
Oh, and if, uh,
two Cambodian guys show up,
send them to our bedroom.
(rattles)
(door opens)
Kids had a few friends over.
I handled it.
So you're good at handling things.
(chips crunch and clatter)
You like?
Me love, but is this
appropriate massage wear?
They were busy, which is what
we should be getting.
Honey.
(switch clicks)
Honey, are you sure this is
okay for your--aah!
Mm-Hmm!
Mmm. Ooh! (whispers) salty.
I still have a few moves.
Mm, that's the chips, sweetie.
Oh, sorry.
Right.
(door opens) Mmm.
Mom, we need to talk to you.
(Claire groans)
Dad told us not to say anything,
but we're really worried about you.
You told them?!
No!
You had a heart attack?
Phil!
That is not what I said.
(sighs deeply and groans)
Kids, everything is fine.
(Haley screams)
(high-Pitched voice)
Call 9-1-1!
Oh, god!
Her heart exploded!
Oh, my god! I did it again!
Phil, it's your nose!
Oh.
Ugh. This is the one thing--
The one thing I ask from you is
not to make a big deal of this,
and you couldn't even do that.
Honey, you need to stay calm.
No, I don't, because I am fine.
We are all fine.
Oh, god.
Haley, revive your sister.
Not in the mood for an apology, Phil.
Good, 'cause you're not gettin' one.
I'm allowed to worry about you.
Mm-Hmm. Yeah, when there's
something to worry about.
But this was nothing.
I told you, my mom has this.
Which I just found out about today.
How has that not come up in 20 years?
I was... getting to it.
Look, I know you feel like
you have to be the rock for this family
and worry about Everybody's
boy problems and nosebleeds
and...
who has enough greens.
They're supposed to cover
half the plate.
Claire, stop it.
I'm saying you could
let us take care of you
every once in a while.
Like for example, when you
clutch your chest and collapse.
This house isn't gonna crumble
in the dust
if you let yourself be vulnerable.
We don't know that.
We could find out.
(sighs)
It was kind of scary.
Of course.
Until I knew what it was,
and then--
don't ruin it.
I just have one more question.
Hmm?
Did it hurt?
Well, I blacked out
before I--
When you fell from heaven?
Nailed it.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
You just take care of Claire.
We got Joe.
(phone beeps) Gloria?
¿Si, mi amor?
Wow.
Happy Valentine's--
(lowered voice)
Wait. Wait. Wait. Time-out.
That was Phil.
They can't watch Joe today.
Claire was in the emergency room
last night.
Is she okay?
She's gonna be fine,
but, you know,
she had a little bit--
Okay, good.
I love how you look in this suit.
Let's see how it looks
on the floor, okay?
Okay, but I gotta be
in a meeting in one hour.
Ay, that's so cute that after six weeks,
you think you're going to need an hour!
(both laugh) happy Valentine's day!
It's the one time of the year
when the world tries to be as
romantic as I am all the time.
Good luck, world.
Get out.
Anyway, since you're
almost done dressing Jay...
Mm-hmm.
How about
we head to school early?
I'll check my hair
and meet you in the car.
Gloria, I'll be back in two hours, tops.
We decide who does what
when you come back.
I got a ticket
running a red light...
(door closes)
So let's make this worth it.
Put the kid down.
I can't. He's being
a real Pritchett.
We need to come up with
a different term for that.
Watch.
(Joe crying)
(crying stops) (whispers) Watch.
(crying)
(crying stops)
Okay, I used to have a tv
got reception like that.
Let me try.
Hey, Joe Joe. Hey Buddy.
Guy to guy, you're blocking me
a little bit. You know that.
Ohh!
Yes, you do.
Yes, you do, Joe.
Hey, how about a half-Hour?
What do you say, pal? Huh?
Can you do it?
Attaboy!
I've never been more
attracted... (whispers) to you.
Prove it.
Are you kissing?
That's a bit of a mood killer.
My daddies kiss a lot.
And flatlined.
(sighs) Mitch and cam are having
a party for Valentine's.
Claire was supposed to take care
of her, but now she can't.
Lily, we're so happy to have you here.
I have a big surprise for you!
Look! A brand-New,
shiny tv remote!
Looks complicated.
Just keep hitting all those buttons
until something good happens.
(under breath) That's my plan, anyway.
Woof!
(doorbell rings)
Where were all these distractions
the night that Joe was conceived?
I'm kissing.
He's a blessing.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm Harlan. I'm here
to do your baby proofing.
Jay, I've been waiting
for this appointment for weeks.
I've waited longer for mine.
The human race has survived
for a thousand years
without these foam bumpers
and--And gates everywhere.
Hell, I used to drive to the supermarket
with Mitchell and Claire
on the Hood of the car.
When did everybody get
so overprotective?
Maybe when kids started flying off cars.
How long?
Normally I have help, but Dale, uh...
you met Dale at the shop.
He's a tall guy.
He's my sister's kid--
Hey, listen. You and I are gonna
bang this out in about an hour.
(grunting)
Where do you want it?
(box thuds)
I know a lot of people think
that I'm attracted to Jay
because of his money, but they're wrong.
I'm attracted to him because he's sexy,
and he's never been sexier than today.
The suit...
the carrying of the boxes...
no, no. You listen to me.
You've had my wife's car four days.
Figure out what
that screeching noise is,
or you'll be making one yourself.
(phone beeps)
(Gloria) the yelling on the phone...
give me that.
(drill whirring)
And the drilling.
So much drilling.
Time to go, Harlan.
Okay. You want me to walk you
through any of the--
No, we'll take it
from here.
Okay. Uh, listen.
Give me a call if you have
any trouble with the gates,
because they're
a little tricky, you know?
(whispers) Yeah
you gotta be gentle with it.
(slams door)
Ten seconds, or I start without you.
(singsongy) Ready or not, here I...
okay.
Hold on!
Okay, you have to lift it.
It's not a lift.
It's a squeeze.
Okay, then squeeze it!
I'm squeezing it!
It's impossible!
Jay, please.
(door opens)
Best day ever!
I just got invited
to a Valentine's party
by a secret admirer!
You should go.
Sounds great! Go!
I obviously need to get dressed first.
Can you keep it
under a half-hour?
You're funny.
(pounds on door) Manny, come on.
Let's go!
(door opens)
Relax.
Come on!
You don't have to drive me.
It's just down the street.
Oh, I thought I...
had to drive you. (grunts)
(latch clicks)
(sighs)
What's with the hat?
My secret admirer requested
I wear a hat with a feather in it.
I'm like, "which one?"
really?
This secret admirer Have
any other requests?
Uh, yes.
She asked me to bring some
poetry to recite at the party.
Mm-Hmm.
These, uh, kids at the party...
(latch clicks)
they wouldn't be
the popular ones by any chance?
The most popular. Why?
No reason.
Just... have fun.
(chuckles) I will.
(door opens and closes)
(rattling)
No, Jay.
It's squeeze.
(clank) UHH!
(clatters)
(giggles)
(giggling)
(laughs)
What? I have cigar breath?
It's not you.
Ay. Did you already...
what?
No!
No. I'm worried about manny.
I think he's being set up
for some kind of humiliation
at that party.
Oh. That's so sweet
of you to worry.
Just when you thought that
you couldn't get any sexier.
Yeah, he's fine, right?
Yeah, he's fine.
(giggling)
Come here... (laughs)
Oh, I think I gotta check on him.
There was something about
some kind of secret admirer
getting him to...
bring his poems?
Yeah, he told me when I was
lint-Rolling his jacket.
And you're not worried it's a prank?
Of course I worry.
I worry about him all the time.
But like you said, we can't
protect them from everything.
So I'm just trying to, like,
let go a little bit.
Let him ride on top of the car?
No, that's just crazy.
That's the hardest part, isn't it?
When you realize you can't stop
the world from hurting them.
Now you're making me want to cry.
This is not what this day is all about.
You're right.
Okay.
I'll go and get us some Champagne.
Good idea.
Manny?
No, nothing.
Just wanted to know
if everything is okay.
Hi, honey. Sorry to bother you.
I know you're resting.
I heard you had
a little scare last night.
Hey, uh, when are you going back
to the doctor?
'cause if you want, I can go with you.
(snoring) (phone ringing)
This year for Valentine's day,
we decided to throw
a lonely hearts party
for all of our single friends.
Sometimes when we're around them,
we feel a little guilty
for having found each other,
like we're waving our love
in their faces.
There's gotta be a better way
of saying that.
Anyway, it was supposed to be
an elegant affair.
Ogle me.
(doorbell rings) Showtime.
Put the cat away.
Okay. Yeah. Great.
Oh, and, Mitchell,
please... Hey.
Yeah?
Please try to have fun tonight.
I always have fun.
No, I know you're great
at stay-at-Home fun
and sit-on-the-Couch fun,
but this is party fun,
and sometimes you--
Okay, this is not fun.
(rings)
Get the door.
♪♪♪
I will show you some fun.
Things got a little hazy after that.
(phone rings)
(grunting)
(beeps)
(gruff voice) Hello?
(clears throat)
(normal voice)
Yeah, hi--Hi, dad.
No, no. I'm up.
I am up.
Yeah, bring her by at any time.
Okay. Good night.
(beeps)
Oh, cam.
Oh, god, that was some party last night.
Yeah. Well, I'm just glad
you made it home safely.
Wha--Made--Made it ho--
I don't--
I don't even remember leaving the party.
Oh, I-I think
I got a little tipsy.
Tipsy?
You were like all
of the "mad men."
Oh, no, no, no.
Don't make it out like I did
a lot of crazy, out of control--
I was hoping
I dreamt that.
Mm.
Come on. Like--like you've
never had a few cocktails
and died a cat pink
with Cherry kool-Aid.
Okay. Well, is there anything
else you need to tell me about?
Not that I remember.
I'm remembering this.
Oh, my gosh, Mitchell,
are these Burt and Dottie Winchell's
Christmas decorations?
How could you?
They never take them down, okay?
I was doing the whole
neighborhood a favor.
Oh, god.
Cam, I... you know, I think--
I-I think there are pictures.
I remember Pepper
and Longinus were--Okay.
Mm.
(gasps) Oh, my gosh.
Those poor reindeer.
Oh, it seems like prancer
is the Belle of the ball--
No surprise there.
Oh. You must be vixen.
Okay. Okay.
Not funny, Mitchell.
Look at this place.
What were you thinking?
Okay. Cam, I... yes,
I went a little nuts, all right?
I-I'm sorry.
But I didn't do anything
that can't be undone.
Hey, roomies.
Hey, thank you so much
for letting me move in here.
Um...
yes. Could you excuse us
for just a...
a moment, Dylan?
Yeah. Take as much time
as you need.
It's your house.
I just live here now.
Cam, did--Did I tell him
that he could live with us?
Obviously.
Oh, my god.
Was he even at our party?
Yes. He's been driving
a limousine for some company,
and J'Marcus hired him for the night,
and now he lives here.
Are you all caught up there?
I-I don't remember
any of this.
Well, let's create
a new memory--
One where you tell him
he can't live here.
Oh.
Can I say one short thing?
I came to this house a broken man
After my mom threw me out
for her new boyfriend.
And then I found out
I was getting let go
from the limo company
the same night Haley
goes to a party without me.
So I had nothing and no one.
And then you...
(cries)
(lowered voice)
okay. Come on. Tell him.
(lowered voice) Let him finish.
I'm sorry.
I mean, gay dudes
Have always been nice to me--
I mean, super nice.
But nothing like this.
I guess what I'm trying to say is...
Oh, my God.
He's gonna sing.
♪ So many years living life underwater ♪
♪ came up for air
in the room of your daughter ♪
♪ I never knew I would find my answer ♪
♪ in my ex-Girlfriend's
uncles' house ♪
♪ with the tiny pink panther ♪
Dylan, Dylan.
I'm--I'm sorry.
Oh, gosh, I--This is...
This is really hard for me to say,
but we--We just cannot...
not wash our cat.
I'm sorry.
(cat screeches)
And yet when I did that drunk,
not a scratch.
Oh, my gosh, this place is
cleaner than when we moved in.
Best houseguest ever.
No, we are not keeping him.
Do you think he took
the christmas decorations
back to the Winchell's?
Oh, well, I think he thinks he did.
What?
Okay, yeah.
Dylan!
No, no, no!
Oh, hey, guys.
I'm up here.
Yeah, hi. Listen, Dylan,
those decorations were on the yard...
of that house.
Oh. No good deed, huh?
Yeah, well...
hey! I can see our house
from here.
Uh... oh!
(thuds)
Oh, jeez.
Are you kidding me?
(high-pitched voice)
Dylan! Dylan!
This day...
aah!
One night.
Just till his bone sets.
Yeah, but there's always gonna
be a reason not to tell him,
isn't there?
Okay. What if we, um--
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No "We." You made your bed.
You lie in it.
Don't lie there. I just made it.
Sorry.
Not looking. Not looking.
It's okay, Dylan.
I made you guys some soups.
Oh, Dylan, you didn't have to do that.
Well, cam didn't have to offer
to let me stay here,
but he did.
So here are soups.
Cam offered?
Well, I know he was
speaking for both of you.
You weren't home yet.
Is that a problem?
Not for me.
Oh. Dylan, can you
give us just a moment?
Not looking.
(doorbell rings) I'll get it!
(chuckles) So I guess in a way,
we're both responsible.
Yeah, but in the real way,
you're responsible.
Take care of that.
Come on.
Let's do it.
Oh, my god.
I hate myself right now.
What kind of monster
throws an injured innocent
onto the street?
(Lily) You can't live here.
Get out!
Lily.
It's weird.
You're a big boy.
I'm sorry, Dylan.
She doesn't mean that.
No. She's right.
Everyone says it.
I need to stop running from conflict.
It's time to be a big boy
and Patch things up
and move back in with my mom.
I'll get my things.
Okay. Sorry.
Sorry, yeah.
(mouths words)
I guess I got off easy.
She is Blunt but effective.
Maybe we should have her
talk to the Gardener.
Hey, c-Cam, um...
do you really think
that I'm not any fun?
What?
Last night,
you said that I--
(Lily) This isn't a hotel!
Yeah, you made your point, honey!
He's got it.
No, it--I only drank
like that last night
because I...
I was trying to be more fun.
Oh. No, I didn't
mean it like that.
I'm sorry.
You know I have party anxiety.
I was nervous.
No, but you're not entirely wrong.
I mean, I-I could be
a little... less uptight
and loosen up a little bit.
Yeah. Maybe we could,
you know,
aim for middle-Ground fun.
You know, if--if you're up
for a do-Over,
I recently heard of an idea
that could put us in the low end
of upper middle-Ground fun.
Okay.
(piano jazz playing)
Do you believe in love at first sight,
or should I walk in again?
(Gloria, singsongy) Jay?
Coming, honey!
Oh, god.
There you are, Jay.
I thought you'd never wake up.
Turns out my night
with my secret admirer
couldn't have gone better.
We danced all night.
And the best part was,
her eyes were just...
(lowered voice)
manny. Manny, manny--
Dying to hear it.
Wait ten seconds and come in
and tell both of us.
Jay, you took so long.
I'm not done with you.
I'm not done with you, either.
(squeals)
(door opens)
(manny) best Valentine's
party ever.
So there's this girl--
I should start from the beginning.
All right.
So first a little history...
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player