Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
I hope so.
- All right, you guys gotta call me.
- Yeah.
Make this happen.
Make this happen, all right?
See you guys. See you. All right.
- Joey, what's up? The usual?
- Yeah.
- Thanks, Willy.
- I hope you had a nice night.
Yes, sir.
What about that new place?
Oh, girl, I gotta go. Bye.
- You're late.
- Time is a relative thing, doll.
Mr. Hardigan, he's furious.
Mr. Blumenthal's threatening
to take his business elsewhere.
Guy named Pat Vinelli said
stay away from his sister or else.
- Patricia.
- Oh, and this one, your ex-wife...
...Donna Hawthorne?
She's really pissed.
- She's always pissed.
- I don't blame her.
Damn.
Mr. Sharkey, he's in his office.
- There he is.
- Hey, boss man.
- Joe, how you doing?
- Good.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, let me take a look at those.
- Watch the fight?
- I didn't. I was working.
Talk to me about Newcombe.
Are you gonna bag him?
- This is a make it or break it for us.
- Got dinner tonight at the Pinnacle.
- Pinnacle? Expensive.
- Yup.
Necessary.
- All right, reel him in.
- I always do.
If you don't, we're fucked.
Now, let me make this very clear.
- If you don't...
I'm_
...you're fucked.
- Got it. I got the deal.
Clean yourself up a little bit. Put on
your best suit. Wear cologne, smell good.
- Aramis. That chickie of his likes you.
- Loveit
- You knock them out, champ.
- I will. Bob and weave. Bob and weave.
Boxing.
Primitive.
- Yeah, Joe Doucett.
- That was a long lunch.
- What can I do for you?
- You know what day this is?
Yes, I do. It's the 8th of October...
...the year of our Lord 1993, which means
that I'm late with my child support again.
That is not why I'm calling, you know it.
I asked you to come to Mia's party three
weeks ago, you never called me back.
- Well, I can't make it, Donna.
- Why not?
- Because I have a big client dinner.
- Well, that's way more important...
...than your daughter's birthday.
- Listen, she is 3 years old, okay?
Three years old, okay? Do you think
she cares whether I'm there or not?
You know what, Joe?
As a husband, as a father...
...you are a fucking joke!
- You know what? You're a bitch, Donna.
- What did you say?
- You're a fucking bitch!
- Fuck...
- Fuck!
We don't make ads for Joe Doakes.
No, John Q. Public, John and Jane Doe,
Mr. Everyman.
No, no, no.
We make ads for Daniel Newcombe.
We make ads for Joe Doucett.
We cater to the elite,
the creme de la creme.
Celebrities, athletes,
entertainers, rappers.
All in a Daniel Newcombe fine motor
vehicle. That's what I'm gonna do for you.
- Ýt's a really great idea.
- It's a great idea. Listen to the lady.
- I'm gonna give you a shot.
- That's what I like to hear.
- Call me at the office first thing Monday.
- I will do so, sir.
I've gotta make a call.
Please excuse me.
You gotta do business
when you gotta do business.
- Don't be long? Okay.
- I'll be right back, baby.
- A beautiful couple.
- He's the best.
You won't regret it. I promise you.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Judy. I don't think
I could've done that without you.
Oh, sure you could've.
Laughing at all my jokes,
telling him what great ideas I have.
- They are great ideas.
- I appreciate that.
From one bullshit artist to another.
Listen.
I was thinking,
what do you say you and I...
...we get together this weekend,
ditch the old man...
...bottle of Scotch, eight ball of coke...
...dirty movies on Skinemax?
- Excuse me?
- What?
Let me get this straight.
You think I said those things
because I wanna fuck you?
- Yeah.
- No.
- No?
- No. I wanna get out of here...
...and away from you
as fast as humanly possible.
- Daniel likes you, God knows why.
- Okay.
- But, Joe?
- Yeah?
You're a dick.
And I would rather fuck a corpse.
Joe.
- You wanna disrespect me?
- No. I didn't...
- That's all right.
- It was just a misunderstanding.
I'm a big boy. I'm a big boy.
I can take it.
Okay.
But you disrespect the woman I love,
son, that's...
- That's just plain stupid.
- It was just a misunderstanding.
Let's go, baby.
He's not worth the trouble.
I'm dry!
Does anybody have any more alcohol?
Shut the fuck up!
Does anyone have more alcohol?
I can't...
I don't wanna go anymore
Hey, wait up!
U.S.A.
What is that?
I know what that is.
- What have you got?
- Five dollar.
What?
I haven't even touched anything yet.
Okay?
- How much is that?
- Five dollar.
My daughter.
She's gonna be 3 years old.
It's her birthday.
- Give me 5 dollar.
- Three years old.
Three years old.
- Spec...
- Give me 5 dollar.
You give me 5 dollar.
No.
Stop it.
Hey-
Hey!
Chucky!
- Chucky!
- We're closed.
No! It's Joe!
- Are you deaf? I said we're closed.
- Joe! Open up.
Hey! Come on! Give me one drink.
- Come on. One...
- Coffee.
No. Fuck coffee.
- No, you promised.
- You promised.
- You promised. Tell the duck.
I don't wanna tell the duck. Come back
tomorrow. You'll thank me in the morning.
No! No!
Fuck, no!
Goddamn it.
You don't wanna have fun!
Nobody wants to have fun anymore.
Goddamn it.
Hey-
What are you doing?
Hi.
Hey, I'm gonna take a piss, all right?
Okay?
Sorry about the toilet.
I didn't mean...
Hello?
Underwear.
What the hell is this?
Where the fuck is the phone?
Hello?
Can anybody hear me?
Son of a bitch.
Hello?
Can anybody hear me on the outside?
I'm stuck in a motel room.
Hello?
Fuck!
Hey. He)'-
Tell me why I'm here. Tell... No, listen.
Tell me why I'm here. No, no, no.
Dumplings. Anything but dumplings.
Please.
Please can I have something else
to eat?
Jesus H. Christ, God love you...
...give me something
other than this crap.
We're gonna squeeze for two...
...and then we're gonna open for two.
Make sure you resist it.
This is a great way to tone
and strengthen your upper legs.
And we all know that's an area
that often gets neglected.
So, if you haven't already,
join with me now.
And squeeze.
Come on, and up. Good.
- Can you feel the burn?
- Yes.
- And release.
- Release.
Here we go.
- And...
- Squeeze.
And release.
- Let's go, keep going. Squeeze.
Squeeze.
And up.
Now we're gonna speed it up.
Oh, yeah.
- Good. Feel it.
- I am.
Good, and open.
Good, and squeeze. And...
Good. Squeeze.
And open.
Squeeze.
There she is.
I owe you one.
Early this morning, the body
of single mother Donna Hawthorne...
...was discovered
in her Southside apartment.
Police confirmed that she was raped
and savagely beaten to death.
The victim was the mother
of a 3-year-old girl...
...who was inside the apartment
at the time of the killing.
To quote forensic investigators:
The evidence is irrefutable.
Prime suspect Joseph Doucett
was the victim's former husband...
...and father of the surviving child.
That's all from Stephanie Lee,
here on the scene. Back to you, Michael.
Remember...
...your enemy is most vulnerable
just before he strikes.
This area is extremely dangerous.
Don't let your guard down for a second.
They're everywhere.
This is really big.
We need to think about
what our next move will be.
We must figure out a plan
and execute it.
More importantly,
we need to get you two together.
- You have to speak with him.
- Unfortunately, it didn't work.
He's still alive.
We're going to have to try
something else.
I don't know. That seems risky.
If those two guys
are who we think they are...
- I am sorry.
- Six, seven, eight.
Up, down.
Let's take it down, down, slow.
Down, down, slow.
Take it lower.
That's it, bring it up.
Down, down, slow.
Arch your back. That's it.
That's it.
Recover before we get back into it.
I, William Jefferson Clinton,
do solemnly swear...
...I will faithfully execute
the office of president...
Come on this way.
You're the king.
Don't ever leave me.
Oh, I won't touch your babies.
I won't touch your babies.
I'll keep you nice and comfy here.
Yes, you protect those babies.
You protect those babies.
Where are you?
No!
No, no, no!
I'm sorry.
No.
Tonight on Mysteries of Crime:
July 30th, 1994.
Donna Hawthorne is brutally raped
and beaten to death...
...by her ex-husband, Joseph Doucett.
It's an open-and-shut case,
but there's just one problem.
The killer has disappeared.
For five years
Joe Doucett has eluded justice.
Where could this fiend be hiding?
I'm James Prestley.
Tonight, we examine
this mystery of crime.
What can you tell us about Mia?
We adopted Mia
shortly after the tragedy.
Neither her mother
or this Doucett murderer...
...had any living relatives...
...so we were lucky enough to...
- Blessed.
Yeah.
We were blessed to have this angel
come into our lives.
- Does Mia know what happened?
- No.
I mean, she knows she's adopted
and that her real mother is gone...
...but no more than that.
We're waiting until she's older
to tell her.
I wanted to talk to Mia,
but instead, Ken and Shirley Roos...
...let us watch their daughter
do what she loves best.
"Dear daughter, dear Mia...
...I saw you on TV today.
You looked very pretty.
When you played your cello,
it was so beautiful.
I'm glad that you're happy.
That you're being taken care of
by such nice people.
I wish it were me.
I'm writing to you to tell you...
- Lift your arms. Bend your right knee.
... that today I vow to change.
And today, I pledge to fight
against the impulses...
...that poison my body...
- No, no, no.
... and my mind...
...and my soul.
And I do this, dear daughter...
...for you...
...in hopes that one day
you will see me not for who I was...
...but for who I am.
- Squeeze.
- And I know that you hate me.
- Good.
And I deserve your hate...
...but not for the death of your mother.
No...
...I did not kill her.
I deserve your hate
because I was never a father to you.
Until now. "
Five, four...
...three, two, one.
Are you Andrew Blumenthal?
Are you Daniel Newcombe?
Are you Patrick Vinelli?
Mr. Sharkey?
Richard Dennison?
Are you Kenny Flowers?
Samuel Carver?
Are you Mark Atlas?
We've fought for the cause of liberty
and for the peace of the world.
Are you Bill Myers?
Are you Tom Marshall?
We are facing a storm
that most of us have feared.
The storm is now a category five...
...with sustained winds
of 150 miles an hour...
...with wind gusts
of 190 miles per hour.
I will get out.
And whoever you are...
...wherever you are...
...I Wm find you.
- Preserve, protect and defend...
- The Constitution of the United States.
... the Constitution of the United States.
- So help you God.
- So help me God.
Freedom is yours. You can do it.
Keep pushing, keep breathing.
Feel the inner peace within you.
Another chance to freedom.
It's always there for you.
- And that's everything. Back to you, Ray.
- Ninety-one, 92...
...93...
...94.
"Dear daughter,
today I leave this place...
...this prison.
And once I'm free,
I will get these letters to you, somehow.
All I ask, Mia, is that you read them
before you judge me.
I beg you.
Please.
Your loving father. "
Over 20 years on the air.
This season we look back...
...at the greatest mysteries of crime
in our history.
Tonight...
...the murder of Donna Hawthorne.
Tell me about your mother.
I don't remember my mother...
...but I know I loved her.
I know it in my heart and my soul.
And your father?
I don't remember him, either.
- I'm sorry, that's not what I was asking.
- I hate him for what he did.
No, there's a part of me
that hates him for what he did...
...but there's another part
that wants to understand...
...that wants to ask why.
Your father's been missing for 20 years.
I don't know if you presume he's dead...
...but if I could somehow bring him here,
do you think you could forgive him?
I could try.
Mia Roos is a beautiful
and very talented young woman...
...but what's most impressive about her
is her gentle and compassionate spirit.
I only hope that she's able to find
some kind of closure one day.
This mystery may remain unsolved,
but one thing is clear.
Justice always prevails.
I'm James Prestley.
God bless you.
Hey-
Hey, slow down a second.
Stop.
- Get the fuck off of me!
- Hey!
Leave the lady alone.
Leave her the fuck alone.
Stop! Stop! Wait!
Please! No! No!
No!
Stop! Stop!
Stop! Please!
Please!
Let him know I stopped by, all right?
Hey. Where is she?
Tell me where she is!
- Don't hurt me!
- Where is she?
Hey! Let him go!
Jesus, let go of him!
Jesus, Johnny, are you okay?
If you wanna see the doctor,
respect the rules, okay?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- I thought he was someone else.
- You okay?
- Is everything all right?
- Yeah, yeah, everything's fine.
That must be yours. Johnny takes things
that don't belong to him sometimes.
I'm really sorry about that.
Hey, I'm Dr. Tom Melby. I run the clinic.
I'm Joe Doakes.
Johnny, can we give Mr. Doakes
his umbrella back?
- Please?
- No.
- No, he can keep it.
- You sure?
Sir? Joe?
Sorry. If you think that you might need
any medical help...
...or, you know, if you just...
If you just wanna talk to someone,
my name is Marie Sebastian.
Please, take that.
We're closed!
Are you deaf? I said, we're closed!
Chucky.
Do I know you?
It's Joe.
Joe'?
Come in.
Twenty years in the same room?
Jesus Christ,
I would have lost my mind.
Why?
Why would somebody do that to you?
What could you have possibly done?
Here, I think you could use this.
- No, I'm fine with coffee.
- Well, what are you gonna do, Joe?
- Hello?
- Hello, Joseph.
How was your first day of freedom?
- Who is this?
- "I believe...
...that we are solely responsible
for our choices...
...and we have to accept
the consequences...
...of every deed, word and thought
throughout our lifetime. "
That was written
by Elisabeth Kilbler-Ross, Joseph.
And now, I want you to look at every...
...deed, word and thought...
...in the course
of your miserable existence.
There's more coming.
A formal proposal...
...that if you are successful, Joseph,
I think you will find peace.
I believe you may even find happiness.
Perhaps with that lovely daughter
of yours, Mia.
- Mia has nothing to do with this.
- Anyway, I'll be in touch.
Was that him? Let me see.
Blocked. What'd he say?
I need your help, Chucky.
Okay, Daniel Newcombe.
Probably gonna be a lot
of Daniel Newcombes.
He owned a bunch of car dealerships.
Daniel Newcombe Fine Motor Cars.
Well...
"Local businessman killed
in mid-air collision. "
We can take him off the list.
You know, if you don't mind me saying,
that's a very long list.
- I know. Bernard Sharkey.
- Yeah.
Advanced...
Advanced Advertising.
"Never Say Die Senior Citizen Club. "
- That's him?
- Yeah.
Why is he on the list?
Because he was my boss.
Is there an address?
- Yeah. This guy?
- Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can check him out.
- What'd he do?
- Oh, it's what I did, not what he did.
Save him.
What do you have to do?
Just write it in there?
Yeah. You write whatever you want
in there and then you hit enter. That's all.
- I can do the rest.
- No, I'm good.
- No, why don't you go to sleep?
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Joe.
Got some coffee.
Joe! Joe!
Hey! Hey, man!
Come on.
Hey, man! Hey!
911 operator, what's your emer...?
He gonna be all right?
Yeah, he'll be fine.
He just needs to rest.
Guy's exhausted.
He's also malnourished and dehydrated.
What happened to him?
He showed up last night
completely out of the blue.
I haven't seen the guy in 20 years.
I didn't even recognize him at first.
Comes inside, we sit down,
he starts telling me this crazy story.
What's the story?
- How do you know him?
- I don't.
- You don't.
- Well, what's the story?
I said enough already.
I don't know who you are.
- Come on, Chucky! It's 9:00 already!
- Shit.
Okay, I gotta open the joint.
Okay. I'm gonna stick around
and make sure he's all right for a while.
Hold your horses.
Dear daughter, dear Mia...
...I have been unjustly held in this
god-awful place for almost 20 years.
When I'm free of this place,
and I will be free of it...
...my purpose will be simple and pure.
I intend to prove my love for you.
To do this,
I must find the man who put me here.
I am your father.
Now it is my duty...
...now it is my responsibility...
...to take care of you.
To love you, Mia.
Please give me that chance.
The world can be a cold, ugly place,
and people can be cruel and deceitful.
But never let that change who you are.
One day I will be there
to share it with you.
Love, Daddy.
You read them?
You read my letters?
You had no right!
Who the fuck are you?
Chucky called me
because you were in bad shape.
- I'm all right now, you can get out.
- No, you're far from all right.
What are you doing here?
I apologize for reading your letters.
You didn't call the police?
- No, I didn't.
- Why?
- I believe you.
I believe that you've been locked up
for a long time.
Okay? I believe you want to be a father
to your daughter.
Don't touch me.
And that you want to prove your love
to her.
- Okay.
- I said, don't touch me.
Okay.
What if I thought
you knew too much, huh?
Reading my letters.
What if I felt
like I needed to kill you right now?
Then I suppose I'd be dead.
Joe...
...please take your hands off me.
If you are trying to find your daughter...
...and clear your name, I could help you.
Or let me take you to people who can.
There are social workers, legal aid,
even cops I trust.
No, I don't need your help.
Bernard Sharkey.
Bernard. He's up the stairs.
It's nice of y'all to come.
He doesn't get many visitors.
- Thank you.
- Bye. Enjoy.
Sorry, boss.
- How do you know that's not him?
- He seems happy.
The one who called me doesn't know
what happy means.
- What?
- I need Yellow Pages.
- Where are all the payphones?
- No. Okay. Hold on.
- What are you looking for?
- A restaurant.
- Okay.
- It's called Dragon something.
There. Here.
- Five dollar.
- Sir, buy something for your girlfriend.
Only $5.
Buy anything, $5.
I have to go.
I have a shift, I can't just not show up.
I put my number in your phone.
- I'll be free all day tomorrow.
- Thank you.
- The usual, sir?
- Yep. Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Put it on the bill.
Have a good day. See you tomorrow.
Where's my next order?
Sir. Excuse me, sir. Sir!
Hey-
You know the drill. Put it on the table.
Thirty-nine across.
"Alter ego of Edmond Dantés. "
The Count of Monte Cristo.
Hello. It's time to feed the pets.
F- O-O-D. F-O-O-D.
Goddamn,
these motherfuckers don't do shit.
Hey, what's up with the...?
Let me up out of here, motherfucker. Me
and you, man-to-man. Come on. Let's go.
Shit.
You want some get back,
then let me get up.
Me and you can go at it, motherfucker.
How about it?
Hold still.
What the fuck are you doing?
- What the fuck are you doing?
- Shut the fuck up.
There we go.
Are you ready?
Might wanna think about
what you're doing.
I've been thinking about it
for the last 20 years.
- Wait. What...?
- Hold still.
Cocksucker.
Motherfucker.
Shit.
You no dick, ass-licking son of a bitch!
- Fuck you.
- No, fuck you.
You booger-eating,
piss-drinking motherfucker.
If you stop now,
you may get out of here alive.
I'm gonna keep going...
...till I can pull your head off
with my bare hands.
Okay?
Listen to me. Listen to me.
I only run this place, all right?
I was hired to keep you here.
Who hired you?
- I can't tell you that.
- Then do me a favor...
...and shut the fuck up.
Who hired you?
I don't know his fucking name!
- Who hired you?
- No, no, no.
I swear. I swear it's the truth.
It's the truth. I never ask their names.
They never tell.
Oh, goddamn you, motherfucker!
God...! Oh, goddamn!
Oh, no. Oh, please. Please.
- I know you're gonna tell me something.
- I don't know shit.
I swear before God and eight
motherfucking white people, all right?
- Look. Look.
- No, no, no.
No, no, no.
- The tapes. The tapes.
- Where?
Over there in the cabinet. Go, look.
First one. Right there.
Go look. Right there.
Right there, right there.
First cabinet.
Second shelf, third tray, first cassette.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That one. That one.
"Tape one. Doucett. "
Go ahead, play it. Listen to it.
I don't know who he is.
I never get names.
I swear.
Sir, for a very long time, we have served
a very elite group of clients.
Now, I surmise that you've encountered
one such individual.
That's the only way
you received this number.
Correct.
Sir, this business existed
long before my tenure...
...and will continue long after I'm gone.
Never has a released guest
made its existence known...
...to the outside world.
- You've convinced me.
- Good.
How long will we have the pleasure...
...of entertaining this Mr. Doucett
as a guest?
Twenty years.
Get your asses up here now.
Open the door!
'See?
I told you.
Well, do we?
- You tell those motherfuckers...
- Tell them what?
Get the fuck away from the door!
Move away from the fucking door!
You hear me say get away?
Get away from the door.
Back the fuck up! Back up!
All right!
Easy. Easy now. Back up!
Easy. Easy.
You're not gonna get away with this,
Joe.
Back up.
Easy. Easy. Easy, Joe.
- Now!
- Get him!
- Get his ass! He killed Marco?
- Yeah, yeah, they killed Marco.
Son of a bitch.
Fuck!
Oh, my God.
You must take care of yourself.
The fun is only just beginning.
Joe.
What the fuck happened?
Come on.
Come on, Joe.
Hello?
Marie, he needs to stay down
for at least a week.
Keep movement to a minimum because
we don't wanna tear out those sutures.
He lost a lot of blood, but if he
stays down, he should be all right.
Half a centimeter difference
on some lacerations...
...it could've been a different story.
I really appreciate this, Tom.
You should let me take him
to the hospital.
- Well, you can't.
- Why not?
Somebody tried to kill him. Isn't that
something we should call the police over?
Well, I'm asking you not to.
He isn't a stray dog
or a bird with a broken wing, Marie.
I know that you love your lost causes...
...but sometimes we meet people
who can get us to engage in old thinking.
So, what, you think I'm using again?
Is that what you think?
Fuck you.
Come in.
Hey. Just wanted to see
if you were feeling all right.
I just wanna take a look at that wound
on your back really quickly, if that's okay.
Just turn around here.
Sorry.
Okay.
Well, it looks like the bleeding
has stopped, so that's a good sign.
I can't tell you what to do.
And I can't tell Marie either.
But I can tell you this.
She's been through a lot.
And if there's one thing that she doesn't
need any more of from anyone...
...it's pain.
Please don't hurt her.
He likes you.
Do you like him?
No. That was a long time ago.
Well, he still likes you.
I got your suit cleaned for you.
They didn't...
They didn't patch up the hole.
Can I help you? Here.
Well, I think you should go.
Come on, go.
Come on, get out of here.
- Go.
- Are you serious?
Don't come back. Go.
Come on, go.
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
last call for alcohol.
Speak up or forever hold your peace.
Hello?
Hello.
Hello. I thought it was time we met.
Hey!
Hey! What the...?
- Cool. Be cool.
- All right, all right.
Kill me now...
...and die seconds later
never knowing why.
Stop it!
I have your daughter.
If you'd like to see her alive again...
...I hope we can continue
without the violence.
May I see your list?
No.
It's of no use to you, trust me.
I have a proposition for you, Joseph.
If you should accept and succeed,
you will be greatly rewarded.
Firstly, with a video tape recording...
...of the rape and murder of your wife...
...Donna Hawthorne.
- No! No!
Oh, God, no.
- No. I don't wanna watch it.
- No!
- Please.
- Turn it off.
Say goodbye. Say goodbye.
- Turn it off. Turn it off.
- Very well.
Secondly,
my handwritten confession...
...to that crime
and your kidnapping and imprisonment.
Thirdly, and this is my favorite one...
...20 million dollars in diamonds.
Lastly, and again,
this is only if you should succeed...
...I will put a bullet through my brain...
...and you can watch.
Answer two questions.
One, who am I?
And two,
why did I imprison you for 20 years?
If you provide satisfactory answers
to both of these questions...
...in little more than 46 hours from now,
you win.
Refusal of the challenge
brings the same result as failure.
You stay a fugitive from justice...
...you get no reward, no closure...
...and I kill your daughter.
If you or anyone you know
should go to the police...
...or try to warn Mia,
the consequences will be severe.
Especially for her.
If you doubt the extent of my will
or my reach...
...I suggest you look in
on your friend Marie.
That is a live broadcast.
My proposition, yes or no?
Yes.
It's 629 Cooper Street,
and you'd better hurry.
Marie.
Marie. Marie.
Hey, Joe.
I was gonna let Cortez here
have some fun with her.
But now that you're here...
...the bitch can wait.
- Let's get him up on the table.
- Come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
Pull him up.
The last person
that got the better of me...
...I tracked her funky ass down...
...and tortured her for 16 fucking days.
Now, compared
to what I'm about to do to you...
...that was like an ant
fucking an elephant.
Yes?
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Reparations must be made.
Indeed it was you
who gave me this address...
...and I appreciate that, but...
No. No, there's nothing you can give me
that will stop me...
"Go to the door. "
Cortez.
Move.
Oh, well, maybe I can...
- I thank you for your generosity, sir.
- Damn.
And thank you
for appreciating my sacrifice.
Yes, sir. You have a good evening too.
You are a lucky motherfucker,
you know that?
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Hey. Hey. He)'-
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I have a friend downtown, so I can...
I can stay with her.
I don't feel safe here anymore.
Hello?
Every time he calls,
the same music plays.
Evergreen Academy.
Have you ever heard of that?
The prep school I went to.
This is so weird, I can't find anything.
Here's something.
Who's Edwina Burke?
She was the headmistress.
She might know something.
I used to drink a lot.
Yeah, well, I used to drink, and I also
did a shitload of other stuff, but...
Tonight was actually... It was the first time
that I wanted to use again.
I'm glad you're here.
Miss Burke?
Edwina Burke from Evergreen Academy?
- Yes.
- I was wondering if I could talk to you...
...about a former student? Joe Doucett.
- Come'm.
- I hope I'm not disturbing you.
Not at all. I was just making some tea.
Please, sit.
Joseph Deuce.
- Do you remember him?
- Of course.
We had many students gain notoriety,
but he was our only murderer.
- Thank God.
- Well, what if I told you...
...that Joe Doucett is innocent
and another man killed his wife?
Someone he knew at Evergreen.
Why don't you tell me who you are?
I'm sorry. My name's Marie Sebastian.
Have you heard
of the Innocence Project?
The Innocence Project
works with convicted felons.
Joseph disappeared 20 years ago.
Excuse me.
You really think he didn't do it?
We have evidence
that suggests he was framed.
That comes as some relief.
He was a very handsome boy.
Terrible student,
but Donna adored him...
...but he never appreciated that or her.
He was the kind of boy
who thought very highly of himself...
...and no one else.
In fact, he could be quite cruel
to the others.
Always with a grin, as if it were a joke.
I always felt he was a bit of a lost soul.
You said you thought
it might be another student?
- I'm assuming Joe had enemies?
- Many.
But for one to do something so horrible?
That would require
a very deep level of hatred.
Well, was there someone?
Anyone like that?
I honestly don't remember.
I drove by the academy this morning.
What happened?
They took it from him.
My father built it brick by brick.
The board of directors sold it
to some faceless corporation...
...and the gates have been locked
ever since.
It's all still there.
Files, records,
the entire history of the school...
."abandoned.
- Bye.
- Marie.
When you first arrived,
you said you believe Joe is innocent...
...not was.
I assumed he was dead.
Thank you.
God, you went to school here?
A long time ago.
- Let's come back tonight.
- Okay.
- Hello?
- I didn't know him back then.
I don't even recognize the name.
Your friends? Maybe they know him.
I haven't seen those assholes in years.
I doubt they'd talk to me.
I hated everything
about that fucking place, except you.
- I'm sorry, Joe.
- No, there's nothing to be sorry about.
Let me see what I can find out. Okay?
All right.
We should change your bandage.
- Need help?
- Yeah, please.
Sister?
The party you have called
is not available. Leave a message.
Joe, it's Chucky.
Call me as soon as you get this.
It's not about him, it's about her.
The whore, remember?
Jesus, Joe, call me.
Chucky?
You called her a whore.
You called her a whore!
Whore! Whore! Whore!
Adrian Pryce. Adrian Pryce.
I got it.
"As we begin our preparation
for the new year, I'd like to call attention...
...to the arrival of a new legacy student
from the Pryce family, Amanda Pryce. "
Will you check for Amanda?
Nineteen eighty-six.
I got it.
Amanda Pryce.
"It has come to my attention...
...that the Pryce family
is relocating to Luxembourg. "
Do you remember her?
Now, hold on.
Freshwomen should be in their rooms.
This is a serious infraction.
- Give it back to me.
- Hey, Joe, leave her alone.
- If she wants to go, let her go.
- Donna, shut up.
This is sexy. Very sexy. Huh, Chucky?
- Give it back to me.
- What a fucking freak.
- Here, douche bag.
- Disgusting.
- Hey.
- Come on.
Joe, let her through.
What dorm number are you in?
Come on, let her go.
- Really?
- That bitch.
Chucky, shut the fuck up.
- You gonna let her talk to me like that?
- I don't care, I'm drunk.
Now, let's get back.
I can't be missed.
Here you go.
There.
"Family Tragedy in Luxembourg. "
We are in the midst
of a most unpleasant mess.
The crime scene indicates
a double murder, suicide...
...and one
seriously injured young man.
The names cannot be released
at this time...
...awaiting the family identification.
"Son Tells Tale of Murder. "
That's him.
The man in the greenhouse that night.
He was her father.
Chucky, where are you? Call me.
If he kills you,
you're not gonna see your daughter.
Okay? And if you kill him...
...you're still not going
to see your daughter.
Just don't go.
I don't have a choice.
Please.
I don't want you to go.
Listen to me.
You promise me
you'll stay in this room.
Hey-
Don't call anyone...
...don't talk to anyone.
You stay.
Will you promise?
Yes.
- This is Dr. Tom Melby.
- Listen carefully to what I tell you.
- Is Marie okay?
- Write this down, you'll need directions.
I'm ready. Tell me where to go.
Where's Mia?
There.
Where? Where is she?
Here.
Quite close by, actually.
But you will not see her...
...you will not save her
until I have your answers.
Please put that away.
She will suffer great pain if you do not.
Your reward.
As I said, I'm a man of my word.
So who am I?
Adrian Doyle Pryce.
Why did I imprison you for 20 years?
- You blame me for what happened.
- Elaborate.
I saw your sister with a man,
down at the greenhouse.
"They were fucking.
They were fucking. "
- Isn't that what you told everyone?
- Yes.
I told Donna.
I told Chucky, I told half of Evergreen.
Gossip spreads like the plague.
- Amanda's a whore! Whore! Whore!
- Stop it!
- Whore! Whore! Whore!
- Leave me alone!
- Chucky! Stop it now!
- Whore! Whore! Whore!
- I didn't do anything!
You have no idea how difficult it was
for Amanda then.
The torture that she endured,
all because of you.
Continue.
I didn't know it was your father
until today.
The school must have found out
what was going on...
...and he got your family out of the States
as fast as possible.
I'm only guessing,
but running didn't help.
He must've been afraid
of what was coming.
You know nothing of my father.
He knew no fear, only love.
Arthur Pryce was a great man.
He will always be a great man.
What we had together...
...was beautiful and special and pure.
My father did what he did
to honor and preserve that.
Father.
Daddy.
My father loved my mother.
He loved my sister.
And he loved me.
You see, Joseph,
my sister Amanda and I thought...
...that what we had with my father
would last forever.
That nobody could take it from us.
And yet, you did.
And, yes...
...that is why I imprisoned you
for 20 years.
It seems you've won, Mr. Doucett.
Take me to Mia.
Yes, of course.
Do you know what I find fascinating,
Joseph?
All this time,
you never stopped to ask...
...the most fundamental question of all.
Why did I let you go?
Mind your head.
Introducing one of the longest-running
shows on television...
...but it had only a single viewer.
You.
We adopted Mia
shortly after the tragedy.
Neither her mother
or this Doucett murderer...
...had any living relatives.
- So we were lucky enough to...
- Blessed.
Yes, we were blessed.
Isn't it amazing?
People just believe whatever they see
on television.
Thank you, Ashley. You can go.
What...?
- Joseph.
- No. No. Mia.
Mia!
Oh, Joseph.
Joseph, that is not your daughter.
Ashley is a musician...
...and very well paid actress...
...that I've had in my employ
since she was 10 years old.
Oh, goodness.
Enough with the games.
You tell me where she is. You tell me.
Answer the question you never asked.
Why did I let you go?
You tell me. You tell me.
You know the answer, Joseph.
In your heart of hearts, you know...
...the plain and simple truth.
- Mia. Mia.
- It took a while...
- Mia. Where are you going?
... to change her name...
...her records...
...to find the right parents.
An insensitive mother...
...a loving father
taken from her too soon.
It took 20 years to create her.
A sensitive, caring woman...
...eager to help those in need...
...because she herself had overcome...
...such a troubled past.
The kind of woman who couldn't help...
...but fall in love with a man like you...
Joseph Deuce..
No!
No, no, no! God!
No, God, no, please, no!
Please, God, no!
- Joe? Joe?
- No way, no way, no!
No, no, no.
You can't hurt her.
Who is this?
Leave her out of it, please. Please.
- Who is this?
- Please, please, please.
No, don't hurt her.
Hurt me. Hurt me.
Kill me. Yes, yes, yes.
Yes. Kill me. Please.
- Please kill me.
- I don't want to kill you, Joseph.
This is why I let you go.
So that I could experience
this moment with you.
So that you could truly understand
what I had...
...and what you took from me.
Heaven make me free of it.
The rest is silence.
"Dear Marie,
you will never see me again.
I'm gone from your life forever.
I have done something terrible.
Something unforgivable.
And for it, I must be punished.
For a short while, I was happy...
...because of you.
And I will cherish that happiness forever.
Marie, I will love you, always.
But you must forget me.
Do not waste one more moment
of your life thinking about me.
I want you to be with someone
who will care for you...
...watch over you, bring you joy...
...not pain.
I want you to find happiness
with a good man...
...who has a good heart.
A man unlike me.
Goodbye.
Joe.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player