Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
I just don't want to
make one of these tapes
if it's something you
do with every girl.
Every girl? No, no. I am
strictly a one-woman guy.
Well, I don't want to end
up all over the Internet.
I pride myself on
keeping a low profile.
My private life is private.
Hm.
Wait. I thought you never did this before.
What are all these?
Oh, uh, just some
movies I rented.
"Me and Brandy, missionary"?
A tale of two girls
who become nuns.
"Me and Brandy, doggy"?
The sequel. The nuns
adopt a chocolate lab.
What are all those?
Oh, that's just your standard
home security setup.
Basic run-of-the mill.
No big deal, nothing too elaborate.
Everybody has them.
And why do you need security
cameras pointing at your bed?
In case a burglar tries
to steal my sex tapes.
Now, let's get into bed.
Let's just make this quick. I have
a court hearing in the morning.
Judge Henderson? No.
I wish. Thompson.
Mm. That's going
to suck for you.
It was a driving mishap thingy.
Do me a favor. Promise
me you won't drive.
That's sweet. You're
worried about me driving.
Mm-mm. I'm worried about me.
I'm a pedestrian.
Ow!
Sorry. That's my
sobriety monitor.
Ow!
Sorry. Sorry.
Ankle. Tracking bracelet.
Oh, wait. Wait. Sorry, just...
Who put that on you? I did.
It's the only way I
can have an orgasm.
Not tonight.
What are you doing? Huh?
Just... warming up.
You sure we're alone here? Feels like
there's somebody else in this house.
Did you hear that?
That's nothing.
Ok, what is that?
Just... unraveling the old hose.
Save it for tomorrow, Raul.
Si, senor.
Wow. That was amazing.
Charlie.
Wow. Get out of here, Emilio.
Charlie, I'm scared.
Lindsay, sweetie, there's
nothing to be afraid of.
Hey, I got the stuff. I got
to call you back, man.
Ow!
I think I better go.
Really? How about tomorrow?
You busy?
I'm going to blow you
across the room.
Sounds awesome.
And thus our story begins.
The large reward offered for
the rescue of Charlie's kids
drew the attention of
police, private detectives
and red cross volunteers.
Everyone was on high alert
for these children,
except these two guys.
No, man, obamacare gives senior
citizens access to cheaper drugs,
free preventative care, and it
closes the medicare part d loophole.
And how does that help if I
get shampoo in my dick hole?
What? Mean to tell me
you ain't never got
shampoo in your pee hole? Ok.
Maybe like once or twice.
Yeah, once or twice
when you was playing
with yourself.
No, I wasn't playing
with myself.
I was showering, and
crazy got up in there.
Bullshit. Cam Newton's
law of gravity is:
That thing must be up in order
for that soap to go down.
Well, either way, that
shit stings like hell.
Sting like a mother, man, it feel
like it's a hornet up in there.
And he found out his girl be, you know,
doing her thing with another man.
Exactly. I don't
understand why
the shampoo company
can't fix that, man.
They got "no more tears."
Why they can't make no
more hornets in your dick?
I don't really think they expect you
to use the no more tears on your dick.
Well, why they call
it Johnson & Johnson?
I got a better question, man. What
the hell are two stoners doing
wandering around these
spooky-ass woods?
Look, it's going to be worth it.
I told you...
This is humboldt county.
This is where all the growers
grow their bomb-ass shit.
You think they're gonna be cool
with us just helping ourselves?
Look, man, we ain't
taking no plants.
We're gonna snip a few buds.
You know what I'm saying?
It's gonna grow back
just like a lobster paw.
You know, that's how nature do.
I don't know, man. Just
doesn't feel right.
Man, they ain't gonna care.
Look, man, we're gonna be cool.
We're gonna roll one blunt, then
we're gonna get up out of here.
Just one? Just one.
They won't care, huh?
Man, just keep running.
Holy shit. Is that a drone? They're
going all zero dark thirty on our ass.
Yo, I think they gone.
Oh, whoa. It's a cabin in the woods.
We need to go hide over in there.
Nah, man, I'm not
going in there.
It reminds me of a
horror movie I once saw.
What horror movie? The one
with the cabin in the woods.
Friday the 13th? No.
The one with the
cabin in the woods.
Texas chain saw massacre?
No, the one with the
cabin in the woods.
The ring. Uh-uh.
The one with the cabin in the woods.
Blair witch project.
No, man, the one with
the cabin in the woods.
The munsters. That
wasn't in the woods.
They wasn't even a damn movie.
Look, man,
we ain't got time for
this shit right now.
We need to get to that
cabin in the woods.
What the hell is that sound?
Sound like the house settling.
It looked new.
I'm gonna take a look around.
Go ahead.
Ah! What is that?
Ah! Oh!
Where we shooting? There.
Where? The dark!
There? No, this dark.
Over there.
Dude, what the hell was that?
Big-ass Alaskan king crab
just ran up on me, man.
Crab? Cuz, we banging?
Ja'Marcus,
put the guns down, man. Put
yours down first, homey.
All right, on three.
One, two, three.
Damn. You want
to try it again?
Sure. One, two, three.
One, two, three.
Uno, dos, tres.
Man, we could do
this shit all day.
Truce? Truce.
Hey, yo, d'Andre. Look, homey.
It's two little girls.
They're little
racist girls, man.
Wearing blackface.
Cool with that?
Hey, little girl,
what's your name?
What'd she say? She said,
"I wonder what your leg"
"tastes like." What? Ah, man!
Little spider girl bit me.
Maybe you're going
to get superpowers.
Ain't no black superheroes.
I'm on it.
' Hi-ya!
Yo. D'Andre, I think they're the
missing kids from the news.
How can you be so sure? Look.
I don't know, man. Well,
if it is the missing kids,
I'm gonna take that reward
money, and I'm gonna buy me
a yacht, fill it with cash,
bitches and a shark.
Why would you want
to buy a shark?
Trust me... we're
gonna need a shark.
No, this can't be right.
Hi, mom.
I got to call you back.
No baby, no baby,
no baby, no baby.
You're pregnant... no!
With anticipation over the
outcome of this ipregnancy test,
which has determined
that you are...
You got to be kidding me.
Oh, no.
Not pregnant.
You dodged a bullet,
you lucky slut.
Thank you, God. Sweet!
Great news: They found
my brother's kids.
Oh, crap.
We're very fortunate the older
one, Kathy, has retained
most of her vocabulary.
The baby hasn't
actually said a word.
Why not? Because he's a baby.
They've been alone here
over three long months.
I need to warn both of you that
this is not going to be easy.
I'm ready for it.
Hello. No, no. Wrong window.
Here's where the children are.
- What is she doing?
- In order to survive
their extreme isolation, the girls
created an imaginary guardian,
a parent figure to feed them, sing to them.
They call her mama.
But these may help
you break through.
And the ritalin may
help, as well.
The proper dosage for
someone their age is...
Wish me luck.
Hey, lily.
Oh, how cute.
Ok. Kathy.
It's ok, Kathy. Remember these?
You used to wear them
to help you see better.
No, no, no!
Maybe we should get her some contacts...
The soft kind.
Daddy?
No, sweetheart. Not daddy.
I'm your Uncle Dan. Remember?
And this is Jody.
Jo...
Jody. No pause between
"Jo" and "dy."
Jo...
Dan, we're at an impasse.
I see constant conflict.
It's fine. They'll
warm up to you.
Oh!
Hey, hey, hey, little
lady, that's not how...
You little mother...!
Well, everything checks out.
They seem like good kids, doc.
Just validate our parking.
We'll take them home.
Folks, I wish it were that easy.
You don't validate?
I'm saying the kids are
not yours to take.
Well, you can't win them all.
Let's skedaddle.
That's not fair. They're my brother
Charlie's kids. We deserve them.
Do you? Your wife plays in a punk rock
band, staying out all night long,
high on drugs, sleeping with
a different man every night.
I don't think the courts are gonna
look upon that too favorably.
But... I was just
messing with you.
The kids are yours. They are?
Did you hear that, honey?
They're ours!
On one condition. This house is owned
by the institute for case studies.
Every room is fully
wired with cameras.
If you move into the
house, you get the kids.
Can't we just sell the house and put
the kids in a high-end orphanage?
Jody, do you really think
you're out out to be a mom?
Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
Of course she is. Dan!
Now, no more rock band,
no more silly wig.
It's not silly. It's
all a part of me.
And no more tattoos.
What are you doing?
What I had to. We're a
perfect suburban couple.
And so Dan and Jody headed to their
new house with their new children.
But, like a slutty sorority girl
returning from spring break,
they were also bringing
home a hidden evil.
All right, kids,
here's our new house.
And here's Uncle Dan.
Hi. Don't forget about mommy!
Dan, I'm not their mommy.
They can call me aunt Jody.
Or jodes, j-mom, Mrs. Sanders.
Or, if they really want to call me...
Garage!
Here comes Jody and Aidan,
entering the house for
the very first time.
This is where we're going to protect
you and make sure nothing bad...
Oh, my God, Aidan! I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Maybe we should put
him in the carrier.
There, see, that's better. Come on, Aidan.
What, what, what?
Relax, it's ok. Oh, my gosh.
Dan, I lost the baby! What?
Oh, my gosh, Aidan!
Aidan, where are you?!
- Aidan!
- Where did you go?
Oh, there he is, ok.
Here's your sister Kathy.
Oh, Aidan, it's ok.
You've just got to
talk in a baby voice.
It doesn't even matter
what you say. Ok.
I'm your stepmommy.
I'm not your fricking mommy.
There you go, you're a natural.
What's that smell?
Oh, my God, what do I do? Oh, oh!
Here, this, hold on!
' Uncle Dan!
' Kathy! Oh, sorry, ow!
All right, there
you go, sweetie.
Is it chilly in here? I felt it
as soon as I entered the room.
Feels fine. Hey, what are these?
This is interesting.
What is this?
I don't know, mama
drew that one.
Look, we drew this
picture for Aidan.
See? It's Aidan on a
rocket to the moon.
Oh. Sitting on a rocket.
Where's lily?
Oh, no, sweetie, the other end.
Ooh!
Let's go introduce Aidan
to the rest of the family.
Oh, and there's our
furry family member.
- Yes, Maria.
- No, Dan, Artie.
Oh, yes, of course,
our dog Artie.
Ay, the new baby. I make blessing.
Oh.
Ok, ok, that's good, Maria.
Oh, my gosh.
With three new
kids to care for,
Dan really needed to start
performing at work.
Unfortunately he was having
some issues with a colleague.
Ok, Caesar, this is the
one, I can feel it.
Eighty-one seconds? Oh, Caesar.
That's your worst time yet.
You're doing even worse
on your creativity test.
I mean, look at all the imaginative
things I made out of blocks.
Like this awesome plane.
Dan, do you have
any results yet?
Oh, well, I've been injecting
the primates twice a day
with the I-13 intelligence drug.
I'm hoping in a week or so...
I hope Caesar is not just a
big waste of time and money.
I'm the one responsible to the board.
Just show me one thing positive.
Look. They still
throw their shit.
But now they can keep score.
We have to kick-start this thing.
When can we go to human trials?
We're close, but there's
an intermediate step.
If the I-13 works on
these reality wives...
You better check that shit.
Who gonna check me, boo?
We're pinning the future
of our lab on wild beasts.
They're not beasts.
They have feelings,
they have families.
Males pee standing up,
females pee sitting down.
These apes are just like you.
And me... you and me,
blacks and whites.
More like whites, of course. We
whites are a lighter shade of ape
whereas you are bla... dder
infection, we're all at risk.
So, what were we talking about again?
Vaginae.
Shut up. Yes, of course.
Caesar has got to show some human
intelligence at that board meeting...
Caesar's probably smarter than
half of those board members.
Dan... I know what
you're going to say.
"If he's so smart, why
is he in a cage?"
You're in the cage.
What?
Oh, you're looking for this?
Uh-huh.
It's my ballerina doll.
You made this? Mama did,
using twigs, moss, spiderwebs,
sparrow bones, lizard eyes,
all held together with rat droppings.
Oh, geez.
Ah, ah, ah. What...
What are you doing?
I just can't deal with these kids.
They're creepy.
We should just take 'em back.
Maybe you guys just need to
find some common ground.
What about that ballerina doll
Kathy's always playing with?
I don't want to talk
about the ballet.
I saw what the ballet
did to my mom.
She became obsessed.
She even danced the swan while
she was pregnant with me.
Boo, ray, boo! Shh!
Shh. Hell. You better sit back before
I punch you in your damn throat.
We're trying to enjoy the show.
You go on... shh... shh me again.
I double-dog dare you, hell.
Better ask somebody who I am.
Whoa!
Got it.
Mom was never the same.
That's unlikely to ever
happen again, ever.
Just give it a shot. Look
what I found earlier.
I mean, I know it's just
a local production.
But could be something for you and
Kathy to talk about, could be fun.
You really think so? Yes.
Well, I suppose I
could check it out.
Ok. But the minute it becomes
too difficult, I'm giving up.
That's the spirit.
Even though Jody only
returned to the ballet
to connect with the girls,
as she got closer she couldn't help
but get excited at the prospect
of becoming the swan queen.
This season we open
with "swan lake."
As you all know, this piece
has the most challenging
and demanding role in all of ballet...
The swan queen.
Sizing up her competition,
Jody knew the battle
would be a tough one.
The white and the black.
Fortunately we have with us
prima ballerina and the lead
in my last 146 productions...
Heather Darcy.
Ah, the seasoned professional.
The still brilliant,
crusty, old, weathered,
leather-faced elder statesman of
ballet to whom these young girls,
less experienced, more
beautiful and delicious,
but still very raw ballerina
hopefuls, look up.
Show these far more desirable
children how it's done, huh?
Music!
Try that thing where
you are skipping
and you hop and you spread
your legs a little bit.
Look at that form,
that technique.
I'll never be that good.
I'm Jody, by the way.
Kendra.
Are you going to try out? Me?
Oh, I don't know. I mean, I
like to dance, but I just...
I don't like to be the
center of attention.
Ok, who's next? Oh, food.
Huh?
It is as if I am seeing
ballet for the first time.
That's not ballet.
The passion, the sensuality.
An ass that makes you want to crawl
inside and take up residence.
I can show passion.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, oh, yeah, oh.
Jody certainly had her
work cut out for her.
That kendra chick was smokin'.
Do you accept Euros?
Kathy, lily, Aidan?
Jody? Ah!
Oh, sweetie, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm fine.
It was on the floor.
Ah, probably a screw loose.
I'll fix it.
I feel like there's
something in this house.
Like what?
Like I feel hot, clammy,
foul-smelling breath on my neck.
You need call psychic.
Kill bad spirits.
Ugh. No, Maria,
enough of this stuff.
Ok, then I do blessing,
I protect house.
Honey, you really need to relax.
You're just stressed out
about the children.
No, it's this house.
I... I feel it.
And Maria's a little off. I mean,
honestly do you really trust her?
Oh, honey, don't worry,
she couldn't hurt a fly.
Look, you have a big day
ahead of you tomorrow.
Let's just get you
some sleep, ok?
Love you.
I don't believe this... our
whole house ransacked.
You leave the house unattended
with the doors unlocked
and look what happens.
They didn't take anything.
It's just vandalism.
Every room except the
kids' rooms was trashed.
So you suspect the kids?
It was mama. Mama did it.
She hates this house.
She hates you.
Ok, Maria, this is camera.
Necesito filming.
Thank you for helping
me clean up, sweetie.
Oh, hey, been looking all
over for this thing.
Still got it...
I'm sorry! God, help, honey!
Maria, honey, help! Geez!
Maria, put the camera...
Oh, look at this.
Mom coaching me when
I was a little girl.
Aw... always applying
the guilt trip.
That got me the lead.
Look, Maria.
Maria, look what I found.
What is this?
Oh, uh, that's... a new type
of electric toothbrush.
Vibrations knock the
tartar off your teeth.
- Look, a whole box of toothbrushes.
- Whoa.
This black one is huge. Ok.
And look, here's a double-sided one.
All right.
And one that I can
strap on to my face.
Nope. Put that over here.
Uncle Dan, what is this?
Beaded floss?
That's grown-up floss, honey.
Graffiti!
Did you see this?
Who does that? What are we...?
Maria.
Maria, por favor.
Miss Jody, miss Jody, you call this man...
Mr. Blaine.
He helped my sister.
This is a psychic.
Si, he'll help you.
No, what we really need are
more security cameras.
Uncle Dan. You know, these toothbrushes
look an awful lot like dildos.
Ow!
This is fun, mama.
You're still awake?
All right, listen,
guys, it's just us
until Uncle Dan comes
back from the hospital.
I don't like it, you don't
like it, I don't like it.
Now go to sleep. I have to be
up early for ballet tomorrow.
You really like ballet, don't you?
Yeah, but I don't want you to go.
Why?
Mama says you're going
to have an accident.
Oh, ok. Is this the same
mama who trashed the house?
Basically, yes.
Don't go in there.
I wasn't going to.
Just don't.
It's my house, I can if I want.
I wouldn't.
Would. Wouldn't.
Would, too. Would not.
You know what? I'm the adult.
You're not the boss of me.
Don't.
I told you not to
let anyone in!
And so Jody was...
Oh, my God, I just smelled that.
It just got to me, yeah.
And so Jody was...
Oh, no, I... I'm sorry,
you have to excuse me.
I got to get some fresh air.
The next section
should explain itself.
All right, attention.
I do not wish to repeat myself.
I repeat, I do not
wish to repeat myself.
I require the sweater
I wear as a scarf.
Ah. Comfortable, huh?
Mm... mother, please,
I am working.
All right, because Heather
Darcy is so old, this season
we will have a new swan queen,
and that person is Jody Sanders.
Now, Jody, show us your routine.
No, I'm the swan queen.
Watch me. Ah...!
As I was saying, my
choice for new...
Her?! Anyone but her!
You might just as well
have picked the janitor!
Me?
Ira, please, not now.
Ok. What?
Yes, it was a
difficult decision,
but I have always been
attracted to Jody.
How could I not? She has the
body of a fifth-grade boy.
But in the event that
she is unable to dance,
I am naming as her
understudy kendra Brooks.
All right, that's lunch.
Ooh, this is a nice house.
I'm gonna go find the girls.
Kathy, how did you know I was going to
have an accident today at the ballet?
Mama told me.
Ok, well, how did mama know I
was going to have an accident?
Oh, there you are. I found
this bandage on my head.
Dan, please. I think there is
something going on in this house,
something about this mama.
I'm gonna call the psychic
Maria told us about.
Jody, do you really think
we need a psychic?
Uncle Dan, come here.
Coming. I want to
show you something.
Uncle Dan, mama taught me some tricks.
Look what I can do.
- Oh, wow, that's really good, honey.
- Dada.
Good lord.
Uncle Dan, look at me.
Evil spirits.
Look, Mr. Dan, look.
Isn't that one of
Jody's bathing suits?
You're facing something our
human minds cannot imagine.
Mama.
Let's get you in a robe.
Do you want to hear
about the ballet today?
Mama's helping us get ready.
Oh, ok, I'll brush, too.
Hm. Where did my toothbrush go?
Hey, we don't lick our
balls in this house.
Sorry, won't happen again.
Try as she might,
Jody just couldn't seem to
connect with those kids.
Or get the taste of that
toothbrush out of her mouth.
Was it just eight-year-old
teen angst,
or were there otherworldly
forces at work here?
Baby. Hm?
Babe, I heard something. What?
I think there's someone
in the kitchen.
See? There's nobody down here.
There it is again! Right there.
Go look.
Jody, calm down. See, there's nothing
to worry about. It's just...
Oh, God! Geez!
Dan, I'm calling the psychic!
Ah! Make the call!
Blaine fulda,
professional psychic.
Hi, I'm Jody.
Indeed you are. Yes. And
this is my husband Dan.
Your payment as requested.
$500 in unmarked bills.
And of course, you know Maria.
Hola, Mr. Blaine. Hi, Maria.
How's your sister?
Dead. Demon kill her.
Well, that explains the
unreturned phone calls.
I'm sensing evil.
I'm gonna have to get some of
your personal belongings here,
just so I can check for
demon and ghost residue.
I'm not gonna be able to
lift all those monitors,
but I'll send my cousin
tomorrow with the white van.
He can get them in there.
Dan was attacked by the
kitchen last night.
We think it might be mama.
Kitchen attack?
You could've said that earlier.
If a room turns on you, it's
either a ghost or a demon.
Can a demon take over someone?
Like, live within them?
Damn, that's some scary shit.
So a demon is about the
worst thing you can have?
No, ma'am, an std is the worst
thing that you can have.
Who do you know who wants to hurt you?
Do you have a jealous colleague at work?
A Facebook friend you
might have ignored?
Maybe you adopted a small
African child named ikatababwe,
promising to feed this
nigga for 25 cents a day.
But then he needs
something to drink!
Anyway, let's begin. Ok.
This is the evil communicator.
When I put this on, I'll be able
to cross over to the other side
and confront the entity. That
will immediately trigger
the final $350 payment of
child support to tisha fulda.
And if you guys would just join
hands, close eyes and concentrate.
Empty your mind of all the
thoughts of today's troubles.
Everything that went on,
get that out of your mind.
This is all about the
spirit world here.
And three, two and one.
What's happening? Things are
starting to move all by itself!
Breathe! Breathe!
- Wait, I don't think he can breathe!
- He's a pro!
A sophisticated piece
of equipment like that?
Of course he can breathe.
Shit, I couldn't breathe.
Almost killed myself. All
right, I communicated.
It was definitely a demon.
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute. I was wrong.
It's a ghost.
So strong.
Ow!
Help, it's got me! Dan!
Dan, wake up!
Ma'am, you got to
get out of here. It's evil!
It's pure evil! It's mama!
Now do you believe that
something's going on?
He got dragged away,
yelling out, "mama."
He got dragged away? I
don't remember that.
Dan, you were unconscious. I
don't remember that, either.
Look, honey, I don't
want to argue.
The important thing is,
we love each other, ok?
No, the important thing is that
this mama thing could be real
and she might be
trying to kill us.
Jod, that guy was a fraud
and that's it. Ok?
What's that? My penis.
No. Yes.
There, right now, there.
I know. I'm trying.
What the hell is that?
My penis?
What's making that sound?
Dan, what is that?
My penis.
Is that smoke?
Maria! What are you doing?!
You're gonna burn down the house!
Kill bad spirits!
What is going on? Maria
almost burned the house down.
What? That's it, she's got...
Enough! This is getting out of hand.
You're scaring everybody.
You can't fire her. I mean,
she's been with us for years.
I don't know what to do.
That's discrimination.
Ok, now what the hell?
This is completely insane! It's
what she believes in, honey!
Give me that!
You're gonna let me go?!
Your family is not safe!
I'm sorry, Maria, it's
just not working out.
I'll give you a recommendation,
just nothing involving kids
or within a mile
of anyone's house.
I can't do this anymore.
I got to go to work.
I don't even understand
what you're saying!
Ow!
Ladies and gentlemen,
for the past two years, our
own Dan Sanders has been
testing the I-13
compound on 30 apes.
Unfortunately, 29
of them turned into
insane, aggressive,
deviant sexual predators.
But one, Caesar,
has experienced a huge
leap in intelligence.
Here he plays three opponents.
Of course, they're apes.
But Caesar's superior capabilities
are the work of one man.
The brains behind the
I-13 project, Dan San...
Are you ok? I'm fine, Martin.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'd like
to introduce you to Caesar...
You're not getting away from me!
Oof!
Oh, no!
Traffic is backed up on
the broad street bridge,
where apparently police are battling
dozens of apes in a running gunfight.
Our reports indicate that a
scientist at a research laboratory
gave these apes an experimental
intelligence drug.
I'm being told that all available
officers are now on the scene.
But at this time, we are advising all
our viewers to find alternate routes.
I'm now being told we
have the actual 911 call
that first alerted the
police to the situation.
911, what's your emergency?
Oh, my God! Apes are
inside the house!
Calm down, ma'am. What happened?
We were making love and...
Oh, my God!
- They're attacking him!
- Who are they attacking, ma'am?
Carl! Oh, my God!
Please, help him!
- Where is your husband right now?
- Carl's not my husband.
My husband's the anchor
for channel 12 news.
He can't know about it.
- Ok, ma'am, but we need to...
- Hurry!
Send help while my husband's
still on the air!
Ma'am, that's not important.
Your life is.
Yeah, you're right.
Why should he care?
I mean, I'm pretty sure he's been
sleeping with his co-anchor, that bitch!
Oh, I'm gonna rip her...
Congratulations, girl.
I knew it was gonna be you. You're
just so perfect, so mechanical.
Watching you dance is
like watching a robot.
Thanks.
So hungry.
Mm.
Is that all? Pierre
has a weight limit.
I'm too heavy. Look at mara.
She looks great.
Look, are you sure you're ok?
Weird things have been
happening at home.
Kathy said there was
going to be an accident.
Then it happened to Heather.
That's some serious shit.
You should talk to those kids.
Whoa, pizza.
I eat and eat and eat, and
I don't gain a pound.
Heather!
You think you can replace me?
Well, we'll see how you like
it once the swan consumes you!
Damn it!
Door!
Son of a bitch!
Oh, I didn't know you
were such a good builder.
Wow.
Kathy, I want you to
tell me about mama.
Mama doesn't like it
when you talk about her.
Who is mama?
She was a woman who
read from an evil book.
Sometimes she comes
to us in a dream.
In a dream?
In your dreams, of course.
I wish I could see what's
inside your dreams.
To extract what's in your dreams.
To perform an inception.
Will you drop that?
That's my birth tuba.
Hello. I'm dom kolb. You called
about a dream extraction?
Yes. I need to find out
about an evil book.
Mm-hm.
This machine will allow us
access to the dream world.
Let's begin.
So when do we start dreaming?
You never really remember
the beginning of a dream,
do you? I guess.
Ok, then,
this is your first lesson in
shared dreaming. Stay calm.
Sorry. I dropped
my phone in there.
You need to clear your subconscious.
And watch what you think about.
Nothing crazy. Right.
Like having your crotch
burst into flames.
What does that have
to do with ma...?
Hey! Oh.
Let's start over.
I'm Jody Sanders.
Yes, my dear. I've
been expecting you.
Please, come in.
They call me Christian grey.
How do you like my blue room?
It's red. Oh. I'm color-blind.
My decorator assured me that...
Never mind.
Champagne? Mm.
Have a seat.
I'll stand.
Hey, Christian, man, golly, man!
I'd like to thank you a lot, man,
for working on my prostrate
like it was a speed bag.
Yes, Michael, I must admit, I was
surprised at your performance, as well.
Not bad for a washed-up,
overweight, facially tattooed...
Do it again.
Oh...!
I have no idea
what that one was.
Me neither.
Mama, are you here?
Dom, is that you? Oh, shit.
You said you'd had a dream
that we'd grow old together.
Right. And we will.
What are you doing here? Hi.
How could you bring her here?
What about our children?
They're not real. Yes, they are.
Watch.
James, phillippa!
Ew.
You're not gonna jump, are you?
I hadn't thought about that.
Thank you.
Ok, we're not getting anywhere.
What does any of this
have to do with Kathy?
Kathy? I thought you were Kathy.
Oh.
"Gort klaatu barada nikto."
What's happening to me?!
That must have been her. Mama.
She wants to take us
home to the cliff.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
But I trust you'll give me
a favorable yelp review?
Jody's mission was clear.
The evil book that created mama
was located in the cellar
of a cabin, in the woods.
If she could find that cabin, maybe
she could find some answers.
If we can find that cabin, maybe
we can find some answers.
Ok, calm down. I'm
gonna come over.
Kendra? What?
Ok, wait, what's going on now?
I think she's out there!
Ok, ok, just... you stay calm!
Front door open.
She's in the house!
Ok, stay... front door open.
Shut the hell up!
No need for that, bitch.
Bitch?! Front door open.
No, you did not just call me a bitch!
Front door open...
Honey? Dan?!
I am so sorry. I didn't
know who you were and...
It's ok, honey, it was an accident.
Right, Caesar?
And of course he can stay here.
Look at that. Caesar wants to
help out around the house.
Aw.
Hey...
I'm sorry, I see an ape,
I come out swinging.
That's understandable.
Here you go.
I am so glad you're ok, but
tonight was a wake-up call.
I think we've got to find that cabin.
Ok. I got an idea.
Wait, we fired Maria. Who's
gonna watch the kids?
I already took care of it.
Naughty nanny's here. Nice
to meet you, naughty.
This is my wife Jody. Threesome?
That costs extra.
Oh, Jesus. Monkey, too?
Oh, you people are freaks,
but for an extra $100.
What agency did you call?
Oh, they have nurses and
cheerleaders and nannies.
Dan, you called an
escort service.
I used the same agency to
book a Santa for Christmas.
Someone called for Santa?
Ho, ho, ho.
Dan, you're watching the kids.
Jody was nervous about what
she might find at the cabin,
but she was comforted
by the fact
that Caesar and the girls
were in good hands.
Who do you work for?
Kendra, this isn't the
cabin I was talking about.
I know, I just thought
you needed to relax.
Take one of these.
Um, I don't know.
Oh, come on, they'll only
last a couple of hours, tops.
Kendra, I don't need
drugs to have fun.
Let me take a picture. Ok.
Oh, that's so hot!
Yeah!
Yeah, ride it, yeah, yeah!
A dollar will make me holler,
honey boo boo child.
Sorry.
I don't always go downtown,
but when I do, I
drink a beer first.
I'm the king of the world!
Woo! Woo!
I'm wicked hard!
Mind if I play through?
Ooh, shit!
Again? You son of a bitch,
I'm gonna kill you!
Oh, my God, rehearsal.
I'm late.
Oh, no, oh, my God, oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Stop, stop! Oh, Jody, thank
God you're here, girl.
I was just dancing
and kissing him
'cause I didn't want him to
think about you being late.
Well, I'm the dancer, so I'll
do the kissing around here.
That was amazing.
I want you to have my children.
But, papa, please, we
want to stay with you.
Back in the car, gaston. Aw...
She can't make you
forget about me.
I overslept because you
just took off this morning.
This morning? Yeah,
you slept over.
What? Wait a minute, did you have
some kind of lezzo dream fantasy
about me? Don't act
like you weren't there.
We had something special. We
made love last night for hours.
What? Oh, and now
you're gonna tell me.
Tiger Woods didn't
come out of my vagina?
Jody.
What?!
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Well, that explains
the poison Ivy.
Jody?
There you are. Kendra?
Oh, the door was open
so I let myself in.
It's ok. Look, I'm so sorry.
I really believed something
happened between us last night.
I must have dreamt the whole thing.
Oh, no, we had sex.
But this morning at
rehearsal, you said...
I can't have the whole
cast knowing my business.
I'm already doing half of 'em,
and besides, me and Pierre...
We have this little thing...
Wait, then, what's this?
Beats me... must have
happened after I left.
Oh, yeah! Girl,
you are freaky.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, get it. Oh, my God.
Oh, shit!
See, I knew she was real.
All right, let's find out
where this cabin is.
Ugh!
What in the hell?
Bad girl.
Oh, what is this?
Oh, my God, it's the same cabin
from the dream. Of course.
So, what are we gonna do
if we find that book?
I don't know, if that's the book
that turned mama into what she is,
maybe it could somehow
reverse the curse.
Ok, we're almost there.
Hey, I'm not going in there.
We have to go inside.
The book is the key to the
nightmare I'm living.
Oh, my gosh, who are you? I'm
Jody and this is kendra.
We're looking for
something very important.
We all are. Come on in.
Go tell it on the Mountain
over the hills and
everywhere go...
Everybody, this is
Jody and kendra.
Hello, Jody and kendra. Hi.
Pardon me for not standing,
but I'm mending the wing of this
bird that we found in the woods.
Ok. Hi, we're in a hurry.
We're actually looking for a
book that could save lives.
Yes, I've got it right here.
Oh, thank God.
Thank him indeed. The Bible.
Here, let me read to you.
Oh, no, no, see, we're
actually looking for...
The book of evil. I
know evil all too well.
You do? This weekend's
devoted to Mia.
It's a detox weekend.
She's hooked on energy shots.
Oh, yeah, that's
a real struggle.
Ok, listen, we're looking
for another book
somewhere in this cabin. Hm.
We haven't seen anything.
We gave it a shot,
let's get out of here.
Ok, wait.
- Is there a cellar?
- Great.
There it is. Oh!
Ok, I don't care what it says.
"The curse begins
with four words.
Gort klaatu barada nikto."
You're all going to die tonight.
"The curse ends with one word.
Adunda."
What the heck?
Why? I don't have an arm.
For some reason I cut
my tongue in half.
Ok, well, let's at least finish the song.
Everyone hold hands.
Except for Eric. Damn.
Go tell it on the Mountain
over the hills and everywhere
well, maybe we
didn't do it right.
"Gort klaatu barada nikto."
"Adunda."
Why does this keep happening?
Where's my arm?
Is this yours? That's a left.
That's mine. Could you
hand it to me, please?
I need a right. Eric
chainsawed it off.
Look, I'm sorry. My... my leg?
No, that's black. It's not mine.
Oh, shit. I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
Oh, cry me a river.
I'm gonna need a little help.
I have to go to the bathroom.
My penis is in the corner.
This is fucked up.
Let me try.
"Gort klaatu barada nikto."
Nothing again.
You know what? Let's go. Wait,
there's a door right here.
Let's go out this way.
Ok, cool, we can avoid
the weirdos upstairs.
We're gonna get you
3 not another peep.
Gort klaatu barada nikto.
Kendra and I recited the
Latin words over and over
at the cabin and
on the way home.
We must have said it a hundred
times, but nothing happened.
What if it isn't the right book?
Maybe the curse has
somehow been lifted.
Luckily for Dan and Jody, there
was someone in the house
who, thanks to the I-13 formula,
had increased intelligence and
superior cognitive ability.
His analytical problem-solving
skills allowed him...
To ascertain crucial
information.
A marvel of modern-day science, his
IQ had surpassed even the most...
Aw, hell.
Why did I think you
could be intelligent?
You're nothing but
a dumb animal.
Ow!
Idiot!
- I can talk.
- Hey, Caesar.
Steve?
Dan's got a mad
demon in his house.
Matt Damon's in his house?
No, a mad demon.
I love Matt Damon. Jason bourne.
Oy.
I should have known not to bring
a wild animal into the house.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
But I believed in Caesar. I
thought he was different.
There's something more to this.
I can feel it. No, he just...
Went crazy.
Forget it. But I still think
mama could be in this house.
But don't you... we just
had a whole night go on
without a single sign of anything.
I guess.
I was just so scared
last night for the kids.
You're coming around.
Am I getting attached to them?
It's the cliff from the dream.
Get in the car now.
Don't make me yell!
Unto thee, Satan, I
sacrifice these children.
Return home to the cliff of...
Holy shit!
Home is at the cliff.
Oh, my God. Girls!
Kathy. It's ok. I saw the cliff.
I know what "home" means.
Whoa!
Come on, girls.
Let's go get Aidan.
That's cool.
Lily! Come on.
Aidan! Are you ok?
Uncle Dan! Uncle Dan!
Mama! Mama! Mama!
She's here!
Whoa. Girls, girls, girls. One at a time.
Lily, you first.
Got it. Now Kathy.
Mama! Mama! She's here!
She's gonna kill us!
How many times do I have to tell
everyone there's no such thing as...
Ow!
Maria? What are you doing here?
I was angry you fire me,
so I bake you this.
A shit pie?
Uh, thanks, but... hot dog?
No, that's still
shit with mustard.
Maybe just a banana, then?
Very much potassium.
So bueno, Mr. Dan.
No, I... I'm sorry. I should
have listened to you...
Mr. Dan, we have our problems,
but I always love you.
So much.
When I see you, I see my father.
Dan. Dan, we have to...
Wait. What's going on here?
I can explain.
There's no time. Mama has the girls.
I know where she took them.
Got to go.
You remind me of my father.
Dan!
Knowing the girls
were in danger,
Dan and Jody sped off, racing
to get to the cliff they...
Oh, my God. What
happened to the car?
Where...? Oh, there it is.
They were no longer able to sit idly
by and let a ghost jump off a cliff,
- sacrificing their children with her.
- Kathy! Lily!
Oh, my God. There they are.
Kathy, lily, stop!
What do we do now?
Um, I'll just...
Read from this and change
her back to human.
Girls, run! Run! No.
No, not that way.
Away from the cliff!
I'm not going to let mama
take you away again.
Hm?
Lily, stop! Come on. Come on.
Here, girl. Come on, lily.
Come on. Look. Oh, look. Yeah.
Come on. Look. Oh, yeah. Lily.
Oh, wow. Yeah.
Oh, come on.
Enough! This is crazy.
Lily's not a dog.
She's a beautiful little
girl who I've grown to love.
I love all these children, mama,
even if they don't all love me.
Lily loves you, too, Jody.
And they belong in this
world with me and Dan.
Because they deserve parents
who aren't decomposing.
Good girl.
All right, enough.
Where's the page? Damn
it, I can't find it.
Forget it.
There, that worked. Maybe not.
Man, we need to stop
smoking this shit.
Told you that shark was
going to come in handy.
Thank you. Lily.
Honey, thank God
you're all right.
Your cue is coming up.
Oh, kendra.
Look, it's ok, girl. Let's
forget about what happened.
You are the black swan.
No. It's you.
Throwing mama off the cliff has really
made me reevaluate my priorities.
My family comes first. You
dance the black swan.
Because sometimes in life...
Ok.
Introducing our new swan
queen, miss kendra Brooks.
This is not ballet. No,
it the hell ain't.
This some bullshit.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
That's what I'm talking about!
Right? Right?
You know that shit, right?
And so our story ends.
If anything is to be
learned from this,
it's that mankind
is a pathetic race
and apes need to take
over this planet.
Enjoy earth while
you still got it.
Well, we'll see how you like
it once the swan consumes you!
I cannot hold it that long. It's, like...
It's so long.
We're kissing.
' Cut! Cut!
Cut!
We're kissing.
- What happened?
- Guy was in the shot.
- Ah.
- Cut!
But was he dressed like a demon?
Do the second "my
penis" as a question.
Ok. And then "my other
penis" is a question also?
Yeah. Ok.
But remember, you're jumping
to "what the hell is that?"
I know. I don't know why.
You're jumping... yeah.
There's just so many penises.
Welcome to Hollywood.
I'm ready for it. Hey.
I'm ok with this.
That's the temporary
nurses' shower.
And we're painting it. Cut.
That's the... temporary
nurses' shower.
I'm ok with this.
Sorry, you guys. I...
That's the nurses'
temporary locker room,
and we're repainting it.
' Cut.
Ouch. Hello here!
B mark!
- And background.
- Action!
Oh!
Jody! Thank God I caught you.
I forgot to tell you, now that
you are the swan queen...
Suck my...
I'll save you, snoop dogg.
My name ain't snoop dogg in this...
Movie, man!
Well, I mean, I... sh...
Stop it!
We're good. We're good.
Now prepare for a night
of unparalleled passion.
Oh, wait, wait, Mr. grey...
The safe word is "deeper."
What?
Damn! Ow!
Whoa!
What does all this have
to do with the ballet?
Ballet? Yes. Aren't you
donating millions?
Millions? What...? I'm broke.
Every cent I have has
been put into this room.
I don't know what
I'm going to do.
Oh, cry me a river.
I'm going to need a little help.
I don't have a penis.
It does not come off.
It does not come off. I'm sorry.
I'm getting tired of
talking about this...
In the woods with this man.
Man, we keep going in circles,
talking about a... man.
Let's talk about a... man,
- or getting some...
- Getting some...
Talking about... these
two dudes in the woods.
If we had a... here, she could wash our...
Off right now.
You understand me? That's
the way I would say it.
Hey, babe, check out this
psychic's book for a clue.
It really freaks me out. Come
on, there's nothing to be...
Nuh!
These books are all...
There's nothing to be scared...
To be scared...
Oh, there's nothing
to be scared...
Oh, wrong animal.
Be scared... a dinosaur?
What does this have
to do with...?
I know. Sorry.
And... action!
- What does this have to do with...?
- Sorry.
You just keep cupping your boobs.
Ok, sorry.
Ok, how do we know
who's a witch?
Do they have a broom?
Do they have a pointy nose?
I'm... I'm going
to pee my pants!
So, what, I didn't get the part?
Where's everybody going?
I just had the most
bizarre dream.
Demons, apes, a ballet.
You have a very
active subconscious.
Anyway, the idea took hold.
Lindsay Lohan's coming over
to spend the night with you.
Awesome!
You were driving.
Subtitles from:
Bibzhd @ subscene. Com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player