[ Rabbi ]
Savree maranun
verabonun verobotay.
Barooch ata adony
elohaynou melech aholam.
Borah pree hagafan.
Barooch ata adony
elohaynou melech aholam.
Asher kideshano bemitzvotaiv...
verazha banou veshabat kodsho...
behava hencheel lanoe.
Zecaron lemase berashit
ke hoe yome...
techelah lemekray kodesh...
zecher letziat mizraim.
Kee banoe bacharta
veotano kedashta mekol hameem.
Veshabat kodsho
behavat razone.
Henchaltanoe.
Barooch ata adony mekadesh
hasabat.
[ Train Whistle Blowing ]
- Name ?
- Horowitz, Salomon.
[ Indistinct Talking,
Various Languages ]
Schneider, Sarah.
Birnbaum, Olga ?
[ Children Crying,
Indistinct Talking ]
Over there.
Over there !
Kommen Sie Doch.
- Isak Hudes.
- Hudes, Isak.
Zucker, Helena.
Hirsch, Salomon ?
Mandel, Maria. Hirsch,
Salomon.
- Hauptman, Chaim !
- Weisman ! Weisman, Marcus !
- Feber, Ludwig !
- Feber, Ludwig.
Elsa Bauman.
-Josef Klein.
- Klein.
- Davidowich, Ignacy.
- Paula Biffer.
- Nadel, Rachela.
Steiner, Gertruda.
Steiner, Hilda.
## [ ''Gloomy Sunday'' ]
[ Indistinct Chatter]
[ Whispering ]
####[ Orchestra Playing ]
[ Maitre D'] Jerzy,
you know who that man is ?
I don't know.
[ Woman Laughing ]
####[ Orchestra Continues ]
Let's get together,
please.
Smile. Good.
Yes, sir.
Bring them over
a round of drinks.
Very good, sir.
And who shall I say
th-they are from ?
You can say
they are from me.
From the gentleman.
Where ?
Do you know him ?
Find out who he is.
Yes, sir.
Agnieszka, I would
give anything...
to hear you
sing tonight.
[ Sighs ]
But I know you won't.
[ Laughs ]
You embarrass me.
What's he doing ?
Stay here.
How are you doing ?
You'd leave a woman
alone at the table
in a place like this ?
Sweetheart,
you're the picture
of loneliness.
Oh.
Mmm, what a lovely
fragrance. You are
breaking my heart.
An extra chair, please.
Vodka for my friend.
And for the lady ?
Pernod.
# Im Grunewald, im Grunewald
ist Holzauktion #
[ Men Laughing,
Whistling ]
# Ist Holzauktion #
# Im Grunewald, im Grunewald
ist Holzauktion #
Come to the table, girls.!
Drink with us.!
# Ist Holzauktion #
# Links um die Ecke 'rum,
rechts um die Ecke 'rum #
# Ueberall ist heute
Holzauktion #
Come to us.!
Marry us.!
[ Whispering ]
# Der ganze Klafter
Suessholz kostet 'nen Taler #
# 'Nen Taler, 'nen Taler #
# Der ganze Klafter Suessholz
kostet 'nen Taler #
# 'Nen Taler-- ##
Thank you.
I'll tell you what
I mean by cooperative.
Two days after the law
is passed that allJews
have to wear the star,
theJewish tailors
are turning them out
by the gross...
in a variety of fabrics
at three zloty each.
Tell me about
your cellar wines.
I have an excellent
German Riesling. 1 937.
Mmm, French.
A Bordeaux.
Chateau Latour, '28, '29 ?
No, I'm sorry.
It's as if they have no idea
what kind of law it is.
As if it's the emblem
of a riding club.
A Margaux, '29 ?
No, no,
we don't have that.
Burgundy then ?
A Romanee-Conti, '37 ?
Yes.
It's human nature.
''We'll do this to avoid that.''
That's what they have done
since thousands of years.
It's what they do.
They weather the storm.
But this storm is different.
This is not the Romans.
This storm is the SS.
## Wem Gott will
rechte Gunst erweisen ##
##Den schickt er
in die weite Welt ##
## Wem Gott will rechte
Gunst erweisen ##
##Den schickt er in die
weite Welt ##
##Faleri, Falera ##
##Faleri
Falera-ha ha ha ##
##Faleri, Falera ##
##Den schickt er
in die weite Welt ##
Martin ?
Yes, sir.
Who is that man ?
That--
That's Oskar Schindler !
##Faleri
Falera-ha ha ha ##
##Den schickt er
in die weite Welt ##
##Faleri, Falera ##
##Den schickt er
in die weite Welt ####
[ All ]
To Krakow !
## [ Singing In German ]
[ Soldiers Laughing ]
####[ Singing Continues ]
[ Loudspeaker ]
An alleJuden !
Ab sofort ist es allen Juden
untersagt...
Fleisch aufkoscher Art
zuzubereiten.
Meldung an alleJuden.
Ab sofort--
Rabbi--
Private property
cannot be confiscated.
How long are the schools
going to be closed ?
I do not know.
Article 47: Pillage
is formally prohibited.
You don't know anything !
I am familiar with
the Hague Convention.
Religious--
They come into our house
and tell us we don't
live there anymore.
It now belongs
to a certain SS officer.
Please. I only know
what they tell me.
And what they tell me
changes from day to day.
Aren't you supposed
to be able to help ?
I mean, what if I just
took this thing off?
What are they going
to do about it ?
They will shoot you.
Why don't you stop
this silly talk ?
Itzhak Stern !
I'm looking
for Itzhak Stern.
[ Schindler ]
Are you Itzhak Stern
or not ?
I am.
Where can we talk ?
There's a company
you did the books for
on Lipowa Street.
Made what ?
Pots and pans ?
By law, I have to tell you,
sir, I'm a Jew.
Well, I'm a German.
So there we are.
A good company,
you think ?
Modestly successful.
I know nothing
about enamelware.
Do you ?
I was just
the accountant.
Simple engineering though,
wouldn't you think ?
Change the machines around,
whatever you do,
you could make other
things, couldn't you ?
Field kits, mess kits.
Army contracts.
Once the war ends,
forget it, but for now
it's great.
You can make a fortune,
don't you think ?
I think most people right now
have other priorities.
Like what ?
[ Sighs ]
I'm sure you'll do just fine
once you get the contracts.
In fact, the worse things get,
the better you'll do.
Oh, well, I can get
the signatures I need.
That's the easy part.
Finding the money
to buy the company,
that's hard.
You don't have
any money ?
Not that kind of money.
You know anybody ?
[ Closes Case ]
Jews, yeah.
Investors. You must
have contacts...
in theJewish
business community
working here.
What community ?
Jews can no longer
own businesses.
That's why this one's
in receivership.
But they
I'd own it.
I'd pay them back in
product-- pots and pans.
Pots and pans.
Something
they can use.
Something they can
feel in their hands.
They can trade it
on the black market,
do whatever they want.
Everybody's happy.
If you want, you could
run the company for me.
Let me understand.
They'd put up all the money,
I'd do all the work.
What, if you don't mind
my asking, would you do ?
I'd make sure it's known
the company's in business.
I'd see that it had
a certain panache.
That's what I'm good at,
not the work. Not the work.
The presentation.
I'm sure I don't know anybody
who'll be interested in this.
[ Exhales ]
Well, they should be,
Itzhak Stern.
Tell them they should be.
[ Loudspeaker ]
Achtung ! Achtung !
An alleJuden...
Ab sofort ist es verboten--
[ Priest ]
Vere dignum et justum est,
aequum et salutare,
nos tibi semper et
ubique gratias agere,
Domine Sancte, Pater Omnipotens,
Aeterne Deus.
I've got a client
who'll sell marks
for zloty at 2.45 to 1 .
Wool, mink collar.
It's a nice coat.
She'll trade it
for ration coupons.
Wicks, for lamps.
You have a truckload
of wicks ?
What am I going to do
with a truckload of wicks ?
Nine by 1 2, nine by 1 4.
I don't know.
Big, beautiful, Persian.
[ Priest Continues ]
Lumen aeternum mundo effudit--
Psst.
What ?
You don't recognize this ?
It's shoe polish.
In metal containers ?
You asked
for shoe polish.
In metal containers.
This is glass.
It's not what I asked for.
What's
the difference ?
What's the difference ?
[ Others ]
Shh.!
My client sold it
who sold it
to the German Army.
Only by the time it got there,
because of the freezing cold,
it broke. All 1 0,000 units.
Mmm,
ooh, ooh, ooh.
This is not my problem.
This is not
his problem.
This is not your problem ?
This is not
my problem.
All right.
The German Army
wants to find out
where it came from.
I am going to make sure
they find out.
Now it's your problem.
You be quiet !
[ Chuckles ]
Metal
containers.
Hello.
Pardon me for interfering,
but that's a nice shirt.
Nice shirt.
Do you know where
I can find a nice
shirt like that ?
[ Priest Continues ]
...laudare, benedicere
et predicare.
Like this ?
It's illegal to buy or sell
anything on the street.
We don't do that.
We're here to pray.
[ Priest Continues ]
Jesum Christum Dominum Nostrum--
Do you have any idea how much
a shirt like this costs ?
Nice things cost money.
[ Priest Continues ]
...adorant Dominationes,
tremunt Potestates.
Coeli coelorumque
virtutes ac Beata Seraphim...
socia exultatione
concelebrant--
How many ?
I'm going to need
some other things, too,
as things come up.
This won't be
a problem.
From time to time.
[ Loudspeaker ]
Achtung ! Achtung !
[ Children Crying ]
[ Officers ]
- Name ? Adresse ?
- Formular ausfuellen !
Weiter, weiter.!
Nicht draengeln.!
Kommen Sie hierher.!
Stellen Sie sich doch an.!
[ Silverware Clattering ]
[ Loudspeaker ]
Achtung, achtung !
AlleJuden sind verpflichtet...
im abgesonderten
juedischen Bezirk zu wohnen.
Nichteinhaltung der Meldepflicht
bei der Einwohnerbehoerde...
verstoesst gegen das Edikt 44l91
und fuehrt zur Anzeige...
beim Militaergericht.
This is obviously the right
place. How are you doing ?
Herr Schindler.
[ Indistinct Shouting ]
Good-bye,Jews.!
Good-bye,Jews !
[ Girl Continues Yelling ]
Good-bye,Jews.!
This iz the vechteka,
Moyshe.
Ojciec.
Nyne, this kan
neash zyane.
[ Sighs ]
[ Baby Crying, Woman Singing
Polish Lullaby ]
Oh, my God.
Oy, God.
[ Crying Continues ]
Oh, my God.
It could not be better.
It could be worse.
How ? Tell me.
[ Shouting ]
How on earth could it
possibly be worse ?
[ Slams Down Suitcase ]
[ Man ]
Dzien dobry.
[ Indistinct German ]
Hey, Goldberg.
Poldek.
What's this ?
Uh, the Judenrat has
its own police now.
You don't say.
Ordnungsdienst.
I'm a policeman now,
could you believe it ?
It's hard to believe.
Oh, no,
it's not hard
to believe.
It's a good racket, Poldek.
The only racket here.
Look, maybe I could
put in a good word for you
with my superiors.
Your superiors ?
Come on, they are not
as bad as everyone says.
Well, they're worse
than everyone says,
but it's a lot of money.
A lot of money.
Give me my
housing assignment.
Come on.
You look funny
in that hat, Goldberg.
[ Laughs ]
You look like a clown,
you know ?
[ Stern ]
He's a very important man.
Just give him
two minutes of your time.
Since when did time cost money ?
Just sit down and listen.
Please.
Sir ?
[ Schindler ]
For each thousand you invest,
I will repay you with...
Two hundred.
200 kilos
of enamelware a month,
to begin in July
and to continue
for one year.
After which time, we're even.
That's it. It's very simple.
Not good enough.
It's not
good enough.
Not good enough ?
Look where you're living.
Look where you've been put.
''Not good enough.''
A couple of months ago you'd
be right, not anymore.
Money's still money.
No, it is not.
That's why we're here.
Trade goods--
that's the only currency...
that'll be worth
anything in the ghetto.
Things have changed,
my friend.
Did I call
this meeting ?
You told Mr. Stern
you wanted to speak to me.
I'm here.
I've made you a fair offer.
Fair would be
a percentage in the company.
[ Laughing ]
Forget the whole thing.
Get out.
How do we know that you
will do what you say ?
Because I said I would.
You want a contract ?
To be upheld by what court ?
I said what I'll do.
That's our contract.
[ Indistinct Polish ]
...mielismy racje.
[ Man ]
Piec, szesc, siedem...
osiem, dziewiec.
[ Machinery Buzzes ]
[ Schindler Clapping ]
The standard SS rate for
Jewish skilled labor
is seven marks a day,
five for unskilled
and women.
This is what you pay
the Reich Economic Office.
TheJews themselves
receive nothing.
Poles you pay wages.
Generally, they get
a little more.
Are you
listening ?
What was that about the SS ?
The rate ? The what ?
TheJewish worker's salary--
you pay it directly to
the SS, not to the worker.
He gets nothing.
But it's less.
It's less than what
I would pay a Pole.
It's less.
That's the point
I'm trying to make.
Poles cost more.
[ Sniffs ]
Why should I hire Poles ?
An enamelware factory
over at, uh, Lipowa Street.
It, uh, it, um--
It's owned by a German.
But it's outside
the ghetto, so you can
barter for extra goods--
for eggs, I don't know
what you need--
with the Polish workers.
You can't get it here.
Also, he's asking for ten
healthy women for the--
I am healthy.
[ Crowd Laughing ]
Bring your sister, okay ?
[ Shouting Orders
In German And Polish ]
Chodz.
You need to convince them
you have a trade, something
valuable to the war effort.
Like what ?
What if you don't ?
I'm a musician.
Your name goes
on a list.
And they put you on trucks--
No, no, no,
that's not true.
You're a musician ?
Yeah.
I'd fid a good
hiding place if I were you.
I'm not going to hide
like some animal.
There are places to hide.
[ Whistle Blowing ]
Der Naechste.!
I'm a graduate
of the University of Lwow.
I used to work at the
hydroelectric station
in Roznow--
Blauschein.
I'm gonna get the necessary
papers because this card
is no good anymore.
You can stay in this line
all day, you'll still get
one of these.
They are no good.
You'll have to leave
the line now,
then you'll get a blue card,
a Blauschein, to say that
you are an essential worker.
I'll get these papers
for you at Pankiewicz.
Pharmacist.
Just there, look.
Guess who is here ?
[ Goldberg ]
Poldek ! Enjoying
the weather, Poldek ?
Enjoying the lines ?
Need some shoe polish ?
In a metal container
maybe ?
[ Goldberg Laughs ]
Not essential ?
I think you misunderstand
the meaning of the word.
No Blauschein, sir.
Stand over there.
Move. Next !
What do you mean,
''Not essential'' ?
I teach history and literature.
Since when is not essential ?
He's a metal polisher.
It was not right ?
It's very good.
He's 53 years old.
It's too new.
Mmm.
Thank you.
You're crazy.
You left it
in your drawer.
How many times
have I told you ?
Your work certificate
you keep in your pocket
at all times.
And you leave everything
in your drawer.
[ Stern ]
How many times I've told you ?
I'm a metal polisher.
[ Man ]
Take the round sheet of tin,
dip it in soap emulsion.
[ Liquid Splashing ]
Then place it centrally
in the press.
We obtain the soup pot.
The soup pot.
Soup pot.
Grosz, Mrs. Grosz,
stay together.
Sir, I have ten work permits
here for the Deutsche
Emailwarenfabrik,
cosigned by Mr. Bankier
and myself.
[ Foreman ]
If it's carbonized,
clean it with a file.
But don't touch
both the electrodes
at the same time.
You'll get electrocuted.
Here, have a try.
[ Foreman ]
Roll the metal
under the press,
but be very careful
unless you want your fingers...
to become part
of the teapot.
Occupation ?
I'm a writer.
I play the flute.
But Moses is
a skilled metalworker.
He can make tin pots.
He can make tanks.
He can make whatever
Mr. Schindler asks.
He's highly skilled.
Give him your card.
Moses, give him your card.
[ Foreman ]
Now, dip the basin
with the tongs...
into the enamel solution.
And after swiveling it around,
carefully place it aside
to drip dry.
And whatever he asks you,
allow me just to represent
you and speak for you.
Don't say a word.
[ Schindler ]
Filing, billing, keeping track
of my appointments, shorthand.
Typing, obviously.
How is your typing ?
Uh, all right.
Please.
[ Typing Slowly ]
[ Typing Slowly,
Bell Rings ]
[ Typing
Extremely Slow ]
[ Barely Typing ]
[ Typing Quickly ]
You need a secretary.
Pick one.
I don't know how.
They're all so...
qualified.
You have to choose.
[ Sighs ]
Prosze sie ladnie usmiechac.
Big smile.
Uwaga.
[ Camera Shutter Clicks ]
####[ Piano ]
If you would,
look after my guest.
[ Schindler ]
Um, boxed teas are good.
Coffiee, pate, um...
kielbasa sausage,
cheeses, Beluga caviar.
Yes.
And, of course, who could live
without German cigarettes ?
Get me as many
as you can fid.
And some more fresh fruit.
The real rarities--
oranges, lemons, pineapples.
I need several boxes
of Cuban cigars. The best.
Yes.
And dark, unsweetened chocolate.
Not in the shape ofladyfigers,
the chunk chocolate.
Yes.
Big as my hand,
you sample at wine tastings.
We're going to need lots
of cognac. The best, Hennessy.
Dom Perignon champagne.
Um, get L 'espadon sardines...
and, oh,
try to fid nylon stockings.
[ Schindler ]
It is my distinct pleasure
to announce...
the fully operational status
of Deutsche Email Fabrik...
[ Foreman ]
Patrzjakies szmaty.!
manufacturers of superior
enamelware crockery...
expressly designed
and crafted for military use.
Utilizing only
the most modern equipment,
D.E.F. 's staffi of
highly-skilled and experienced
artisans andjourneymen...
deliver a product
of unparalleled quality,
enabling me to proffier,
with absolute confidence
and pride,
a full line
of field and kitchenware...
unsurpassable in all respects
by my competitors.
See attached list
and available colors.
Anticipating the enclosed bids
will meet with your approval.
Made in Havana, Cuba.
Looking forward to a long and
mutually prosperous association.
Look at this.
I extend to you in advance
my sincerest gratitude...
and very best regards.
Oskar Schindler.
Yeah, I need 700 gross
from here for next Thursday.
Nine hundred--
No, make it ten
for Wednesday.
All this stuff here goes
to Madritsch's factory
on Tuesday of next week.
[ Horn Honking ]
[ Schindler ]
My father was fond of saying,
''You need three things in life
''a good doctor,
a forgiving priest...
and a clever accountant. ''
The first two... [ Chuckles ]
I've never had much use for.
But the third--
Just pretend,
for Christ's sake.
Is that all ?
I'm trying to thank you.
I'm saying I couldn't
have done this without you.
The usual thing would be
to acknowledge my gratitude.
It would also, by the way,
be the courteous thing.
You're welcome.
[ Sighs ]
Get out of here.
[ Door Buzzer ]
[ Schindler ]
Klonowska, who is it ?
She's so embarrassed.
Look at her.
You know something ?
You would like her.
Oskar, please.
What ?
I don't have to like her...
just because you do.
You would, though.
It doesn't
work that way.
[ Door Closing ]
You've done well here.
You look wonderful.
Be careful
of the step, miss.
Mrs. Schindler, Marek.
## [ ''Gloomy Sunday'' ]
It's not a charade,
all this ?
How could it
The clothes, the car,
the apartment.
Wait a minute.
Take a guess how many
people are on my payroll.
Oskar.
My father, at the height
of his success, had 50.
I've got 3 50.
3 50 workers
on the factory floor,
with one purpose.
To make pots and pans ?
To make money.
For me.
[ Sighs ]
Does anyone
ask about me ?
Back home ?
Everybody.
All the time.
Hmm.
They won't soon forget
the name Schindler here,
I can tell you that.
''Oskar Schindler,''
they'll say.
''Everybody
remembers him.
''He did something
extraordinary.
no one else did.
''He came here
with nothing--
''a suitcase--
''and built a bankrupt
company into a major
manufactory.
''And left with
a steamer trunk--
''Two steamer trunks
full of money,
all the riches
of the world.''
Hmm.
It's comforting to see
that nothing's changed.
You're wrong, Emilie.
[ Kissing Sound ]
There's no way I could have
known this before,
but there was always
something missing.
In every business I tried,
I can see now, it wasn't me
that failed.
Something was missing.
Even if I'd known what it
was, there's nothing I could
have done about it...
because you can't
create this thing.
And it makes all
the difference in the world
between success and failure.
Luck ?
War.
Should I stay ?
It's a beautiful city.
I asked you
if I should stay.
It's up to you.
Promise me, Oskar,
no doorman or maitre d'
will ever presume...
I'm anyone other
than Mrs. Schindler,
and I'll stay.
Good-bye, darling.
[ Indistinct German ]
I could try to read this
or I could eat my lunch
while it's still hot.
We're doing well ?
Yes.
Better this month
than last ?
Yes.
Any reason
to think next month
The war could end.
What ?
There is a machinist
outside...
who'd like to thank you
personally for giving him a job.
Every day he comes.
He's very grateful.
It'll just take a minute.
Mr. Lowenstein ?
I want to thank you, sir,
for giving me
the opportunity to work.
You're welcome.
I'm sure you're doing
a great job.
The SS beat me up.
They would have killed me,
but I am essential
to the war effort,
thanks to you.
That's great.
I work hard for you.
I'm sure you do.
I'll continue
to work hard for you.
That's great.
Thanks.
God bless you, sir.
All right.
You are a good man.
He saved my life.
Yes, he did.
God bless him.
Yeah.
Come on.
God bless you.
[ Stern ]
I'm sorry, Herr Direktor,
but you're running very late.
This is for the
Obersturmbannfuehrer, sir.
And this is for his niece,
Greta. It's her birthday.
Greta as in Garbo.
By the way, don't ever
do that to me again.
Go. Go, go, drive !
Don't bow.
Did you happen to notice that
that man had one arm ?
What ? Did he ?
What's his use ?
Very useful.
[ Shouts ]
How ?
Very useful ! Success !
##Achrar kach loe nedah ##
[ Officer ]
Besen und Schaufeln
werden ausgeladen...
jeder nimmt sich eine und dann
wird die Strasse gereinigt.
We'll be late for work.
[ Horn Honking ]
[ Rolf Czurda ]
You shouldn't think of them
as yours, Oskar.
You need to understand that
some of the officers here...
don't give a damn
about production.
To them, it's a matter of,
um, national priority...
thatJews
be made to shovel snow.
It's got nothing to do
with reality, Oskar.
You know it and I know it.
Jews shoveling snow--
It's got a, um,
ritual significance.
Come with me.
I am an essential worker.
Essential worker ?
[ Laughing ]
Yes.
[ Officer Laughing ]
I work for Oskar Schindler.
Essential worker
for Oskar Schindler.
A one-armed Jew ?
Twice as useless !
Yes, yes.
I lost a day
of production, Rolf.
[ Lowenstein ]
I work for Oskar Schindler.
Danka, look at the snow.
Look at the snow.
Look at the snow !
[ Gunshot ]
I lost a worker.
I expect to be compensated.
File a grievance
with the Economic Office.
It's your right.
Would it do
any good ?
Of course not.
[ Chuckles ]
A big shot from the SS Budget
and Construction Office
came to lunch...
and he told us that to believe
theJewish skilled worker
had a place...
in Reich economics
was a treasonable idea.
A one-armed machinist, Oskar ?
He was
a metal press operator.
Quite skilled.
[ Moaning ]
[ Panting, Moaning ]
Herr Direktor?
Shit.
I don't believe it.
Stern, is that you ?
No, it's Poldek.
It's about Stern.
[ Soldier ]
Leave your luggage
on the platform.
Clearly label it.
Given name first,
then your surname.
Do not bring
your baggage with you.
It will follow you later.
Leave your luggage
on the platform.
Clearly label it.
[ Loudspeaker ]
Lassen Sie Ihr Gepaeck
am Bahnsteig.
Stern ?
He's on the list.
He is ?
Well, let's find him.
I'm sorry.
You can't have him.
He's on the list.
If he were an essential worker,
he would not be on the list.
I'm talking to a clerk.
What is your name ?
Sir, the list
is correct.
I didn't ask you about the list.
I asked you your name.
Klaus Tauber.
Tauber.
Hauptscharfuehrer,
this gentleman thinks
a mistake's been made.
My plant manager is
somewhere on this train.
If it leaves with him on it,
it'll disrupt production...
and the Armaments Board
will want to know why.
[ Loudspeaker ]
Achtung, dieser Zug
faehrt jetzt ab.
Is he on the list ?
Yes, sir.
Itzhak Stern.
Well, the list
is correct, sir.
There is nothing I can do.
What is your name ?
[ Loudspeaker ]
Close and secure all doors.
My name ?
My name is Kunder.
This train is now leaving.
Kunder.
Hauptscharfuehrer Kunder.
K-U-N-D-E-R.
And what's yours ?
Schindler.
S-C-H-I-N-D-L-E-R.
Gentlemen,
thank you very much.
I think I can guarantee you
you'll both be in...
Southern Russia before the
end of the month. Good day.
[ Conductor ]
Zamykac dokladnie drzwi.
Dokladnie zamykac drzwi.
Stern !
Itzhak Stern !
[ Train Whistle Blowing ]
Stern !
Itzhak Stern !
[ Kunder, Tauber ]
Stern.! Stern.!
Itzhak Stern.!
Stern !
Sir ?
Herr Direktor.
[ Coughing ]
My apologies.
Stop the train !
He's here !
I apologize.
- Stop the train !
- Stop the train ! Stop it !
Sign here.
Initial there.
[ Whistle Blowing ]
Makes no difference
to us, you understand.
This one, that one.
[ Train Whistle Blowing ]
It's the inconvenience
to the list.
It's the paperwork.
I somehow left
my work card at home.
I tried to explain them
it was a mistake, but--
I'm sorry, it was stupid !
What if I got here
five minutes later ?
Then where would I be ?
Shechel.
Sacrean,
sacrean end tzukeer.
Tzukeer end sacrean.
I woke up from a dream
this morning.
I was broke and sharing a room
with 1 2 people I didn't know,
only to discover
I was broke and sharing a room
with 1 2 people I didn't know.
[ Chuckling ]
You laugh about it ?
I have to laugh.
You are living
behind walls.
The walls I can deal with.
It's the restrictions
to my life I'm tired of.
Those walls keep them out.
That's all I care about.
I like it here.
There's a kind of,
I don't know,
ancestral squalor
to it all.
You are a slave
to these people.
No one envies us anymore.
I'm smart.
Oh, yes,
you're smart.
You're
a real genius.
You had your chance.
Today,
today I actually found time
to organize a thought.
I can't remember
the last time I did that.
When's the last time
we did this ?
we stood around and talked ?
No one ordered me
onto a truck today.
No one took my business
away from me.
You don't really have
a business to take.
There's nowhere
down from here.
This is it.
This is the bottom.
The ghetto is... liberty.
This street
divides the ghetto
just about in half.
Right side, Ghetto A:
civil employees,
industrial workers
and so on.
Left side, Ghetto B:
surplus labor,
the elderly
and infirm mostly.
Which is where you'll
want to start, huh ?
Do you have any
questions, sir?
Ja, why is the top down ?
I'm fucking freezing.
[ Wilhelm Kunde ]
We expect a labor force
of 25,000 to 30,000.
Segregated, of course.
The men in the barracks
near the quarry.
The women on the other
side of the wire.
[ Goeth ]
My place is where ?
There, sir.
There ?
You call that a villa ?
Yes, the villa.
Their synagogue,
can you see it ?
That's not a villa.
We're planning to turn it
into the camp stables.
It's a house.
[ Goeth ]
What's that over there ?
[ Kunde ]
Kindergarten.
Fifty-one.
And we have
a dentist, shoemaker,
practical physicians.
[ Guard ]
There they are, sir.
[ Goeth Sniffs ]
Hmm.
One of you is, uh,
a very lucky girl.
There is an opening
for a job,
away from all this...
backbreaking work,
at my new villa.
[ Sniffs ]
Uh, which of you has...
domestic experience ?
Ja, on second thought,
I don't really want
someone else's maid.
All those annoying habits
I have to undo.
[ Chuckles ]
I don't want
to give you my cold.
Uh, what's your name ?
Helen Hirsch.
What ?
[ Coughing ]
Helen Hirsch.
What ?
I can't hear.
Helen Hirsch.
Ja.
[ Woman ]
Take it all down.!
[ Officer Blows Whistle ]
To work.!
[ Woman Arguing ]
Take it down.!
It is not safe.!
She says
the foundation was poured wrong.
She's got to take it down.
I told her it's the barracks,
not the fucking Hotel Europa.
Fucking Jew bitch engineer.
You fucking bitch !
Herr Kommandant.
The entire foundation...
has to be torn down
and repoured.
If not, there will be
at least a subsidence...
at the southern end
of the barracks.
Subsidence,
and then collapse.
And you are
an engineer ?
Yes.
My name is Diana Reiter.
I'm a graduate...
of Civil Engineering
from the University of Milan.
Ah, an educated Jew,
like Karl Marx himself.
Unterscharfuehrer.!
Jawohl?
Shoot her.
What ?
[ Gasps ]
Herr Kommandant,
I'm only trying to do my job.
Ja, I'm doing mine.
But, sir,
she's foreman
of construction.
We are not going
to have arguments
with these people.
Okay.
No. Shoot her here,
on my authority.
It will take
more than that.
[ Goeth ]
I'm sure you're right.
Take it down, repour it,
rebuild it. Like she said.
We have more to see,
but we have only one more
hour of light.
## [ Humming ]
[ Goeth ]
Today is history.
Today will be remembered.
Years from now, the young
will ask with wonder...
about this day.
Today is history,
and you are part of it.
Six hundred years ago...
## [ Singing
Morning Prayer]
when elsewhere they were footing
the blame for the Black Death,
Kazimierz the Great, so-called,
##Ke laolam chasedo ##
told theJews
they could come to Krakow.
Chaja, bread.
[ Goeth Continues ]
They came.
Not that fat. No, less.
They trundled their belongings
into the city.
Yes, a bit less.
They settled.
They took hold.
They prospered...
in business, science,
education, the arts.
They came here with nothing.
####[ Praying Continues ]
Nothing.
And they flourished.
For six centuries
there has been a Jewish Krakow.
Think about that.
By this evening,
those six centuries
are a rumor.
They never happened.
Today is history.
Absitzen und in Zweierreihen
antreten.!
Kameraden.!
Schneller.!
[ Whistle Blowing,
Indistinct Shouting ]
I think we will start...
with Ghetto B.
Hopp, hopp, hopp, hopp.!
[ Dogs Barking ]
All right ?
Start from
both sides ?
I would like you
to start there.
The right side ?
The right side, yeah.
And then move around.
Okay.
[ Loudspeaker ]
Beschriften Sie es deutlich.
Es wird Ihnen nachgeschickt.
Lassen Sie
Ihr Gepaeck stehen.
Beschriften Sie es deutlich.
Es wird Ihnen nachgeschickt.
[ Soldier ]
Aufmachen !
Lakoom.
Loe ani loe yodahat olay
kaday lehachnese at hayladeem
mitachat la shoolchan.
Mitacht la meeta.
Bohow.
[ Soldiers ]
Hopp, hopp, hopp, hopp !
[ Soldiers Shouting
In German ]
[ Soldier ]
'Runterkommen !
[ Soldiers Shouting,
Banging On Doors ]
[ Soldier ]
'Rauskommen,Juden !
[ Soldiers Shouting ]
[ Soldier ]
Ziehen Sie sich warm an !
Kommen Sie 'raus !
[ Soldier ]
Na Platz !
[ Whistle Blowing ]
Gold, Chaim !
Platz Chodi.
Yes, Chaim Gold.
Shoot him.
[ Speaking Polish ]
Nie zabijaj.!
[ Woman Screams ]
[ Soldier ]
Ziehen Sie warme Kleidung an
und begeben Sie sich zum Platz--
[ Whistle Blows ]
Keine Koffier.!
Gehen Sie durch.!
Keine Koffier.! Keine Koffier.!
Hey, little boy.
Wie alt bist du, huh ?
Na, wie hiesst du ?
Wie heisst du, huh ?
Keine Koffier,
hab'ich gesagt.!
[ Screaming ]
Packt keine Koffier.!
Keine Koffier.!
'Rueber zum Platz Chodi.!
Koffier hierlassen.!
Blauschein.
Platz Chodi.!
Was soll
der Koffier hier?
Alles 'rueber
zum Platz Chodi.!
[ Shouting Continues ]
[ Footsteps ]
We're getting out
through the sewers.
I have to check
if they're clear.
Mila, pack some things.
Nothing bigger than this.
I can't go in the sewers.
I told you I won't go
in the sewers.
You can go.
Yes, you can.
I won't go in the sewers.
[ Whistle Blows ]
[ Soldier]
Move ! Over there !
Over there ! Move !
Your card,Jew !
Deine Papiere,
Jude !
Deine Papiere,Jude.!
That line.
[ Whistle Blowing ]
Deine Karte.!
Ich geh'nicht 'rauf
wegen Deiner verdammten Karte.!
Deine Scheisskarte !
[ Whistle Blowing ]
[ Woman Wailing
In German ]
Was soll denn die Scheisse ?
Bist du denn verrueckt geworden?
Mit diesem Scheissgewehr
haettest du mich
erschiessen koennen.!
Du hast so nah an mir
vorbeigeschossen.!
Was heisst hier Entschuldigung.
Du bist wohl verrueckt geworden.!
[ Soldier ]
Zurueckbleiben !
Nicht sprechen, nicht sprechen !
Einfach zu den Lastwagen gehen !
Weiterlaufen ! Weiterlaufen !
Nicht sprechen !
[ Whistle Blows ]
Komm her, du Judensau.!
Bleib stehen, hab'ich gesagt.
Bleib stehen.!
[ Whispering
In Polish ]
[ Indistinct Polish ]
Chodzcie tu szybko.!
[ Footsteps ]
[ Door Bursts Open ]
[ Chattering,
Baby Crying ]
[ Whistle Blowing,
Soldiers Shouting ]
She's good as dead.
Leave her.
Give me a moment.
Just let me bring her inside.
[ Gasps, Screams ]
[ Man Speaking German
Over Loudspeaker ]
You can join her...
or join the line.
[ Soldiers Shouting,
Whistles Blowing ]
Women to the left.!
Wilhelm !
Rose !
Men to right.
Women to the left.
[ Protesting In German ]
Women
to the left.
Let me go !
[ Shouting, Wailing ]
Women to the left,
and men to the right.
Promise me, be safe.
[ Man ]
Your government
is in the wrong country.!
[ Shouting,
Wailing Continue ]
Mama ! Mama !
[ Shouting In Polish ]
[ Dogs Barking,
Soldiers Shouting ]
[ Machine Gun Fire ]
[ Gasping, Panting ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Gasps ]
Mila !
[ Women Panting ]
[ Distant Machine Gun Fire ]
[ Bell Chiming ]
Oh, God, Danka !
[ Gasps, Whimpers ]
You have a Blauschein.
Blauschein doesn't
matter anymore.
They are cleaning
out the ghetto.
There's not enough room for you.
What are you talking about ?
We tried it before.
There's more than enough room.
- I changed my mind !
- Mama !
Look at the space in there.
Now look at me.
You are just scared.
I can fit the girl,
but not you.
- Mama, I'm coming out !
- Stay where you are.
I'd rather you be here
than who knows where.
Mama.!
[ Soldiers Shouting
In German ]
[ Dogs Barking ]
Herr Kommandant.!
[ Soldiers Laughing ]
Very good saluting.
I respectfully report
I've been given orders to clear
the bundles from the road...
so there will be no obstructions
to the thoroughfare.
Finish and join the lines,
little Polish clicking soldier.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Dogs Growling ]
[ Laughing,
Muttering Continue ]
[ Distant Machine Gun Fire ]
[ Blows Whistle ]
Mrs. Dresner ?
Yes.
Oh, you are a friend
of my son's.
Don't worry, I'll go quietly.
I'll be no trouble.
No, get under the stairs.
They'll be done searching soon.
You'll be safe there.
Please hide ! Please !
[ Muttering ]
...warmed by the sun.
Hide under the stairs.
[ Boy ]
I've searched the building.
There's no one here.
Also, gehen wir
zum naechsten Block.
Einverstanden.
Danka.! Ah.!
Mama !
[ Panting ]
Hello, Adam.
H-Hello, Danka.
[ Soldiers Shouting
In Distance ]
Come with me.
I will put you
in the good line.
Do you know the saying, ''An hour
of life is still life'' ?
You are not a boy anymore.
I'm saying a blessing for you.
[ People Shouting,
Machine Guns Firing ]
####[ Children's Choir Singing
''Oyfin Pripetshok'']
## Ofyn pripetshok
brent a fayerl ##
## Un in shtub iz heys ##
## Un der rebe lerent
kleyne kinderlech ##
##Dem alefbeys ##
[ Machine Gun Fire ]
## Un der rebe lerent
kleyne kinderlech ##
##Dem alefbeys ##
[ Gunshot,
People Screaming ]
##Zetzhe kinderlech
gedenktzhe tayere ##
## Vos ir lerent do ##
##Zogtzhe noch amol un take
noch amol ##
##Komets alefo ##
[ Shouting ]
##Zogtzhe noch amol un take
noch amol ##
##Komets alefo ##
## Ofyn pripetshok
brent a fayerl ##
## Un in shtub iz heys ##
[ Officers Shouting ]
## Un der rebe lerent
kleyne kinderlech
Dem alefbeys ##
[ Shouting,
Gunshot ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Gunshots ]
Oh, please, let's go.
Let's go, please.
Come on.
##Zetzhe kinderlech
gedenktzhe tayere ##
## Vos ir lerent do ##
##Zogtzhe noch amol un take
noch amol ##
##Komets alefo ##
[ Whistle Blowing ]
##Zogtzhe noch amol un take
noch amol ##
##Komets alefo ####
[ Whimpering ]
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Whistle Blows,
Dogs Barking ]
Markieren.
[ Speaking Polish ]
Nie.!
Prosze pana, niech pan--
## [ Hits Piano Keys ]
[ Girl ]
...nie znajdziemy !
[ Machine Gun Fire ]
####[ Piano ]
[ Shouting In German ]
####[ Piano Continues ]
[ Machine Gun Fire Continues ]
[ Both Panting ]
Was ist das ?
Ist das Bach ?
Nein, nein. Mozart.
Mozart ?
Ja.
####[ Piano Continues ]
[ Machine Gun Fire,
Piano Continue ]
[ Dog Barking ]
Das wollen wir heute
noch schaffien ?
Nee, schaffien wir nie.
Jemu niedobrze sie robi.
Nee, das schaffien wir nie.
I wish this fucking
night were over.
####[ Piano Continues ]
[ Machine Gun Fire
Continues ]
-[ Whistle Blows ]
-Appell.! Fuenferreihen.!
Antreten.!
Halt, alle anstellen.!
Fuenferreihen.!
Muetzen ab.!
Namen verlesen.!
Wer aufgerufen wird, hebt seine
Hand und ein deutliches Jawhol.!
[ Shouts Name ]
[ Man ]
Jawohl.
[ Shouts Name ]
[ Man ]
Jawohl.
Keller, Fanni !
Adalbert, Hermann !
[ Man ]
Jawohl.
Faber, Dorothea !
[ Woman ]
Jawohl.
Goldstein, Pola.!
[ Woman ]
Jawohl.
Warmberger, Markus !
Edelstein, Max !
[ Soldiers Continue
Shouting Names ]
Appell
abtreten.!
Do pracy.!
The worst is over.
We are workers now.
[ Man Speaking German
Over Loudspeaker ]
[ Officer Shouting
In German ]
[ Officer ]
Keine Muedigkeit vorschuetzen.!
[ Woman Shrieks,
People Shouting ]
Oh, God, Amon.
[ Officer Shouting
In German ]
[ Loudspeaker ]
Sofort in der Baracke
zurueckmelden !
[ Gunshot ]
[ Man Shouting
In German ]
[ Reloading Rifle ]
[ Woman Shrieking ]
[ Officer Shouting
In German ]
[ Bones Crack ]
[ Officer Shouting ]
Komm du mal schoen her !
Komm du schoen !
Na komm !
Amon, you're such
a damned fuckin' child !
Wakey, wakey.
[ Sighs ]
[ Woman ]
Make coffiee.
Make it yourself.
[ Grunting ]
[ Man ]
The SS will manage...
certain industries itself
inside Plaszow--
a metalworks,
brush factory,
another for reprocessing
Jewish clothing...
from the ghettos for use by
bombed-out families back home.
But it's private industry
like yours that stands
to benefit most...
by moving inside the wire of
Commandant Amon Goeth's camp--
No, no, no. Sit, sit.
Julian, how are you ?
How are you ?
Good to see you,
my friend.
Oskar Schindler.
LeoJohn.
[ Whispers, Chuckles ]
Franz, good to see you.
Hello, Oskar.
Glad you could join us.
My pleasure. Julius.
How are you ?
You lost weight.
Only in the shoulders.
Please, everybody, sit down.
How are you doing ?
Oskar Schindler.
We started without you.
Fine.
I miss anything good ?
I was explaining
to Herr Bosch
and Herr Madritsch...
some of the benefits
of moving their
factories into Plaszow.
I meant the food.
[ Chuckles ]
Since your labor is housed
on-site, it's available
to you at all times.
You can work them
all night if you want.
Your factory policies, whatever
they've been in the past,
they'll continue to be.
They'll be respected.
I have to know, where
do you get a suit like that ?
What is that ? Is that silk ?
Of course.
Ja. It's-- It has
a nice sheen about it.
Thank you.
Very nice.
I'd say I'd get you one,
but the man who made it
is probably dead.
I don't know.
[ Schindler's Voice ]
I go to work the other day.
Nobody's there.
Nobody tells me about this.
I have to fid out.
I have to go in.
Everybody's gone.
No.
[ Sighs ]
They're not gone.
They're here.
They're mine !
Every day that goes by,
I'm losing money.
Every worker that is shot
costs me money. I have to
find somebody else.
We are going to be making
so much money that none of this
is going to matter.
It's bad business.
[ Sniffs ]
Thank you.
Leave the bottle.
Take that.
Lena... thank you.
Scherner told me
something else about you.
Yeah ?
What's that ?
That you know the meaning
of the word ''gratitude.''
That it's not
some vague thing with you...
like it is with others.
You want to stay
where you are.
You've got things
going on the side.
Things are good.
You don't want anybody
telling you what to do.
I can understand all that,
you know. I-- I know you.
What you want...
is your own sub-camp.
Do you have any idea
what is involved ?
The paperwork alone ?
You've got to build the thing.
Getting those fucking permits
is enough to drive you crazy.
Then the engineers show up,
they stand around, they argue
about drainage, foundations,
codes, exact specifications,
fences four kilometers long,
1 ,200 kilograms of barbed wire,
[ Chuckling ]
6,000 kilograms of electrified
fences, ceramic insulators,
three cubic meters
of air space per prisoner.
I'm telling you,
you want to shoot somebody.
I've been through it. I know.
Well, you know.
You've been through it.
[ Spits ]
You could make things
easier for me.
I'd be grateful.
Aus dem Weg da.!
[ Dogs Barking ]
Weitergehen.!
[ Speaking Polish ]
[ Whistle Blows ]
Wlewo zwrot.!
Trzymac szereg.!
Weitergehen.
Nach links.
[ Dogs Continue Barking ]
[ Whistle Blows ]
Where's Stern ?
Goldberg and Chilowicz...
make sure I see my cut...
from the, uh,
factory owners in this camp,
leaving you to take care
of my main account--
the Schindler account.
He wants his independence.
I gave it to him.
But independence
costs money.
This you
understand ?
Look at me.
Don't forget who
you are working for now.
[ Chattering, Shouting ]
####[ Accordion ]
Jawohl.!
[ Schindler ]
Make sure he kisses
Ja. Now, girls,
everyone.
We need more wine.
More wine !
Stand in my place.
Don't let him leave.
[ Laughing, Singing ]
[ Chattering,
Shouting Continue ]
## Was passiert denn
in einem Leben ##
Prost.! Prost.!
Thank you,
Herr Direktor.
Prost,
Herr Direktor !
What are you
doing ?
What ?
Makes them think we have lice.
Helps them keep their distance.
[ Exhales ]
Do you have lice ?
Do you have your notebook ?
The calendar on my desk has
the birthdays of our SS friends'
wives and children.
Don't forget
to send something.
Record payoffs
to the Main Administration
and Economics Office, the Arm--
Slower, Stern, slower.
The Armaments Board,
Governor General's Division...
of the Interior
and Chief of Police as ''fees,''
and make them
on the first of each month,
as opposed to individual payoffs
to our SS contacts.
The list is in the lower drawer
of my desk, which you--
''First of month--''
SS contacts: list,
lower drawer of my desk,
which you handle...
as cash contributions
to legitimate charities
sent to each official's office.
Dealings with
our black market contacts,
listed as suppliers...
in the legitimate ledger,
are more complicated.
Forget it.
What do you mean, forget it ?
You can't forget it !
It gives me a headache !
[ Dogs Barking ]
[ Sighs ]
I couldn't get you
out of here.
I'll be all right.
Anyway, I'm here
almost every week.
Wednesdays, usually.
I'll look in on you,
see how you're doing.
Here, put these
in your pocket.
Come on.
[ Inhales ]
Herr Direktor,
don't let things fall apart.
I've worked too hard.
Thanks for--
Good luck.
## [ Music, Shouting
Continue ]
Achtung, Muetzen ab.!
- Work !
- An die Arbeit.!
What are you making ?
Hinges, sir.
Ja, I've got some workers
coming in tomorrow.
Where are they from again ?
Yugoslavia,
Herr Kommandant.
I've got to make room.
Make me a hinge.
Yes, sir.
[ Guards Muttering ]
Keep going,
you're doing well.
Says he's
doing well.
Oh, that's very good.
But I'm a bit confused,
and perhaps you can help me.
What I don't understand
is that you've been working...
since I think, what,
about six this morning ?
Yet such a small pile
of hinges.
[ Train Whistle Blows ]
[ Gun Clicks ]
Oh, Christ.
May I try that, sir ?
Check the angle-lever.
Maybe it's bent.
No, no.
You wouldn't hear a click
if it was the angle-lever.
Maybe it's the pin.
Maybe the pin shaft is greasy.
Ja, come on.
What did I just say ?
Here.
[ Gun Clicks ]
Herr Kommandant,
I beg to report
that my heap ofhinges
was so unsatisfactory...
because the machines
were being recalibrated
this morning.
[ Gun Clicks ]
I w-was put on
to shoveling coal.
[ Gun Clicking ]
[ Grunts, Yells ]
[ Gasps, Sobbing ]
Strange, huh ?
Yeah.
Thank you, Muek.
Ah, Lisiek.
Don't touch the leather,
it's just been oiled.
Rottenfuehrer.
Oh, for me ?
Oh, thank you very much,
Herr Direktor. Thank you.
[ Stern ] Herr Direktor !
Herr Direktor.!
He was making
hinges slowly.
So the man can turn out a hinge
in less than a minute.
Why the long story ? Hmm ?
[ Machines Rumbling ]
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
Nobody knows
who stole the chicken, hmm ?
Tell him about the chicken.
A man walks around
with a chicken and
nobody notices this.
Save yourselves.
Tell him
about the chicken.
Still nobody knows.
[ Sobbing ]
It was you.
You committed this crime.
No, sir.
But you know who, though.
Yes.
Who ?
[ Sobbing ]
Him !
He's very gifted.
Yeah, sure.
Bring him over.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Thank you again,
Herr Direktor.
You're welcome again.
It's an honor to work
for such a great company.
It's great to have you.
I promise to learn everything
about enamelware production.
That's great.
Hello ?
Miss Elsa Krause is here.
I only need five minutes.
She wants to speak
to the Herr Direktor.
[ Typewriter Keys Clicking ]
Yes.
He won't see you.
Please, sit down.
Pernod ?
Cognac ?
Uh, no.
So, what
can I do for you ?
[ Nervous Chuckle ]
They say that no one
dies here.
They say your factory
is a haven.
They say you are good.
Who says that ?
Everyone.
My name is Regina Perlman,
not Elsa Krause.
I've been living in Krakow
on false papers since
the ghetto massacre.
My parents are in Plaszow.
Their names are
Chana and Jakob Perlman.
They are older people.
They are killing older people
now in Plaszow.
They bury them
up in the forest. Look...
[ Sighs ]
I don't have any money.
I, I borrowed
these clothes.
I'm begging you.
Please, please
bring them here.
I don't do that.
You've been misled.
I ask one thing:
whether or not a worker
has certain skills.
My father is an importer,
not a metalworker.
[ Continues Arguing ]
Such activities are illegal.
You will not entrap me !
Cry, and I will
have you arrested.
I swear to God !
[ Mutters, Sobbing ]
People die.
It's a fact of life.
He wants to kill everybody ?
Great ! What am I supposed
to do about it ?
Bring everybody over ?
Is that what you think ?
Send them over to Schindler.
Send them all !
His place is a haven,
didn't you know ?
It's not a factory.
It's not an enterprise
of any kind.
It's a haven for rabbis
and orphans...
and people with
no skills whatsoever !
[ Sighs ]
You think I don't know
what you're doing ?
You're so quiet
all the time.
I know, I know !
Are you losing money ?
That's not the point !
What other point is--
It's dangerous !
It's dangerous to me !
You have to understand.
Goeth is under enormous
pressure.
You have to think of it
in his situation.
He's got this
whole place to run.
He's responsible
for everything here,
all these people.
He's got a lot of things
to worry about.
And he's got the war
which brings out
the worst in people.
Never the good,
always the bad.
Always the bad.
But in normal circumstances
he wouldn't be like this.
He'd be all right.
There'd just be the good
aspects of him which--
[ Chuckles ]
He's a wonderful crook.
A man who loves good food,
good wine, the ladies,
making money--
Killing.
He can't enjoy it.
Bejski told me the other day,
somebody escaped...
from a work detail
outside the wire.
[ Gunshots ]
Goeth lined up everybody
from the missing man's barracks.
He shot the man
to the left of Bejski,
the man to the right ofhim.
He walked down the line
shooting every other man
with the pistol.
Twenty-five.
What do you want me
to do about it ?
Nothing, nothing.
We're just talking.
''Perlman.''
[ Shouting ]
Perlman !
Husband and wife.
Jakob and Chana Perlman !
Have Goldberg
bring them over.
[ Officer ]
Muetzen ab !
Appell abtreten !
## [ Drunken Singing
In German ]
I'm sure this will be better
than those rags, Lisiek.
Herr Direktor,
I was just helping Lisiek
to find something...
to clean the stains
from the Herr Kommandant's
bathtub.
Go, please.
Pardon me,
Herr Direktor.
[ Chuckles ]
You don't have to report
to me, Helen.
You know who I am ?
Hmm ?
[ Whispering ]
I'm Schindler.
Of course.
I-I have heard and...
you have
been here before.
Here, why don't you
keep this someplace ?
Go on, take it.
I get extra food here.
Well, if you don't
want to eat it, trade it.
Or give it to Lisiek.
Why not
build yourself up ?
My first day here,
he beat me...
because I threw out
the bones from dinner.
He came down to the basement
at midnight, and he--
he asked me
where they were.
For his dogs,
you understand.
I said to him, I--
I don't know how I say this.
I never could say it now--
I said to him,
''Why are you beating me ?''
He said, ''The reason
I beat you now...
is because you ask
why I beat you.''
I know your
sufferings, Helen.
It doesn't matter.
I have accepted them.
Accepted them ?
One day
he will shoot me.
No, no, no, no,
he won't shoot you.
I know.
I see things.
We were on the roof on Monday,
young Lisiek and I,
and we saw the Herr Kommandant
come out of the front door...
and down the steps by the patio
right there below us and--
and there on the steps
he drew his gun and he...
shot a woman
who was passing by.
A woman carrying a bundle.
Through the throat.
Just-- Just a woman
on her way somewhere,
you know.
She was no fatter
or thinner...
or slower or faster
than anyone else,
and I couldn't guess
what had she done.
The more you see
of the Herr Kommandant,
the more you see
there is no set rules
that you can live by.
You can't say to yourself,
''If I follow these rules,
I will be safe.''
He won't shoot you
because he enjoys you
too much.
He enjoys you so much
he won't even let you
wear the star.
He doesn't want
anyone else to know...
it's a Jew
he's enjoying.
He shot the woman
from the steps...
because she meant
nothing to him.
She was
one of a series,
neither offending
or pleasing him.
But you, Helen.
It's all right.
It's not that kind
of a kiss.
[ Sobbing ]
Thank you.
Shh.
Here.
Right. The wine.
Wonderful party, Amon.
Thank you.
[ Groans ]
Why do you drink
that motor oil ?
Hmm ? I send you
good stuff all the time.
Your liver's
going to explode
like a hand grenade.
The more I look at you--
[ Sniffs ]
I watch you.
[ Sighs ]
You're never drunk.
[ Sniffs ]
Oh, that's--
that's real control.
Control is power.
That's power.
[ Schindler ]
Is that why they fear us ?
We have the fucking
power to kill, that's
why they fear us.
They fear us because
we have the power
to kill arbitrarily.
A man commits a crime,
he should know better.
We have him killed,
and feel good about it.
Or we kill him ourselves
and we feel even better.
That's not power,
though.
That's justice.
It's different than power.
Power is when we have every
justification to kill...
and we don't.
You think that's power ?
That's what the emperors had.
A man stole something,
he's brought in
before the emperor,
he throws himself
down on the ground,
he begs for mercy.
He knows
he's going to die.
And the emperor...
pardons him.
This worthless man.
He lets him go.
I think you are drunk.
That's power, Amon.
That... is power.
Amon the Good.
I pardon you.
[ Laughs ]
[ Goeth ]
What do they want ?
[ Stern ] I don't know,
but they're in my office now
reviewing our books.
As my accountant, tell me,
should I be alarmed...
that the auditors
are reviewing my books ?
Well--
Or have you done
your job properly ?
You needn't be alarmed.
I needn't
be alarmed.
[ Shouts In German ]
[ Gasps ]
I'm sorry, sir.
Do you know how much
this saddle is worth ?
it costs ?
All right.
[ Panting ]
Stern, what the hell are you
doing following me around ?
[ Loudspeaker ]
Barracken eins, elf,
fuenfzehn
und zwounddreissig...
am Appellplatz melden.
[ Whistling ]
[ Both Whistling ]
[ Children Chattering ]
[ Gasping, Whimpering ]
[ Horse Neighs ]
She was smoking
on the job.
Tell her
not to do it again.
[ Shouting In Polish ]
[ Footsteps ]
I have to report, sir,
I've been unable to remove
the stains from your bathtub.
What are you using,
Lisiek ?
Soap, Commandant.
Soap ? Not lye ?
Go ahead, go on, leave.
Leave, I pardon you.
[ Birds Chirping ]
I pardon you.
[ Gunshot ]
[ Inhales ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Woman ]
Although I am not a rabbi,
in these circumstances...
I pray to the Almighty
that you will forgive me...
if I intone the blessings.
Baruch ata Hsham eloiyni
melech hoylam...
asher ztivonee
al aariuouth.
Vouser lanou at harosth,
Vhesserlanou at hansooes...
lanou al yaday cheepah
ve kidesheem.
[ Woman Singer In Club ]
# Milosc tak pieknie tlumaczy #
#Zdrade i klamstwo i grzech #
# Choc bys ja przeklal
w rozpaczy #
##Zejest okrutna i zla ##
##Milosc ci wszystko wybaczy ##
# Bo milosc moj mily to ja #
[ Sobbing ]
So...
this is where you come
to hide from me.
I came to tell you...
that you, um, you really are
a wonderful cook...
and a well-trained servant.
I mean it.
If you need a reference
after the war,
I'd be-- I'd be happy
to give you one.
It must get lonely
down here...
when you're listening
to everyone upstairs
having such a good time.
Does it ?
You can answer.
But what's the right answer ?
That's what you're thinking.
What does he want to hear ?
The truth, Helen,
is always the right answer.
Y-Yes, you're right.
Sometimes
we're both lonely.
Yes. I--
[ Sighing ]
I mean--
I would like so much to...
reach out and touch you
in your loneliness.
Wh-What would that be like,
I wonder ? I mean...
[ Chuckles ]
what would be wrong with that ?
I realize that you're not
a-a person in the--
the strictest sense
of the word, but--
[ Sighing ]
No, maybe you're right
about that too, you know.
Maybe what's--
what's wrong isn't--
It's not us.
It's no--
It's this.
I mean, when they
compare you to--
to, uh, vermin
and to rodents and to lice...
[ Panting ]
I just, uh--
N-No, you-you make
a good point.
You make
a very good point.
Is this the face
of a rat ?
Are these the eyes
[ Singing Continues ]
# Milosc... #
Hath not a Jew eyes ?
# Ci wszystko wybaczy #
# Bo milosc moj mily #
I feel for you, Helen.
## Toja ####
[ Panting ]
No, I don't think so.
You're a Jewish bitch.
You nearly talked me into it,
Helen, didn't you ?
- Bravo.
- [ Chattering ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Grunts ]
- [ Chattering Continues ]
- [ Grunting Continues ]
- [ Applause Continues ]
- [ Goeth Yelling ]
[ Guests Shouting ]
Hoch .! Hoch .! Hoch .!
####[ Violin ]
- Jawohl.!
- Hoch.! Hoch.!
Hoch !
[ Laughing ]
[ Music, Talking Stops ]
On behalf of the--
of the workers, sir,
I, I wish for you
a happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
Well, thank
the staff, please.
Thank you very much
for the lovely cake.
[ Officer
Clears Throat ]
Thank you very much.
Tell them thank you from me.
## To ostatnia niedziela ##
##Dzisiaj sie rozstaniemy ##
The trains arrived
and the people were
driven out with clubs.
They were lined up in front
of two big warehouses.
One was marked ''Cloak Room,''
and the other ''Valuables.''
And there they
were made to undress.
AJewish boy handed them
pieces of string to tie
their shoes together.
They shaved their hair.
They told them it was needed
to make something special
for U-boat crews.
And then they were herded
down a big corridor...
to bunkers with
Stars of David on the doors,
and signs that said
''Bath and Inhalation Room.''
SS gave them soap.
They told them to
breathe all the time because
it's good for disinfecting.
And then they gassed them.
Mila, why soaps ?
So that they would agree
to go in, I think.
Come on, Mila, stop it.
Your bedtime stories
are scaring everyone.
I just don't believe it.
Ja. You know
it's ridiculous.
I don't believe it
either.
I cannot believe it.
I didn't say I believed it.
I said I heard it.
From who ?
From somebody who heard it
from someone who was there.
You know,
if they were there,
they would
have been gassed.
Yes.
It doesn't
make any sense.
We're their work force.
What sense does it make
to kill your own work force ?
To go to all this trouble
of assembling a work force
only to--
No, it can't be true.
We are very, very
important for them.
Ja, we do now.
Good night.
Sweet dreams.
[ Man Over Loudspeaker ]
Attention, attention.
Everyone who is alive...
is to come
to the Appellplatz.
[ Coughing ]
Attention, attention.
Come, we have to go
to the Appellplatz.
Everyone who is alive...
[ Mrs. Dresner ]
The listmakers are here.
is to come to the Appellplatz.
There is going
to be a selection.
Attention, attention.
Everyone who is alive...
is to come
to the Appellplatz.
[ Whistle Blowing ]
[ Whistle Continues ]
[ Indistinct German ]
Meine Herren.
Raz.!
Dwa.!
...die Hunderttausend
Ungarn kommen...
[ Indistinct German ]
[ Officer ]
Alle in einer
Einzelreihe aufstellen !
You could afford
to lose some weight, Amon.
And you've got to
cut down on the cognac.
Morning.
What's going on ?
It's another
semiannual physical.
There.
Oh, I've, um, got another
shipment coming in of, uh--
What are they this time ?
Hungarians.
Oh, ja, Hungarians.
We've got to separate
the sick from the healthy
to make room.
[ Soldier ]
Teraz ! Teraz !
[ Whistle Blowing ]
####[''Gute Nacht Mutter'']
[ Shouting In German ]
## Gute Nacht Mutter ##
## Gute Nacht ##
[ Shouting In German ]
Das darf nicht
bis zum Abend dauern.!
####[ Continues ]
Ruszac sie.!
[ Indistinct German ]
[ Coughing ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Woman ]
Let me help you.
[ Soldiers Continue
Shouting In German ]
[ Soldier ]
Zack, zack, zack !
[ Woman ]
We've got to go out there.
Don't go.
Look alive, Rebeka.
[ Soldier ]
Schneller !
## Gute Nacht Mutter ##
Naokolo !
Predzej ! Predzej !
Naokolo.!
## Gute Nacht ##
####[ Continues ]
That's my mechanic.
Whose bright idea was it
to get rid of him ?
Ruszaj sie.!
Naokolo.!
Szybciej.! Szybciej.!
Trzymaj ubrania.!
## Gute Nacht ##
Ruszac sie.!
Naokolo.!
Otworz usta.
Zajrzymy do gardla.
Wez gleboki oddech.
Jeszcze. Jeszcze.
Unies ramiona.
Obroc sie. Przykucnij.
[ Soldier Shouting ]
Formowac kolmune.!
##Du hast verziehen mir
Du hast gewacht ##
No, no, no.
Wait, go away.
She can work.
Come here. Look,
separate the sick
from the healthy.
Those who can work
and those who can't.
She can work.
You can work,
you can come.
[ Soldier ]
Ruszac sie !
Szybciej !
####[''Mamatschi'']
##Es war einmal
ein kleines Buebchen ##
[ Children Singing Along ]
##Das bettelte so wundersuess ##
##Mamatschi schenke mir
ein Pferdchen ##
##Ein Pferdchen
waere mein Paradies ##
##Daraufbekam der kleine Mann ##
##Ein Schimmelpaar
aus Marzipan ##
Stehenbleiben.!
##Die sieht er an er weint
und spricht ##
##Solche Pferde wollte
ich nicht ##
##Mamatschi schenke mir ein
Pferdchen ##
##Ein Pferdchen waere
mein Paradies ##
##Mamatschi solche Pferde
wollte ich nicht ##
##Es war einmal
ein kleines Buebchen ##
##Das bettelte so wundersuess ##
##Da kam das Christkind
reingeflogen ##
## Und schenkte
ihm was er begehrte ##
Those not selected
for transport,
put your clothes back on.
[ Hujar ]
Men, go back to the barracks.
Return to the barracks.
[ Giggling ]
[ Man ]
Go back to the barracks.
[ Truck Engine Rewing ]
Oh, my God !
##Ein Pferdchen waere
mein Paradies ##
##Mamatschi solche Pferde
wollte ich nicht ##
[ Women Shrieking ]
[ Women Screaming ]
Olek ? Olek ?
[ Mrs. Dresner ]
Danka ?
Olek ? Olek ?
Olek ! Olek !
[ Screaming ]
Olek ?
Danka ?
Ab in die Barracke.!
In die Barracke mit euch.!
I didn't see him !
They're hiding.
I'm telling you, they're hiding.
I know Danka.
She took them to a good place.
She took all of them together.
[ Soldier ]
Zurueck in die Barracken !
##...mein Paradies ##
##Mamatschi solche
Pferde wollte ich nicht ##
####[ Continues ]
Find your own hiding place.
There's no room for you here.
Go away, quick !
####[ Continues ]
[ Hat Splashing ]
Get out. This is our place.
Get out !
[ Men Shouting ]
Oskar !
Amon. Gentlemen.
Why didn't you call me ?
I tried to call you.
Here, Hujar, move.
Quite a picnic, huh ?
Madritsch.
Oskar.
I'm running a little late.
This is taking longer
than I thought.
A drink ?
Something cold.
Bowle.
The Bowle.
Oh, another
beautiful day.
[ Woman Shouting
In Polish ]
Cisza.! Spokoj.!
[ People Moaning ]
Die Beladung der Transportwagen
ist beendet.
Wir sind abfahrbereit.
Wody.!
[ Whispering ]
Wasser... wasser.
[ Gasping, Panting ]
Wohlsein.
Oh, thank you.
What do you say we get your
fire hoses out here and hose
down the cars ? Thank you.
[ Chuckling ]
Indulge me.
Hujar.
Yes, sir.
- Go bring the fire hoses.
- Where's the fire ?
[ Laughing ]
[ Schindler ]
In the windows.
That's it, that's it.
On the roof.
That's it, good, good.
In the window, in the window.
Come on. Come on.
That's it, more, more.
That's it, that's it.
More, more.
This is really cruel, Oskar.
You are giving them hope.
You shouldn't do that.
That's cruel.!
Come on, try and
reach the far end.
Look out--
[ Man Wailing ]
Water.! More water.!
I've got some 200-meter
hoses back at Emalia.
I have 20 meters
at home in my garden.
We can reach
the cars at the end.
[ Laughing ]
What ? What ?
Huh ?
Hujar.
Yeah, sure.
[ Water Spraying ]
[ Woman Shrieking ]
[ Laughing ]
Don't forget
the roof.
On the roof
on the other side.
[ Water Spraying ]
[ Woman ]
Water.!
Scharfuehrer,
every time the train stops,
you open the doors,
you give them water, ja ?
Jawohl.
Ja. This car !
This car !
[ Woman Shrieking ]
[ Schindler]
I'm not saying you'll
regret it, but you might.
You should be
aware of that.
We will have to risk regret.
All right, sure.
It's a nice day. I'll go
for a drive with you.
What about you ?
I violated the
''Race and Resettlement Act.''
Though I doubt
anyone can point out
the actual provision to me.
I kissed a Jewish girl.
[ Laughing ]
Did your prick fall off?
[ Man Laughing ]
[ Goeth ]
He likes women.
He likes
good-looking women.
He sees a beautiful woman,
he doesn't think.
[ Laughing ]
I mean,
he has so many women.
And they love him.
Ja, they love him.
I mean, he is married,
ja, but he's--
All right, it's not--
She was Jewish.
He shouldn't have done it.
But, you didn't see this girl.
I saw this girl.
This girl was, woof--
She was very good-looking.
They cast a spell on you,
you know, theJews.
When you work closely with them,
like I do, you see this.
They have this power.
It's like a virus. Some of my men
are infected with this virus.
They should be
pitied, not punished.
They should receive treatment.
This is as real as typhus.
I see this all the time.
It's a matter of money ?
Hmm ?
You're offering me
a bribe ?
A bribe ? No. No, please.
It's a gratuity.
Heil Hitler.!
Hello, Amon.
Sit down.
We give you Jewish girls
at five marks a day, Oskar.
You should kiss us,
not them.
God forbid you ever get
a real taste forJewish skirt.
There's no future in it.
They don't have a future.
That's not just good,
old-fashioned,Jew-hating talk.
It's policy now.
[ Man ]
Ja, schoen gefangen ! Gut !
[ Laughing ]
[ Man ]
Nochmal,ja ! Schoen !
[ Soldier ]
Also los ! Bewegung !
Schneller hier.!
Zack, zack, zack.!
[ Soldier ]
Beweg deinen Arsch !
Das geht
auch schneller.!
Bewegt euch.!
Schlaft nicht ein.!
####[ Choir Singing Requiem ]
Nur die ganzen Fetzen,
nicht das Gemuese.!
Was ist denn hier los ?
Komm, das kannst du mit
den Haenden machen,
fass da vorn an.!
Hier.!
Los, raus mit den Fetzen.!
Die Kleinteile lass liegen.!
####[ Requiem Continues ]
Jetzt macht aber schnell,
verdammt noch mal.!
Weg mit den Scheissdingern.!
[ Screaming Insanely ]
[ Indistinct German ]
So ist es.! Walhalla.!
Walhalla laeuft hier.!
[ Gunshots ]
####[ Requiem Continues ]
[ Goeth ]
Can you believe this ?
As if I don't have enough to do,
they come up with this ?
I have to find every rag
buried up here and burn it.
The party's over, Oskar.
They're closing us down,
sending everybody to Auschwitz.
When ?
I don't know. As soon as
I can arrange the shipments.
Maybe 30, 40 days.
That ought to be fun.
####[ Choir Continues ]
[ Schindler ]
I've been talking to Goeth.
I know the destination.
These are
the evacuation orders.
I'm to help organize
the shipments, put myself
on the last train.
That's not what
I was going to say.
I made Goeth promise me
he'd put in a good word for you.
Nothing bad is going to happen
to you there. You'll receive
special treatment.
The directives coming in
from Berlin mention ''Special Treatment''
more and more often.
I'd like to think
that's not what you mean.
Preferential treatment.
- Do we have to invent
a whole new language ?
- I think so.
You're staying,
I take it.
In Krakow ? What on earth for ?
What for?
You have a business to run.
Of course, you'll have
to hire new workers.
Poles, I guess.
They cost
a little more, but--
What are you going to do ?
You run my business.
No, I'm going home.
I've done what I came here for.
I've got more money than any man
could spend in a lifetime.
Someday, this is all
going to end, you know.
I was going to say
we'll have a drink then.
I think I better
have it now.
[ Bottle Clinking Glass ]
[ Billie Holiday ]
##Bible says ##
##And it still is news ##
##Mama may have ##
##Papa may have ##
##But God bless the child ##
## That's got his own ##
## Yes, the strong gets more ##
## While the weak ones fade ##
##Empty pockets don't ##
##Ever make the grade ##
##Mama may have ##
##Papa may have ##
##But God bless the child ##
## That's got his own ##
##Money ##
## You've got lots of friends ##
## They're pounding on your--####
[ Goeth ]
I don't understand.
I mean,you want these people ?
''These people''?
My people,
I want my people.
Who are you, Moses ?
Come on, what is this ?
Where's the money in this ?
Where's the scam ?
It's good business.
It's good business
in your opinion.
You've got to move them,
the equipment, everything
to Czechoslovakia.
Pay for all that
and build another camp.
Doesn't make any sense.
Look, Amon--
It's good for me.
You're not telling me something.
I know them.
I'm familiar with them.
I don't have to train them.
You're not telling me something.
It's good for you.
I'll compensate you.
That's right.
It's good for the Army.
You know what
I'm going to make ?
What ?
Artillery shells.
Everyone is !
Tank shells,
they need that.
Tanks shells, ja.
Everybody's happy.
Except me.
You're probably
scamming me somehow.
If I'm making 1 00,
you've got to be making 300.
If you admit to 300,
then it's 400 actually.
But how ?
I just told you.
You did, but you didn't.
Ah, ja, all right,
don't tell me.
I'll go along with it.
It's just irritating
I can't work it out.
Look, all you have
to do is tell me
what it's worth to you.
What's a person
worth to you ?
No, no, no, no.
What's one worth to you ?
Poldek Pfefferberg.
Mila Pfefferberg.
And, uh--
Uh, Stagel, Stagel--
Paul.
Paul Stagel.
[ Stern ]
Doctor.
The investors.
I want all of them.
Yes, sir.
Uh, Fischer.
Ismail Fischer.
Fischer, Ismail.
Josef Scharf.
One moment, sir.
I'm sorry, sir.
Come on, Stern.
Scharf, Scharf.
The children.
All the children.
[ Stern ]
Herbert Stier.
[ Schindler ] Thank you.
How many ?
Four hundred, 450.
More, more.
[ Typewriter Keys Clicking ]
[ Keys Continue Clicking ]
Good morning.
[ Typing Continues ]
Think of Feigenbaum,Jakob.
Wolf. Wolf Wein.
Feigenbaum: Lutek,Jakob,
Nacha. Yes ? Nacha.
Nacha, that's right.
[ Schindler ]
And Wolf.
How many ?
Six hundred.
More.
[ Schindler ]
You can do
the same thing I'm doing.
You might even
make money at it.
[ Madritsch ] I don't know.
Come on,Julius, I know
about the extra food
and clothes you give them.
Paid for out of your own pocket.
If we make a combined approach,
we could get more than
4,000 out, mine and yours.
Oskar--
We could relocate them
in something like safety,
in Moravia.
I don't know.
How many cigarettes
have you smoked tonight ?
Too many.
For every one--
[ Coughing ]
you smoke, I smoke half.
I've done all I can.
I will not accept that.
No, Oskar,
I can't do anymore.
I will not accept that.
No.
How many ? How many ?
Eight hundred and fifty,
give or take.
Give or take what, Stern ?
Count them. How many ?
That's it.
You can finish that page.
What... did... Goeth...
say about this ?
You just told him how
many people you needed and--
You're not buying them.
You're buying them ?
You're paying him
for each of these names ?
If you were still working
for me, I'd expect you
to talk me out of it.
It's costing me
a fortune.
[ Sighing ]
Finish the page and leave
one space at the bottom.
Look.
The list is
an absolute good.
The list... is life.
All around its margins
lies the gulf.
Oskar, there's
a clerical error here
at the bottom of the last page.
No, there's one more name
I want to put there.
I'll never fid a maid as well
trained as her at Brinnlitz.
They are all country girls.
No.
One hand of 21 .
If you win, I pay you
7,400 Reichsmark.
No.
Hit a natural,
I make it 1 4,800.
No.
If I win,
the girl goes on my list.
I can't wager Helen
in a card game.
Why not ?
Wouldn't be right.
She's just going to Auschwitz
on Number Two anyway.
What difference
does it make ?
She's not going to Auschwitz.
I'd never do that to her.
No, I want her to come back
to Vienna with me.
I want her to come
to work for me there.
I want to grow old
with her.
Are you mad ?
Amon, you can't take her
to Vienna with you.
No, of course I can't.
That's what I'd like to do.
What I can do, if I'm
any sort of a man, is the
next most merciful thing.
I should take her into the woods
and shoot her painlessly
in the back of the head.
What was it you said
for a natural 21 ?
Was it 1 4,800 ?
[ Man ]
Schindlerjuden to these tables.!
Say your names clearly.
We are the family Dresner.
Juda,Jonas,
Donata and Chaja.
We are Rosners.
Henry, Manci--
And Leo.
And our son.
I am Olek.
Maria Mischel.
Chaim Nowak.
Wulkan, Markus.
Michael Lemper.
Itzhak Stern.
Rebeka and Josef Bau.
Rosalia Nussbaum.
Wilhelm Nussbaum.
Jakob Levartov.
Farber, Rosa.
Farber, Arje.
...Sara.
Friehof, Fischel.
Mietek Pemper.
Poldek and Mila Pfefferberg.
Horowitz, Dolek.
Adam Levy.
Marcel Goldberg.
Klipstein, Isak David.
Altmann, Eduard.
Grunberg, Miriam.
Luftig, Eliasz.
Hilmann, Eduard.
Erna Rothberg.
Zuckermann,Jetti.
Helen Hirsch.
[ Pencil Scraping Paper ]
The worst is over.
Men to this transport
and women to this transport.
Be careful.
Men to this transport and
women to this transport.
Watch your step.
Men to this transport
and women to this transport.
[ Train Whistle Blowing ]
[ Coughing ]
[ Stern ]
Wonderful, Olek, wonderful.
You know how we make
ice into water ?
[ Blowing ]
Olek, get another one !
[ Train Whistle Blowing ]
[ Train Approaching ]
[ Coughing ]
[ Train Brakes Screeching ]
[ Man ]
Alle in eine Einzelreihe
aufstellen !
You'll be pleased with
the level of efficiency
I get from these workers.
Budzyn, under my command,
was the envy
of every other commandant
in the labor camp system.
The prisoners,
however--
Excuse me.
They would have rather
been somewhere else.
[ Coughing ]
[ Schindler ]
The train with the women
has already left Plaszow...
and will be arriving
here very shortly.
I know you've had
a long journey.
But it's only a short walk
further to the factory...
where hot soup and bread
is waiting for you.
Welcome to Brinnlitz !
[ Train Whistle Blowing ]
[ Mrs. Dresner ]
Beans in tsunt ?
[ Mila ] Beans are the best.
[ Danka ]
I don't like beans.
Beans and meat
and potatoes and bread.
That's not the way
you make tsunt.
Eggs in tsunt ?
Yes !
[ Danka ]
I don't like tsunt.
[ Mrs. Dresner ] No,you don't.
What do you like ?
I like caviar.
[ Rebeka ]
One day on the fire.
[ Train Whistle Blowing ]
[ Coughing ]
[ Train Approaching ]
[ Dogs Barking, Snarling ]
Alle vorm Wagen
in Position bleiben.
Alle in der Gruppe
zusammenbleiben.
Wegbleiben vom Wagen.!
Wegbleiben vom Wagen,
hab ich gesagt.!
Bagaze zostawic !
Schneller.!
Dalli, dalli, dalli.!
Was ist da hinten los.!
[ Dog Barking ]
Schnell.!
[ Soldier ]
Los, 'raus mit euch.
Zack, zack, zack ! 'Raus !
Dreissig, fuenfunddreissig,
vierzig, fuenfundvierzig.
Aussteigen.!
[ Soldier ]
'Rausgehen !
Schneller !
[ Soldier ]
Alle 'raus !
Where are the listmakers ?
Where are the tables ?
[ Indistinct Noise ]
[ Soldier ]
Move the line.!
'Raus mit euch !
Hopp, hopp.!
...bagaze w wagonach.!
- Dalli.! 'Rausgehen.!
-Schneller.!
Zostawcie bagaze w wagonach.!
Schneller.!
Los, ein bisschen
schneller !
Mama, where are we ?
[ Stern ]
Seventeen, 1 8, 20--
They're in Auschwitz.
The train was
never routed here.
Apaperwork mistake.
[ Polish Woman ]
Szybciej ! Szybko !
[ German Woman ]
Die Schuhe werfen !
[ Scissors Clipping ]
Schneller !
Ubrania skladac.!
Pod prysznic !
Zieht euch aus !
Bewegung !
Bewegt euch !
Stellt euch auf
und zieht euch aus !
Rozbierac sie tam szybciej.!
Schneller !
[ Woman ]
Szybko sie rozbierac.
Dostaniecie mydlo
i recznik i pojdziecie
pod prysznic do dezynfeckji.!
Szybko sie rozbierac.!
Schneller !
Zabierajcie to
mydlo i szybko !
Zieht euch schneller aus !
Bewegung !
Szybko !
Sofort hinein !
Pojdziecie pod prysznic !
Szybko !
Schneller !
Hineim zum Bad !
Szybko !
Tu wchodzic !
[ Screaming, Shrieking ]
[ Sobbing ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Laughing ]
Blick hinunter.!
Die Hand auf
die Schulter.!
[ Man ]
How old are you, Mother?
Sixty-eight.
Cough for me, Mother.
They say to fall against
the fence is a kindness.
Don't kill yourself
against the fence, Clara.
If you do, you'll never
know what happened to you.
How old are you,
Mother ?
Sixty-six, sir.
Sir ?
Good morning.
A mistake has been made.
We are not supposed
to be here.
We work for Oskar Schindler.
We are SchindlerJews.
Who is Oskar Schindler ?
He had a factory
in Krakow.
Enamelware.
A potmaker.
How old are you, Mother ?
You are not
the only industrialist
who needs labor,
Herr Schindler.
I remember
earlier this year,
I.G. Farben ordered...
a trainload of Hungarians
for his chemical factory.
The train came in
through the archway,
and the officer in charge
of the selection went
immediately to work...
and sent 2,000
of them...
straightaway
to Special Treatment.
It is not my task
to interfere with the processes
that take place down here.
Why do you think I can
help you if I can't
help I.G. Farben ?
Allow me to express
the reason.
[ Train Whistle Blowing ]
I'm not making
any judgment about you.
It's just that I know
that in the coming months...
we're all going
to need portable wealth.
I could have you arrested.
I'm protected
by powerful friends.
You should know that.
I do not say
I am accepting them.
All I say is,
I'm not comfortable
with them on the table.
I have a shipment
coming in tomorrow.
I'll cut you
300 units from it.
New ones.
These are fresh.
The train comes,
we turn it around.
Mmm, yes, yes.
It's yours.
I understand.
I want these.
You shouldn't
get stuck on names.
[ Train Whistle Blowing ]
[ Water Fizzing ]
That's right. It creates
a lot of paperwork.
Zoldinger, Ernestina.!
Waldergrun, Hilda.!
Waldergrun, Leonora.!
Laast, Anna !
Pfefferberg, Mila !
Dresner, Chaja !
Dresner, Danka !
Nussbaum, Sidonia !
Rosner, Manci !
Hirsch, Helen.!
Grosz, Chaja Sara.!
Seelenfreund, Estella.!
[ Dogs Barking ]
[ Shouting ]
[ Barking ]
[ Woman Soldier]
Schneller laufen.!
Schneller laufen.! Schneller.!
Schneller.!
Mach schon.! Voran.!
[ Whistle Blowing ]
Los, los, los.!
Schneller.!
[ Soldiers ]
- Schneller !
- Bewegt euch !
Bojcie sie !
No ! No ! No !
[ Woman Soldier ]
Maedchen, los jetzt aber !
Jetzt aber Tempo !
[ Screaming, Shrieking ]
No ! No ! No !
Danka ! Danka ! Danka !
[ Screaming ]
Hey.! Hey.! Hey.!
What are you doing?
These are mine !
These are my workers !
They should be on my train !
They're skilled
munitions workers !
They're essential !
Essential girls !
[ Sobbing, Gasping ]
Their fingers polish the insides
of shell metal casings.
How else am I
to polish the inside of
a .45 millimeter shell casing ?
You tell me.
You tell me !
Back on the train !
[ Train Whistle Blowing ]
[ Dogs Barking ]
[ Coughing ]
Under Department ''W''
provisions,
it is unlawful to kill
a worker without just cause.
Under the Businesses
Compensation Fund,
I am entitled to file
damage claims for such deaths.
If you shoot
without thinking,
you go to prison,
I get paid.
That's how it works.
So, there will be no
summary executions here.
There will be no
interference of any kind
with production.
In hopes of ensuring that,
guards will no longer be
allowed on the factory floor...
without my authorization.
For your cooperation,
you have my gratitude.
Come on, come.
[ Soldier ]
Mensch, seitJahren hab' ich
so etwas nicht mehr gesehen.
[ Schindler ]
Come on, boys, come.
Guck dir mal die Buddeln an !
[ Priest ]
Et dimitte nobis debita nostra,
sicut et nos dimittimus...
[ Congregation ]
...quotidianum da nobis hodie,
et dimitte nobis
debita nostra...
sicut et nos dimittimus...
debitoribus nostris--
No doorman or maitre d'
will ever mistake you again.
I promise.
...sed libera nos a malo.
[ Schindler ]
Itzhak.
This is Itzhak Stern,
my accountant. Itzhak--
You must be Mrs. Schindler.
It's a pleasure.
Emilie has volunteered
to work in the clinic.
Very generous
of you.
I know.
We need to talk
when you have a moment.
This is my wife, Stern.
I don't keep any secrets
from my spouse.
Oskar, please, attend
to business. It's much
more attractive.
Madam.
Hello.
What is it ?
We received an angry complaint
from the Armaments Board.
The artillery shells,
tank shells, rocket casings--
Apparently all of them have
failed quality control tests.
That's to be expected.
Start-up problems.
This isn't pots and pans.
This is a precise business.
I'll write them
a letter.
They're withholding payment.
Sure, so would I, so would you.
I wouldn't worry. We'll get it
right one of these days.
There's a rumor
you've been going around
miscalibrating the machines.
They could shut us down,
send us back to Auschwitz.
I'll call around, find out
where we can buy shells.
Pass them off as ours.
I don't see the difference
whether they're made here--
You don't see a difference ?
I see a difference.
You lose a lot of money.
Fewer shells will be made.
Stern, if this factory
ever produces...
a shell that can
actually be fired,
I'll be very unhappy.
[ Woman ]
Hello, madam.
How do you do ?
[ Machine Whirring ]
[ Machine Grinding ]
How are you doing,
Rabbi ? Rabbi !
Good, Herr Direktor.
Sun's going down.
Yes, it is.
What day is this ?
Friday ?
It is Friday, isn't it ?
Is it ?
What's the matter with you ?
You should be preparing
for the Sabbath.
Shouldn't you ?
I've got some wine.
In my office. Come.
[ Rabbi Levartov ]
Savree maranun
verbanun verabuty...
Baruch ata adoshem,
Elokynou melach hoyleam...
boyrah paree hagofan.
[ Workers ]
Amen.
[ Rabbi Continues ]
Baruch ata adoshem elokynou
melach hoyleam.
Asher kideshanou
bamezvoytaiv veratzah banou...
ve shabath kodshoy beahava ve
razoun hencheelanou...
zicarone lemahsa barashit...
yhom techelah lemikrahy kodesh
zecher letzeat Mitzraim.
Kee banou bachartah veotanou
kedashtah mekol ahameem.
Ve Shabath kodshou beahava
ve razoun hencheltanou...
Barooch ata adoshem
mekadesh hashabat.
Geet Shabath.
[ Workers Respond ]
[ Schindler ]
What ?
Do you have any money,
uh, hidden away someplace...
that I don't know about ?
No.
Why ? Am I broke ?
Uh--
Well--
[ Winston Churchill On Radio ]
Yesterday morning, at 24 1 a.m.,
at General Eisenhower's
headquarters,
General Jodl...
signed the ''Act of
Unconditional Surrender''...
of all German land,
sea and air forces
in Europe...
to the Allied
Expeditionary Force,
and simultaneously
to the Soviet High Command.
The German war is,
therefore, at an end.
[ Footsteps Approaching ]
[ Knocking ]
But let us not forget
for a moment--
I think it's time the guards
came into the factory.
Japan, with all
her treachery and greed--
[ Schindler ]
The unconditional surrender of
Germany has just been announced.
At midnight tonight,
the war is over.
Tomorrow you'll
begin the process...
of looking for survivors
of your families.
In most cases,
you won't find them.
After six long years
of murder,
victims are being mourned
throughout the world.
We've survived.
Many of you have come up
to me and thanked me.
Thank yourselves.
Thank your fearless Stern...
and others among you
who worried about you...
and faced death
at every moment.
[ Sighing ]
I'm a member
of the Nazi party.
I'm a munitions
manufacturer.
I'm a profiteer
of slave labor.
I am a criminal.
At midnight you'll be free,
and I'll be hunted.
I shall remain with you until
five minutes after midnight.
After which time,
and I hope you'll forgive me,
I have to flee.
I know you have received orders
from our Commandant,
which he has received
from his superiors, to dispose
of the population of this camp.
Now would be
the time to do it.
Here they are, they're all here.
This is your opportunity.
[ Murmuring ]
Or you could leave,
and return to
your families as men...
instead of murderers.
[ Sighs ]
In memory of the countless
victims among your people,
I ask us to observe
three minutes of silence.
[ Rabbi Levartov ]
Yetkadal veytkadosh shamy raboo.
Vealmah Devyrsah
veyamlich malchootay.
Vysmach Palkoney
bekoor meshchay.
Vchyachoon ovyomachoon
ovachaye bechol bayeth ysrael.
Bahgoola ovzman Kariv veemree.
Amen.
[ Workers ]
Yahee Shmay Rabah Mevoorach
leolame oleomlay olmaya.
Yetbarach veyeshtabach
veytpaehar veytromam.
Veytnasah veytader
veytalah veythalel.
Schmy dekodsha breech hoe.
Yehee shalama Rabah
Mean shamaya...
vechayeem toveem alayno veal
kol israel. Vemree. Amen.
[ Workers ]
Amen.
Thank you, Mr.Jereth.
Thank you,
Mr.Jereth.
Thank you, Mr.Jereth.
[ Stern ]
Open wide.
Thank you, Mr.Jereth.
Thank you,
Mr.Jereth.
As soon as peace occurs,
I want...
um, I want that cloth
distributed to the workers.
Two and a half meters each.
Also, each person is
to get a bottle of vodka.
They won't drink it.
They know its value.
Likewise for those
Egipshi cigarettes
we organized.
[ Stern ]
It'll be done.
Everything you ask.
We've written a letter,
trying to explain things...
in case
you are captured.
Every worker
has signed it.
Thank you.
It is Hebrew,
from the Talmud.
It says,
''Whoever saves one life,
saves the world entire.''
[ Ring Clattering ]
I could have got more out.
I could have got more.
I don't know.
If I just--
I could have got more.
Oskar, there are 1 ,1 00 people
who are alive because of you.
Look at them.
If I'd made more money.
[ Laughs ]
I threw away so much money.
[ Sobbing ]
You have no idea.
If I had just--
There will be generations
because of what you did.
I didn't do enough.
You did so much.
This car.
Goeth would've
bought this car.
Why did I keep the car ?
Ten people right there.
Ten people.
Ten more people.
This pin.
Two people.
This is gold.
Two more people.
He would have given me
two for it; at least one.
He would have given me one,
one more.
One more person.
A person, Stern.
For this.
[ Sobbing ]
I could have gotten...
one more person
and I didn't.
And I-I didn't !
[ Loud Sobbing ]
[ Sobbing Continues ]
[ Door Closes ]
[ Horse Snorts ]
You have been liberated...
by the Soviet Army !
Have you been
in Poland ?
I just came from Poland.
Are there
anyJews left ?
[ Horse Snorts ]
Where should we go ?
[ Russian Officer ]
Don't go east, that's for sure.
They hate you there.
I wouldn't go west either,
if I were you.
We could use some food.
Isn't that a town
over there ?