I knew Harvey Dent.
I was his friend.
And it will be a very long time before
someone inspires us the way he did.
I believed in Harvey Dent.
Dr. Pavel, I'm CIA.
He wasn't alone.
- Uh, you don't get to bring friends.
- They are not my friends.
Don't worry, no charge for them.
- CIA OP: And why would I want them?
- They were trying to grab your prize.
They work for the mercenary.
The masked man.
- Bane?
- Aye.
Get them on board. I'll call it in.
CIA OP: The flight plan I
just filed with the agency...
...lists me, my men,
Dr. Pavel here...
...but only one of you!
First one to talk gets
to stay on my aircraft!
Who paid you to grab Dr. Pavel?
He didn't fly so good!
Who wants to try next?
Tell me about Bane!
Why does he wear the mask?
A lot of loyalty for a hired gun!
Well, perhaps he's wondering why
someone would shoot a man...
...before throwing
him out of a plane.
At least you can talk.
Who are you?
It doesn't matter who we are.
What matters is our plan.
No one cared who I was
till I put on the mask.
If I pull that off, will you die?
It would be extremely painful.
You're a big guy.
For you.
Was getting caught
part of your plan?
Of course.
Dr. Pavel refused our
offer in favor of yours.
- We had to find out what he told you--
- Nothing. I said nothing.
Well, congratulations,
you got yourself caught!
- Sir?
- Now what's the next step of your master plan?
Crashing this plane...
...with no survivors.
Mayday, Mayday!
Aah! What you doing to me?
Let me out!
No!
No, no, no! No!
No! They expect one of us
in the wreckage, brother.
Have we started the fire?
Yes, the fire rises.
Calm down, doctor.
Now is not the time for fear.
That comes later.
OR: Harvey Dent Day may not be
our oldest public holiday.
...but we're here tonight because
it's one of the most important.
Harvey Dent's uncompromising stand
against organized crime.-.
...had made Gotham a safer place than it was
at the time of his death, eight years ago.
This city has seen a
historic turnaround.
No city is without crime, but
this city is without organized
crime because the Dent Act...
...gave law enforcement teeth
in its fight against the mob.
Now people are talking about
repealing the Dent Act...
...and to them I say,
"Not on my watch."
I want to thank the Wayne
Foundation for hosting this event.
I'm told Mr. Wayne couldn't be here tonight.
I'm sure he's with us in spirit.
And now I'm gonna give way
to an important voice...
You ever lay eyes on Wayne
at one of these things?
No one has. Not in years.
--people put their faith in a
murderous thug in a mask and a cape.
A thug who showed
his true nature...
...when he betrayed the
trust of this great man...
...and murdered him in cold blood.
Sweetheart,
not so fast with the chow.
- Shrimp balls?
- Thank you.
Jim Gordon can tell you the truth about
Harvey Dent. I'll let him tell you himself.
Commissioner Gordon.
The truth?
I have...
...written a speech...
...telling the truth
about Harvey Dent.
Maybe the time isn't right.
Maybe right now...
...all you need to know is that there are...
...1000 inmates in Blackgate Prison
as a direct result of the Dent Act.
These are violent criminals, essential
cogs in the organized-crime machine.
Maybe, for now, all I should say about
the death of Harvey Dent is this:
It has not been for nothing.
MAID 1: You see the guy who owns the house?
MAID 2: No. I heard...
-...he never leaves the east wing.
- I heard he had an accident.
- Yeah, that he's disfigured. He has to wear a--
- Mr. Till?
Why are your people using
the main staircase?
And where's Mrs. Bolton?
Uh, she's at the bar, sir.
Can I help?
The east drawing room.
Unlock the door, put the tray on the table,
lock the door again. Nothing more.
ED: I'm sorry, Miss Tate I tried,
but he won't see you.
And you mustn't take it personally.
Everyone knows that Wayne's holed
up in there with 8-inch nails...
...peeing into Mason jars.
It's very good of you to
let me on the grounds.
Why are you wasting your time
trying to talk to a man...
...who threw away your investment on
some save-the-world vanity project?
He can't get your
money back. I can.
I could try explaining that a
save-the-world project, vain or not...
...is worth investing in,
Mr. Daggett.
But you understand only money and
the power you think it buys...
...so why waste my time indeed?
ON: Second shift reports in?
You should spend more time with the mayor.
Well, that's your department.
Anyone shown him the crime stats?
He goes by his gut and it bothers him,
no matter what the numbers.
- Must be popular with his wife.
- Not really. She took the kids to Cleveland.
He'll have plenty of time for visits.
The mayor's gonna dump him in the spring.
- Really?
- Mm-hm.
- But he's a hero.
- A war hero. This is peacetime.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
I'm so terribly sorry, Mr. Wayne.
It is Mr. Wayne, isn't it?
Although you don't have the long nails or,
heh, the facial scars, sir.
Is that what they say about me?
It's just that no
one ever sees you.
That's a beautiful necklace. Reminds
me of one that belonged to my mother.
It can't be the same one...
...because her pearls
are in this safe...
...the manufacturer
clearly explained...
...is uncrackable.
Oops.
Nobody told me it was uncrackable.
I'm afraid I can't
let you take those.
Look, you wouldn't beat up a woman any
more than I would beat up a cripple.
Of course, sometimes
exceptions have to be made.
Good night, Mr. Wayne.
Can I have a ride?
You read my mind.
Let's go.
Miss Tate was asking
to see you again.
She's very persistent.
And quite lovely,
in case you were wondering.
- I wasn't.
- What are you doing?
Examining print dust. We've been robbed.
And this is your idea of, uh,
sounding the alarm, is it?
She took the pearls,
tracking device and all.
- She?
- One of the maids.
Perhaps you should stop letting
them in this side of the house.
Perhaps you should start
learning to make your own bed.
- Why were you dusting for prints?
- I wasn't.
She was.
Sir. Congressman Gilly's
wife has been calling in.
The congressman never made it home
after the Wayne Foundation event.
That's a job for the police?
When you and Dent cleaned the streets,
you cleaned them good.
Pretty soon we'll be chasing down,
uh, overdue library books.
And yet here you are,
like we're still at war.
- What's your name, son?
- Blake, sir.
You have something
you want to ask me?
It's about that night. This night,
eight years ago. The night Dent died.
The last confirmed
sighting of the Batman.
He murders those people,
takes down two SWAT teams...
...breaks Dent's neck
and then just vanishes?
I'm not hearing a question, son.
Don't you want to know who he was?
I know exactly who he was.
He was the Batman.
Let's go see about the
congressman's wife.
Master Wayne?
You haven't been down
here in a long time.
Trying to find out more about
ourjewel thief. I ran her prints.
Unless she's lost
a lot of weight...
...she was wearing someone
else's fingerprints.
She's good.
She may be, but we have
a trace on the necklace.
We do. I cross-referenced the
address she went back to...
...with police data on
high-end B-and-E's, and, um...
Selina Kyle.
The databases are full of close-calls,
tips from fences.
She's good, but the ground is
shrinking beneath her feet.
We should send the police
before she fences the pearls.
She won't. She likes them too much.
And they weren't
what she was after.
- What was she after?
- My fingerprints.
It was printer toner mixed
with graphite on the safe.
It gives a good pull
and it's untraceable.
Fascinating. You two should
exchange notes over coffee.
You're trying to set me
up with a jewel thief?
At this point, I'd set you up with a chimpanzee,
if it brought you back to the world.
There's nothing out there for me.
And that's the problem.
You hung up your cape and your
cowl but you didn't move on.
You never went to find a life.
To find someone.
Alfred...
...I did find someone.
I know, and you lost them.
But that's all part of living, sir.
But you're not living, you're just waiting,
hoping for things to go bad again.
Remember when you left Gotham?
Before all this, before Batman?
YOU were gone seven years.
Seven years I waited,
hoping that you wouldn't come back.
Every year, I took a holiday.
I went to Florence.
There's this caf?© on the banks of the Arno.
Every fine evening I'd sit there
and order a Fernet Branca.
I had this fantasy...
...that I would look
across the tables...
...and I'd see you there,
with a wife.
Maybe a couple of kids.
You wouldn't say anything to me,
nor me to you.
But we'd both know
that you'd made it.
That you were happy.
I never wanted you to
come back to Gotham.
I always knew there was nothing here
for you, except pain and tragedy.
And I wanted something
more for you than that.
I still do.
DWP MAN: They wash up here a
couple of times a month.
More when it gets colder.
Homeless, sheltering
in the tunnels.
We pulled him from the basin,
but other than that we didn't touch him.
- What?
- Name's Jimmy.
He's from St. Swithin's.
It's the boys' home where I coach some ball.
LY: Jimmy hadn't been around for months.
- No? Why?
- Blake, you know why.
He aged out. We don't have the
resources to keep boys on after 16.
I thought the Wayne Foundation
gave money for that.
Not for the past couple of years.
- He has a brother here, doesn't he?
- Mark. I'll tell him.
I'd like to, if that's all right.
You know what he was doing in the tunnels?
Lot of guys been going down
the tunnels when they age out.
Say you can live down there.
Say there's work down there.
Work?
What kind of work are you
gonna find in the sewers?
More than you can
find up here, I guess.
So you know about him?
Of course.
Do you think he's coming back?
I don't know.
You brought a date?
I like having someone
around to open doors for me.
Right hand. No partials.
- Very nice.
- Mm-hm.
Not so fast, handsome.
You got something for me?
Ah, yes.
I don't know what you're planning
to do with Mr. Wayne's prints...
...but I'm guessing
you'll need his thumb.
You don't count so good, huh?
I count fine.
In fact, I'm counting
to 10 right now.
Okay.
My friend's outside.
Just hit "send."
This place is a little dead.
It'll liven up in a minute.
Trust me.
Is everything okay?
Great. Catch you later.
Hmm.
It would have been a lot easier...
...to just give me what we agreed.
We can't have loose ends.
And even in that dress,
no one's gonna miss you.
No.
But my friend over there?
Every cop in the
city's missing him.
That's cute.
But they're not gonna be
looking in a place like this.
I don't know. You did
just use his cell phone.
SWAT 1: Go! SWAT 2: Go!
Police! Get down now!
Help me! Help me!
Help me, please! Please help me!
Keep some pressure on that,
sweetheart.
Call me?
- You okay, miss?
- He's bleeding. You gotta help him.
I got the congressman.
Clear!
Manhole! Get this up! Get the DWP down here!
You three, down with me.
You two, you go down, cover the next exit!
What, they went down there?
- We're gonna go down there, right?
- That was a gas explosion, kid.
- Wasn't gas. It's a sewer.
- No one goes in till we know what's there.
We know, sir.
The police commissioner.
Someone get this
hothead out of here?
And where's that DWP guy?
Why are you here?
Answer him.
I was asking you.
It's the police commissioner.
And you brought him down here?
- MERCENARY 1: We didn't know what to do.
- You panicked.
And your weakness has cost
the lives of three others.
No, he's alone.
Search him.
Then I will kill you.
- He's dead.
- So show me his body.
The water runs to any one of the outflows.
We'd never find him.
Follow him! MERCENARY 2: Follow him?
You okay? You okay?
Hey, hey, you awake?
I need to see Bruce Wayne.
I'm sorry, Mr. Wayne doesn't
take unscheduled calls.
Even from a police officer.
And if I go get a warrant for the
investigation of Harvey Dent's murder?
That still count as unscheduled?
What can I do for you, officer?
Commissioner Gordon's been shot.
He chased a gunman down into the sewers.
When I pulled him out, he was
babbling about an underground army.
A masked man called Bane.
Shouldn't you be telling
your superior officers?
They asked me if he saw
any giant alligators.
He needs you.
He needs the Batman.
- If Commissioner Gordon thinks--
- Oh, he doesn't know or care who you are.
But we've met before.
It was a long time ago.
I was a kid. Uh, St. Swithin's.
It used to be funded by the Wayne
Foundation. It's an orphanage.
My mom died when I was small. It was a
car accident, I don't really remember it.
But my dad got shot a couple years
later over a gambling debt...
...and I remember
that one just fine.
Not a lot of people know
what it feels like, do they?
To be angry...
...in your bones.
I mean, they understand.
Foster parents.
Everybody understands...
...for a while.
And then they want the angry little kid
to do something he knows he can't do.
Move on.
So after a while, they stop understanding.
They send the angry
kid to a boys' home.
I figured it out too late.
You gotta learn to hide the anger.
Practice smiling in a mirror.
It's like putting on a mask.
So you showed up this one day,
in a cool car.
Pretty girl on your arm.
We were so excited.
Bruce Wayne, billionaire orphan.
I mean, we used to make up
stories about you, man. Legends.
And, you know, with the other kids,
that's all it was, just stories, but...
Right when I saw you,
I knew who you really were.
I'd seen that look
on your face before.
It's the same one I taught myself.
I don't know why you took the
fall for Dent's murder...
...but I'm still a
believer in the Batman...
...even if you're not.
Why did you say that your boys' home used
to be funded by the Wayne Foundation?
Because the money stopped.
Might be time to get some fresh air.
Start paying attention to the details.
Some of those details might need your help.
You check that name? Bane?
He's a mercenary. No other known names.
Him and his men were behind
a coup in West Africa...
...that secured mining operations
for our friend John Daggett.
- Now Daggett's brought them here.
- Or so it seems.
- I'll keep digging.
- Yeah.
Alfred, why did the Wayne Foundation
stop funding boys' homes in the city?
The foundation is funded by the
profits of Wayne Enterprises.
There have to be some.
- Time to talk to Mr. Fox, I think.
- I'll get him on the phone.
No, no, no. Do we still have
any cars around the place?
Yes. One or two.
I need an appointment at
the hospital for my leg.
- Which hospital?
- Whichever one Jim Gordon's in.
- I have seen worse cartilage in knees.
- That's good.
No. That's because there is
no cartilage in your knee.
And not much of any use in
your elbows or your shoulders.
Between that and the scar
tissue on your kidneys...
...the residual concussive
damage to your brain tissue...
...and the general scarred-over
quality of your body...
-...I cannot recommend that you go heli-skiing.
- Right.
We were in this together...
...then you were gone.
The Batman wasn't needed anymore.
- We won.
- Based on a lie.
And now there's evil rising
from where we tried to bury it.
The Batman has to come back.
What if he doesn't exist anymore?
He must.
You took my goddamn wallet,
didn't you?
- You f-- You took my wallet!
- No, I--
- Get out.
- She took my-- Ah!
- Now.
- Creep!
I don't know what he's so upset about.
There's only 60 bucks in here.
Probably the watch.
Who's that?
A stiff can barely climb
out of his sports car.
- No, that's Bruce Wayne!
- Mr. Wayne, over here!
- I'm not sure if my assistant--
- Right through here.
Thank you so much.
Bruce Wayne at a charity ball.
Miss Tate, isn't it?
Even before you became a recluse,
you never came to these things.
The proceeds go to the big fat spread.
It's not about charity.
It's about feeding the ego of
whichever society hag laid this on.
Actually, this is my party,
Mr. Wayne.
Oh.
And the proceeds will go where
they should, because I paid
for the big fat spread myself.
That's very generous of you.
You have to invest if you want
to restore balance to the world.
Take our clean-energy project.
Sometimes the investment doesn't pay off.
- I'm sorry.
- You have a practiced apathy, Mr. Wayne.
But a man who doesn't care about the world
doesn't spend half his fortune to save it.
And isn't so wounded
when it fails...
...that he goes into hiding.
Have a good evening, Mr. Wayne.
Mind if I cut in?
Thank you.
- You don't seem happy to see me.
- You were supposed to be a shut-in.
I felt like some fresh air.
Why didn't you call the police?
I have a powerful friend who
deals with things like this.
That's a brazen costume
for a cat burglar.
Yeah? Who are you pretending to be?
Bruce Wayne, eccentric billionaire.
- Who's your date?
- His wife's in Ibiza.
She left her diamonds behind, though.
Worried they might get stolen.
It's pronounced "Ibiza
You wouldn't want these folks realizing
you're a crook, not a social climber.
You think I care what anyone
in this room thinks of me?
I doubt you care what anyone
in any room thinks of you.
Don't condescend, Mr. Wayne.
You don't know a thing about me.
Well, Selina Kyle, I know you came
here from your walk-up in Old Town.
A modest place for a
master jewel thief.
Which means that either you're
saving for retirement...
...or you're in deep
with the wrong people.
You don't get to judge me because you were
born in the master bedroom of Wayne Manor.
- Actually, I was born in the Regency Room.
- I started out doing what I had to.
Once you've done what you had to,
they never let you do what you want to.
Start fresh.
Ugh. There's no fresh
start in today's world.
Any 12-year-old with a cell phone
could find out what you did.
Everything we do is collated and
quantified. Everything sticks.
Is that how you justify stealing?
I take what I need from those
who have more than enough.
I don't stand on the shoulders
of people with less.
Robin Hood?
I think I'd do more to help someone than
most of the people in this room. Than you.
You think maybe you're
assuming a little too much?
Maybe you're being unrealistic about what's
really in your pants other than your wallet.
Ouch.
You think all this can last?
There's a storm coming, Mr. Wayne.
You and your friends better batten down
the hatches, because when it hits...
...you're all gonna wonder how you
ever thought you could live so large...
...and leave so little
for the rest of us.
You sound like you're looking forward to it.
I'm adaptable.
Those pearls do look better on
you than they did in my safe.
But I still can't
let you keep them.
You-- You scared her off!
Not likely.
Must have lost my ticket.
- Your wife said you were taking a cab home.
- My wife?
Just you, sir?
Don't worry, Master Wayne.
Takes a little time to get
back in the swing of things.
Bruce Wayne, as I live and breathe.
What brings you out of
cryo-sleep, Mr. Wayne?
You haven't lost
your sense of humor.
Even if you have lost
most of my money.
Actually, you did that.
If you funnel your
entire R and D budget...
...into a fusion project
that you then mothball...
...your company is
unlikely to thrive.
What are my options?
Well, if you're unwilling
to turn on the machine...
I can't. I can't, Lucius.
Well, then sit tight.
Your majority keeps
Daggett at bay...
...while we figure out a future for
the energy program with Miranda Tate.
She has supported the project all the way.
She's smart. And quite lovely.
We all just want what's
best for you, Bruce.
Show her the machine.
I'll think it over.
Anything else?
Nope. WW?
These conversations used to
end with an unusual request.
I retired.
Mm-hm. Well, let me show
you some stuff anyway.
Just for old times' sake.
I figured you'd have shut this place down.
Oh, it was always shut down,
officially.
All this new stuff.
After your father died, Wayne Enterprises
set up 14 different defense subsidiaries.
For years, I've been
shuttering and consolidating...
...all the different
prototypes under one roof.
- My roof.
- Why?
Keep them from falling into the wrong hands.
Oh, now you're just showing off.
Defense Department projects for
tight geometry urban pacification.
Rotors are configured to maneuver
between buildings without recirculation.
What's it called?
Oh, it has a long, uninteresting
Wayne Enterprises designation.
I just took to calling it the Bat.
And, yes, Mr. Wayne,
it does come in black.
Works fine,
except for the autopilot.
Takes a better mind
than mine to fix it.
Better mind?
Well, I was trying to be modest.
A less busy mind.
Yours.
- Is it really painful?
- You're very welcome to try it, Alfred.
Happy watching. Thank you, sir.
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
If you're seriously considering
going back out there...
...you should hear the
rumors surrounding Bane.
I'm all ears.
There is a prison in a more
ancient part of the world.
A pit where men are
thrown to suffer and die.
But sometimes a man rises from the darkness.
Sometimes the pit
sends something back.
- Bane.
Born and raised in hell on earth.
- Born in a prison?
- No one knows why, or how he escaped.
But they do know
that once he did...
...he was trained by Ra's Al Ghul,
your mentor.
Bane was a member of the League of Shadows?
And then he was excommunicated.
And any man who is too extreme for
Ra's Al Ghul is not to be trifled with.
I didn't realize I was known
for trifling with criminals.
That was then.
And you can strap up your leg
and put your mask back on...
...but that doesn't make you what you were.
If this man is everything that you
say he is, then the city needs me.
The city needs Bruce Wayne.
Your resources. Your knowledge.
It doesn't need your body,
or your life.
That time's past.
You're afraid that if I go
back out there, I'll fail.
No.
I'm afraid that you want to.
You can't short the stock because
Bruce Wayne goes to a party.
Wayne coming back is change.
Change is either good or bad. I vote bad.
On what basis?
I flipped a coin.
It says rye-- I said no rye, man.
Hey, rookie, lose the helmet.
We need faces for camera.
Come on. Let's go scalping.
Come on.
Everybody down, now!
This is a stock exchange.
There's no money you can steal.
Really? Then why are
you people here?
SECURITY CHIEF: Everybody,
stay back! Go down to the end of the block!
We have an emergency situation!
You gotta get in there!
This is a hostage situation.
No, this is a robbery. They have direct
access to the online trading desk.
I'm not risking my
men for your money.
We have to ask you to move.
We have a situation.
It's not our money,
it's everybody's.
Really? Mine's in my mattress.
You don't put these guys down,
that stuffing in your mattress
might be worth a whole lot less.
Cut the fiber cable and
take out that cell tower.
- SECURITY CHIEF: Thank you.
- That'll slow them down.
Move back!
All the way! Go! Sir,
get back, please!
They cut the fiber.
Cell's working.
For now.
Get all these barriers up. All
of them up. No one gets in or
out of any of these streets.
Where am I supposed to move it?
Back it up.
All right, just stay
in your vehicle, okay?
How much longer does the program need?
Eight minutes.
Time to go mobile.
Everybody, up!
You two, move!
Thank you.
Steady.
I've got something.
Hold your fire,
they've got hostages.
Hold your fire!
Go. go!
Please! Just let me go!
Hey, please! Hey!
Shoot the tires.
There's no shot.
Now back off. Back off,
they've got hostages.
MAN --P.D. are pursuing the four
suspects through downtown...
...in response to a
hostage situation.
What's going on with the lights?
It can't be.
What the hell was that?
Oh, boy, you are in for a show tonight, son.
Please! Help, help, help!
Sorry
Put that thing away before
you hurt yourself. Get in!
Let's go. You, get in the car.
They've spotted the Batman.
Call everyone in. Every car patrol,
beat cop, off-duty too.
Pull them in now. I'm gonna do
what Jim Gordon never could.
- What's that?
- I'm gonna take down the Batman.
MAN 1 --are confirming four suspects
are carrying two hostages...
...kidnapped from the Gotham Stock Exchange.
Reports from the eyewitnesses-- MAN 2:
Scott, dead center of your screen.
MAN 1: What do you see? MAN 2: I see Batman.
MAN 1: Hard to believe, but the
suspects are now being pursued...
...by what appears to
be the Batman.
Well, what do you know?
Sir, what about the armed robbers?
Please! Just let me go! Please!
SPOTTER One bike's pulled off.
No hostage. Should we pursue?
Negative. Stay on the Batman.
- He's getting away.
- Who do you wanna catch?
Some robber, or the son of a
bitch who killed Harvey Dent?
MAN 1 --the entire upper west hill...
Central Heights and East Park Side areas.
Eight years,
and he has to pick tonight.
He's drawing the cops off Bane.
Please! Just let me go!
Please!
COP We lost him.
How could you lose him?
OP: He's got a lot of firepower.
What, and you don't?
OP: He's heading back downtown.
Then he's as dumb as he dresses.
Close it off, gentlemen.
Like a rat in a trap, gentlemen.
You might have the wrong animal there, sir.
You sure it was him?
ER: Bane says the Batman interfered,
but the task was accomplished.
What about the men they arrested?
He said, and I quote,
â?oThey would die before talking."
Where does he find these guys?
Open the champagne.
And can we get some girls in here?
Careful what you wish for.
Cat got your tongue?
You dumb bitch.
Nobody ever accused me of being dumb.
You're dumb for
coming here tonight.
I want what you owe me.
Want doesn't get.
Nice outfit. Those heels
make it tough to walk?
- I don't know.
- Aah!
Do they?
- So where is it?
- Where's what?
The program. The "clean slate."
The ultimate tool for a
master thief with a record.
Hold it right there!
Where is it?
The clean slate?
Where you type in someone's name,
date of birth...
...in a few minutes they're gone
from every database on earth?
- Sound a little too good to be true?
- You're lying!
Rykin Data took it
to prototype stage.
That's why I bought them.
But they had nothing.
It was a gangland myth.
Stay back!
I'm not bluffing!
They know.
They just don't care.
You've gotta be kidding me.
- No guns. No killing.
- Where's the fun in that?
My mother warned me about getting
into cars with strange men.
This isn't a car.
See you around.
You're welcome.
I had it under control.
Those weren't street thugs.
They were trained killers.
I saved your life.
In return, I need to know what you
did with Bruce Wayne's fingerprints.
Wayne wasn't kidding
about a powerful friend.
I sold his prints to Daggett...
...for something that
doesn't even exist.
- I doubt many people get the better of you.
- Hey, when a girl's desperate...
- What's he gonna do with them?
- I don't know...
...but Daggett seemed pretty interested
in that mess at the stock market.
Miss Kyle?
So that's what that feels like.
I see from the television coverage that you
got your taste for wanton destruction back.
I retrieved this.
Aren't the police supposed
to be investigating, then?
- They don't have the tools to analyze it.
- They would if you gave them to them.
One man's tool is
another man's weapon.
In your mind, perhaps. But there aren't
many things you can't turn into a weapon.
Alfred, enough. The police
weren't getting it done.
Perhaps they might have if you
hadn't made a sideshow of yourself.
- You thought I didn't have it in me.
- You led a bloated police force on a chase...
...with a load of fancy
new toys from Fox.
What about when you come
up against him? What then?
- I'll fight harder. I always have.
- Look. His speed, his ferocity, his training.
I see the power of belief.
I see the League of
Shadows resurgent.
You said he was excommunicated.
By Ra's AI Ghul.
Who leads them now?
Ra's Al Ghul was the League
of Shadows and I beat him.
Bane is a mercenary.
We need to find out what he's up to.
Trades of some kind. Coded.
And my fingerprint,
courtesy of Selina Kyle.
Get this to Fox.
He can crack the code and tell us
what trades they were executing.
I'll get this to Mr. Fox,
but no more.
I've sewn you up, I've set your bones,
but I won't bury you.
I've buried enough members
of the Wayne family.
- You'll leave me?
- You see only one end to your journey.
Leaving is all I have
to make you understand.
You're not Batman anymore.
You have to find another way.
You used to talk about finishing,
about a life beyond that awful cave.
Alfred, Rachel died knowing that
we had decided to be together.
That was my life beyond the cave.
I can't just move on.
She-- She didn't. She couldn't.
What if she had?
She-- I can't change that.
What if before she died
she wrote a letter...
...saying she chose Harvey Dent over you?
And what if...
...to spare you pain...
...I burnt that letter?
How dare you use Rachel
to try to stop me?
I am using the truth, Master Wayne.
Maybe it's time we all stopped trying to
outsmart the truth and let it have its day.
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
You expect to destroy my world...
...and then think that
we're gonna shake hands?
No, no, no.
I know what this means.
What does it mean?
It means your hatred.
And it also means losing someone
that I have cared for...
...since I first heard
his cries echo...
...through this house.
But it might also
mean saving your life.
And that is more important.
Goodbye, Alfred.
Alfred?
- Answering your own door?
- Yeah.
Page three.
Seems you made a series of large put
options on the futures exchange...
...verified by thumbprint.
Those options expired
at midnight last night.
Long-term, we may be able to prove fraud.
But for now, you're completely broke...
...and Wayne Enterprises is about to
fall into the hands of John Daggett.
The weapons. We can't let Daggett
get his hands on Applied Sciences.
Applied Sciences is all
locked up and off the books.
The energy project, however,
is a different story.
Miranda Tate.
Let's convince the board to get behind her.
Let's show her the reactor.
We're meeting her there in 35 minutes,
so you better get dressed.
You brought me out here
to show me this, Mr. Fox?
Bear with me, Miss Tate.
Please keep hands and feet
inside the car at all times.
This is it, isn't it?
The reactor is beneath the river...
...so it can be instantly flooded
in the event of a security breach.
Is Bruce Wayne
really that paranoid?
I'm gonna plead the
fifth on that one.
I thought you might like to see
what your investment built.
No fossil fuels.
Free clean energy
for an entire city.
DA: Three years ago, a Russian
scientist published a paper...
...on weaponized fusion reactions.
One week later, your reactor
started developing problems.
I think this machine works.
Miranda, if it were operational,
the danger to Gotham would be too great.
Would it make you feel better to
know that the Russian scientist...
...died in a plane
crash six months ago?
Someone will work out
what Dr. Pavel did.
Someone will figure out a way to make
this power source into a nuclear weapon.
I need you to take control
of Wayne Enterprises...
...and this reactor.
To do what with it?
Nothing.
Until we can guarantee its safety.
And if we can't?
Decommission it. Flood it.
Destroy the world's best chance
for a sustainable future?
If the world's not ready, yes.
Bruce, if you want to save the world,
you have to start trusting it.
I'm trusting you.
Doesn't count. You have no choice.
I could have flooded
this chamber at any time.
I'm choosing to trust you.
Please.
All right, ladies and gentlemen.
This meeting will now come to order.
I'd like to point out that we
have a non-board member here...
...which is highly irregular,
even if his family name is above the door.
Bruce Wayne's family
built this company.
And he himself has run it.
Into the ground, sir! Does anybody disagree?
Check the share price this morning.
Crazy gambling on futures has not
only cost Mr. Wayne his seat...
...it's cost us all a lot of money.
And he has to go.
I'm afraid he has a point,
Mr. Wayne.
Now, back to business.
MAN 1: Mr. Wayne, over here! MAN 2:
How's it feel to be one of the people?
Mr. Wayne, they're towing your car! I
didn't know what to do, they had paperwork.
Looks like you need a ride, huh?
Wayne, we'll give you a ride!
How the hell did Miranda Tate get
the inside track on the Wayne board?
She been meeting with him?
Sleeping with him?
- Not that we know of.
- You don't know much of anything, do you?
- Where's Bane?
- We told him it was urgent.
- Where is that masked--?
- Speak of the devil...
...and he shall appear.
What the hell is going on?
- The plan is proceeding as expected.
- Oh, really?
Do I look like I'm running
Wayne Enterprises right now?
Your hit on the stock exchange,
it didn't work, my friend.
And now you have my construction crews
going around the city at 24 hours a day.
How exactly is that supposed to
help my company absorb Wayne's?
- Leave us.
- No. You stay here.
I'm in charge.
Do you feel in charge?
I've paid you a small fortune.
And this gives you power over me?
What is this?
Your money and infrastructure
have been important...
...till now.
What are you?
I'm Gotham's reckoning.
Here to end the borrowed time
you've all been living on.
You're pure evil.
I'm necessary evil.
No. No, no, no!
When you started, why the mask?
- To protect the people closest to me.
- But you were a loner, right?
- You didn't have any family?
- There are always people you care about.
You just don't realize how
much until they're gone.
The idea was to be a symbol.
Batman could be anybody.
That was the point.
- Well, it was damn good to see him back.
- Not everybody agrees.
- They'll figure that out in the end.
- You got anything on Bane's whereabouts?
Yeah. I got 500 pages of tunnel
records and a flashlight.
I could use some help, actually.
You know what? Drop me in Old Town.
Hey, hey, hey. I don't think so!
- That's the way this works!
- I don't think so!
- That is the way--
- He's not a mark.
And he doesn't have a
cent to his name, anyway.
Yeah, it's not much. But it's
more than you've got right now.
Actually, they're letting
me keep the house.
The rich don't even go broke the
same as the rest of us, huh?
My powerful friend might hope to
change your mind about leaving.
- And how would he do that?
- By giving you what you want.
- It doesn't exist.
- He says it does.
He wants to meet tonight.
Why?
He needs to find Bane. Says you'd know how.
- Tell him I'll think about it.
- Okay.
I like your place.
MT. Wayne?
I'm sorry they took all your money.
No, you're not.
- Can we help you, officer?
- Uh, yeah.
John Daggett's body was just found
in a Dumpster about an hour ago.
- Thought you might want to know.
- Why?
His name's all over these permits I just
pulled to, uh, map the tunnels under Gotham.
That's MTA maintenance, uh,
sewer construction, couple of other things.
Where did you get to
with the tunnel searches?
Remind me to tell detail
to keep hotheads out.
We've had teams down there.
It's a huge network.
Well, get more men.
Work a grid. I want him found.
Yeah, the, uh, masked man.
We're on it.
Lose the uniform, you're working for me now.
We could use some hotter heads around here.
- Sir, that could also be a coincidence.
- You're a detective now, son.
You're not allowed to believe
in coincidence anymore.
Nobody's answering.
No.
I'm on my own now.
Do you have keys?
Never needed them.
Hope you didn't like
me for my money.
Suffering builds character.
I'll take care of your
parents' legacy, Bruce.
Who's this?
Where's Alfred?
He left...
...taking everything.
What's that?
My power's been shut off.
You're good at that.
When I was a child, we had almost nothing.
But on the nights when we had a fire,
we felt very rich indeed.
I assumed your family was wealthy.
Not always.
Not when I was young.
An old mistake.
I've made a few myself.
More than a few.
We could leave.
Tonight.
Take my plane,
go anywhere we wanted.
Someday, perhaps.
Not tonight.
Don't be shy.
Wayne says you can get me the clean slate.
- That depends.
- On what?
On what you want it for.
I acquired it to keep it
out of the wrong hands.
Still don't trust me, huh?
How can we change that?
Start by taking me to Bane.
You asked.
From here, Bane's men patrol the tunnels.
And they're not your
average brawlers.
Neither am I.
- He's behind you.
- Who?
Me.
What do you think you're--?
Just a little further.
I had to find a way to stop
them trying to kill me.
You made a serious mistake.
Not as serious as yours, I fear.
Bane.
Let's not stand on ceremony here...
...Mr. Wayne.
Peace has cost you your strength.
Victory has defeated you.
Theatricality and deception,
powerful agents to the uninitiated.
But we are initiated,
aren't we, Bruce?
Members of the League of Shadows.
And you betrayed us.
"Us"? You were excommunicated...
by a gang of psychopaths.
I am the League of Shadows.
And I'm here to fulfill
Ra's Al Ghul's destiny.
You fight like a younger man.
Nothing held back.
Admirable, but mistaken.
Oh, you think
darkness is your ally?
But you merely adopted the dark.
I was born in it.
Molded by it.
I didn't see the light
until I was already a man.
By then, it was nothing to me but blinding!
The shadows betray you
because they belong to me!
I will show you where I have made my home...
...whilst preparing
to bring justice.
Then I will break you.
Your precious armory.
Gratefully accepted.
We will need it.
Ah, yes. I was wondering
what would break first.
Your spirit...
...or your body.
Get me Commissioner Gordon. I got a
line on the congressman's kidnapping.
- Excuse me, miss.
- Uh, yes?
I'm gonna need to see your ticket
and identification, please.
Oh. Do you mind?
I showed your picture to the
congressman. Guess what.
Don't tell me. Still in love?
Oh, head over heels.
Pressing charges, though.
You've made some mistakes,
Ms. Kyle.
- Girl's gotta eat.
- And you have an appetite.
Why would you run? You can't
hide with a record like this.
Maybe it's not you
I'm running from.
Who then? Bane?
What do you know about him?
That you should be as afraid of him as I am.
We can offer you protection.
Okay.
When I spotted you, I was looking
for a friend of mine. Bruce Wayne.
Did they kill him?
I'm not sure.
Why didn't you just...
...kill me?
You don't fear death,
you welcome it.
Your punishment
must be more severe.
Torture?
Yes.
But not of your body.
Of your soul.
Where am I?
Home.
Where I learned the
truth about despair.
As will you.
There is a reason why this prison
is the worst hell on earth:
Hope.
Every man who has rotted
here over the centuries...
...has looked up to the light and
imagined climbing to freedom.
So easy.
So simple.
And like shipwrecked men turning to
seawater from uncontrollable thirst...
...many have died trying.
I learned here there can be
no true despair without hope.
So as I terrorize Gotham...
...I will feed its people
hope to poison their souls.
I will let them believe
that they can survive...
...so that you can watch them clambering
over each other to stay in the sun.
You can watch me
torture an entire city.
And then when you have truly
understood the depth of your failure...
...we will fulfill
Ra's Al Ghul's destiny.
We will destroy Gotham.
And then, when it is done...
...and Gotham is...
...ashes...
...then you have my
permission to die.
You're locking her up in here?
The Dent Act allows non-segregation
based on extraordinary need.
First time she broke out of
women's correctional, she was 16.
Little closer, baby.
Why, honey? You wanna hold my hand?
She's gonna be fine.
I still don't see the need of a board
meeting for the energy project.
Bruce got a lot of things right.
Keeping the board in the
dark was not one of them.
How good of you to join us.
Chair. President.
All I need now is one more
ordinary board member.
Mr. Fox, would you
like to nominate?
No.
I will volunteer.
Where are you taking us?
You were right, commissioner.
Will you excuse us, please?
What happened?
Your masked man kidnapped
the Wayne Enterprises board.
He let most of them go,
but he took three into the sewers.
No more patrols.
No more hide and seek.
Get every available cop down
there and smoke him out!
The mayor won't want panic.
So it's a training exercise.
I'm sorry I didn't
take you seriously.
Not you.
You're telling me
the Batman's gone...
...so you chase up the Daggett
leads any way you can.
Yes, sir.
He asks how much you would
pay us to let you die.
I told him. I told
him you have nothing.
Do it for the pleasure.
They pay me more than
that to keep you alive.
He will try the climb.
Has anyone ever made it?
Of course not.
He says there is one who did.
A child.
A child born in this hell
Bane.
An old legend. Nothing more.
Don't.
Whatever it is they want you to see,
it's happening soon.
Fire in the hole!
Turn it on.
I only need one other board member.
There are eight others waiting.
I won't do it.
All right, stop.
Lucius, you'll kill this man,
and yourself...
...and you'll barely
slow them down.
Go on, then. Do your work.
Take them up to the surface.
People of their status...
...deserve to experience the
next era of western civilization.
KE: I've been to half of Daggett's
cement plants and locations
they poured underground.
GORDON Anything strange about the pourings?
Honestly, commissioner, I don't know
anything about civil engineering.
But you know about patterns. Keep looking.
L: It's done
This is now a 4-megaton
nuclear bomb.
Pull the core out of the reactor.
No, you cannot.
This is the only power source
capable of sustaining it.
If you move it, the core will
decay in a matter of months.
Five, by my calculations.
And then it will go off!
And for the sake of your children,
Dr. Pavel...
...indeed I hope it does.
Hey. Hey!
That was you in front of the
stock exchange, wasn't it?
- When?
When cops were trying to pull onto Castle
Street and your truck was shutting them out.
- Oh, yeah. You're the cop.
- Detective now.
And, uh, as a detective, we're not
allowed to believe in coincidence.
What were you doing here?
What are you working on?
Commissioner, it's Blake.
I got two dead witnesses and a lot
of questions. Call me whenev--
Wait a minute. I'm looking at
four barrels of polyisobutylene.
That looks like motor
oil right next to it.
Jesus, they're not making cement.
They're making explosives.
- - Patch me in to Foley.
Foley's overseeing the operation.
They're heading into a trap!
ER: We're seeing thousands of police
heading into the sewers.
- Mr. Mayor? Literally thousands.
- It's a training exercise, that's all.
Now if you'll excuse me, I've got tickets
to watch our boys thrash Rapid City.
- - Foley. - It's a trap!
Pull everyone out!
Bane has been pouring concrete...
-...laced with explosives!
- Where?
Oh, say, can you see By the
dawn's early light
What so proudly we hailed
At the twilight's...
KE: There's a ring around the
tunnels! They'll blow it and
trap the cops underground!
Pull them out. Pull them out now!
ER: Through the perilous fight
O'er the ramparts we watched
Were so gallantly streaming
And the rockets' red glare
The bombs bursting in air
Gave proof through--
That's a lovely, lovely voice.
--That our ï¬,ag was still there
Oh, say does that star-spangled
banner Yet wave
O'er the land of the free
And the home of the brave
Let the games begin.
Everybody okay?
COP 2: Let's move! Move,
move! COP 3: Go, go!
Gotham...
...take control.
Take control of your city.
- Foley.
- Jesus, Blake.
Every cop in the city's
in those tunnels.
Not every cop.
Sir, are you okay? I'm a police officer.
I need your car right now.
Clear the corners, rookie.
Get my coat, son.
This...
This is the instrument
of your liberation.
Satellite shows a radiation spike.
Whatever it is, it's nuclear.
Identify yourself to the world.
Dr. Leonid Pavel,
nuclear physicist.
Pavel was confirmed dead.
Plane crash on an agency pull
out of Uzbekistan, but...
It looks like it's him.
And what...? What is this?
It's a fully primed neutron bomb...
...with a blast
radius of six miles.
And who is capable of
disarming such a device?
Only me.
Only you.
Thank you, good doctor!
Now, this bomb is armed!
And this bomb is mobile!
And the identity of the
triggerman is a mystery.
For one of you holds the detonator!