Now, we come here not as conquerors...
...but as liberators, to return
control of this city to the people.
And at the first sign of interference
from the outside world...
...or from those people
attempting to flee...
...this anonymous Gothamite...
...this unsung hero,
will trigger the bomb.
For now, martial law is in effect.
Return to your homes,
hold your families close...
...and wait.
Tomorrow, you claim what
is rightfully yours.
Pull back the fighters.
Start high-level
reconnaissance flights.
Get the president on the line.
MERCENARY 1: Tanks and planes cannot
stop us from detonating our device.
Send an emissary to discuss terms of
access for supplies and communication.
How many of you are there, son?
You don't have enough men to stop 12
million people from leaving this island.
No. No, we don't.
But you do.
Now, why the hell would I try
to help you keep your hostages?
If one person crosses
this bridge...
...Gotham gets blown to hell.
The people of our greatest
city are resilient.
They have proven this before,
and they will prove it again.
We do not negotiate with
terrorists...
...but we do recognize realities.
As this situation develops...
...one thing must be understood
above all others.
People of Gotham, we have not abandoned you.
What does that mean?
It means we're on our own.
I have to get in front of a camera.
They will kill you the
second you show your face.
Bane says he's giving Gotham back to the
people. They need to know I could lead.
Bane's not gonna let that happen.
Then he'll show his true colors.
And you'll be dead.
Behind you stands a
symbol of oppression.
Blackgate Prison...
...where a thousand
men have languished...
Harvey Dent.
Who has been held up to you...
...as the shining example
of justice!
We're just gonna keep moving you till
we can get you in front of the camera.
You have been supplied with
a false idol to stop you...
...tearing down this corrupt city!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Let me tell you the
truth about Harvey Dent.
From the words of Gotham's
police commissioner...
on:
The Batman didn't murder
Harvey Dent
He saved my boy...
...then took the blame for
Harvey's appalling crimes...
...so that I could, to my shame...
...build a lie around this...
...fallen idol.
I praised the madman who tried
to murder my own child.
Well, I can no longer
live with my lie.
It is time to trust the people
of Gotham with the truth...
...and it is time
for me to resign."
And do you accept this
man's resignation?
And do you accept the resignation
of all of these liars?
Of all the corrupt?
KE: Those men locked up for eight
years in Blackgate...
...and denied parole under the Dent Act,
it was based on a lie.
Gotham needed a hero.
Well, it needs it now more than ever,
but you betrayed everything you stood for.
There's a point far out there
when the structures fail you...
...when the rules aren't
weapons anymore...
...they're shackles,
letting the bad guy get ahead.
One day, you may face...
...such a moment of crisis.
And in that moment, I hope you
have a friend like I did...
...to plunge their hands into the filth,
so that you can keep yours clean!
Your hands look plenty
filthy to me, commissioner.
We take Gotham from the corrupt!
The rich!
The oppressors of generations...
...who have kept you down
with myths of opportunity.
And we give it back to you...
...the people.
Gotham is yours!
None shall interfere.
Do as you please.
But start by storming Blackgate
and freeing the oppressed!
Open it!
Step forward,
those who would serve...
...for an army will be raised.
The powerful will be ripped
from their decadent nests...
...and cast out into the cold
world that we know and endure!
Courts will be convened.
Spoils will be enjoyed.
Blood will be shed!
The police will survive...
as they learn to serve true justice
This great city...
...it will endure.
Gotham will survive!
He says you must
first fix your back.
How does he know?
He was the prison doctor.
He's a morphine addict who
incurred the displeasure...
...of powerful people,
including your masked friend.
How?
Many years ago,
it was a time of plague.
Some of the other
prisoners attacked Bane.
The doctor's fumbling attempts
to repair the damage...
...left him in perpetual agony.
The mask holds the pain at bay.
Bane was the child you spoke of?
He was born here?
The legend is that there was a mercenary
who worked for a local warlord.
He fell in love with the warlord's daughter.
They were married in secret.
When the warlord found out...
...the mercenary was
condemned to this pit.
But then he exiled him instead.
The mercenary understood that it was the
daughter who had secured his release.
But what he could not know was the
true price of his freedom.
She took his place in the pit.
And she was with child...
...the mercenary's child.
Innocence cannot flower underground.
It has to be stamped out.
One day, the doctor forgot to lock the cell.
But the child had a friend...
...a protector who showed the others that
this innocence was their redemption.
It was to be prized.
The mother was not so lucky.
This is Bane's prison now.
He wouldn't want this story told.
There's a vertebra
protruding from your back.
It has to be put back.
Stay like this until you stand.
RA'S AL GHUL: Tsk, tsk, tsk. Did you
not think I would return, Bruce? Hmm?
I told you I was immortal.
I watched-- I watched you die.
Oh, there are many
forms of immortality.
Once, I had a wife...
...my great love.
- She was taken from me.
- You were the mercenary.
Bane is your child.
Your heir.
An heir to ensure the League
of Shadows fulfills its duty...
...to restore balance
to civilization.
No.
You yourself fought the
decadence of Gotham for years...
...with all your strength...
...all your resources,
all your moral authority.
And the only victory you
could achieve was a lie.
Now you understand. Gotham is beyond saving.
No.
- And must be allowed to die.
- No!
Yeah, just lift your head.
Oh, that's good.
No, no!
- What's that?
- This was someone's home.
And now it's everyone's home.
There's a storm coming,
remember? This is what you wanted.
It's for the bus, in case
there's a chance to evacuate.
Any news? ls the commissioner--?
The less you know, Father.
How are the boys doing?
Well, we've had more power on,
so they've got some TV.
It's good to see you.
Blake, you be careful out there.
They're hunting down cops like dogs.
Why build yourself?
- I'm not meant to die in here.
- Here, there. What's the difference?
I told you it could not be done.
You told me a child did it.
But no ordinary child.
A child born in hell.
Forged from suffering.
Hardened by pain.
Not a man from privilege.
We got boots on the ground, sir.
Just waiting on intel.
You have ID?
Of course not.
- Well, how can we trust you?
- We don't have any choice.
Commissioner Gordon.
Captain Jones, Special Forces.
Captain. Glad to have you here.
It's our job, sir.
Now, uh, how many of you are there?
Well, there's dozens.
I'd rather not say exactly.
But the men trapped underground
number almost 3000.
- - ES: Condition?
Getting food and water.
- Can we break them out?
- Yes, sir.
Take out the mercenaries
south of Ackerman Park.
Blow the rubble, make a hole big
enough for 10 at a time.
I'm in contact with my partner who's
down there. They're just waiting.
- Men who haven't seen daylight in months?
- Officers who haven't seen daylight in months.
What about the bomb? Satellite
can't pick up radiation hot spots.
ON: They keep it on a truck.
It must have a lead-lined roof.
- - They move it constantly.
Good. So you know the truck?
ON: Well, it's one of three.
We've been tracking it.
Decoy.
- You don't really think he's coming back?
- Doesn't matter what I think.
Actually, it does. You should put your
faith in something a little more real.
- - ON: The routes don't vary much.
Okay. What about the triggerman?
No leads. It's a bluff. Bane wouldn't
give control of that bomb to someone else.
We can't take that chance. Until we have
the triggerman, we just track the device.
And meanwhile, Gotham lives under a warlord,
like some failed state?
Dial it back, officer.
This situation is unprecedented.
- We can't do anything to risk millions of lives.
- You gonna tell him what's really going on?
Captain, the situation is more
complicated than you think.
There's someone you need to meet.
Came upstairs looking for a vantage point.
Found the people who run the corporation.
What corporation?
Wayne Enterprises. You good?
Mr. Fox, would you like
to brief the captain?
Miss Tate's fully aware
of the situation.
And as CEO of Wayne Enterprises,
I have to take responsibility for it.
- Why?
- We built it.
You built the bomb?
It was built as a fusion reactor.
First of its kind.
Bane turned the core into a bomb
and removed it from the reactor.
- Here's the important part.
- As the device's fuel cells deteriorate...
...it becomes
increasingly unstable...
...to the point of detonation.
This bomb is a time bomb.
And it will go off in 23 days,
regardless of Bane's revolution...
...or what we, or the
outside world, choose to do.
So your plan might not be
as practical as you thought.
- Could you disarm it?
- I could reconnect it to the reactor. Stabilize it.
- Let's move from this location and call it in.
- Right. Let's go.
No, no, we'll take it from here.
You stay and look after these folks.
Someone sold us out.
Go, go, go!
I'll die before I talk.
I'm on your schedule, captain.
There were people living upstairs.
Round them up for judgment...
...and hang them where
the world can see.
ER: Police have cordoned off
the entire Central Heights and
East Park Side areas...
...as well as Merchant and South Shoreline
Boulevards in an attempt--
He says the leap to freedom
is not about strength.
My body makes the jump.
Survival is the spirit. The soul.
My soul is as ready
to escape as my body.
Fear is why you fail.
No, I'm not afraid.
I'm angry
Bruce.
Why do we fall?
You do not fear death.
You think this makes you strong.
It makes you weak.
Why?
How can you move
faster than possible...
...fight longer than possible...
...without the most powerful
impulse of the spirit?
The fear of death.
I do fear death.
I fear dying in here...
...while my city burns.
There's no one there to save it.
Then make the climb.
How?
As the child did...
...without the rope.
Then fear will find you again.
Ah, supplies for your journey?
Oh, that's wonderful. That's...
What does that mean?
Rise.
No.
No, there's been a mistake!
Take me to Bane!
I want to see Bane!
Order!
This is a mistake! Where is Bane?
There's been no mistake,
Mr. Stryver.
You are Philip Stryver...
...executive vice president
of Daggett Industries...
...who for years has been living
off the blood and sweat...
...of people less
powerful than him.
Call Bane. I am one of you.
Bane has no authority here.
This is merely a sentencing hearing.
Now, the choice is yours.
Exile or death!
Order!
Exi-- Exile.
Sold.
To the man in the cold sweat.
You follow the thick ice.
You try to swim,
you're dead in minutes.
Has anyone made it?
ON: Where are they? It's not like
we have a lot of time.
How long?
The bomb goes off tomorrow.
- We have about 18 hours to do something.
- To do what?
To mark the truck. Get a GPS on it so we can
start to figure out how to bring it down.
That's it?
Foley.
- Where's Foley, damn it?
- You shouldn't be out on the streets.
- Jim, he's not here.
- You let your wife come to the door?
- When the city's under occupation?
- Wait in the kitchen, honey.
What did you do, bury your
uniform in the backyard?
You saw what they did
to those Special Forces.
Have you forgotten all the
years we were out on patrol?
When every gangbanger wanted to plant
one as soon as our backs were turned?
That was different. These guys run the city.
The government's done a deal with them.
Bane's got their balls in a vice.
That's not a deal.
You move on Bane, the triggerman
is gonna hit the button.
You think he's given control of
that bomb to one of the people?
You think this is part
of some revolution?
There's one man with his finger
on the button. That's Bane.
Look, we've all got to keep our
heads down till they can fix this.
- If you still had a family here--
- This only gets fixed from inside...
...the city!
Look, Peter.
I'm not asking you to walk down Grand in your
dress blues, but something has to be done.
- Sorry, Jim. I gotta--
- Keep your head down?
What good's that gonna
do when that thing blows?
You don't know that's gonna happen.
I hear you're looking for men, commissioner.
How about me instead?
Miss Tate, I, uh,
can't ask you to do that.
Please.
You little punk! What'd you take?
Nothing! I didn't take anything!
You steal from us,
you little bastard?
Now, you boys know you can't come into
my neighborhood without asking politely.
Never steal anything from
someone you can't outrun, kid.
You're pretty generous for a thief.
- I thought they killed you.
- Not yet.
- If you're expecting an apology, I--
-it wouldn't suit you.
I need your help.
And why would I help you?
For this. Clean slate.
You'd trust me with that?
After what I did to you?
I'll admit, I was a little letdown.
But I still think there's more to you.
In fact, I think that for you...
...this isn't just a tool.
It's an escape route.
You want to disappear. Start fresh.
- I can't even get off this island.
- I can give you a way off...
...once you get me to Lucius Fox.
Find out where they're
holding him and take me in.
Why do you need Fox?
- To save the city.
- Who says it needs saving?
Maybe I like it this way.
Maybe you do...
...but tomorrow that
bomb's going off.
Got your powerful
friend on the case?
I'm trying
...but I need Fox.
As it approaches...
...flip the switch.
The needle hits 200, you give me the signal,
I'll mark the truck. Okay?
Heads up, heads up.
- I got it.
- Mercenaries on your 6.
Stand still! Keep your hands
where we can see them!
Commissioner Gordon, you are under arrest.
On whose authority?
The people of Gotham.
No lawyer? No witnesses?
What sort of due process is this?
Your guilt has been determined,
this is merely a sentencing hearing.
Now, what will it be?
Death or exile?
Crane, if you think we're going
out onto that ice willingly...
...you have another thing coming.
Death, then.
- Looks that way.
- Very well.
Death...
...by exile.
Bring her to me.
Hey, we're going now. Blake says
they're ready! Get your gear on!
Hey, you hear me? We're going now.
Let's do it.
MERCENARY 1: Find this one a spot,
got a big day tomorrow.
MERCENARY 2: We all do.
It's not every day you bag Bruce Wayne.
- Bruce.
- You okay?
Picked a hell of a time to
go on vacation, Mr. Wayne.
How long until that core ignites?
- That bomb goes off in 12 hours.
- Unless we can reconnect it to the reactor.
- Can you get Miranda out of here?
- Not tonight. I'm sorry.
- Do what's necessary.
- Tonight I need you.
- What for?
- To get me back in the game.
Sorry to spoil things, boys,
but Bane wants these guys to himself.
- I won't forget about you, Miranda.
- I know.
I like your girlfriend, Mr. Wayne.
He should be so lucky.
Any move I make on
Bane or the bomb...
...the triggerman sets it off.
Well, they won't use radio or cell.
Too much interference.
Infrared doesn't have the range.
It'll have to be a
microburst. Longwave.
- Could you block it?
- Yes.
But I'll need the EMP cannon
guidance mount from the Bat.
Remember where you parked?
She ям,y okay?
Yeah, even without the autopilot.
- Thanks.
- Autopilot? That's what you're there for.
Okay. It's clear.
Come on, quick. One at a time.
Wait, wait!
2: Ross!
Ross?
Lock it up. COP 3: No, keep down.
Get down!
Who are you?
Light it up.
Dad, check it out. MRS.
FOLEY: Honey, come take a look.
Impossible.
Keep her close.
He'll come for her.
Where's Miranda Tate?
Bane took her.
He's holed up at city hall,
surrounded by his army.
This blocks the remote
detonator signal to the bomb.
Get it onto it before sunrise.
They might hit the button when it starts.
When what starts?
War.
You missed a spot.
- If you're working alone, wear a mask.
- I'm not afraid to be seen standing up to them.
The mask is not for you.
It's to protect the people you care about.
Count to five, then throw.
No offense, but you got
something bigger in that belt?
- What now?
- All-out assault on Bane.
But you need to get
people across the bridge.
- Why?
- In case we fail.
Lead an exodus.
Save as many lives as you can.
You don't need me here?
You've given me an army.
Now go.
Hey, thanks.
Don't thank me yet.
Well, I might not
get a chance later.
You shouldn't have.
The midtown tunnel's blocked by debris...
...but the cannons have enough
firepower to make a path for people.
Wait until the fighting begins.
You're gonna wage a war to
save your stuck-up girlfriend?
To start it, throttle--
- I got it.
- We have 45 minutes to save this city.
No, I've got 45 minutes to get
clear of the blast radius.
- You don't stand a chance against these guys.
- With your help, I might.
I'll open that tunnel,
then I'm gone.
There's more to you than that.
Sorry to keep letting you down.
Come with me.
Save yourself.
You don't owe these
people any more.
You've given them everything.
Not everything.
Not yet.
MERCENARY Disperse!
Disperse or be fired upon!
There's only one
police in this town.
Open fire.
- Here it comes!
- Get ready!
So you came back to
die with your city.
No. I came back to stop you.
NOW!
That's impossible.
Cut over to Fifth!
Here you go.
Get on the bus. Go ahead.
You, come with me. You too.
Hey, you, you, and you,
come here, come here.
Everyone else get on the bus, okay?
You guys, you go knock on doors
and spread the word, okay?
The bomb is gonna go off. Get out by the
South Street tunnel or over the bridge.
You do two blocks and you get
back to the bus, all right?
Go, go, go!
Is he back?
Keep your eyes open. Go, go.
Cover the doors!
Where's your trigger?!
Where is it?!
You'd never give it to an ordinary citizen!
Where is it? Where's your trigger?
Where is it?! Where is it?!
Tell me where the trigger is.
Then you have my permission to die.
I broke you.
How have you come back?
You think you're the only one who
could learn the strength to escape?
Where's the trigger?
But I never escaped.
But the child.
The child of Ra's Al
Ghul made the climb.
But he's not the child
of Ra's Al Ghul.
I am.
And though I'm not ordinary...
...I am a citizen.
Miranda?
Why?
Talia.
My mother named me Talia,
before she was killed...
...the way I would have been killed,
if not for my protector...
...Bane.
Goodbye.
I climbed out of the pit.
I found my father...
...and brought him back to
exact terrible vengeance.
But by that time...
...the prisoners and doctor had
done their work to my friend.
My protector.
The League took us in.
Trained us.
But my father could
not accept Bane.
He saw only a monster.
His very existence was a reminder of
the hell he'd left his wife to die in.
He excommunicated Bane
from the League of Shadows.
His only crime was
that he loved me.
I could not forgive my father.
Until you murdered him.
He was trying to kill
millions of innocent people.
Innocent is a strong word to
throw around Gotham, Bruce.
I honor my father by
finishing his work.
Vengeance against the man who killed
him is simply a reward for my patience.
You see...
...it's the slow knife...
...the knife that takes its time.
The knife...
...that waits years
without forgetting...
...then slips quietly
between the bones.
That's the knife...
...that cuts deepest.
Please.
Maybe your knife...
...was too slow.
The truck is under attack.
Gordon. You gave him a
way to block my signal.
No matter.
He's bought Gotham 11 minutes.
Come on!
This Way!
Stay there! What are you doing?
Blake, MCU! I'm getting
these boys to safety!
You'll get us all killed!
If anyone crosses this bridge,
they'll blow the city!
It's gonna blow anyway!
We need to open this bridge, now!
Detective, if you take one
step forward we will shoot you!
If you take two steps forward,
we will blow the bridge!
Okay, go back by the bus and wait for me,
all right? Go back and wait.
Prepare a convoy. We must secure
the bomb until it detonates.
Don't kill him, I want him to feel the heat.
Feel the fire of 12
million souls you failed.
Goodbye, my friend.
Goodbye.
Keep moving forward!
Flank them at the stairs!
Shoot them.
Shoot them all.
We both know that I
have to kill you now.
You'll just have to
imagine the fire.
About the whole no-guns thing...
...I'm not sure I feel as
strongly about it as you do.
Pull up.
Stay level.
We have to force that convoy east
to the entrance to the reactor.
I need you on the ground,
I'll be in the air. Go.
The situation has changed.
Your orders are out of date.
I'm a cop, like you,
and I'm walking out there.
Please do not shoot me!
Shoot at his feet.
Nothing like a little
air superiority.
Detective! Please stop!
Please, detective! Stop!
Stop walking!
Blow it! Do it!
You have to get that bomb here.
You've got 10 minutes.
They're pushing us to the
entrance of the reactor.
They're gonna try to
reconnect the core.
You idiots!
You sons of bitches!
You're killing us!
Yeah, follow your orders!
All right, boys. Get in a circle.
Bow your heads.
It's on my side.
Hey, Father! Let's get everyone
back on the bus, okay? Go, go, go!
- Back on the bus!
- There's nowhere to go.
On the bus!
You've got to turn the truck east!
Stay straight!
Give me a hand! We can get a cable on it!
Fox showed me how to override the reactor.
Oh, dear.
Including the emergency flood.
There's no way...
...this bomb...
...will be stopped.
What are you doing?
Protection from the blast.
We're gonna be all right!
It's an atom bomb!
Think they need to hear that?
Let them die without hope? Come on!
Prepare yourselves.
My father's work...
...is done.
- What are you doing?
- I can get it out over the bay!
Set it to fly out over the water,
then eject?
No autopilot.
You could've gone anywhere, been anything.
But you came back here.
So did you.
I guess we're both suckers.
- I never cared who you were.
- And you were right.
Shouldn't the people know
the hero who saved them?
A hero can be anyone.
Even a man doing something
as simple and reassuring...
...as putting a coat around a young
boy's shoulders to let him know...
...the world hadn't ended.
Bruce Wayne?
Come on! There you go! Okay, you too.
Come on, Father.
Hey, heads down! This is it!
- No.
- No, that's Batman!
That's detonation!
It's out over the bay!
Clear of the city!
ON: "I see a beautiful city...
...and a brilliant people...
...rising from this abyss.
I see the lives for which I
lay down my life...
...peaceful...
...useful, prosperous and happy.
I see that I hold a sanctuary
in their hearts...
...and in the hearts of their descendants...
...generations hence.
It is a far, far better
thing that I do...
...than I have ever done.
It is a far, far better
rest that I go to...
---than I have ever known-"
I'm so sorry.
I failed you.
You trusted me...
...and I failed you.
Can I change your mind...
...about quitting the force?
You know what you said about
structures becoming shackles?
You were right, and I can't take it.
The injustice.
I mean, no one's ever gonna
know who saved an entire city.
They know.
It was the Batman.
ER: Mr. Wayne's will was not amended to
reflect his more modest estate.
Nonetheless, there are
considerable assets to dispose of.
The contents of the house are to be
sold to settle the estate's accounts...
...and the remainder is left in its
entirety to Alfred J. Pennyworth.
The house and grounds are left to the
city of Gotham on condition that...
...they never be demolished,
altered or otherwise interfered with...
...and that they shall be used for
one purpose, and one purpose only:
The housing and care of the city's
at-risk and orphaned children.
My clerk can help with the smaller
correspondences and instructions.
KE: Blake, John.
- Nothing here.
- Uh, try my legal name.
You should use your full name.
I like that name.
- Robin.
- Thanks.
SCIENTIST 1: Why worry about the
stabilization software?
This entire autopilot
system's completely obsolete.
Please, I just need to know
what I could've done to fix it.
But, Mr. Fox, it's already been fixed.
Software patch. Six months ago.
Check the ID on the patch.
Bruce Wayne.
- Any news on the missing item?
- Not yet.
They better leave
no stone unturned.
We can't leave a string of
pearls on the manifest as lost.