Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Professor!
Catherine.
Watch your step. OK.
- We have found something beautiful!
I don't believe it. Big, big surprise!
- Yeah? I can hardly wait.
Over here!
Dr. Langford.
- Hello.
What have we here?
Cover stones.
It's fantastic.
Catherina, come!
What in God's name is that?
- I wish I knew.
...there are symbols painted everywhere.
Names, titles of owners, list of offerings.
Every other major architectural structure
at the time
was covered with detailed hieroglyphics.
When is the academic community
going to accept the fact
the pharaohs of the 4th Dynasty
did not build the Great Pyramid?
Inside the pyramid, the most
incredible structure ever erected,
there are no writings whatsoever.
- Dr. Jackson,
you left out the fact that Colonel Vyse
discovered quarrymen's inscriptions
of Khufu's name within the pyramid.
His discovery was a fraud.
Well, I hope you can prove it.
Who do you think built the pyramids?
I don't have any idea who built them.
Men from Atlantis?
Or Martians perhaps?
The point is not who built them,
the point is when they were built.
I mean we all know,
new geological evidence
dates the Sphinx back to
a much earlier period. Knowing this,
I think, we have to begin to re-evaluate everything
we've come to accept about...
I've been able to show
a fully developed writing system
appeared in the 1st two dynasties.
Almost as if it was based on
an even earlier prototype.
Is there a lunch or something,
that everybody...?
Dr. Jackson!
- What? Yes?
Someone wants to speak with you.
The Air Force? What is this?
- Could you step over
to the car?
We goin' somewhere?
- You're gonna be fine.
We'll take care of these.
Those your parents?
Foster parents.
What is this all about?
A job.
What kind of a job?
Translation.
Ancient Egyptian hieroglyphics.
Interested?
I'm gonna go now.
Go where?
You've just been evicted.
Your grants have run out.
Everything you own
are in those two bags.
You want to prove
that your theories are right?
This is your chance.
What's this?
Travel plans.
Mrs. O'Neil?
Come on in.
Mrs. O'Neil, is your husband home?
Yes.
Do you think we might be able
to speak with him?
You can try.
Excuse me, Colonel O'Neill,
we're from General West's office.
We're here to inform you
that you've been reactivated.
That guy's a mess.
How'd he get like that?
- His kid died. Accidentally shot himself.
- Jesus.
Cleared.
Cold?
Allergies.
Always happens when I travel.
There you go.
Dr. Jackson, Dr. Gary Meyers.
- Hello. - How are you?
What is this place?
- Nuclear missile silo.
Now don't worry, it's been
completely converted. Barbara Shore.
OK, Jackson, welcome to the well.
- Hello.
Where did you find this?
- Giza Plateau, 1928.
I've never seen anything like this.
- Of course you haven't.
No one has.
- Now there's two lines of hieroglyphics.
The inner track has
the classic figures.
But the outer track is like
the cartouche in the center.
It's got writing unlike we've ever found before.
- Those aren't hieroglyphics.
It might be
some kind of hieratic or cuneiform.
Well the translation
of the inner track is wrong.
Must have used Budge.
I don't know why they keep reprinting his books.
Excuse me. What are you doing?
We've used every known technique.
That's a curious word to use eh, "Gebeh?"
Yeah.
- Then an adverbial, "sedjem-en-ef."
Then "sealed and... buried."
Excuse me, what are you doing?
It's not "coffin."
"For all time."
Who the hell translated this?
I... I did.
Well this should read "A million years
into the sky is Ra, Sun God,
sealed and buried for all time."
It's not "door to heaven,"
it is...
"Stargate."
Well, so, why is the military so interested
in 5,000 year-old Egyptian tablets?
My report says ten thousand.
Afternoon, Colonel.
Do I know you? - I'm Colonel Jack O'Neil,
from General West's office.
I'll be taking over from now on.
This figure, 10,000, is ludicrous. Egyptian culture
didn't even exist until...
We know, but the sonic and radiocarbon tests
are conclusive. - Well these are cover stones. Was there a tomb underneath?
No, no, no, no. But we found something a lot
more interesting. - Excuse me.
This information
has become classified.
From now on, no information
is to be passed on to non-military personnel
without my express permission.
What's going on?
- I'm not sure.
Colonel O'Neil.
I think you owe me an explanation.
I was told I had complete autonomy.
Plans change.
Why are you here?
Why did they bring you
on this project?
I'm here in case you succeed.
TWO WEEKS LATER
Completed search of cuneiform
and other pre-dynastic hieroglyphics.
No matches whatsoever.
I've exhausted all reference material in
comparing the symbols on the cartouche
against all known writing samples
from the period, pre and post.
Still no similarities.
I'm never gonna get paid.
Can I borrow this?
Orion.
Right here, Daniel.
- Jackson,
I'd like you to meet General West.
- Oh hello. Oh! Right, General.
So you think you've solved in 14 days
what they couldn't solve in 2 years?
2 years?
Any time.
I have some stuff to look at.
If you'll just pass 'em down.
You'll have to share them, cuz I,
I'm sorry I don't have enough.
Anyway...
We're obviously looking at the
picture of the cover stones.
Now, on the outer track, these figures that
you had believed to be words to be translated
were in fact...
were, in fact, star constellations.
These constellations were placed in a unique order,
forming a map or address of sorts.
Seven points to outline
a course to a position.
To find the destination within
any three-dimensional space
we need six points
to determine an exact location.
You said you needed seven points.
Well no,
six for the destination.
but to chart a course
you need...a point of origin.
Except
there's only six on the cartouche.
The 7th isn't actually
inside the cartouche. It's just below,
designated by...
a little pyramid with...
two...
funny...
neat little guys and a funny line
coming out of the top.
Anyway, uh...
He did it.
No.
That symbol isn't anywhere on the device.
Uh what device? I don't...
Show him.
What is that?
It's your "Stargate."
Come, Jackson.
Monitors up!
- Monitors are up.
Mitch, you wanna bring up the details
on the center monitor, please?
I've got details...on.
Hold it.
Wait.
Do you have a, uh...
...oh, here. Sorry.
Hey hey hey don't!
- Two figures...
on either side,
praying beside a pyramid
with the sun directly above it.
He's right.
It was in front of us the whole time.
General West,
Jackson has identified the 7th symbol.
Go ahead. - Programming
7th symbol into computer.
Chevron 1 is holding.
Chevron 1 is locked in place.
Power output at 23 percent.
Chevron 2 is holding.
Engaged. - Chevron 2 is locked in place.
- We're at 35 percent.
All right we've got a condition red
in the gate. Evacuate all personnel.
Area secure.
Heading back. Seal the door.
This was under the cover stones?
- Yes. My father found it. 1928.
Made out of a mineral
unlike any found on Earth.
Chevron 5 lock in place.
79 percent.
Chevron 6 is holding.
Chevron 6 is locked in place.
This is as far as we have
ever been able to get.
The breakers aren't holding.
Override manually.
Chevron 7 is locked in place.
Send in the probe.
Let's go!
Yes, sir.
Record all information from the Stargate.
Clear inner silo for approach.
- Everybody outta here. - Let's go!
It's guiding itself.
Can you believe that?
The beam
has locked itself onto a point
somewhere in the Kaliam galaxy.
It has mass. It could be a moon
or a large asteroid.
Where are we on that map?
The blue dot.
That's right, Jackson.
It's on the other side
of the known universe.
We're losing the signal.
This is the information the
probe sent back to us.
Freeze and enhance.
You can clearly see
the gate on the other side.
Both gates must have functioned
as a doorway between our worlds.
These readings tell us
it's an atmospheric match.
Barometric pressure,
temperature...
...and most importantly, oxygen.
These markings are different.
They don't match the symbols on our gate.
- That's why we may have to abort.
This project is for naught
without a reconnaissance mission.
Once there we would have to
decipher the markings on their gate
and, in essence, dial home, in
order to bring the team back.
Based on this new information,
I don't see how we can do that.
Well, I could do that.
Are you sure?
Positive.
He's full of shit.
You're on the team.
You understand,
this complicates things.
That's why I wanted you, Jack.
We've opened a door
to a world we know nothing about.
I have something for you.
No, I...
- Yes.
I found it with the Stargate
when I was a child.
It has brought me luck.
You can bring it back to me.
Back-up storage.
Reserve power, on.
We're secure. Clear the area.
- Move it, let's go.
Surveillance and monitoring.
...equipment, reserve power...
If anybody has anything to say,
now's the time to say it.
Vector tracking set.
Molecular deconstruction in progress.
Jackson, it's all right.
It's over. Stay with him.
Jackson just listen to me.
Keep moving.
It wears off in a minute.
What a rush!
Prepare to move out.
It's all here, yeah.
Three teams, let's go.
White team, go!
Team 2 Move up!
Clear, no contact.
O2 ratio stable.
- Conditions are similar to inside.
I wanna take a look around.
Kawalsky, Feretti.
Let's rock 'n roll.
Move up there, good.
I knew it.
One - three - three - two.
Report.
Our quarter mile perimeter survey
is just about complete, sir.
Wrap this up, get
everybody back inside.
I want you all people back
through the Stargate within the hour.
You're coming with us
aren't you, Colonel?
Jackson,
start working on the Stargate.
What's that all about?
- I don't know Feretti.
I'm gonna need more time.
There's bound to be more structures,
or some other traces of civilization.
Not this trip. Just get back in there
and re-establish contact.
Well it's not that easy. This is a replica
of the great pyramid of Giza.
We're not gonna find any
hieroglyphic inscriptions or carved relief.
We...really...we really need to
look around more.
Your job is to re-align the Stargate.
Can you do that or not?
I can't.
You can't, or you won't?
I can decipher the symbols on the Stargate,
but I need an order of alignment.
Now those co-ordinates
were marked on tablets back on Earth.
And there must something like that here.
And I just...I just need
to find it.
Find it?  What do you
mean, "find it?"
You didn't say anything about finding anything.
- Well, I assumed the tablets would be here.
You assumed?
You're a lying son of a bitch!
You didn't say a word about finding anything!
Set up a camp down here.
Organize our supplies.
Sir?
You've got your orders.
This is hot.
You know, I can't believe we're stuck here.
- Don't be such a doomsayer Faretti.
Yeah, give it a rest.
- Yes, please.
If we're not back soon, they'll just turn
on the gate from the other side.
Oh no.
It doesn't work that way.
You see, if you don't turn it on
from here, we're screwed. Ok?
So I'm tellin' you guys, we're
not goin' anywhere. - Shutup.
This is a nice tent.
Oh, we each get a tent. That's nice.
...the hell is that?
A thermal blanket, don't need that.
I got everything here but sun-block.
Hey!
Hi.
Hey.
Isn't there something you
should be doing right now?
Like getting us outta here!
Foot powder. Great.
That's cold, man.
Base camp is up, sir.
Where's Jackson?
It's OK. No, It's OK.
Shh. Shh. Shh...
That's a good boy...
What do you want?
You want some of this?
Here ya go.  Ya like that?
There ya go.
I wouldn't feed that thing!
It's got a harness.
It's domesticated!
Dammit.
Let go of it!
Do something!
Come on!
Help me!
You OK, Jackson?
Kawalsky.
- You dropped these. - Brown.
Get away from me.
Easy.
All right, Jackson.
You're on.
Me?
You're the linguist.
Try to talk to 'em.
Hi.
What the hell did you say to him?
- Nothing.
Hey.
It's OK.
It's OK. See?
Quartz, primary element.
I can't make it out...
It sounds familiar,
a bit like Berber.
Or maybe it's Chadic or Omotic.
Thank you.
What's that mean?
I have no idea.
He's inviting us to go with him.
How can you be so sure?
Because he's
inviting us to go with him.
We were looking for signs of
civilization.  Obviously we've found it.
You want me to get us back home, this is
our best shot. - Colonel he's right.
I took some readings
on what they're mining.
This is the same
material as the Stargate.
Radio base camp.
Tell them to keep that area secure,
until we get back. - Yes, sir.
Base camp, come in.
- Feretti, I've got 'em.
Come on.
Yes Sir?
What...can you repeat that, sir?
...Col. O'Neil has requested that you secure base camp.
Looks like we're gonna be here for awhile.
OK, sir.
- Understand? - Yes, sir.
So what's the story?
- They're not coming back. OK, this is not good.
The eye of Ra.
It's the Egyptian Sun God.
They think he sent us here.
I wonder what could have
give them that idea...
Ra.
Ra?
Where they all going?
Come in. Come in.
Feretti I can't hear you.
Sir, I can't make this out.
Feretti, say again.
We have to abandon base camp!
Repeat, we have to abandon base camp!
It's useless. It won't work in this.
Freeman, let's go! Let's move!
Everybody back inside!
C'mon just take what you can carry!
- Battery! Get the battery packs!
We're going back right now.
Wait!
Get over here.
Stay here.
What is it, Colonel?
- Sandstorm. Coming this way.
That would have been an excellent
reason to shoot everyone.
We'll stay until it's over.
Sorry.
We've gotta get back to the pyramid!
Where the hell'd that come from?
Kawalsky, Brown, do you read?
Hey Jackson.
I don't think we should eat any food here.
I don't know.
They might consider that an insult.
Well, we don't want
to offend them now, do we, Daniel?
Tastes like chicken.
It's good.
It tastes...
Tastes like chicken.
Good!
Jackson.
You said that was an Egyptian symbol.
- Yeah. The eye of Ra.
Would you say then it might stand to reason that...
if they know one Egyptian symbol...
Yes.
What the hell's going on?
It seems like
writing is forbidden to them.
What?
They want me to go with them.
Should I stay? I'll go with them.
I'll be fine.
OK, that's good.
What is that smell?
I think that's good.
My hands are clean. Thank you very, very much.
Thank you, very, that was very nice.
Thank you. That was great.
I smell much better now than...
Yes, thank you.
O Christ, I smell like a yak.
No, no please, no more, please.
Please no more.
I'm fine.
I'm clean...I'm...
I'm...
Oh.
I thought
you were one of the other cleaning...
No, no, no.
You don't have to do that.
Maybe you should go. OK?
It's OK. Maybe you should go.
No, no. It's OK. It's OK.
It's all right. Here, let me grab this
No, no, no no, it's me.
I wanted to uh, th-thank you.
I'm very, I'm very happy.
Thank you.
Daniel.
I'm Daniel.
We came... uh
This pyramid.
See, we came from...
We came from the pyramid.
It's OK.
Never mind.
The Earth.
You know the symbol?
You've seen the symbol?
Show me.
You show me.
Kawalsky, this is base.
Do you copy?
You're wasting the battery.
We'll never get anything in this storm.
You'll have to wait till it passes. - Yeah, right.
IF it passes.
You know I was stationed in the Middle East.
I've never seen anything like it.
Yeah, yeah...
- I don't understand.
Why don't we just
turn the gate back on ourselves.
yeah, how hard can it be?
- That would be great!
We could turn the thing in the wrong order and
materialize the vacuum of outer space.
Do you have any idea how many
possible combinations there are?
No. How many?
Shut up.
What the hell is goin' on?
All right, spread out.
Let's move out!
It's OK. It's just a lighter.
See?
Here!
Yeah, it's pretty fabulous.
You're right. It's pretty stupid.
No, you keep it.
It's yours.
No!
It's dangerous!
What is this place?
I'll be damned.
What?
No signal at all?
- Nothing.
More interference?
No.
They're simply not there.
...no sign of him?
- I haven't been able to locate Jackson, sir.
I'm lookin' for Jackson.
Jackson. The guy that wears this jacket.
He's uh, he's got like long hair that
comes down...no, no.
No, no, no, no it's...
He wears glasses, so he can see.
I guess the word "dweeb" doesn't mean anything
to you guys, does it? Why not?
I'm on Planet X lookin' for a dweeb,
He wears green fatigues. He wears this jacket.
He's got long hair. It comes over his eyes.
He wears glasses,
and...sneezes.
Chicken, chicken!
Chicken man. You got it.
You want this?
I thought
you couldn't speak their language.
Huh? Hi... scared me.
It's an ancient Egyptian dialect. I mean in like the rest of
their culture it's evolved completely independently.
But uh, once you know the vowels...
Just answer the question.
I just had to learn how to pronounce it.
It hasn't been a living spoken
language for more than one thousand years.
I mean look at this. It says,
"A traveler from distant stars
escaped from a dying world looking
for a way to extend his own life.
His body decaying and weak,
he couldn't prevent his own demise."
Apparently his whole species
was becoming extinct.
So he traveled or
searched the galaxies,
looking for a way to cheat death.
Look here: He came to a world
rich with life where he
encountered a primitive race.
Humans.
A species which, with all his powers and knowledge,
he could maintain indefinitely.
He realized, within a human body,
he had a chance for a new life.
Now, he apparently, found a young boy.
It says
As the frightened villagers ran,
night became day,
curious and without fear,
he walked towards the light.
Ra took him and possessed his body,
like some kind of a parasite,
looking for a host.
And inhabiting this human form
he appointed himself ruler.
He used the Stargate to bring
thousands of people here to this planet
as workers for the mines.
Just like the one we saw.
This mineral is clearly the building block
of all his technology. With this
he can sustain eternal life.
Now uh, something happened, where is it,
back on Earth...
A rebellion, or uprising,
and the Stargate was buried there.
Fearful of a rebellion here,
Ra outlawed reading and writing.
He didn't want the people
to remember the truth.
Jackson, I think you better take a look at this.
That's it.
That's what we're looking for.
They must have hidden it here, in hopes that one
day the gate on Earth could be reopened.
I knew they'd have it
written down someplace.
Wait a minute.
Where's the 7th symbol?
It must have broken.
It's gotta be here somewhere...
Got it. I got it here.
It's worn off.
I can't make it work without the 7th symbol.
All right, that's it. Kawalsky, Brown.
Come on, Jackson.
What the hell is that?
Here. You might need this.
Look out!
Where are we going?
Why are we going to the Stargate?
I can't make it work.
Stay right here and shoot at anything
that comes down that ramp.
- What are you doing? - Just cover me.
What is that?
What are you looking for?
- It's gone.
Put it down, Jackson.
You have come here to destroy me.
What is that?
It's a bomb isn't it?
That's what you were looking for.
What the hell were you thinking?
What'd you come here for?
Wait! Don't!
No!
No! No!
Colonel, it's me.
You all right?
Where's Jackson?
Sha'uri, what happened here?
Ra punished us.
Why?
What happened to Daniel?
Son, we should not
have helped the strangers.
I was dead?
That is why I chose your race...
your bodies, so easy to repair.
You have advanced much...
harnessed the power of the atom.
What are you going to do?
You should not have reopened the gate.
Son, I will
send your weapon back to your world,
with a shipment of our mineral,
which will increase your weapon's
destructive power a hundredfold.
Why would you do that?
I created your civilization,
now I will destroy it.
But before
my workers question my authority,
you will prove
that I am their one God,
by killing your companions.
If I refuse?
Then I will destroy you,
and all who have seen you.
There can be only one Ra!
Sha'uri, Ra has called an assembly.
An execution.
Skaara, Nabeh, I want you to listen.
We can't let this happen.
I want you to know
what Daniel told me,
about where our people came from,
and why
we can no longer live as slaves.
C'mon!
Freeman!
Freeman! Freeman!
Jackson!
Follow me! Come on! Kawalsky!
C'mon!
Jackson!
To our victory!
We recovered your weapons.
Here, Colonel.
So, what do you think?
They're not exactly special forces, but
they sure were eager to join up.
Take these guns away, Lieutenant,
before they hurt themselves.
Sir?
You heard me. Send 'em all home.
- There's no place for these kids to go.
Anyway we could sure use their help right now.
- For what?
Huh?
To do what?
Why don't you just tell 'em everything?
Why don't you tell 'em about the bomb?
What's he talking about?
My orders were simple.
Track down signs of any possible danger.
If I found any, blow up the Stargate.
Well, I found some.
Well, your bomb is his now, and
tomorrow he's going to send it back to Earth,
along with a shipment
of that mineral they mine here.
And when that thing goes off, it's gonna cause an explosion 100 times more destructive
than that bomb alone is capable of.
I'll intercept that bomb
before he can send it through.
Why wasn't I told of this?
Because there wasn't any reason to tell you Kawalsky.
You weren't even supposed to be here
You were all gonna go
right back through with Daniel.
I was gonna stay behind alone
and blow up the Stargate and that's exactly what I'm going to do.
It's the gate on Earth that poses a threat
that's the one we have to shut down.
You're absolutely right. But since
you don't know how to get us back,
we don't have that option, do we?
Where are they?
Answer!
We looked everywhere.
Some kids are helping them.
You had accepted the fact that no matter what
happened, you would not be going home?
Don't you have people who care about you?
Do you have a family?
I had a family.
No one should ever have to
outlive their own child.
I don't wanna die.
Your men don't wanna die. And these
people here don't wanna die.
It's a shame you're in such a hurry to.
How could you let them escape?
I will not accept failure!
Why are you laughing?
- Husbands don't do this work.
Husbands?
Married?
Don't be angry. I didn't tell them.
Tell them what?
That you did not want me.
What are you drawing?
The day of our victory.
Connect the moons...
This is the symbol for this planet.
That's it.
The point of origin.
What are you doing?
I've found it!
What are you talking about?
The 7th symbol.
We're goin' home.
Let's go.
You'll bring disaster
to all of us, son.
Father, we will not live as slaves.
Kasuf!
Take a look at your Gods.
Take a good look.
The caravan is approaching.
Send the bomb down to the Stargate.
What's happening up there?
How you doin'?
Damn! Come on, Feretti!
Come on!
Get that door!
Hey, you OK? You all right?
Spread out!
Let's go!
We're dead! - Quit talking like that man!
- Well what're we gonna do? - Cover me.
Cover you?
Kawalsky!
C'mon Feretti, help me push this thing over.
Send the bomb to Earth now.
I will send it myself.
What are you doing?
- Completing this mission.
We agreed to dismantle the gate
on the other side. - And you will.
That's your job now. I'm gonna stay here
and make sure this goes off.
You've got seven minutes.
Daniel.
What are you doing?
Jackson!
- Wait for me.
Nabeh!
You got any rounds at all, Feretti?
- We're all out of ammo. - Incoming. - Get down!
Kawalsky, we gotta do something.
Damn.
Stop!
I am no longer amused.
You will die together.
Give my regards
to King Tut, asshole.
How much time do we have left?
- 45 seconds.
He's leaving. Turn it off.
- I'm trying to I can't disarm it. - What?
I can't stop it they got it rigged.
I got an idea.
I always knew you'd get us back.
- Yeah, right. - Later.
Thanks, Daniel.
You sure you wanna do this?
Yes, I'm sure.
You gonna be all right?
I'm gonna be all right.
How about you?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
Tell Catherine
this brought me luck.
I will.
I'll be seein' you around,
Dr. Jackson
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player