Ithought he was supposed
to have a breakfast date, right?
I mean, they told me
that last night.
Breakfast?
Is that on the sched?
It isn't,
but the lieutenant told me
that he'd be doing
breakfast with someone
down at the harbor.
I mean, if he ain't,
I could go get this gassed up
at the Fallsway.
I hate this detail, man.
It's off duty.
Lotsa perks.
All this stand around
and wait, you know?
Hoskins says
I do the one year,
and I'll make sergeant
on the next list.
Yeah. They told me,
careerwise,
you can't do better
than drive the mayor.
Shit, if you could
make rank the right way,
I'll still be working
Western drugs.
All right, fuck this,
I'm gonna go look
for the lieutenant.
Anyone comes looking,
I'm back up
on the second floor.
Sir?
I understood
that the mayor
might be going to, uh,
breakfast at the harbor?
With Kweisi.
But, um, that's up
in the air, I thought.
Would you happen to know
where Lieutenant Hoskins is?
Sir?
Lieutenant?
Umm...
You don't look happy,
Detective.
We're about
to raise some hell.
Maybe too much hell.
A state senator,
two councilmen,
the City Development Agency,
all those developers...
Princes of the city.
Lester, tell me
the thought hasn't
crossed your mind
that some kinda shit
could blow
back on us, man.
Do you know what
Theodore Roosevelt said
about hunting grizzly bears?
The thrill is in overcoming
your own fear.
What was the thrill
for the bear?
I should've run every one
of these subpoenas
by my front office.
That's not procedure.
Fuck procedure, Lester.
My boss is running
two points behind
in the polls with
the mayor's support.
How do you think
he's gonna do
if he pisses off Royce
and starts dropping off
incumbent tickets?
Why do you care?
If Demper thinks
I fucked him and he wins,
I will be at Central Booking
covering bail reviews.
If he loses to Bond,
a new front office comes
in and maybe they bounce
the white girl
back to a trial team
and give the Narcotics Division
to one of their own.
It's Baltimore, Lester.
We're missing
a couple of subpoenas.
We are?
Clay Davis
and Andy Krawczyk.
I'm holding those
till October.
Oh, the hell you are.
Lester...
we drop subpoenas
on either of those guys
three weeks
before the primary,
and all hell breaks loose.
That's what I'm sayin'!
Clay Davis is Royce's
deputy campaign chairman,
and the number-two man at
the City Legislative Caucus.
And Krawczyk is his
number-one fundraiser!
You're giving me resumes
and job titles.
I'm just following the money.
And we will follow it...
after the polls close.
We can drop a second batch
of subpoenas.
There is no reason to do
this now and risk--
A year ago, if we had gone
after these records,
City Hall would've
stomped on this unit
and the subpoenas.
And a month from now,
after Royce is reelected,
they'll do us
the same way.
But right now,
with the primary coming,
they gotta worry
about how they look,
how they behave.
Right now, they gotta
worry about scandal.
You told me you wanted
to do this a year ago,
but fresh cases
got in the way.
You told me that.
Oh.
Very clever, Lester.
You got it all figured, huh?
Me?
I'm just the police.
I saw the teachers' union
finally endorsed Royce.
You knew
they were gonna.
What time's
your first appearance?
Today?
I meet up with you guys
at the SoWeBo forum.
And tonight, it's me
and the kids next to Tommy
at the Roland Park fundraiser.
Better speed things along.
A kick in the ass
sometimes helps.
- B-5?
- No, Daddy, D-5.
You sure
you didn't say B-5?
D-5.
What did I hit?
Submarine.
Umm...
E-6.
Miss.
Just gimme 10 minutes.
You seen your
schedule today?
You ain't got
10 minutes.
Norman, I got
this pretty girl's
aircraft carrier boxed in.
- D-4.
- Ow! Hit.
Tommy,
for Christ's sakes.
Is there any way
that I can win?
With the numbers what they are,
is there any way at all?
Right, so if it's just a matter
of playing out the string,
then that's what
I'm gonna do.
That game's pretty much
over, Norman.
But this game--
this game right here--
this one could still
go either way.
H-11,
sweetheart.
Miss. D-3.
So I guess y'all getting
what y'all need?
- Brianna keepin' y'all close?
- She come up with it.
Money comin' through
every month like she say.
A'ight, 'cause I'm standin'
tall up in here.
They don't need
to worry about me
an' I ain't need
to worry about them.
- You a soldier, Bey.
- You know it.
Everything all right
with my fishes?
You'd tell me if
it wasn't, right?
The fish be fine.
I mean, they fish, right?
How I know how they
feelin' about shit?
- De'londa...
- They fine, Bey.
Ask Namond.
Cleaned the tank an' all,
like you say.
- Cleaned the filter, too.
- A'ight, a'ight.
Check you out, though.
Getting some fuzz
up there, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah, whatever.
I know when I was
a little kid, boy,
I couldn't wait till
I started shaving.
One of the old heads
on the corner say,
"Hey, little man,
you wanna grow a 'stache?
Next time
you take a piss,
take some of that piss,
get it on
your fingertips,
do like this, here."
Eww! You do it?
You damn right I did it.
Shit.
What's going on with you,
though, son?
Ain't nothing.
School about to start.
So what about Bodie
and his boys?
They treatin' you right?
Yeah, he cool.
Boy, don't lie
to your father.
He don't even show up for work
half the damn time.
- Bodie told me.
- I missed a few days. That's all, Dad.
And what money
you do make,
you waste on nonsense.
And if you think
I'm gonna give you a dime
for your school clothes,
you better think again.
What Bodie
got you doin'?
I'm a runner,
most days.
Everybody got
to start somewhere.
You better listen
to your father.
He ain't tell you 'bout
that hair, though, huh?
Yeah, he said
I gotta get it cut.
I like it this way.
Even the white police
lookin' out from
three blocks away gonna
be able to spot you
from every other nigga
out there.
They gonna hop out and say,
"Look at the boy over there
with the pretty-ass
ponytail. Get him."
You think
I'm bullshitting.
Either you real out there,
or you ain't, Nay.
You see what I'm sayin'?
Let me get some!
Hey, yo! Over here!
- Whoa! $100!
- Thanks, mister!
- Thank you, Mr. Marlo!
- Thank you!
That's my money, yo!
Your name gonna
ring out, man.
Manuel...
Boy, you talk that shit
better'n me
and I been dealin' with
these Mexicans for years now.
Yeah, I don't think
they would call
what I'm speakin'
Spanish, man.
Just a dirty word
or two here or there.
Yeah, well. Once you can
talk to these cats,
the only thing you need
then is a truck, man.
Could be runnin'
your own crew,
pickin' up fresh clients.
I mean,
if we put in together
we could be coverin'
twice the ground,
makin' twice as much.
Nah, man, I got
other obligations.
Oh, right.
You set to be
the new Angelo Dundee.
I near forgot.
I thought
you already went up
to Mondawmin to get
your school shit, man.
Yeah,
but not all of it.
And my boy,
he need to pay
for his own shit
and his little brother, too.
The fuck this look like,
a Social Services office?
You want a check,
go the fuck up Rosemont.
Come on, man,
I'll work for it.
Nay, I took you on outta respect
for your father,
a'ight, but I can't go hirin'
the whole damn neighborhood.
You can have
my job until
you get enough
for you an' Bug.
- Thanks, man.
- Yeah, work for y'all, work for me, yo.
Po-po.
Step the fuck off.
Looking for your man Lex.
I see his broom,
but I don't see him.
Where's your
number two been at?
- I ain't seen him.
- Since when?
I thought we were
on better terms.
Or do you want me
rolling past
Iookin' for Lex
every 15 minutes?
He come past,
I'll call you.
I will!
If he come past.
Oh no, I don't know.
They're spinning
their wheels.
You know,
poor Tony Gray,
pulling 20%
of the black vote.
It's embarrassing.
Well, who knows
what the fuck
Carcetti's
trying to prove?
But I tell you,
at the end of this thing,
he's gonna regret getting
on the wrong side of me.
Mm-hmm.
A'ight, now.
I got what you need, boy,
clean tees,
any sizes, huh?
Lookin' for socks, briefs,
you lookin' for dice,
Zippos, cards--
come on over
to the Rollin' Emporium.
You ain't gotta
walk to Rite-Aid.
Shit, Rite-Aid
comin' to y'all.
What can I get you, baby?
Fresh dice
an' a pack of Trojans.
- All righty.
- You got Philly Blunts, too?
Bubbles got it all, dawg.
I'm the one-stop shop.
- How much is that?
- Six an' a bit.
Thank you.
Thank you kindly.
Yes, sir, I see
what you're lookin' at.
Two a deck,
name brand.
You can't beat that price.
Yeah, let me get
two decks, man,
and a white tee,
double-X.
And give me the rest
of them paint cans, too, man.
All right, all right,
there you go. That's it?
Yeah, what's that?
How much the man owe,
Sherrod?
- 13.
- Whoa whoa whoa.
He asked for all the cans.
Three cans is $12,
plus the other stuff.
It's $19.
$19, sir.
Come on, you still gettin'
off with a deal,
Now, you didn't have
to move your feet.
We came to you, right?
My bad.
$19, like he said.
Thank you very much.
He's an intern,
I'm working with him.
But, ma'am,
what I'm asking is
when was the last time
you saw Lex?
Oh, excuse me-- Curtis?
Hmm?
- Two days ago?
- I don't know where he at.
Three days?
You mind
if I look around?
I'd rather you
leave my house be.
Well, Ms. Anderson...
your son is in trouble,
and I can tell
you're upset.
But the best thing
that you can do for him--
the best thing that
he can do for himself--
is talk to me.
I'm gonna
tell you the truth:
We know
he's selling drugs.
And I'm gonna tell you...
I don't know
nothin' about that.
But I'm telling you
that I don't care
he's selling drugs.
I'm not even gonna
bother with that.
I'm here
because of a homicide,
and the way
it looks right now
your boy is running
from the police
behind that killing.
I don't know
where he at...
Ma'am...
Councilman,
my people got only
cost-of-living bumps
for four years.
Morale is at rock bottom.
All things being equal,
you'd be our guy.
We like what we hear.
The polls say
it's going to be Royce.
We endorse you now,
we're out in the cold.
Bobby... this might be
the chance to get in on
the ground floor
of something better.
That may be true, Major.
But for now,
we're gonna play the cards
that we were dealt.
Councilman,
if you were me, I'm sure--
I'd cover my ass
and endorse Royce,
along with the teachers
and the firefighters.
But I'd also
tell my membership
not to get carried away.
I mean,
it's one thing
for the police union
to call out for Royce,
it's another thing entirely
for off-duty cops
to be manning
the mayor's phone banks
and polling stations.
I don't think
any of my officers
will be too aggressive
for anybody.
That much I can give you.
Best you could do,
Tommy.
Royce has got all those
fucks runnin' scared.
Yeah...
best I could do.
Call it a night, Tommy.
You got a debate
to prepare for tomorrow.
Yeah. Debate.
Nothing matters more
at this point.
Let the truth
set you free, Norman.
Nothing matters at all.
Thanks.
Come on, boy,
come on now.
Man, you better not
be getting tired,
'cause you gonna
get put to the test
- on Saturday night.
- I'm ready.
- Hey, Miss Johnson.
- Hey, Justin. Hello, Dennis.
You're Spider's mother, right?
Right, Sharon.
Sharon Johnson.
Your boy left here
a while ago.
I ain't looking for him.
He at his grandmother's.
I wanted to ask you something.
You know, my son
is crazy about you.
All he talks about is boxing,
bein' at the gym,
and what his coach
been teachin' him.
Well, Spider's a good kid.
He really studies
the sport.
Dennis,
I am so grateful
for your interest in Spider,
I want to cook you dinner.
How 'bout tonight?
Well, ah, that is
really nice, Sharon.
But the thing is, I got four of my boys
fighting this weekend,
and I got to train 'em
really hard
these next few evenings.
You in here every night
of the week.
What you do for fun?
Look here,
you got to eat, right?
And you can look
at me and know
I throw down
in the kitchen--
among other places.
Yeah, I tell you what:
If you fix me up a plate
and bring it over here,
I would love that.
That I can do.
- He said what?
- "Me? I'm just the police."
Like butter wouldn't
melt in his mouth.
And the thing
that I resent most
is that he's not
just playing the system,
he's playing me.
Like I'm part
of the problem.
You were gonna
hold back the paper
for Davis
and Krawczyk, right?
Only until
the primary was over.
And now you feel
guilty about it.
Did he do that thing
where he, uh,
stares at you over the top
of his reading glasses?
You know,
that look that says,
"I'm the father
you never had,
and I don't want to be disappointed
in you ever again."
It's not funny, Cedric!
Those subpoenas
went out today!
The front office is
gonna go batshit!
But you did it anyway.
I'm sorry, but shit,
I'm just glad to see
Lester doing it
to somebody other than me.
Hey, you holdin'
us back, Sherrod.
I made a mistake, man.
Why you trippin'?
If I can cut you loose
to handle the money,
we can cover
twice the ground,
selling twice
the merchandise.
More-- more--
what you call it,
uh, market share.
Instead I gotta
keep your ass close.
You shoulda been promoted
to your own cart by now.
You keep on hittin' your dome
on the glass ceiling.
- Glass what?
- You gotta step up the math skills
if you wanna advance
in this here enterprise.
You remember
last spring when
you tried to take me
up to Harlem Park?
They couldn't even find
my records, Bubs.
They didn't want
shit to do with me.
They put you
in a classroom, right?
The teacher didn't
look at me once.
So you rolled out.
An' who got hurt
behind that, huh?
The teacher or you?
What's four times five
plus six times seven?
See? See?
Fuck that shit, son.
I can't wait until school starts.
- You joking, right?
- Nah, seriously, son.
I can't wait to see
all them girls,
see which ones got phat
over the summer,
- you know?
- Guess who I saw last week?
- Who?
- Kwaneese Davis.
Oh, shit, you mean
Cute-Ass Kwaneese?
- Uh-huh.
- She phat?
Got titties, too.
I'm definitely tappin' that pussy,
now, y'all watch.
I'm be all up
in Kwaneese this year
Iike this, bangin' that...
Just like you tried to do
last year, right?
Fuck you, nigga,
I only halfway tried.
So, Michael, who you
gettin' with this year?
Stankin' ass, uh-- what's her name?
What's her name?
- What's her name?
- Oh, Tina.
Tina-- Tina Jenkins.
Don't talk bad
about Tina, man.
I'm not sayin'
that it bad.
I'm sayin' she be
sucking dudes' dicks
in the boys'
bathroom and shit,
- that's all.
- I heard you, man.
She suck dick even better
than you do, Namond.
- Oh!
- Wow.
What up?
What up, see?
Good jabbin', man.
Chill chill chill!
Don't rip this shit.
I just bought
this throwback.
Yo, Michael, son,
if I ain't had this shit on,
I'd have fucked you up.
Word up.
You little niggas ain't up
to no good, is you?
Yo, what up, Monk?
Look here, first day
of school coming up, right?
- Yeah, next week.
- Y'all need school clothes and shit?
Here...
Yo, what's this for?
What, you ain't hear me?
For new clothes,
whatever else
you need to get.
- Thanks, man!
- Damn, 200?
- Yo, thanks, Monk.
- Oh, you need to thank my man Marlo.
He ain't wanna see you
little motherfuckers
going raggedy
on the first day.
Whoa. That Marlo?
- Naw, man, no thanks.
- You ain't gotta do nothing for it.
No thank you, man.
Hey, yo, Mr. Monk?
I'll take his
if he don't want it.
- I'll hold his for you--
- Yo, don't press, man.
Don't press.
Fuck is wrong
with you, boy?
You too good
for my money?
Or is you such
a bitch-ass punk
you worried about where
my money come from?
Yeah.
Ain't no thing, shorty.
We cool.
You can't tell nobody.
Swear to me you won't
spread this around.
And he saw you?
Yeah, he saw me.
Carv, I'm fucked in the ass
with a pineapple on this.
- What the helI'd you say to him?
- I said, "Mr. Mayor,
that's a good,
strong dick you got there,
and I see you know
how to use it."
I didn't say shit!
And I didn't wait for him
to say anything, either.
Shit, I'm never gonna
make rank now.
I'll end up riding the boat
or some shit like McNulty.
This is way beyond
my pay grade.
We need to get with someone
who knows politics.
Who do we know
like that?
On crime,
he knows you're coming,
so he's gonna
set some traps
and lean on stats
that say crime is down.
He'll also try
to inoculate himself
by making it about you.
Like you're playing
the race card
if you talk about drugs
or violent crime.
He's hoping
you'll back down.
But you come on
twice as hard:
"Clarence Royce has not
made this city safe."
Hey, Jen, what's up?
- You got a second?
- No, I got time, what is it?
- You forgot the check.
- Oh no, you're kidding me.
You've got to
pay it right away.
No, no, I got
the number here, yeah.
No, I'll straighten
it out straightaway.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Shit.
I forgot to mail the check
to the fuckin' archdiocese.
My kid's gonna get tossed
outta St. Albans
if I don't get
my shit together.
Tommy. Focus.
He comes at me with race
and some bullshit crime stats.
I ignore the race thing
and counter by noting
that homicides are up
15% even though
other violent crime stats
are down 12%.
I point out
this does not make sense
unless Royce is cooking
the crime stats,
making robberies, rapes,
and assaults disappear.
I suggest the mayor is not telling
the truth about crime in the city.
I conclude by declaring that
it is for all of Baltimore--
every neighborhood--
that I'm making public safety
the cornerstone
of my campaign.
Tomorrow night,
I will kick his ass.
But the next morning,
I still wake up white
in a city that ain't.
Sister Theresa?
Hey, how you doing?
Yeah, Tommy Carcetti.
Yo, Randy, man,
you crack me up, son.
Running behind him
talking about,
"I'll take his, Mr. Monk.
Give his to me."
Listen, man,
I could've used that extra.
I already spent
all the clothes money
Miss Anna gave me on stuff
to sell at school.
Yo, and plus Marlo
wanted us to have it.
He want to show us
who callin'
the shots out here.
- Yo, Michael, why you ain't take it?
- that ain't me, man.
- Say what?
- That owin' niggas for shit, man.
- That ain't me.
- I'll take any motherfuckin' money
- if he givin' it away now.
- Why?
Shit, your family got
more money than all of us.
Yeah, but my mom said
she cuttin' me off,
she ain't buyin' me school
clothes and shit.
You already took my job
with Bodie, so...
- Gentlemen.
- Oh my God.
Oh shit!
- Donut, you crazy, man.
- Yo, Donut.
You think you could steal us
one of them camper trucks?
Yo, you steal us a camper truck,
we can all go campin'
- out in the woods an' all.
- I be scared in the woods.
I don't mean far like that.
I mean like Howard County.
Naw naw naw, man.
The Ku Klux Klan
live in Howard County.
I know that for a fact.
Nigga, my aunt live
in Howard County.
There ain't no
Ku Klux Klan there.
Nigga, you simple,
I swear.
Hey, yo, Donut,
drive me away
from these
ignorant bitches, man.
You can't tell
these niggas nothin'.
Move, motherfucker.
Can you see
over the steering wheel?
You think
he'll talk to me?
Use my name
if you have to.
I had one of his sectors
for eight months.
What's wrong
with that picture?
Nigga, if there was a
black one in the parking lot,
I would've took one.
Yo-- narcos,
narcos!
760 to K-G-A.
I got a bailout
at Calhoun and Mosher,
six to eight juveniles
beating feet north
in the alleys
around Calhoun.
10-4. K-G-A to all units--
I love this.
Just like old times.
I don't need to chase
these fucking knuckleheads.
I know half of 'em.
Shit, I know
where they hang.
Besides,
you're a little overdressed.
Let's just call this in and go see
the man about your thing.
Yo, yo, man,
I ain't do nothin'!
- I ain't do nothin'!
- Then why you runnin'?
- 'Cause you chasin' me.
- Yeah, right. What's your name?
- For real, man, I ain't do nothin'.
- What's your goddamn name?
- Randy.
- Randy what?
- Wagstaff.
- I know you ain't lying.
Wouldn't nobody
make that shit up.
Put your hands against
this fucking wall.
Come on--
what do you know
about hoppers bailing
from a stolen car?
Nothin'.
Little motherfucker.
You slingin'.
- No, sir. I swear to God.
- Hell you ain't.
How else you walking around
with 200 in your pocket?
My foster mother gave me that
to buy school clothes with.
Your foster mother
gave you 200 cash?
Yeah.
Tell her to come down
to the Western,
and I'll give it back to her.
Beat feet, motherfucker,
before I lock your little ass up.
Don't be fucking
lookin' at me, move.
This right here is fire.
That said, I'm ready
to serve 'em myself
and keep your names off
the returns.
I've got my 20.
You two got to live
in this department.
Fuck 'em
where they live.
Let's go.
The price of steel
being what it is,
that's gonna kill us
if we can't
pass along the overage.
Mr. Krawczyk?
Baltimore City Police.
- What's this?
- A subpoena for records.
You need these right now,
because, uh,
I'm kinda up to my ass
in stuff today.
Honor it in a timely fashion.
I think that's
the legal standard.
- No problem, Detective--
- Shakima Greggs.
You're with the city?
- Which unit?
- Major Crimes.
Senator.
What the hell is this?
Subpoena for records.
Sphinx Club?
- Man of the year.
- What kinda bullshit is this?
You people must be out
your damn mind.
You were in
the Sphinx Club?
My uncle used
to tend bar over there.
Marvin Thompson?
Short guy--
What is your name,
Officer?
Detective Sydnor, sir.
"Major Crimes"?
Shit...
Enjoy your day, sir.
Son, we're gonna see
about this.
That's it.
Yankin' that bitch.
Son, that's too much knuckle.
Why the fuck
you keep callin' me?
But what I say, though?
He got
the message, fool.
Yo, Monk.
Who that, man?
Andre.
Old Face Andre.
Here, let me
holla at that dude.
Yo, check this out, man.
I'm gonna show you
how you do this
right here, man.
Don't rush me on shit.
I'll get at you
when I'm at you.
Yo, remember who
you're talking to
before you say
another fuckin' word.
Andre, man.
Nigga need
more maintenance
than both
my babies' mamas.
By accident.
It was accidental.
And the mayor
doesn't say anything?
I think
he's pretty mad.
I mean, Major,
I only took this detail
to try and make sergeant
on this list.
Kid, you made
sergeant already.
Shit, if Royce
gets reelected,
you'll be a lieutenant in two years
and a major in four.
You go back down
to the hall.
You act like
it never happened.
You shut up.
Say nothing to no one.
But the mayor,
he's gonna--
He's gonna watch
and see how you carry it.
And kid,
you're a fucking rock.
When the mayor
looks in your face,
he knows he can
trust you with this.
And I'll bet
in a couple of weeks,
he comes asking,
real friendly-like,
what are you looking
to do with the department?
With your career?
He's interested in you.
But he doesn't mention
no blowjob,
and neither do you.
Uh-uh, it just lays there
Iike a bad pierogi
on the plate,
both of you pretending
it ain't there.
What if he
screws me over?
Bounces me
to a midnight shift?
He does that,
you will talk.
What I wouldn't give to be
in your shoes right now.
Kid, careers have
been launched
on a hell
of a lot less.
Just shut up
and play dumb.
I can do that.
No problem.
Thanks, Major.
Thanks for taking the time
to meet me on this.
I mean, it's a weight off
my mind talking to you.
It really is.
Don't mention it.
Maybe you get a chance
to do me a turn
one day after
you make rank, huh?
Oh, boy.
It's all good, Carv.
Because if some
federal motherfucker comes
through the door,
I say, "Hey,
it's all in the game."
But a City Police?
Baltimore City?
Hell, no.
Can't be happenin',
'cause I know
I have raised too much
goddamn money
for the mayor
and his ticket.
Hell, no!
Ain't no soul
in the world
that fuckin' ungrateful!
- Calm down, Clay, hmm?
- Money laundering?
They gonna
come talk to me
about money laundering?
In West Baltimore?
Shit... Where do y'all
think I'm gonna
raise cash for
the whole damn ticket?
From laundromats
and shit?
From some tiny-ass
Korean groceries?
You think I have time
to ask a man
why he givin' me money?
Or where he gets
his money from?
I'll take any motherfucker's money
if he givin' it away.
- I don't wanna know.
- I know you don't wanna know.
But I'm scratchin'
an' clawin'
to get it done for you,
Clarence.
For you and me
and the rest of the team.
And who comes
through my door
but a Baltimore City Police
Iookin' to get up
into my shit about it.
Clay, we didn't know
about that.
I'm sorry, I gots
to leave up out of here
before I lose
my damn mind.
Nobody knew about that.
You want
to run a campaign
with my money
pillowed under your ass,
you need your people
to back the fuck up, Clarence.
Krawczyk's on line one.
I'll jump on Burrell
and Demper both.
Find out
what the hell's going on.
Wait-- wait a minute.
That new driver,
the bald-headed, white kid.
Where did he
come here from?
Hoskins brought
him in, I think.
Hoskins?
He doesn't have a better rabbi
in the department than that?
Why, you want
to lose him?
Let me think about it.
Yeah, man, Officer Walker
be shady like that.
Police be stealin', yo.
Yo, what I really wanna
get is a bubble Caprice.
I seen
a nice one, too.
'94 caprice on 22's.
Shit was tight.
You better be careful.
They almost caught you today.
Nigga, they ain't
almost caught shit.
Shh. Be quiet, y'all.
Y'all know
who I am, right?
Carver.
You a narcos.
Today I'm auto theft.
Fair warning.
If I see any of
y'all little hoppers
even smile
at a motor vehicle again,
it ain't gonna be no juvenile hearing.
No, it's gonna be my people
settlin' up with y'all in the alleys.
You understand?
- You can't do that, yo.
- Try me, Namond.
Yeah, that's right.
I know your name,
I know where you live
and I know where
y'all hang.
Damn, yo!
Nice ride.
- Hey, Bunk.
- Hmm?
You have any luck
finding your shooter?
Naw. He's runnin'.
But at least I know who
my shooter is, right?
I just got
to find the boy.
- Family won't go for nothin'?
- Nah.
Mother wouldn't say shit.
But it wasn't the usual way
a mama lies.
- What do you mean?
- I don't know.
It was a weird vibe, man.
I can't explain it.
It was like she was off
somewhere else in her head.
Line four.
Communication.
- Who's up?
- I'm up. I'll take it.
No, wait.
If it's yours,
you lucky bitch,
then it's a domestic
in a house with four wits.
- You want the call?
- But I pick up that phone,
do I make it unlucky?
Or is it still your call?
You want the call,
pick it up.
If you don't, don't.
Homicide. Norris.
Right. Uh-huh. I got it.
1400 Lanvale, in the street,
found by the post officer,
no suspects,
no witnesses.
Ah, man.
Better to be lucky
than to be good.
You wanna work
the heavy bag?
G'head. Four rounds.
Hey.
- Hey.
- I'm Gail.
I made this for you
and the other men
to let you know
you're appreciated.
- That's real nice.
- Peach cobbler.
I'm sorry, I forgot
whose mother you are.
Oh, I don't have
any boys.
I just appreciate
what you been doing,
you and the other coaches
volunteering and all.
Well, thank you,
that's real nice.
I got three girls. Y'all don't
teach girls, though, do you?
- No, I'm real old-fashioned about that.
- Oh, I agree wit' you.
Men should be men
and women should be women.
That's what I think.
Single wound,
upper back, no casings,
no witnesses, and nothing
on the canvas.
- Dead when you got here?
- Actually not.
He was still conscious
and coughin' blood when I pulled up.
- You ask who shot him?
- Yeah, I asked who shot him.
He said it was
a guy with a gun.
Yo, why the fuck
you keep calling me?
He got the message, fool.
Yo, Monk,
who that, man?
Andre.
Old Face Andre.
Yo, Monk,
who that, man?
Andre.
Old Face Andre.
Lemme key that.
Yo, Monk.
Who that, man?
Andre.
Old Face Andre.
Yo, check this out, man.
Don't rush me on shit.
- I'll get at you when I'm at you.
- I'm just saying...
Old Face Andre.
Tryin' to reup
with Monk Metcalf.
Yeah, well, Monk took the call
on his cell phone.
But that second voice
ranked him.
Ranked everybody,
by the sound of it.
Marlo Stanfield.
On the phone.
The way he shut that call down,
I'd say, yeah, that was him.
Yeah, but what was all that
in the background? Fireworks, or--
Naw, it was regular intervals.
Semi-auto from the sound.
Target practice, maybe.
Either that
or a firing squad.
There are no bodies
on this guy in months,
but we get him
on the phone
and it sounds
like a war zone.
Well, at least he gets
on a phone now and then.
- That's something.
- Sounds arrogant, doesn't he?
Like he's the lil' king
of everything.
Ah. Youth.
Yo, bubs.
Thought you asleep.
If you want...
I could go
to school some.
I ain't been
for a while,
so I don't even
know if I can.
But if you
want me to go...
ain't no thing.
His Honor was mad?
I can't begin
to describe it.
- What's he want from us?
- To block the subpoenas,
but he knows we can't
once those things go out.
What I could promise him
is no more surprises
out of our shop.
Is this that
cocksucker McNulty?
Not this time. He's been gone
from that unit a year.
My best guess would be
Lester Freamon.
- Freamon?
- Lester's got a helluva game.
Well, we need to sit
on the motherfucker.
All that unit needs,
Commissioner,
is proper supervision.
Hey, the State of Maryland
just lost another
cooperating witness,
and I just found a lot
of fucking overtime.
This case went from
a who-gives-a-fuck drug murder
to straight-up red ball.
Fuck, I should've
picked up that phone.
Hey, Sarge.
My boy's a witness.
Drug case pending
in part 18.
You know for sure
he's killed for that reason?
Don't know shit. But from the look
of the court computer,
this guy's
the state's whole case.
Don't put it in the 24 that
the guy was a witness.
Trust me,
we do not wanna kick shit
in an election year.
Work the case, take the O.T.,
but bury the witness angle
till we know for sure.
And close the door.
Yeah.
It's Landsman. Homicide.
Is the major
in this morning?
Next order of business:
class rules.
It helps if the team
is constant on these.
Less wiggle room
for the children.
Mrs. Scott?
Same as last year,
double space.
Language Arts,
we grade a lot of papers.
It doesn't make them
write any better,
but it saves my eyesight.
Make sure you
demonstrate it for them.
Some of them think double-space
means more space between words.
I'd of thought
by eighth grade--
Rule of thumb around here,
Mr. Pryzbylewski: Never assume.
Explain what
you want them to do,
have them do it,
then explain again.
With time and patience,
they'll get it.
- Mrs. Shapiro?
- It's easier to keep track of lab work
if we all use
the same heading.
Upper right-hand corner,
above the first blue line:
name, date, and class number,
in that order?
Mr. Pryzbylewski, do you have
anything you want addressed?
Can we have them
not chew gum?
They won't do it
in Ms. Sampson's class,
but in four years, I have not
been able to stop them.
You can try, but first year,
it's best to stick with basics.
And team rules--
we can only go
with what
we can all enforce.
Also, keep your
windows closed.
Makes them drowsy,
and drowsy's good.
There's a lot to learn.
But for now,
build in lots of activities
in your lesson plan.
You can't have enough.
You keep them busy,
you keep them off-guard.
You need soft eyes.
Excuse me?
Yeah, but that
doesn't prevent you
from giving more
under your wife's name,
your children, if they
got separate accounts...
yeah.
Sorry, Richie,
can you hold a moment?
Your buddy
from the F.O.P.
And he says
it's important.
Hey, Stan.
I'm a little busy
losing an election here.
You remember about
six months ago,
you told me
to keep an eye for
any witnesses
gettin' clipped?
You remember that?
Who's better than me,
Tommy?
Hey, Richie,
can I call you back?
Thanks.
Anything else you want me
to do, Miss Donnelly?
Uh...
you live near
Duquan Weems, correct?
Dukie?
I want you to take
this to his house.
These clothes won't
stay clean long.
Make sure you deliver
them just to Duquan,
not any of the adults
in the house.
- Just Duquan.
- Want me to do it tonight?
that would be great.
And, Crystal, thanks for today.
You're welcome,
Miss Donnelly.
- Can I help you?
- Yes, ma'am.
This young man has to be
registered for school.
- Does he attend here?
- He should.
What I mean is, what grade
were you in last year, dear?
He kinda lost his way
some time ago.
He's livin'
with me now.
And you are his...
Uncle.
I'm his uncle.
Come into my office.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Yo, look at coach
workin' it, yo.
A'ight, man, break.
That's what I like to see, baby.
That's what I like to see.
You gotta use that left
- a little more, though, a'ight?
- Yo, man, you finished?
- Got another two minutes.
- Fuck that, I got a fight coming up.
You can come back
later, a'ight?
Yo, man said he got
one more round, a'ight?
Step aside, youngin'.
Naw, man, bag is mine
for four rounds
- and I only did three.
- Fuck that.
What the fuck you
tryin' to prove, huh?
Whoa, whoa. Come on, man,
come on. Come on.
- What's going on, boy?
- I got a fight Saturday night,
an' the boy won't
get off the bag.
What the fuck he on
the bag for anyway, huh?
He don't even fight.
He don't even spar.
Spar with
your ass any day.
- Come on, then.
- Hey hey hey.
Y'all be cool,
you hear me?
I ain't putting up
with this foolishness.
Come here, Michael.
- I can work the bag now, right?
- Not yet. Just wait.
- You said four rounds.
- Yeah, I know what I said.
You finish up your rounds,
and then Justin gets on.
I don't want hear
no more street talk.
We boxin' up in here,
we ain't fightin'.
He wanna get in
the ring with me,
- we can go.
- Look here, look here,
Iet me tell you something:
You can come here,
work out,
use the equipment.
But nobody
gets in that ring
unless they're being trained.
You wanna be trained?
I've been watching you
hit that bag.
You got
a natural right hand,
the way you throw it,
the way you land it.
Now if I was
to train you,
we'd have to start
with floor work.
'Cause see, if you don't
know how to move,
you ain't got no business
being in that ring.
So what you think?
I'd train you myself,
personally.
Nah, really I just wanna keep
doing what I been doing.
All right.
Let's see that right.
Uh-huh.
Is Dukie here?
What's that?
That's for Duquan, right?
I take it to him.
Gimme.
Hey, Crystal.
Miss Donnelly said
to give you these.
Okay.
I'll be right down.
What?
And for either of
my opponents to suggest
that downtown development
comes at the expense
of our city's neighborhoods,
well, that's just unfair
and, uh, divisive.
For them to suggest
that my administration
has not been
responsive, well...
Economic development
cannot be a band-aid.
It is a long-term process
that requires commitment
to retraining our workforce
and, as I said before,
this can only be successful
in a city where
people feel safe.
So before we can
even begin to think about
Iuring new industries to Baltimore,
we need to think about
how we can make
these neighborhoods
and this city safe once again.
Mr. Carcetti may think
it's in his interest
to exploit people's fears.
He's been doing it
throughout this campaign.
I'm offended by it,
personally.
But the fact is,
that violent crime
is down citywide,
and our police department
is working hard
to keep it that way--
and will continue to do so
under my administration.
Councilman Carcetti,
you have two minutes
to respond.
Does anyone in this room
really believe
that crime is down
in Baltimore?
You calling me a liar,
Tommy?
Gentleman, please.
No personal interactions.
- Councilman Carcetti.
- Can the mayor honestly tell
the people of Rosemont,
of Belair Edison,
of Highlandtown
or Cherry Hill
there's less drug-dealing,
less violence?
Any statistics coming
from the police department
cannot be trusted,
because under this mayor,
the police are more concerned
with protecting Clarence Royce
politically than fighting crime.
There's no leadership
and morale has never been lower.
I'll change that.
It's business as usual
down at City Hall
and as a result,
our response to crime
has been characterized
time and time again
by wanton indifference.
...32 yards!
What do I mean
by business as usual?
by wanton indifference?
Well, last night
in West Baltimore,
on Lanvale Street,
another citizen
was shot and killed.
This time, the victim
was a key witness
in a drug case that
had yet to come to court.
Courageously, this man
had agreed to testify
in two weeks time
in that case.
The police should have
been protecting him.
They were not,
and he was murdered.
- Oh, shit.
- Why? Because this mayor...
You're prime-time, Eddie.
...would not spend the money
to protect him.
Now I have no doubt
that in a moment or two
Clarence Royce will
accuse me of exploiting
this man's death
for my own political purpose.
But the truth is,
a year ago I wrote
the mayor a letter.
I have copies for anyone
who wants one.
I begged him
to spend the money
and make witness protection
a priority.
He ignored me.
I even teamed up
with our legislative leaders--
Delegate Watkins
and others--
to get matching funds
for witness protection
approved in Annapolis.
And incredibly
those matching funds
were never claimed
by this administration.
Now to mention this
now may be exploitive--
I don't know.
I only know it's true,
and on such truths
I ask the voters
of our city
to consider a change.
Folks, please, please,
hold your applause
until after the round
of questions is over.
Mayor Royce?
No more surprises, huh?
I am unaware of the specifics
of the incident
to which Councilman Carcetti
is referring,
uh, so I can't answer
that directly, um...
however, I can say
that this city places
the highest priority
on protecting those citizens
who come forward to testify,
and we will continue
to do so.
Mr. Carcetti states
that he wrote a letter
expressing his concerns,
and I'm sure that he did.
I mean it's-- it's--
it's easy enough
to write letters
when all you have to do
is write letters.
But when you
are required
to run a city
on limited resources,
and balance priorities,
well, then-- well,
then you understand
that writing letters will
not solve the problem.
Oh, no...
Shit, girl.
You know
I'm-a roll wit' you.
Huh, I need
some kinda break.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, shit.
Ain't nothin' worse
than them bitches
with fucked-up nails
at the blackjack table.
You know.
Hold on.
You think my son
gonna go up
to that school lookin'
like himself?
And I don't believe
we can get a handle on crime
until we get a handle
on the schools.
Because we need to be
thinking about these kids
before the corners
take them.
And this means a renewed focus
on our schools...