On this Sunday
before the primary
when we will go to the polls
to exercise our blessed franchise,
our lesson comes from
Exodus, chapter 18.
"And it came to pass
on the morrow
that Moses sat
to judge the people:
and the people stood by him
from the morning
unto the evening.
And Moses judged the people.
And he shouldered
this tremendous burden all alone.
And one day,
his father-in-law said to him,
'Moses, why do you carry this
awesome responsibility
by yourself?
You need other wise men
to help you rule
justly over the people.'
So Moses hearkened to the voice
of his father-in-law,
and chose able men
to rule over the people."
Can I preach it like I feel it?
Hey hey hey.
This Tuesday,
when we choose
the men and women
who will lead our city,
we would do well to keep
those standards in mind.
Men of truth,
who fear God
and hate covetousness.
Hallelujah! Hallelujah!
Hey.
God bless you.
Good to see you.
How you doing?
- Just fine.
- How's Mama?
- Tell her I said hello.
- Fellowship committee at 2:00?
- If I'm late...
- We'll wait.
All right. Thank you for coming,
young man, young lady.
- Reverend.
- Councilman.
Mrs. Carcetti.
How are you?
Thank you so much
for having us.
- Thank you.
- lnteresting sermon.
Polls seem to think
you have a chance.
Well, we're within
the margin of error.
Margin of error.
That's an interesting phrase.
And I see you've got
Delegate Watkins working the crowd.
Well, I'm hoping
he's not going to be the only one.
I'll tell you what, Councilman.
I will keep an open mind
until I walk into that booth on Tuesday.
- And if you win--
- You're holding me to a high standard.
- Moses? I mean, Jesus, Reverend...
- Tommy.
I'm sorry. I can't believe I said that.
Moses will do for now.
We'll save Jesus
for your second term.
- Have a good one now.
- Thank you.
Thank you all
so much for coming.
- Signs o' life?
- Not even a lookout.
- Maybe they went to church.
- Our Lady of the Re-up.
He'll show up sooner or later.
- Call me.
- All right.
Vote for Carcetti.
Vote for Carcetti
on Tuesday.
Tommy Carcetti running
for mayor. Thanks.
- Hello, Councilman.
- Good morning.
I've been following
your campaign. I'm a teacher.
- Excellent.
- High-school biology.
- What? Here in the city?
- Baltimore County. I just wanted say
I think your position
on school-board reform
- is very encouraging.
- So you'd vote for me?
If I lived in the city,
I absolutely would.
- Good luck on Tuesday.
- Thank you.
They're all fucking county people.
We're almost
done here anyway.
- Thomas, look at this.
- What's that?
Check it out.
In your private practice,
you ever represent a Bobby Harrison?
The slumlord?
Fuck, no.
I don't remember ever
even meeting this guy.
"Carcetti got the most
serious charges dismissed
and the others reduced
to small fines.
The slumlord once again walked free
with a slap on the wrist
while hundreds of tenants
continue to suffer
substandard living conditions."
Last-minute smear.
They're running scared.
- Royce.
- Who else?
65% of the city rents.
Bobby Harrison's name
is dirt in this town.
Two days before the election
and they smear me?
Courthouse steps.
When the fuck was this taken?
- It's a fake. They photo-shopped me.
- We have time to prove that?
- We can try.
- Try, shit.
- I'm gonna lose behind this.
- Easy, Tommy.
We always figured they'd
pull some last-minute shit.
At least now we know
what it is.
Fuck.
I want you to remember,
you're representing your daddy.
Yeah, I know.
What she wanna
see us for, anyway?
Maybe she got somethin'
special in mind for you, boy.
- Cool.
- She's a Barksdale.
She know talent
when she sees it.
Besides, they owe
this family a lot.
Your daddy,
he stood tall for them.
I know, I know.
He a soldier.
- Like father, like son.
- No doubt.
- What time you got?
- 3:30.
Motherfucker late.
Yo.
It's for you, Marlo.
Yeah, speak.
You on it.
As long as she hit
her mark, we straight.
What time I gotta pick up
that skinny girl?
A'ight.
So what time they say?
Tomorrow night.
She be on the 8:45
from New York. Yeah.
We can take care of that.
No. I'll do it.
Don't want nothin'
to go wrong.
You sure about that?
It's a'ight.
You can hang back on this.
Yeah, I think I got
this one, too.
Marlo Stanfield.
He ain't so much.
Using cell phones and shit.
What's he sayin' now?
"What time I gotta
pick up the skinny girl?
I do it.
Don't want nothing
to go wrong."
Maybe he's picking up
a girlfriend?
"Skinny girl from New York"?
It's code. Cocaine.
Damn. For Marlo himself
to get near a package...
He's a mope. I told ya.
- So what do we do about it?
- We work up some counter lit.
That's why we have
a printer on retainer.
Best if we run down
the original photograph.
If we can prove
this one's a fake--
I didn't work at "Sun" Papers
for 22 damn years
not to know somebody.
I'm gonna call Paul McCardle
at the photo library.
And if we still
can't find it?
Then we put out
a fake photo of our own.
Show Royce in a motel
with a dead girl and a live boy.
We can't sling mud back.
Not this late.
Relax. I'm kidding.
You get back on your schedule.
Hit all your stops.
Go to that donors' dinner
tonight and make nice.
We'll take care of this.
You can't do this to us.
Bey took the weight
for all y'all.
And you've been
amply compensated.
- But time moves on.
- Not for Bey, it don't.
What I meant to say is there's
no more money coming in.
No more business.
Avon is gone.
So are his people.
Shit.
You seem to still be doin'
all right for yourself.
There's nothing more
I can do for you.
Bey know everything.
You forget that?
And what's he gonna do?
Who's he gonna tell?
And what do I care
if he does?
Bey never heard me say
a damn thing about business.
What about your brother?
Avon could be gone longer
if Bey gets to speakin' his mind.
I couldn't care less
about Avon.
The thing is I wanted
you both to hear it from me
so there ain't no lies
from here on in.
She even paid enough
over the last two years
that you should have enough
money going forward, son.
Your father has not been
disrespected here.
You both got
what was coming.
But ain't nothing
lasts forever.
Jailhouse snitch?
Called last overnight.
Worden talked to him.
Says for a deal,
he can give us the case.
- No shit.
- Gonna write up a writ,
send it over
to the State's Attorney's office,
get them to sign off on it
first thing tomorrow morning.
- What's the rush?
- We jump on this.
We cause a major shit stink
right before the election.
If this guy really knows
why the witness-- what's-his-name?
- Braddock.
- --was killed,
might be bad for the mayor.
If it's not bad
for the white boy, Carcetti.
You care, either way?
Fuck no. I don't give
a shit either way.
I don't even vote.
But it'll be fun to fuck
with them downtown suits.
Maybe get you on the 1 1 :00 news.
Get a little payback
for all that shit they put you through.
With only two days left
before the primary,
campaign officials
traded charges today
over a controversial
flier distributed
in some African-American
neighborhoods.
What seemed to be a secure lead
for the incumbent mayor
has evaporated in recent days.
The latest "Sun"-WQMD poll
shows the two men
in a virtual dead heat
with Councilman
Tony Gray trailing.
4% of the likely voters
are still undecided,
and with the prim--
I can't wait
for it to be over.
Yeah, me either.
Can that flier hurt you?
You know, we found
the original photo
in "The Sun"'s files.
They grafted my puss
onto some perp-walk shot
on the courthouse steps.
I'm standing where some
sheriff's deputy was.
Oh my God.
What a nasty business.
Royce is swearing
he had nothing to do with it.
Claims it must've been
somebody freelancing.
Well, Norman and Terri
say not to worry.
It's all in the game.
You know, when I was
15 points behind,
I was resigned,
you know?
A landslide,
I could live with that.
I mean, what else did
anyone expect, anyway?
White guy runnin'
for mayor in Baltimore?
But this?
Jen, if I lose this here
by two points, it's gonna kill me.
It's gonna just fucking kill me.
You gonna have to
step up now, Nay.
A'ight.
Be the man of the family.
You older than your daddy was
when he went out on the corner.
That's what I been sayin'.
Damn. He quit school.
You ain't quittin' school.
- Not yet.
- Ma.
But you are goin' out
on your own.
You gonna ask Bodie
for a package.
What if he say no?
I ain't take
no for an answer.
- Just did.
- What you mean?
- From Brianna.
- Hand me the damn phone.
What she say about you already
gettin' paid enough money?
She a lyin' bitch, Namond.
You see?
There's a lot about this world
you just don't know.
What it come down to is
she know you ain't gonna snitch.
- No matter what shit she pull.
- She got that right.
She takin' advantage of you, Bey.
She takin' advantage of you.
Sound like she got it all figured.
Bitch got it figured out, all right.
She cuttin' us loose
without notice. Nothin'.
Like comin' home,
findin' our shit in the street, Bey.
She don't give a fuck
about you, Avon, none of it.
She had the nerve
to talk to me on this,
Iike she gonna
set things straight
so I don't tell no lies.
Jen, I'm sorry.
He said he'd be up.
He's already gone
to the office.
Well, what's he doing there?
He couldn't sleep.
He's been there for hours.
Aw, shit. See ya.
And given that we still
have a shortage of officers
willing to work secondary
at the polling stations,
we're asking
for anyone interested
to contact Tactical
this afternoon.
Next order of business:
fresh warrants,
beginning with murder
and weapons charges
on one Omar Little.
Anyone know this mutt?
Oh, yeah!
- Who'd he kill?
- Some lady in a store.
- Reads like a taxpayer.
- A taxpayer?
From what this says,
he's charged with felony homicide,
to wit: murder in the commission
of a robbery.
About fuckin' time someone got
some paper on that motherfucker.
Anyhow, we got no fixed
address, no known abode.
But if apprehended,
contact Detectives Holley
and Crutchfield in Homicide.
You wanna find Omar Little?
You look for a corner boy
running away from a corner
with shit in his pants.
You ever know Omar
to do a citizen?
Anyway, pass these around.
- Jesus, Tommy.
- I spent a couple hours
going over the latest data,
rearranged the schedule.
Tommy.
A little bit of knowledge--
There's a bunch
of middle class black precincts
which are strong on Tony
but still have a high undecided.
I think we can
pick up some votes--
Those people hate the mayor.
You're gonna get those votes,
- and if you don't, Gray will.
- We go door to door today.
As long as they
don't go to Royce.
I need some black votes
if I'm gonna be mayor.
I need some kind of mandate
from that community.
If I sneak in with a bare plurality...
We might just win this thing.
What do you think
kept me up all night?
With all due respect
to your early-morning analysis,
we got three back-to-back
drive-time radio interviews
I wore out
my kneepads to get.
The people running your campaign
are professionals, Tommy.
Don't try this shit at home.
You know, there might
just be a job for you
in a Carcetti administration--
press secretary, chief of staff.
Oh, get in the fucking car.
Duquan?
Mr. Prez.
Can you come
with me, please?
What'd I do?
Get here early.
I'll let you in, and you can shower.
My dirty clothes?
Put 'em in this bag,
leave 'em in the locker.
I'll bring 'em home
and wash 'em.
Go ahead and get cleaned up.
You'll be late for class.
Hey, Paul.
Hey, Monnel.
Skanky ho.
Damn, she good, though.
Yeah yeah.
You right about that.
Hey, yo, Tiff, baby.
I got 50¢ too.
Fuck y'all.
Damn. All three at once?
You know she could.
I know you could.
- Sir.
- At ease.
Man, I hate it when the bosses
creep below the eighth floor.
Yeah, well, I need a moment
just to unclench my asshole.
- Sir?
- The Braddock investigation.
It's coming. Norris and Greggs
are wringing it out.
I fuckin' know it's coming.
Commissioner Burrell
had a visit first thing this morning
from State's Attorney
Demper himself,
asking why one day
before the primary
our detectives were trying
to writ out a jailhouse snitch.
The tip came when it did.
I didn't push it,
and I didn't hold it back either.
Let the chips fall
where they may.
Exactly, sir.
Sergeant?
Fuck your falling chips.
If Braddock was killed
because he was a witness
and we break the case
one day before the primary,
Royce hates us forever--
and Royce might win the election.
If Braddock was killed
for any other reason
and we break it today,
then Carcetti hates our guts--
and Carcetti could win.
I see your point.
Tactical tells me
we're still about 20 bodies short
for manning
the polling places.
I want you to detail
two detectives
to uniformed
election duty immediately.
Lemme guess:
Norris and Greggs.
Sounds good.
They're to report
to Tactical at 1 300 today
for election orientation.
They can pick up
their writ
and talk to their snitch
on Wednesday.
American democracy.
Let's show those
Third-World fucks how it's done.
Yes, sir.
I have what I think is
some very good news for all of you.
We're going
to be implementing
the University of Maryland
pilot program.
You're only taking
three of my knuckleheads?
A total of 10 children
from the eighth grade
in this first class--
eight boys and two girls.
- If things go well...
- It's a start.
- When?
- This morning.
Hallelujah.
Not a moment too soon.
- How was l?
- Good on Steiner.
Better on the A.M. talk shows.
I thought you handled that call
about the fliers well.
Fucking Royce.
If I lose because of this bullshit--
You lose, we can blame it
on 10 different things.
Same thing if you win.
Guess who I just
got off the phone with?
State Senator Davis.
He wants a meet.
Clay Davis? Why would I wanna get
into bed with that motherfucker?
He didn't actually
come out and say it,
but it sounds
like he's ready to follow Watkins
and jump the mayor's ship.
What's he want in return?
Shee-it. Same thing
he always wants.
At least 20k to his favorite
campaign committee is my guess.
Maybe even 30,
'cause you know Clay ain't cheap.
Well, I'm not promising him
anything policy-wise.
You think Clay Davis
gives a fuck about policy?
Naw, this is strictly
for services rendered.
He might be conning us--
taking the money,
then sitting on his hands.
Maybe. But then all
we have to lose is money.
Could be the extra little push
we need on the West Side.
Set it up.
I already did.
- lnvert the denominator--
- What invert mean?
The numerator
and the denominator switch places.
- Turn upside down.
- Why you do that?
Because it works.
That's the formula.
Excuse me,
Mr. Pryzbylewski.
Namond Brice, Darnell Tyson
and Zenobia Dawson.
Grab your things
and come with us, please.
- Ooh!
- Quiet, quiet.
Calm down, please.
- What'd we do? We in trouble?
- Just come with me.
Shit. It's the story of my life.
They ain't coming back.
Yo, Mr. Prezbo,
they gettin' arrested?
No...
Yo, Nay,
can I have your Xbox?
'Cause you ain't gonna
need it where you are.
What'd they do?
Markeith, Kwame
and Latonya.
Bring your things
and come with us.
Ooh!
Again?
You know I can't
publicly endorse you.
Not at this late hour.
Then what are
we talking about?
I lay back and not do
what I usually do on election day.
I see you all get a push
in the Seventh
and Ninth Districts, say,
and maybe that piece
of the 1 1th west of Freemont.
I split some
of my tickets for y'all.
I split my walkaround money.
You know,
the usual to-and-fro.
Politics is
a good thing, pardner.
That's a minority opinion.
Let's order.
I'm hungry enough to eat
the horse you rode in on.
If you don't mind,
we're a little busy
- for a sit-down lunch.
- Oh, no doubt.
Just leave enough
for the tab.
Naw, she crazy.
She says you were there.
I wasn't. Besides,
it wasn't even rape.
- She wanted to.
- How do you know? You weren't there.
I saw her go in with them.
Go in with who?
This is no time
to play, young man.
You are in very serious trouble.
Who did you see her go
in the boys' bathroom with?
Paul and Monnel.
Paul and Monnel?
And what were you doing?
- Lookout.
- So you were involved.
But I didn't even see
what happened.
You were standing guard.
No, listen,
Monnel gave me $5
and just told me to stand by the door
and holler if someone came.
This isn't even fair.
I didn't even do nothing.
You stood lookout
while two eighth-grade boys
raped an eighth-grade girl.
But she wanted to.
That's not what Tiffanie says.
There'll be an investigation.
You'll be suspended.
You could very well be expelled,
maybe even face criminal charges.
Mrs. Donnely, please don't.
Mrs. Donnely, please don't
call my foster mother.
I'll tell you everything
I know about this.
I know all about it already.
No, but I know
some other stuff,
Iike who been thieving
from the teachers' lounge,
or tagging gym lockers, or even...
- Miss Jeffries, please.
- Miss Donnelly, please...
This is Mrs. Donnelly
calling from Tilghman Middle.
Listen... I know...
remember, the boy who cut
Mr. Philmont's tires?
I know who did that.
I know about a murder.
I do.
We've identified certain students
we feel will benefit
from the special curriculum
and the smaller class size.
We've chosen 10 students
from the eighth grade
to participate in this program.
You get chose,
you got to go?
- That's right.
- What if you don't wanna?
It's mandatory.
We feel that this program
will benefit everyone.
You'll get the attention you need.
And we outta
everybody else' shit.
My bad.
I ain't mean to curse.
Yeah, but you're right, though.
This class get tore up,
it's only on y'all.
- So we get put outta class.
- This is a classroom, too.
And every one of you
has proven time and again
that you're not ready
for a regular classroom.
But this is a new program
that if you work it
is going to make you ready.
Ready for gen pop.
This is prison, yo.
And we in solitary an' shit.
- Word.
- Solitary.
That's good, son.
This is solitary.
This is the hole
up in here.
He's a good kid.
He really is.
And once you make that call,
his name's gonna be in the system.
What can I do?
He says he knows about a murder.
I have to notify police on this.
At least let me call
someone I trust.
That's him right there.
Stand by. You don't wanna
be in on the collar?
Nah. If you take it, he'll think
it's a straight interdiction,
and I get to surprise him
at the bail review.
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
Can I have your attention?
Now boarding at
gate letter D, track 4,
the southbound
8:45 Acela Express from New York,
making station stops
at BWl Rail Station
and Union Station, Washington.
Sister, help you
with your bag?
- No, thank you.
- Don't be afraid.
What should I be afraid?
Who are you?
Just walk you to the door.
My husband
is waiting outside.
Like to meet him.
I'll wait with you,
make sure you're safe.
That really
won't be necessary.
- Amtrak police, sir.
- Could you step over here please?
- What is this?
- Give me the bag.
What is going on?
I don't know this man.
Where are you taking me?
- What'd he say about it?
- Nothing much.
Drugs?
I didn't question him
too close.
A murder.
I should
take it downtown.
Who knows
what he really knows?
I just-- I don't want to see him
get chewed up by the system.
Let me try
to keep this close,
give it to someone with
a little bit of discretion.
Appreciate it.
- Carver.
- Carver?
Ellis has come a long way.
I think he'd be right for this.
Why do you care?
And what's this kid to you?
I don't know.
He's one of my students.
Sergeant.
Clean. Both of 'em.
Say what?
Nothing in that bag
but ladies clothes.
Nothing dirty
on either one of 'em.
Unless you got another idea,
we gotta cut 'em loose.
From what he says,
he was just a go-between.
He delivered a message.
He told the victim to be
at a certain place at a certain time.
Then how does he know?
He says everyone knows
what happened to Lex.
It's in the streets.
This other thing at the school.
I swear I didn't
do it, Miss Anna.
I didn't do it.
You'll see.
School's gonna look into that,
we're gonna look into this.
As long as Randy cooperates,
tells everybody the truth--
- But if word got out--
- Understand.
That's why he's gonna go to school,
keep his mouth shut,
his nose clean,
go about his business.
Child's shown such bad judgment
in both instances.
Agreed.
But from what I can tell,
he's not a bad kid.
Dennis?
Where you goin'
at so early?
Oh, I'm gonna go run,
and then I got lawn work later.
You comin' back, right?
What you mean
am I comin' back?
It's gonna be
like that, huh?
What do you mean?
Like what?
- Where to?
- Highlandtown.
Flush out yo' base,
little trooper.
- What up, Spider?
- Hey, shorty.
Thank you, but I know
how I'm voting.
I'm gonna
be late for work.
Miss Anna, is it okay
if I stand out here
while you go vote?
- Don't you go nowhere, boy.
- Yes, ma'am.
So, what up, man?
So, how much they payin' you for this?
They say like 40, but I gotta work
the whole day though.
Know what I mean?
Yo, Spider.
Yo, that was Spider, right?
- Yeah.
- Well, where'd he go?
No, thank you, man.
I can't vote.
Conviction? Felony?
Move on, man.
A'ight, man.
You see Spider again, you tell him
he need to come past my gym.
He ain't been round in weeks,
and we need to talk. A'ight?
A'ight.
- Where's the older kid?
- I don't know.
- Okay. You're hired.
Shove one of those
into every hand you can.
Thank you very much.
Why you ain't at school?
Ain't no school today.
- One them Jew holidays?
- Election.
- So what you gonna do?
- Dunno. Hang.
What'd I say
about steppin' up?
Brianna turn off the faucet.
We gotta make some rain.
I'm gonna get dressed.
We go see Bodie.
Kid, I got
something else for you.
Put one of these
in every door
between the expressway
and Winchester,
and from Freemont to Fulton.
You can do it by yourself
or you can get some friends,
but I'm gonna come past
this afternoon, make sure it's done.
Okay. One in
each door. Cool.
This is
for the day's work.
- Whoa.
That's your walk-around.
But don't you fail me.
Took forever.
What's all this, son?
Man said if I put
these fliers in doors, I can get paid.
I come right home after.
You right you will.
You ain't
in these streets no more.
No, ma'am.
Sounds like she mean it.
"11 :00 News," huh?
Shut up.
I'm on this shit detail
because you wanted
to stir the pot.
And tomorrow, if we bust open
the Braddock case,
nobody's gonna give a fuck.
Life is timing.
No shit, fucknuts.
Tommy Carcetti.
How you doing?
- He's a cute one.
- Thanks.
Hey, Tommy Carcetti.
Hope you're voting today.
I am.
Well, who's it gonna be?
Give me a hint. Come on.
Don't keep me
in suspense.
You don't have
to worry about me.
Appreciate it.
Tommy Carcetti,
running for mayor.
Nice to meet ya.
- How much longer?
- I think we can wrap this up.
We got a lot more
places to be today.
Tommy Carcetti.
I knew your dad.
First District Democratic Club.
- No kidding.
- Just wanted to say you got my vote.
- Thank you.
- They had their chance.
Look what shape
the city's in.
I'm hoping
to turn things around.
Anyway, thanks for your support.
I mean,
you expect politicians to steal.
- I don't, actually.
- It's part of the game. I understand.
But we took one dollar
outta every three, not two outta three,
Iike these moolies.
I mean, leave something
for the city, for Christ sake.
Am I right?
Best of luck, Councilman.
Moolies?
Sorry.
Election fliers?
Yeah, just run up,
stick 'em in mailboxes,
you know, screen doors,
whatever.
- What about the vacants?
- We ain't even got to do the vacants.
Shit. Some blocks
ain't nothing but.
That's what I'm saying.
This be easy money.
Don't wanna do it?
- I do it.
- Me too.
Yo, this shit'd
be easier if we had a car.
Dang, Donut. I'm in enough trouble
with Miss Anna as is.
So, what up, Mike?
You in?
All right, then.
I'll holla at you later, boy.
Look, Namond's been--
what's the word?
He been inconsistent.
You know sometimes he be doin' good,
then other times, he just--
We talked about that.
He gonna do better.
Ain't you?
Election day special,
two for two!
- I don't know.
- Oh, I do.
You gonna give this boy
his own package
or there gonna be some drama.
You want me to talk to Wee-Bey?
Maybe you wanna talk to him.
I give you his number.
He got a cellphone.
All that's not even necessary.
I got all the respect
in the world for Bey.
Then show some
for his family.
Make me proud, hear?
Damn, boy. Your mama's
what niggas call a dragon lady.
She don't blink.
Yeah, gimme some
insight, though.
- To what?
- Why you is what you is.
Yo. What up?
Where y'all goin'?
Hungry, man.
I need to eat.
Nah, come one.
Let's finish this.
Nah, yo.
This shit is boring.
- Fuck it.
- Listen, I ain't even gonna pay y'all
if you don't finish
the job, so...
You already
got the money?
Fool, if the motherfucker
paid you out already,
then why the hell
are we still here?
'Cause this is the job.
Shit, the man ain't got
nobody to blame but hisself.
It's his fault
for payin' up front.
Yo, you need to split
that money up or something
'cause time is a-wastin'.
Didn't even finish
the day's work.
Get me something
at least.
- Lake trout.
- Soda too?
- Yeah. Strawberry.
- A'ight. I got ya.
Hey. Where the crew at?
Randy got 'em all some job
handin' out election
fliers or whatever.
You ain't wanna do that?
Hell, no.
It's bullshit, man.
- I got a job too.
- Word?
Yeah, with Bodie.
I'm movin' the package.
You wanna go
in on it with me?
You sure?
We could work together.
Nah, man,
that's your thing.
Go do what you do.
Yeah, a'ight.
I'm gonna holler at you.
She a cute one,
ain't she?
Yeah, boy. You know
I love the women.
Hey, you seen Spider
around any?
I mean, he ain't been
'round the gym in like a month, man.
I leave messages,
he don't call.
I don't understand, man.
He was one
of my best welterweights.
Now, why would he just
quit like that?
Why don't you ask his moms?
Well, shit. I was locked up
a good while, right.
I mean
I ain't no angel.
Naw. You ain't that.
Thanks a lot, folks.
Good job. Keep it up.
We're almost home.
You're the best.
The best.
Heavy turnout all around.
Big lines on the West Side
might be bad for us.
- I dunno but--
- Shh.
We're out here
in West Baltimore,
- the heart of his political base.
- This is today?
This is live,
right now in Lafayette Square.
Clay Davis just said
his whole organization
was out going door-to-door
for Royce's ticket.
So much for laying back
on the mayor.
We paid $20,000
for this shit?
He probably went to Royce
and shook him down for another 30.
Motherfucker. Clay Davis
must know something we don't.
He knows just enough
to get paid twice.
Gotta blame ourselves
for payin' this thief up front.
Hey, it was
worth a shot.
Aides to the mayor have told me
privately that they are concerned...
Thanks, yo.
I'm-a get me a cold one.
Grab the wall.
Officer Walker.
I ain't gonna be
out here strapped.
Aw, you gonna
take that on a humble?
Boy, you don't know there's
rules to this here game.
- Rules?
- Yeah.
Ugh!
Where your shotgun at,
Mr. Omar?
What is wrong with y'all, man?
Y'all ain't got no charges here.
Charge is murder, motherfucker.
Murder? Who I kill?
Hey, Omar.
- McNulty. What the hell goin' on here?
- You tell me.
We got a warrant
for a robbery murder. In a store.
Wagon's here.
Hey, yo, McNulty,
I need a phone, yo.
Fuck your phone.
If I'm going to Booking,
I need to make a call tonight, yo.
410-958-6612.
An' let it ring.
Here.
- Hey.
- Yo, Butchie. I'm locked up, yo.
What you need?
I got your bail.
Nah, no bail.
They sayin' it's murder.
Murder?
Well, don't worry. I got ya.
You some
kinda Democrat or what?
Voter turnout was heavy
all day across the city
with some precincts
reporting lines
as soon as the polls opened
at 7:00 this morning.
Election officials, however,
reported few problems
throughout the day.
Now the polls have closed,
officials at the Board
of Elections downtown
have begun the tedious process
of tallying the vote,
prepared for what could be
a long night.
With just over half of the city's
316 precincts reporting,
Councilman Thomas J. Carcetti
has a narrow lead of 2%.
Traditionally, those precincts
that report latest
tend to be
from West Baltimore,
which is expected to favor
Mayor Royce in the late going.
- How it go?
- Good. Nothin' to it.
I'm countin' on you, Nay.
Exit polls done earlier
in the day in key precincts
show voters divided
over the challenges facing this city,
such as crime
and education.
...be quite an election.
Since this race tightened
in the last couple of weeks,
I've been saying
that this election
would be won on the ground.
And whoever has the best
field operations will take it.
It's all about the turnout,
and this is something--
What about Bond?
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Yeah.
All right.
Talk to you in a few.
Bond's running really strong
against Demper.
Looks like we might have
a new State's Attorney.
What does that
mean for you?
Well, Demper's Royce's boy.
Dare to get
your hopes up, Tommy.
You know what? Let's get
outta here for awhile,
take a walk.
I'll get your ass.
- Pretty.
- A little ripe.
Well, can't do anything about
the way the harbor smells.
People are gonna
expect you to.
I guess.
You sound confident.
I have a feeling.
Could be a great city again.
Pull some jobs in here.
People move back,
fix up the houses.
It's ringing again.
Terri.
Maybe you should answer it.
I don't need an update
every five minutes.
- No, we should go anyway.
- Do we have to?
I'm sure they're frantic.
They don't know where you are.
Yeah?
Taking a walk with my wife.
On our way.
Royce is conceding.
The West Side
precincts came in
and we pulled two
outta five votes in some precincts.
We stole his base.
We won.
Are we happy about that?
I think so.
I think we are.
Yeah.
You sure?
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Please.
I want to thank you all
for your hard work and dedication.
Give yourselves
a hand. Come on.
I just got off the phone
with Mayor Royce and Councilman Gray.
They were very gracious.
I asked for their help.
I mean, we still have
a general election to win.
Is there
a Republican candidate
for mayor in Baltimore?
I don't know. I'm not sure.
But, assuming that we win,
we still have--
we still have a lot of work
to do to turn this city around,
and we need everyone--
everyone who's willing to join us
in making a better Baltimore
for our children.
I don't want to make
a long speech. Believe me.
You don't want to hear it.
I don't want to make
a long speech,
so I'll thank each
of you individually.
But for tonight,
let's celebrate.
Tommy! Tommy!
How you doin'?
Thanks. Hey.
Damond.
I look forward to working
with you, Mr. Mayor.
Likewise.
And congratulations to you, too.
- Thank you.
- I'm going home.
No, come on. Stay.
I won't be long.
Yeah, you will.
It's your night.
Tommy. Tommy.
Look what washed up
on the beach.
Congratulations, Mr. Mayor.
Just came by to wish you well.
Looking forward
to working with you.
Shouldn't you be dead to me?
Sheee-it. I took it
easy on you, son.
I coulda had you
for twice as much.
You got off cheap.
He's right.
Butchie sent us.
What you in for?
I'm here on a 22-55.
I talked back.
- Moolie?
- Moolie.
He said that
in front of you?
He made a point of it, in fact.
You're the one said
I oughta shore up my base.
You didn't call him on it?
The ironies of democracy.
A vote's a vote.
And I never throw one back.
Speaking of ballots,
did you vote for me, Norman?
The sanctity
of the voting booth
is a cornerstone
of American democracy.
I gotta go.
You need a ride?
- Yeah.
- Come here. You're the best.
Thanks, Norman.
- Yeah, take a break.
- You got it.
One day.
Two days.
Come here, you.
- Be good.
- I'm gonna call you.
I have
a feeling you might.
Good night.
Ooh, I should go, too.
One for the road?
Sure. Scotch okay?
Sure.
You know, I gotta admit,
it feels good.
You deserve it.
You worked hard.
I did. I do.
- Cheers.
You know, when I took this job,
you promised me a win bonus.
Well, you earned it.
I can't do this.
Not now.
Oh, come on, Tommy.
You haven't changed.
Hell, from what
Norman tells me,
you nearly fell off
the campaign trail for a blonde
at the Stonewall dinner
two months ago.
He had to drag you
out of the bar.
It's not that
I don't want to--
Oh, you're feeling
a bit mayoral. Right.
You're onstage now.
Well, Tommy...
four years is a long time
for a fellow like you.
This could be
your last chance for a while.
You sure?
Maybe you have
learned something.
Write me a check.