Oh!
Oh, man!
Fuck.
- What's next?
- One to the head.
I keep it quick.
Not yet, motherfucker.
You shoot live rounds
like paint,
boy, you'll be the shit,
you hear?
Yo, but these really do
look like Glocks.
Yeah, they make them
look that way.
Yo, why you shoot low?
All right, if you're close,
aim for the head.
If not, think vest.
That's the way you said it.
A'ight.
Boy's learning.
- You going inside this one too?
- I'm gonna do the whole block.
It's bad enough
you popped the top
off one house
and give us a body.
What the fuck do you think
you're doing now?
- An experiment.
- An experiment?
Oh, fuck me.
I'm dealing with
Madam Curie here.
This nail here
comes from a nail gun,
and it comes from the house
with a dead man inside.
Every other house
has screws that H.C.D. uses.
We find these in the plywood
anywhere in this city,
and there's a body inside.
Gosh, that's good work.
No, I'm very impressed.
Do you see
a tool belt on me?
Do I look like one
of those fucking jerkoffs
in aisle five of
the Home fuckin' Depot?
There's three weeks left
in the year,
and our unit clearance
rate is under 50%.
We do not go
looking for bodies,
especially moldering
fucking John Does.
We do not put red up
on the board voluntarily.
Jay, the bodies
are in the houses,
Marlo Stanfield's bodies.
Then they belong to him.
Now I realize you're
no longer in my squad,
Mr. Major Crimes, but you're still
part of C.I.D., right?
And look,
I'm still a sergeant, right?
And I'm giving you
an order on this, Lester.
Until I feel chain-of-command
down on this
and until you hear otherwise,
you will not--
I repeat not--
pull down any more...
fucking wood!
Let's go, man.
I mean, you know,
I expect a shortfall
when I look at the school budget.
It's a natural.
But how in Christ's name
do you lose $54 million?
One million
at a time.
Exactly. It didn't
happen this morning.
This was
on Royce's watch.
You didn't get a whiff of this
during council review?
You can't blame the council or Royce
for the school budget.
The fiscal responsibility is
with the school board itself.
But the council
does have oversight.
Don't even pretend
to put this shit on me.
Only the city share shows up
on our budget review.
We never see
the state money.
You'd better tell your
pretty new chief of staff
that whatever happens
up on North Avenue
is on the school system.
That's a simplistic
view, I think.
How would you
complicate it?
As president of the school board,
I'll argue this is a bookkeeping issue.
We've simply been rolling the system's
debt over since '99.
You rolled it and rolled it
until it ran out of cash.
That's not bookkeeping,
that's stupidity.
So what are we talking
about here, waste?
Fraud? Embezzlement?
I would say that although the system
has some poor accounting practices,
in the end we're going to find
that most of the money
was properly spent
on programming.
Okay okay okay.
We get it.
No one's responsible,
not the school board,
not anybody on North Avenue,
not Clarence Royce,
not the city council,
no one at this table.
Fine.
So what's our next move?
Bump the property tax rate?
Scale back our budget.
No pay hikes, hiring freezes,
reduced services,
tell everyone-- schools,
police, fire, public works--
they have to hold the line
for a year or two.
How?
I just ran a clean-up-the-streets
campaign.
I just got done promising the world
to every cop in the city.
Annapolis.
You go beg
his Republican ass.
The Cheese stands alone.
This the drop?
I hope not, 'cause
they ain't called yet.
Make me feel bad
toward old Prop Joe.
Yeah, go around
where we can see y'all.
Vamonos, 'Naldo.
Nice hookup.
Private.
Damn, y'all some Semper Fi
motherfuckers, ain't ya?
Where Cheese go
to enlist?
That's 25 back to Joe
from what we was short before,
and another 1 50
to up our order to six.
Whoa, we had you down
for four.
I don't know if we got
extras coming off the boat.
Short someone else then.
I'll see what Joe says.
Yeah.
When we set with the re-up,
we'll hit you on that.
The shit will be where you told us
half hour later.
- Yo, we ain't using these no more.
- Us neither.
What we do is ring you
from a 958 exchange,
East Side,
don't need to answer.
Just toss it,
go to the meet.
See you when I see you.
Money on the table,
"hairon" to follow.
Stay here on Marlo?
Nah, we gonna stay
with Cheese.
Detective, would you
get the door for me?
Sometimes life just
gives you a moment, huh?
He was gonna do me,
and instead he gets done?
I'm dipped in shit here.
I'm the luckiest
motherfucker you know.
Gentlemen,
the target is still
Mr. Stanfield,
and from the look
of things,
we're no closer to him
than when I left here two months ago.
Now they might not
let me go after murders,
but they cannot stop me
from chasing the drugs.
Leander, I want you
surveilling his people.
See if they're still up
on cell phones.
How are you
with the paper trail?
- Okay.
- I want you down
at the city assessment office
pulling paper on all the purchases
on the West Side
over $100,000.
Then get down
to M.V.A. and check
Iuxury cars in his name,
all right?
Now this boy has been
in the game for a while now.
He might try
to launder money.
Herc, I want you
on the paperwork,
re-requisitioning
the wiretap equipment
that Marimow shipped
on down to l.S.D.
We're gonna need all of that
to get backup, okay?
If anyone needs me,
I'm down at Missing Persons,
all right?
Let's go.
- Lester?
- Yes?
- All this is cool...
- Mm-hmm.
...but you think we can do it
so that the direction comes from me?
I mean,
I am the sergeant here.
Donut, you think
this look right?
Why you knock 'em down?
So the police
won't scope me so easy.
But now all they gotta do is be like,
"Yeah, go over there
and just grab that little nigger
with the braids."
Damn, boy, you later
than a motherfucker.
Been sitting out here
watching money walk away.
You about to have
the day off.
Package was stolen, Na'.
What? Out the back
of your basement?
They kicked my motherfucking door in.
That's how they do.
Well, look,
how the police know
where you even be keeping
your stash at?
Some snitch-ass bitch,
that's how they know.
I'ma find his ass too.
All right, man, I'm out.
I never did understand
why you stopped eating the pig.
I ain't been in a Polack Johnny's
since 1974,
and if you knew what
was good for you--
Look, I know what's good.
I remember when you did too.
I never saw you
going all Muslim on me.
Ain't that, but I do
believe that other faiths
have got the pig figured
better than us A.M.E.s.
See that?
If you checking out,
I might feel the need
to say a few words.
Nah, I ain't got nothing
to do with that.
I love my PJs,
but they do repeat on me.
As memory serves,
you got to go with the original sauce,
not the kraut and chili
like you do.
My pain ain't
about no sauerkraut.
"The Puzzle Palace"
is ready to clip any program
that ain't tied
to the statewide tests.
The thing is, we're just starting
to make a little headway
- in what we're doing.
- You take it upstairs?
Yeah, me and the professor
went all the way
- to go see the school superintendent.
- And?
You read the papers?
They're a little busy
ducking that budget mess.
$50 million in the hole,
and they're scared
to take any more problems
to the new mayor.
- Is your thing a problem?
- Depends on how you look at it.
A cover-your-ass
type of person might say
we're just tracking any students
that can't hack in the regular classes,
giving them work that don't show up
on no statewide tests.
City Hall says it's okay,
they keep our program.
If not, we on the street.
Odell Watkins.
I was hoping
you'd say that name.
Yeah, he got
Carcetti's ear.
If we sell him,
maybe we sell the Hall.
Stalk that nigger, man,
that stole your shit.
- Yeah.
- Soon as he nod out,
bust him in the head
with a brick or some shit.
Nah nah.
That ain't me.
You can always give him
a hotshot then.
Y'all recall Junior Bunk?
Cutting his shit with,
uh, what you call it?
Stole it from
the funeral home.
Oh, you thinking
formaldehyde.
That's the shit.
Nigger's got a taste
of that shit,
university started
a "Junior Bunk" ward.
My cousin laid his ignorant ass
up there two, three times.
Ain't no guarantee
in that, though.
Use some rat poison then.
No, man, that stuff
don't cook up right.
What you need to use
is that sodium cyanide.
That shit looks and cooks
- just like the real thing.
- Where I find that?
Try, uh, Minter's
over there by the tracks,
or one of those metal shops
where they do plating.
- How much I need?
- It ain't gonna take much.
A vial of that shit'd kill every horse
in this stable.
- That's all there is to it?
- It ain't no thing to kill a nigger
who's already about the business
of killing himself.
And the police, they ain't
gonna pay no never mind.
You the one's got
to live with it is all.
More young males
than I'd have thought.
I don't suppose they all went off
in search of adventure.
You get a chance to do any
street work on these files?
Shit, no, Lester.
They cut Missing Persons
to one detective five years ago.
I barely keep up
with the paperwork.
Feel free.
Just make copies and return
the originals for the files.
For the files... right.
Damn, son.
Kenard said
the police took it?
He said they
kicked his door in.
And they ain't
lock no one up?
Yo, you see
that door?
Were the hinges broke?
I mean, if he said
they put the boot to it...
them hinges
gotta be hanging free.
I sweated him, yo.
He wasn't
trying to scheme me.
That little motherfucker
took that shit for himself.
Bet it.
And now you gotta
step to him,
put something real
behind them words.
Where your
Spanish boy at?
He's down on point with Cheese
while I round up soldiers.
You got soldiers
right here.
Your 2255 must have
pleased some judge, huh?
Enough to get me home,
didn't it?
I'm just saying, Butch,
I know they soldiers,
but I'm thinking about
being a little more subtle on this one.
You feel me?
So they don't see me coming.
It ain't like you
to work with strangers.
I'm celebrating diversity.
I'm thinking now the time
to start doing that.
Oh-hoo! What up, shorty?
What's up, baby?
- Mm, mm.
- Mm.
- Damn, girl, you looking good.
- I'm maintaining.
- Shit, I know that's right.
- You doing all right?
Yeah.
Long time, long time.
I got your word. Some real money
to be made on this one, huh?
You remember
how to do this?
I reckon it'll
come back to me.
See that's what
I'm talking about, Butch--
- subtle.
- Hmm.
Glasses first,
so they don't spot.
Yes, ma'am.
- Hello.
- Ho, Mr. Prezbo.
- Come in, please.
- Oh, that's okay.
I just wanted to stop by
on my way home
and drop off Randy's
work for next week.
Hopefully this thing
will be over soon.
Maybe so, but we're looking
at the possibility
of moving him to Booker T. Washington
next semester.
I hope
that isn't necessary.
I hope so too. Anyway, thanks
for bringing this.
I'll try to keep him
up to speed.
- Hang in there, kiddo.
- Thanks.
Long conference call.
About an hour
so far by my watch.
Got me out here
riding the wood.
Unfortunately
the governor's phone call
has gone longer
than anticipated.
Can I get you anything?
Coffee?
Look, I have
other appointments.
It shouldn't be
much longer.
Check out Fisher's
column in Metro.
He says,
the governor thinks, quote,
"This latest fiscal emergency
calls into question
the Baltimore school system's
ability to manage itself
as well as the local
oversight of the system,"
unquote.
Motherfucker.
He's playing
to the D.C. suburbs.
He sees you coming for him
two years from now.
He ain't no fool.
There's all your electronic
requisitions right there.
Mm-hmm.
What one's that, a cop?
Nah, security guard.
I don't think he's
one of Marlo's, though.
Lieutenant.
Will someone explain to me
what the fuck the brass is doing?
First I get bounced
to telephone reporting,
then I get
a call this morning...
How's that beach house
coming, huh?
It's almost done.
I just need a load of lumber--
That's great,
just great.
Welcome.
Welcome back.
Who the fuck is that?
That, Sergeant Hauk...
is one of the most
effective supervisors
in our police department.
Sorry. It's just taking a little longer
than we expected.
It shouldn't be
much longer, though.
I understand
what you're saying.
Some of those kids
are ready for high school,
but not Duquan.
- I've...
-...adopted him?
I've noticed Duquan
this semester.
He's more nourished,
wears fresher clothes.
Sometimes he even
smells like soap.
You and your wife,
you don't have children,
do you?
- Not yet, no.
- Well, have some.
For better or for worse,
they're yours for life.
The kids in this school
aren't yours.
You do your piece with them,
and you let them go.
Because there'll be plenty more
coming up behind Duquan,
and they're gonna
need your help too.
You've got your third period
in five minutes, right?
Settle down.
We need to concentrate
on these tests.
- Aw, fuck this, man.
- Talking about, "lf Jane's father
gives Jane one week's
worth of allowance..."
Shit, I ain't got
no allowance where I stay at.
No father, neither.
How many sides a sexagon got?
Why I care about that?
You need to take the test
so you can move on to the next level.
I ain't moving nowhere
but out this motherfucker.
- Hell, yeah.
- All right. Let's settle down.
Let's start with
question number one.
Settle down!
All right.
All right, listen up.
Here's the problem:
Two couples go
into a restaurant.
- They get the check--
- Yo, when they say "couples,"
- do it mean they married?
- Why they got to be married?
Mr. Prezbo, why you
even get married?
Well, to build a life
together, for one--
you know, family.
- Also to have intimacy.
- What do that mean?
- Mean, like, getting some.
- No no. It's not just that.
Intimacy can be, um,
a quiet conversation.
Or it can be fun,
you know?
Like when you tickle
your partner.
Yo, tickle my nuts.
All right, all right,
no more of that.
Come on, let's get
to the test material.
The statewide exam
is next week.
And then we'll get back
to the regular lessons.
Can we talk
about intimacy?
If you like, and if I don't
get too embarrassed.
All right, uh... so,
the grand total on the check
is $67.40, but if they
want to leave a tip--
Look at your
sample test, please.
I got to say, Ms. Duquette,
I feel like y'all schemed us.
This class is the same
as the ones down the hall.
Yeah, it's 'cause
the test's coming up.
Okay, class, let's take a look
at the sample math test.
In sample "A",
we start with...
Kid's right.
This is bullshit.
The test material doesn't
exactly speak to their world.
Yeah, don't speak
too loud to mine, either.
An estimate,
Detective.
We start opening
those houses,
we might turn over
a couple of dozen bodies,
but that's
just me guessing.
All of them homicides?
The boy took over
half the West Side.
We never saw the violence.
This right here
is the reason why.
You're asking us to call out
half of public works
and pull the plywood off
thousands of vacant houses
all so we can raise
the city's murder rate by 10%?
What else are we doing
on Stanfield?
I'm trying to get backup
on his people's cell phones
as fast as I can.
And I started to look
for his money.
But if I'm right about this,
they have to be worked.
Is there any evidence at all that
links all these missing-persons reports
to the Stanfield
organization?
I'm just starting at that.
The one body
that we pulled out of the Fulton
Avenue house is Lex.
His case is a direct tie.
And there are two other names
on those missing persons reports
that show up in our wiretaps
from earlier this year.
So, yes, there are links,
Counselor.
By any chance did Landsman
run this up the chain
to you guys?
No.
Your call.
My office won't care
until they see case files.
I'll run it upstairs
and we'll see what comes.
- Okay, I get it.
- He's still tied up,
but it really should only be
a little while longer.
Can you tell the governor
I have to go back to Baltimore?
I have a little bit
of business today.
I'm the mayor of a major American city,
for chrissakes.
How much shit do l
have to eat from this guy?
Wouldn't you play the politics
if you were him?
It's not like the state
had no role in this thing.
You know, the state money for those
schools had no oversight either.
But I'm not telling
"The Washington" fucking "Post,"
talking about how he might be forced
to bail me out because--
what was the quote again?
Because "Those are my children
in Baltimore too."
He's gonna bleed me
for that money.
Mayor Carcetti?
The governor's office says he's
ready to see you now.
$54 million's a big number.
We won't go until we get some,
we won't go until we get some--
Did I do
something wrong?
I ain't acted up or nothing.
You're ready for this.
You can do the work.
I know you can.
And if you need
to come back here
and use the showers
or give me laundry,
use the computer,
you can do that any time.
Anyway,
let me show you.
This here's the way
to the hard drive.
This isn't
necessary, Duquan.
Just in case
I'm busy, Mr. P.
So you know
how to work it.
Hey, boy.
What's up?
Big day for you.
See here?
I got the inventory
divided between us.
You gonna go up one way
towards North Avenue...
and I'm gonna stay down
by the highway.
You gonna let me handle
the money alone?
- You ready, ain't you?
- Yeah, I'm good.
All right.
Let's get on it.
I see you
back here tonight.
All right.
Hey hey, you see that foul motherfucker,
you let him have his money, okay?
I don't need you
messing with him.
- All right.
Make sure
that count's right!
Yo, I need to talk to
the little motherfucker.
Maybe you can
do that with me,
see it don't
get out of hand.
Hey! Yo, Mike!
Yo, what up, Duke?
Yeah, I heard Randy's foster ma
gonna take him out of Tilghman too,
send him somewhere else.
That's messed up, man.
All right,
holla, man.
How many?
As a theory,
Detective Freamon
believes there could be
additional bodies in those vacants,
maybe a dozen or more.
- He believes?
- Lester Freamon is not in the habit
of selling woof tickets.
I, for one,
would not bet against him.
And what do you suggest
I do with this information?
My feeling is
that City Hall should be
brought into the loop.
We pull the bodies now
before New Year's,
and the stats go to Royce's
last year in office.
Matter of fact,
it gives Carcetti an advantage
with regards to
next year's crime rate.
- You mean--
- Tell the mayor that now is the time
to empty those houses,
not next year, when it's on his watch
and he has to eat the stats.
Colonel, I see you've
thought this through,
politically, I mean.
- I'm learning as I go.
- I bet you fuckin' are.
Colonel, keep this
conversation close.
That's a direct order.
You seen them girls
at Douglass, man?
Yo, you right, Duke.
Ain't gonna be like
middle school no more.
You know,
I'm just thinking, yo.
Dag, man, not again.
Where your
people at now?
Need any of your
stuff from the pile?
It ain't no thing.
Yo, man, listen.
Me and Bug got
our own spot now,
so you could come
crib with us if you want.
What you mean
Kenard took the stash?
And he's still
walking around?
I'm gonna talk to him, Ma,
make sure this never happen again.
Look at me, boy.
Kenard got to feel
some pain for what he did.
- He got to.
- I don't--
You don't what,
motherfucker?!
This how you pay me back
for all the love I showed?
Shit, I been kept you in Nikes
since you were in diapers.
- I'm trying.
- You trying, huh?
That's what you
gonna tell your father
the next time you see him,
that you trying?
Or you gonna tell him
what you've done?
What he done
got him locked up--
That's right. Wee-Bey walked
in Jessup a man,
and he gonna walk out one.
But you out here,
wearing his name,
acting a bitch!
Aw, look at you,
crying now.
Fuck you think you going?
Get your ass back here.
I ain't done talking to you.
I mean, I'm police, right?
Murder police,
and I got bodies.
I'm just supposed
to let them laying lie?
"We don't throw red up
on that board voluntarily."
That John-Goodman-
off-his-diet-looking
motherfucker
was clear on that.
- So go over Landsman's head.
- Mm, Jimmy, that's you--
send an anonymous fax. But you see,
Lester here don't fancy boats.
And me, I get sick
just filling the bathtub.
It's just wrong.
Yeah, just like when I seen J-Lo with
that little itty-bitty Spanish dude.
Genius. He hid his mausoleum
right in the neighborhood.
How little Pedro gonna
fill that big thing up?
Oh, man, that girl got
a prime cut of ass, boy.
- And a good heart.
- A good inverted heart.
This nail's
like their signature.
Find it in any door
in the West Side,
and right as rain
you're gonna find a body.
Yes, sir. I'm proud to be
chasing Mr. Marlo Stanfield.
Man, you act like you on the trail
of Pol Pot or some shit.
- Who?
- Motherfucker, I got $10 says
we can leave here
right now,
go to any boarded-up
rowhouse
with a nail like that
in the door,
and we will find a body.
- Make it $20.
- There you go.
Well, but first let's have another
little taste. Jimmy, you in?
- No, I'm good.
- Oh, come on, man.
Take that skirt off and have a drink,
for chrissakes.
- Drink that.
- Agh!
Man, don't play
like that. Aww.
Icicles, get 'em
before they melt!
Icicles!
Icicles, come get 'em!
Hey, yo, Kenard.
Why you lie to me?
Fuck you talkin' about?
You said the police
kicked your door in.
I seen the door.
They ain't kicked shit in.
- How you gonna lie?
- Go on, man.
- Yo, where the package at, man?
- Package up my ass, gump.
- I'm about to--
- You about to?
Go on, walk,
gump-ass motherfucker.
Hey, yo,
Iook at that little dude
getting his ass beat!
Y'all was talking too goddamn much.
Go ahead, Na'.
Get your pack off
this bitch so we can go.
I don't want it.
I'll take that
20 now, Bunk.
I can't see shit in here.
Aw, man. I might pull out
my wallet, reach in,
and pull out
a $25 by mistake.
I need me some
Braille bills, something.
Hmm.
You ladies want
to call the Crime Lab?
Nah, man.
I'm like Stevie: too high.
You know I can't do no scene.
Well, there's not gonna be one,
on account of there is no body,
not until the bosses say there is.
And when that happens,
you gonna miss
all the fun, junior.
You know Daniels is gonna
keep this alive.
The white shirts will fuck it up
somehow. You know it, Lester.
Maybe not, this time.
Daniels is C.I.D.
It's a new day downtown.
I got it.
Whew,
world is on its hole
when Jimmy McNulty is
the most qualified to drive.
Yeah, up is down,
black is white... Ieft is right.
What we got here, huh?
- Quiet overnight.
- Cool.
Relief will be here
for you after roll call.
It's Sergeant Carver.
How you doing, dawg?
Quiet overnight.
You going to school
this morning?
We're gonna wait a little
longer on that to be sure,
but I can't say
I'm comfortable
going to work every day
and leaving him here.
Blow over in a week
or so, you'll see.
Till then we still have
a car on the house,
and you have my cell number
if anything comes up.
We're gonna look out
for you on this.
- Have you had breakfast, Sergeant?
- No, but I gotta--
You have time
for a plate, I'm sure.
Sure.
Yo,
I just dreamt something
gave me an idea today.
Hey, Sherrod.
You remember when
we turned that knocked down
Iight pole at the scales?
Pulled $80?
I been thinking
we can get to toppling
a couple of those
bad boys ourselves,
get all Paul Bunyan
and shit, you know?
I mean, we'll be all
discreet and all.
Not take the hacksaw
to no more than a couple
on some quiet streets,
leave more than enough
for some people
to have light and all.
Thing is,
I got this other thing
I still need to
take care of today.
Come on, Sherrod.
Wake up.
It's late.
No no no!
What you do? What you do?
What you do?
Aw, man, come on,
Sherrod.
Come on, man.
Come on. Come on.
You weren't supposed
to do this, man!
Oh, man!
- No phones?
- Not a one.
And the players that
were using them before--
Chris, Monk, Ray-Ray--
they were out there
on those corners.
Now I would have seen if
someone went to a burner.
God damn it!
If we just stayed up
on the wire two months ago,
we wouldn't be
going through this sh--
Can I help you?
Which one of you
is Sergeant Hauk?
I am.
I'm Shea.
This is Thomas. I.I.D.
Let me ask
if you remember
pulling a surveillance
camera from l.S.D.,
serial number AW466J9.
You remember that?
We also need to go over
your paperwork
on a couple of informants,
so if you don't mind
coming back downtown with us,
you and...
Detective Sydnor
and the third guy,
what's his name?
Dozerman.
You don't need
Sydnor or Doze, either.
Paperwork's all mine--
on the camera,
on the informants,
me alone.
Bodies?
How many?
Could be quite a few. We won't
know until we take down those doors.
And this is one drug organization
you think did this?
That's the theory, but nothing's
certain at this point.
What is certain is that
if we're going to do this,
you probably want us to do it now,
before the new year,
while the bump
in the murder rate
is still attributable
to Mayor Royce.
Thoughtful, Deputy,
very thoughtful.
I don't want any more stat games
from your department.
You need to get your people
into those houses because if there are
bodies in there,
they need to come out.
But do it now.
I don't want to be finding
any more bodies come January.
Yes, sir,
Mr. Mayor, sir.
Choice comes down to this:
We take the state money,
and instead of being
fucked up and broke,
our schools go back to being
merely fucked up.
No teacher layoffs, no program cuts,
no school closures.
But the price
the governor's asking is
more state control
over the school board
and changes in the teachers' union
contracts that would allow them
- to remove tenured faculty for cause.
- Ouch.
If we don't take the money,
it looks like we're shorting our kids.
We take the money-- we're giving up
local control of education,
which is gonna lose us
a lot of middleclass black folks.
Not to mention the problem
you might have two years from now
running in the D.C.
suburbs,
explaining how you
needed their money
to bail out
your schools.
He sees you coming, Tommy.
That's not
important right now.
Take the money.
We need it.
Don't look at me.
If you take it,
you're selling out the teachers,
and that's my base.
If you don't take it,
you're selling out the kids.
Either way, I'll probably rip you,
and half the council will too.
Just glad
I'm not the mayor.
- You called?
- Word down the chain: Open 'em up.
And it's my guess this case
is gonna need more manpower.
Yeah, no doubt.
In fact,
I might have lost Herc
to an l.I.D. file.
Really? I went light
on him for that car stop.
I didn't even think
it would get to a trial board.
This feels like
a bigger jacket.
Pick any two you want
from C.I.D. for now.
If you get back up on a wire,
we'll detail a few more.
Beautiful.
I don't know what
you're talking about,
but she was hot.
I'm going back on Friday
right after work.
Hold on.
What the fuck
are you staring at?
How are you
liking Homicide?
Loving it. Why?
Anyway.
It's on the way, boss.
It's Joe
and his message,
but we already know
what it is.
All right, girl.
Keep it close.
All right, 'Naldo, call your amigos
and tell them it's on.
That's right.
Yep. That's it.
One, come on.
Let me see
that footwork.
That's it.
One, one,
one, one.
That's right.
Yo, what's going on,
Mike?
Man, yo, I feel like
I could just pancake
a young'un right now,
you know what I mean?
What about you, Duke?
Want some go?
No, I'ma
work this rope.
Yeah, you working it.
Like a gump.
They pull around back,
we're gonna come at 'em
from both ways, feel me?
Ooh.
Hey, yo, call your friends,
tell 'em where we at.
Yo, let me get that rope.
I said I'm workin' it.
Man, I said you's a gump,
fucking dogshit
and smelling-ass nigger.
Hey. Hey! Hey!
Man, fuck this.
Yeah! Go along! Get!
Don't nobody want you
in here, no way!
You see what happened?
That be it.
Hey, Daddy.
Kiss the butt
of this lyricist.
Blow on my mike
and make a wish.
Get up! Everybody, get up.
Get up!
Let me get a $10, Daddy.
Let me get a $10. I need a $10.
Get the fuck
out of here, now.
- Come on, I'll suck your dick for $15.
- Trick-ass bitch, I said get.
Don't you want
to see my stuff?
Nah, ain't nobody
want to see that stink box.
- Get your ass gone.
- Come on, let me get a $10, player.
What the fuck is this,
the lnner Harbor?
Yo, what the fuck y'all
think you doing?
- We painters.
- Si, we paint.
Move the van out the way.
Oh, you gonna like
what I got, soldier.
See? We paint.
We paint.
Oh... okay.
Which one of y'all
gonna open the truck for me?
Fucking amateurs.
Drink it slow, son.
What am I gonna do?
I'll run you home.
I-- I can't go home.
She expect me
to be my father, but...
I ain't him.
I mean, the way
he is and shit...
it just ain't in me.
What's between
you and Michael?
Mike ain't Mike no more.
He went hard
on this boy last night,
fucked his shit up.
I can't go home.
I can't.
Give us a minute.
Mad at myself, man.
I shouldn't have shut
Michael out like I did.
Namond did push it.
He ain't pushing
nothing now.
Reckon I'll go
mend the fence.
This ain't no motel.
Deacon, how'd you
get by my people?
You can't turn away church folk,
ain't done in these parts.
You only come by
for a favor, so what is it?
You know a fella
named Bunny Colvin?
Yeah, that rogue
police commander,
tried to legalize drugs.
- What's he done now?
- He can tell you best.
You did not bring--
It's something
positive, Odell.
- Has to do with kids.
- Positive, huh?
Bunny.
Delegate Watkins.
What's this all about?
It's another bright idea.
- You Michael Lee's mother?
- He got papers on him or something?
I ain't no kind of police.
- I'm just looking to get up with him.
- You ain't alone.
He booked on out of here,
got his own spot,
took his little
brother with him.
- You know where he stay at?
- He ain't tell me nothing.
You find the boy, you let him know
I need some help around here.
I popped him
and Bug out my ass,
and now they forgot
where they came from.
What my ma say
when you called?
She was mad, right?
Not really.
His mother...
Lovely lady.
What she say?
"Put that bitch in baby booking
where he belongs,
Iet him learn
something."
She hung up
before I could
tell her we didn't
have a charge.
Baltimore City 911.
Yeah, they beating a cop
over here on Pennsie and Gold.
- Police officer?
- Yeah, they're beating on him bad.
- Pennsylvania and Gold?
- Yo, they firing shots now.
Signal 13, report of shots
fired, Pennsylvania and Gold.
Signal 13--
They cleaned
the motherfucker out, Joe,
put it in the van them Mexican
niggers rolled in.
I ain't hearing
about no resistance.
Man, wasn't
no time for that.
Omar had one of them
commando squads with him, man.
I mean,
he had this one ho
pulling guns
out her pussy, Unc.
The shit was unseemly, man.
I got to hand it
to Mr. Little,
- I ain't see this one coming.
- They took the shipment, Joe.
Not no package, man,
the motherfucking shipment.
Man, what we gonna
tell the co-op?
Hey, where you think
my mind at right now?
All I know, it's a lot of gangsters
out a lot of shit, man.
I say we mob up and go
find this faggot, see?
That's what's really 'hood right there.
That's how you deal with shit.
A lotta gangsters in that room need to
take us at our word first.
Yeah, first thing
they gonna wonder about...
is us.
You need to see my man.
I'll hook you up.
Who is this motherfucker?
Let me get
a word with you, Mike.
Listen, you got
to understand
I can't be having
no physical confrontation
Iike the one took
place back there.
That kind of thing
got to stay outside my gym.
Yeah. Go ahead, Montel.
I come to tell you
I was wrong,
the way I handled it.
Step off, nigger.
Mike...
Don't touch me, man.
Look, man,
this here ain't you.
Man don't want you
touching on him.
Mike.
I told you,
step the fuck off.
Young man, if I was talking
to you, you'd know I was.
Shit!
He'll listen next time.
Go ahead, man.
Do him.
Nah, man.
I'll hang here
for the ambo, all right?
Go with your people.
Go ahead, son.
Dr. Johnson, please call Neuro l.C.U.
I'm sorry, son.
I'm gonna talk
to Social Services.
We'll get you some help.
Randy...
Would the on-call please
return to Neuro l.C.U.?
On-call, please
return to Neuro l.C.U.
You gonna help, huh?
You gonna
look out for me?
You gonna look out for me,
Sergeant Carver?
Do you mean it?
You gonna
look out for me?
You promise?
You got my back, huh?!