You been nipping
at me all night, son.
Thing I got to figure is,
is you ready to
bite the whole ass?
Ain't me with
a mountain by my elbow.
Oh, so you
doing all right.
You like the Town Car?
You young'uns, you
all into them Lexus
and hum-fucking VSU
fucking U-ray or some shit,
I don't know.
See, but me?
I like me a Town Car.
Man look quiet and correct
in one of them.
So, I tell you what--
you win this,
you be sure to pick one
up for yourself, son.
Bye-bye.
Showtime.
Shit, nigger, turn.
Man got clubs.
One day soon I'm walking out
with a Rolls, hear?
Way you been going to school
up in this here room, son,
I suspect you're gonna
walk out of here
with Morgan-fucking-Freeman
to drive it for you, too.
See y'all
next time.
Yo.
I'm up the grocery
on Monroe.
All right.
Water, $1.
What the fuck?
You think I dream of
coming to work
up in this shit
on a Sunday morning?
Tell all my friends
what a good job I got?
I'm working to support
a family, man.
Pretend I ain't
talking to you.
Pretend like I ain't
even on this earth.
I know what you are.
And I ain't stepping to,
but I am a man.
And you just
clip that shit
and act like you don't
even know I'm there.
I don't.
I'm here.
Look, I told you
I wasn't stepping to you.
I ain't disrespecting you, son.
You want it
to be one way.
What?
You want it
to be one way.
Man, I don't
know what you're--
- You want it to be one way.
- Man, stop.
Stop saying that.
But it's the other way.
I'm saying, man, the way she
was all, "aah" on Chiquan,
Iike, like,
like, like,
"Laugh now,
stanky bitch!
Laugh now, huh?
How you like this?
How you like I cut your
titties off, huh?"
Man, get the fuck
away from me.
"How you like I carve
your pussy to your chin?"
Yo, come on, come on,
come on, come on.
- What?
- He said leave him be, so leave him be.
- I'm just saying.
- You're just saying.
That's all you
ever do, just say.
Dude, shit was
fucked up.
So it was fucked up.
Her father killed,
like, three police.
- What?
- Nah, it's true.
Her father killed like three police,
and her mama boil cats.
- Nigga, please, man.
- It's what I heard. She boil cats and
serve 'em and shit.
Serve 'em to who,
boiled-cat-eating motherfuckers?
- Who want him some boiled cats, huh?
- Heard that's how she live.
Nigger, you been boiled.
Laetitia live up one of them
group homes off Edmondson.
In them places,
you don't need to eat cats
to make you crazy.
Hey, Coach!
If the boy not coming, you might as
well let me and Michael go in the ring.
Ain't none of y'all
seen Spider today?
I ain't seen him.
Now how in the hell
he gonna fight next week
if he don't
show up to train?
I tell you what--
until the boy shows up
for his lesson,
you can lace 'em up and
step on the mat one time.
Ha ha ha!
No no no no no.
Not him.
Me.
Oh-ho-ho-ho.
Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna show you as
gently as I can how much
- you don't know, a'ight?
- A'ight.
Yeah, nigger,
that's yo ass.
You about to get
yo ass whipped.
Your Sabbath best?
You hang around, you can see me
preach on some young'uns,
solemn left and
sanctified right.
Why you down here on
a Sunday, Deacon?
You need to see Ms. Donnelly
at Tilghman Middle.
She's got some custodial work,
you might call it.
Union wage.
- Custodial?
- See Ms. Donnelly tomorrow.
She can explain it
better than I can.
Tell me something--
how is it you got
so much wisdom
about who
should be where?
A good church man
is always up in everybody's shit.
That's how we do.
Yo, Coach,
you ready?
Who's winning?
No one wins.
One side just
loses more slowly.
Why don't we get
out of the house?
Take a walk.
It's a nice day.
I got this talk I got to
give to my first period...
about what happened.
An hour.
I got--
I gotta say something
to those kids.
I mean--
Okay.
See?
Somebody's winning.
I didn't expect
you till tomorrow.
I heard my new squad
had the weekend shift.
And besides, I figured
if I got my shit
out of Major Crimes
on the Sunday,
I wouldn't have to run into
that cocksucker Marimow.
Marimow does not
cast off talent lightly.
He heaves it away
with great force.
Freamon got
here Friday.
Yeah, Lester's
quick like that.
There's the colonel's office.
This is my humble abode.
The board.
And over here,
this is your desk.
- It's clean.
- You'll fix that.
A clean desk is
the sign of a sick mind.
Homicide.
Damn.
I don't know where
your chair went.
Make that your
first case.
And put that down, will you?
You live here now.
Ooh, look.
Actual po-lice work.
- Any of these?
- He the one, right there.
Just put it
to Fruit's head,
and the next thing Fruit
on the ground flopping,
and his girl
all screaming,
and this pink shit coming out
the side of his head.
"The Bunk,"
working weekends.
The man's dedicated.
I'm gonna partner you with
Crutchfield to get started.
You won't catch anything
as a primary for the first few months.
Give you time
to learn the basics.
Our H files by year.
Witness dump.
Our cut necktie
mausoleum.
The coffee...
and the mailboxes, arranged
by shift and squad.
Lester.
I believe you two refugees
know each other well.
Still getting your
head around it?
A bit, yeah.
You'll do fine.
Just fine.
As tender as this moment may be,
Detective, you've got mail.
You got Lyon
on your ass already?
Another switch-up
on the methane probes.
I'd call that number.
Get on top of that shit
before you catch a case,
chair or no chair.
What the hell is
a methane probe?
Hello, Kathleen O'Shea.
- Yes, hello?
- Mm-hmm.
I need to speak with Mr. Lyon
about the protocols.
I beg your pardon?
Mr. Lyon, please.
You sound a little
old for this, hon.
Excuse me?
Who is this?
This is Detective
Greggs with the--
This is
the Baltimore City Zoo.
Fine, and this is
Detective Greggs--
and you're calling
for a "Mr. Lion."
I'm sorry.
I misdialed.
Hee hee hee.
Methane probe.
- Scarred-up faggot.
- Hmm.
I need to
hunt him down,
'cause there ain't no protection
against that shit.
Huh.
Can't plan
against that nigger.
It's like, like,
you know what he's like.
What he like?
He like one of them
terrorist motherfuckers.
Just blowing up
shit just to.
Don't care who get hurt,
what kind of sense it makes.
He got a point.
And the government, right?
If they have one of
them terrorist attacks,
they cut Delta or
whoever some slack.
The insurance companies,
the banks,
the whole NASDAQ and shit get some
time to pay back what they owe,
because the government know
ain't nothing they could do.
Huh.
Yeah, I know you see it.
You see the big picture.
Problem with niggers today,
they always see the narrow view.
That's nice.
What?
Oh, you like that?
I had it for
a long time now.
It's got some
sentimental values.
- Just a thing.
- What's the real value?
- Huh?
- Real value?
I ain't much
for sentiment.
Oh, you know.
It's been a while
since I checked.
I mean, the fluctuation
in the global economy and all.
- I'll find out for you.
- You don't have to.
I'll find out for you.
Finger's swelled
over the years.
- Need some help?
- Yeah, man, you need help?
Nah, I got it,
I got it.
- Maybe use some spit.
- I don't want the man's spit.
No, I got it now.
Omar ain't no terrorist.
He just another
nigger with a gun.
And you ain't no
Delta Airlines, neither.
You just a nigger
got your shit took.
So, bring me
what you owe
and talk that global
economy mess somewhere else.
Feel me?
Yeah.
I got another game.
How much you
down already?
Learning their ways
requires some patience.
Some money, too.
How much you need
this time out?
A hundred and a half
ought to do.
A hundred and a half?
I take that chicken-nose
fool one day soon.
Take Super Stick, too.
Take 'em all.
Else, maybe I get bored,
send you to take 'em.
And my point,
Colonel Foerster,
is that your man Norris,
he's fucking the dog
on this, way I hear it.
Sir, this is
a top priority case,
and Norris knows there's a possibility
of a murdered state's witness.
We don't even know yet
if that was the motive
for the murder.
This is my point.
Norris is a pro, sir.
His clearance rate this
year says otherwise, Colonel.
Sir, Norris is
good police.
Look Ray, we need someone
who can work it hard,
work it around the clock,
work it till it falls.
And I understand we just pumped
some fresh blood into Homicide--
female, took one in
the line a few years back.
She's never
worked Homicide.
Fresh eyes, then.
But with all
due respect, sir,
if I could guarantee that
no further information
on this case would be
leaked to the press,
certainly not before
election day,
would it be
possible to keep
veteran investigators
working it, sir?
I resent the implication.
My apologies, sir.
You killing my time
coming up here.
And if you ain't noticed,
it's costing us money.
How am I gonna trust you
if you keep telling lies,
saying one thing
and doing another?
I just missed Friday,
that's all.
Look, think on it
like this--
School is work. They're the
same thing right now.
So, you skipping out on school
is like not showing up for work.
And I done heard, made up,
and tested every excuse invented.
So, unless you dead or dying,
there ain't none you can use.
I told you I'm-a go.
Yeah, okay, I know.
For school or out the business,
you are gonna go. Come on.
Falling behind now isn't the way
to start out a school year,
particularly after
a three-year hiatus.
We haven't seen you
since you enrolled.
Is there a reason
you haven't joined us?
Look, I know you reaching out
for Sherrod.
I want to apologize
for the boy
because he's been working hard
at helping me get a business going.
But he need
to be here though.
Ain't no
bout a-doubt it.
It's up to him,
isn't it?
That's what I've
been trying to say.
That's it right there.
What about it,
young man?
I'm good.
Okay.
One thing though been
bothering me, ma'am--
if Sherrod already missed
the last three years,
should he maybe be back in
the fifth or sixth grade,
instead of up with his age?
I mean, so he can
follow the work.
Social promotion.
Excuse me?
We don't have the resources
to repeat grade levels,
and we feel to place the older children
in the younger classes
is unfair to teachers who are
responsible for maintaining order.
Your nephew has been
socially promoted.
He's an eighth-grader,
headed to high school.
Sorry, but Ms. Johnson's
here about Qadriyyah.
Excuse me for a moment.
- Bill, this is nuts.
- I told him that.
You know if this gets out, who
do you think it's gonna land on?
I got two years to make
40 and a pension bump.
Look, I don't agree
with the call either,
but it's his call,
not yours, not mine.
He's the one
over at City Hall
every day getting
his ass chewed.
I don't care about
nothing you say, man,
'cause if you start
shit, you can't
complain how somebody
finish that shit.
Man, she was on her
from the beginning
with the mirror
and everything, man.
I wouldn't have waited.
Mr. Pryzbylewski,
this is Sherrod.
- And he's all yours.
- Okay.
Take a seat, Sherrod.
Okay, listen up.
I'd like to--
everybody--
everybody,
I'd like to talk--
Listen up!
Now, we all know
something, um,
unpleasant happened
here Friday,
and, look,
I know some of you are still trying
to get your heads around--
Ain't my head
got a big old gash.
And, uh, l'd
like to discuss--
- Yo, is it true that you police?
- What?
Miss Carmandy up in the office say,
"Mr. Prezbo, he police."
- Yo, you police, man?
- You ever shoot somebody?
I think we should
talk about--
He ain't shot no one.
Look at him. Yo,
you ever bust a man
named Ashanti Graham?
Sometimes when
something bad happens--
- That your dad?
- Nah, my brother.
Why can't you tell us
if you shot somebody or not?
- What kind of gun you carry?
- You Narco?
I used to be police.
Now I'm a teacher.
But being a police isn't
just about carrying a gun.
Yeah, right.
It's about working
with the community.
The community?
Y'all ain't been up in my community
in a long time except
to whale on people.
Yo, Mr. P,
you ever been shot?
I mean, like, bah.
Namond,
that's enough.
Get up.
Get back in your seats.
Thank you,
very entertaining.
Sit down.
Get in your seats!
Sit down, sit down.
Kwaneese, sit down.
Sit down, now.
Yo, Mr. P, you ever
choke somebody dead like--
Yo, you ever
get videoed?
Mr. P,
Ashanti Graham.
You gots to know him.
He was a player for real.
He work Sunday
to Thursday,
7:00 early to
5:00 late.
So, it ain't no
moonlighting thing, then.
Nah, he ain't
no real police.
He full-time on this
Mickey Mouse shit here.
What he do again?
Talked back.
Go over Hilltop now?
Yeah, we got
that, too.
See ya.
Decision time, son.
Yo, what's your play?
Well, I told Little Kevin
right there
to shoot y'all both
in the head twice.
But seeing as he
done walked away...
Oh, you funny.
Yeah, I guess
I'm on your package.
Where the boy at--
Michael?
Well, he ain't
no regular.
He's just working
off a debt.
- Why? Why you care?
- Never mind you why.
"Why" ain't in your
repertoire no more, nigger.
60-40 split on that.
Do not be messing
with Marlo's money.
Randy Wagstaff,
you aren't a sixth-grader,
are you?
Uh, hey, Ms. Reese.
If you were
a sixth-grader,
it would mean you
and the rest of the knuckleheads
would still be in my
first-period English class.
And that would mean
it was two years ago.
And that would mean time stands
still at Tilghman Middle,
and that would
be a catastrophe.
I just forgot and
wore my old shirt today.
Mmm-hmm.
Well, if this isn't your lunch,
then where is your hall pass?
Why not just write
it in crayon?
Come on.
Deacon says you're
a good man.
Good enough to swing
a mop, I guess.
- A mop? More like a vacuum cleaner.
- What?
I get a few fellas like you
to help me out every September.
You go out
on the street,
you find these kids,
you drag them in.
Oh, a truant officer.
The system
hasn't been funded
for truant officers
in 20 years.
Where the hell you think you are,
Montgomery County?
Nah, I keep a couple
custodial positions
unfilled every year
just for this.
Those kids? You haul 'em in,
you cross 'em off the list.
Each kid, one time,
clear the list.
Come October,
you start on
the list again.
Job's yours if you want it.
Pays $12 an hour.
Excuse me, hon.
Sit.
Why'd you
leave class?
I got hungry,
couldn't concentrate.
Maybe, Randy, you had another
reason for running the halls, huh?
Tagging walls, maybe?
Uh-uh.
You know I don't.
I don't know anything.
I know it's the second week,
and I got walls
covered with tags.
Does that make you feel good,
walking past that?
- I don't know.
- Maybe you don't know,
'cause you're the one
doing the marking.
- I'm not.
- Then who is?
- Miss Thompson?
- Yes, ma'am?
Could you get me the number for
Randy Wagstaff's foster mom?
- Not a problem.
- What you want to call Miss Anna for?
Because you're skipping
class, running the halls,
maybe worse. She's
got a right to know.
- Is this her work number?
- Yes, ma'am.
Hold on. Wait.
The new girl, Greggs--
Sir, if I may,
respectfully--
Norris has
a full plate, okay?
The Braddock case
goes to Greggs.
His plate is fine.
No, it's not. His plate's a pile of
shit, okay? Listen to me.
Burrell wants this case
stalled until everybody votes.
And Rawls?
How the fuck I know
what Rawls wants?
He never said shit.
And let me tell you something,
even he knows this is fucked up.
I have this correct?
We are pulling a veteran off
a pending case and giving it to a rook
so as not to make timely
progress on said case?
The Braddock case
to Greggs.
- A pilot program?
- For one of your middle schools, yes.
- A $200,000 grant is attached.
- Free money.
- I'm just trying to help, Mrs. Conway.
- Help how?
You say that
your target group
is repeat violent
offenders.
Are you in any way
suggesting that
the system's lost
control of the school?
No no no, that's not what
I'm suggesting at all.
The system's fine.
The system's great.
I mean, this isn't
about the system.
We're just gonna
try to find a way
to get to some of
the troubled kids
who won't be in the
system too much longer.
Well, look, just make sure
there's no fuss.
I mean, nothing that gets
anyone upset, you know?
There's an election going on,
and we don't want to put our schools
- in the middle of that mess.
- No, indeed.
Humping a radio car
like a young sprite.
I'm a little bit
proud to know you,
- Officer McNulty.
- Just a little bit?
Well, it ain't like there aren't better
things you could be doing.
- Like what?
- See, I told you, Lester,
the worm has
turned for my boy.
So, I heard they
torpedoed your wiretap.
Yeah, they sent us
a new lieutenant.
- Marimow from E&T.
- "The Unit Killer."
Lester and Kima already
bailed to Homicide,
and now Sydnor's looking to jump
at the first good opening.
So, Major Crimes
is dead, huh?
Yeah, Lester
killed it good.
Went looking
for the money.
Guys like you,
you never learn.
- Guys like me?
- Yeah, 13 years--
- four months.
- Four months.
- Ha ha ha.
- You guys call for backup or what?
Yeah.
We got arrest papers
on a murder
for one Curtis Anderson,
aka "Lex."
He's been on the wing
for a couple of weeks,
so I don't expect him at
his mama's, but you never know.
- What's the address?
- 643 Harlem.
How about you taking the door
with me for old time's sake, Jim?
I'll take the back, gents.
- Oh!
- The back?
Damn, junior, the worm
has turned for you.
You know what they
say about the man
who volunteers
to take the back?
He buys.
B&O Tavern,
tonight at 9:00, son.
- I throw myself out after one.
- Shit.
You don't believe me,
ask Bunk.
True.
The bedroom's clear.
Yeah, basement, too.
Clear.
Yeah.
9:00 tonight, McNulty,
B&O Tavern.
He's not here.
I told you.
Is he coming home again?
Ma'am, is
your son alive?
Because if he's not,
we can end
this right now.
Otherwise, we've
got a witness.
That gives us
a murder warrant,
and that warrant says that we
can come through your door
as many times
as necessary.
I don't know
where my son is.
It's like them birds
of yours.
They go out, and they
fly around the city.
They free to do
as they do.
End of the day,
they come back here,
get water, get fed,
'cause they know
you got this place
set up regular
as the rain.
No surprises, 'cause
at the end of the day,
a man don't want
no surprises.
You know,
birds neither.
Same as what
I'm offering.
You part of
a co-op,
a whole lot of surprises
you never worry about again.
You just do
as you do,
knowing the product
will always be there
and be
the finest quality;
knowing that if one
of yours takes a pinch,
he got a lawyer
and a bondsman
waiting for him before he
even step out the wagon.
I know how to
hire lawyers.
It ain't just
about the lawyers.
It's having a connection
so that you know
before the bust
even go down.
What I got to give up
to get that good dope?
Muscle.
You got muscle.
You stand with us,
we run these New York boys
right out of East Baltimore.
Fuck I care about
East Baltimore?
The point of the co-op
is we stand together.
We share information,
and no one fucks
with any of us.
No one fucks
with me now.
Well, that don't
mean there couldn't be
some unforeseen cir--
No one fucks
with me now.
African colors. Subtle.
Tony Gray is
pulling 24% now.
You need new colors and
a new message, Clarence.
You need to
rally the base.
You want me to start
wearing dashikis?
Go all Marion Barry
and shit?
I'll tell you what
I would like--
another 75 in cash
for walk-around money.
75, huh?
Call another game.
It's a waste of time,
and right now,
time is everything.
They're gonna spit in your eye
and endorse Royce.
They only waited this long out
of respect to Tony Gray.
Otherwise, they give
it to Royce months ago.
That's not the point.
You go there uninvited, and you're
only gonna piss them off.
Am l? Or do I piss them off
even more
by pretending that
they don't exist,
that I don't need them?
I've door-to-doored every
neighborhood in this city,
saying I'm ready to be
mayor to all of it,
not just my base,
but all of it.
What does it say I don't
go see these guys?
He's right.
They endorse Royce, fine.
The hell else they gonna do?
But what they say
and don't say
from the pulpit that Sunday
before the primary,
we still got a dog
in that fight.
I do this right,
they'll respect it.
And if they don't,
at least they get to see
a begging-ass
white man on his knees.
Always a feel-good
moment for the folks.
And as to my attendance
at council meetings,
those who know
the job understand
there is more to
being a councilperson
than just the meetings.
Yes, Charles?
Yeah, they putting a halfway house at
the end of my block. Addicts and such.
Not if I have anything
to say about it.
Where you living
at, sir?
800 block North Carrollton.
Oh, I'm gonna take
a look into that.
Is there anyone
with a question
for any of
the other candidates?
Anyone with an issue,
a concern?
Well, I would say
that with regard to
the gentleman's concern
about the halfway house,
that while I share
your concern,
it's also true
that the city has
thousands of drug
addicts in recovery,
and those halfway houses
and shelters have to go someplace.
Though not in
white neighborhoods.
Ma'am, could I see that,
that Royce flyer?
- Thank you.
- Well, that is a fair point as well.
But these are people--
our brothers and sisters,
our children, our friends.
And they are trying
to change their lives,
and so it's up to us to
be responsible for them.
Feel good to miss
a hand, huh?
What's the point?
Eventually, we all
got to ante up.
Yeah, we do.
But I can't believe he
had the balls enough
to call two games
in one month.
I mean, please.
He's loading up on
walk-around money.
He wants cash on the street
come election day.
Carcetti got to him.
Called it a war chest.
Maybe we got us
a war this time.
I wouldn't mind if he wasn't
so fucking ugly with it.
That two pair he bet on,
right into Roger's trip nines.
I folded on a flush.
Full boat, four hands ago.
It's immoral,
what it is.
So, what's
the game, gents?
Clarence's deal.
Texas Hold 'Em.
I begin to understand
the popularity of this game.
No limit.
Oh, peachy.
I was beginning to
think you'd lost it, son.
That living room
shrine of hers
would have shamed
Elvis and Tupac both.
Her son's deader
than both of 'em.
She's just too scared
to say so.
That shit wasn't
there the first time
I talked to her.
I'd have seen it.
- You being a detective and all.
- Mmm-hmm.
Hey, look,
she got a friend.
She too young
for you, boy.
Young?
They get younger, William.
Skinnier, too. We don't.
Younger, skinnier--
where's Jimmy?
That's just the nature of
things. Age is age,
fat is fat,
and nature is nature.
- Aw, pitiful.
- And pitiless.
Nature don't care.
Nature just is.
Now my boy Marlo, I thought
he was skewing that.
Screwing what?
- The boy's a young lion.
- "Hello, is Mr. Lyon home?"
And a lion has
to have his kill.
"Methane probe
for Mr. Lyon."
- So then where are my bodies?
- Hmm.
Here I am over here
on the one hand
without a body
in six months,
and here you are
looking for a suspect
who's most likely dead,
and most likely for
dropping one of Marlo's.
Then again, if he's dead,
where's that body?
You know what
the plural of pussy is?
Puss-i.
Jimmy taught me that.
Where's he putting
the bodies, Bunk, huh?
In the sewers?
Rogue funeral
home, maybe?
Yeah, they teach
that fancy-ass Latin
at them Catholic
schools, they do.
- You remember the Eddy Crane case?
- Mmm-hmm.
Word was they put
him in an acid vat
down near Curtis Bay.
Oh, they're coming
up on us now.
Now, for a West Side boy
like Marlo Stanfield,
that would be the traditional
dumping grounds,
- Hey, girl. How are your doing?
- Right?
- Hey, girl.
What?
Oh, man.
Jimmy.
Tying to get some
of that puss-i.
What the hell you still
sitting here for?
Fucking Huxtables
and shit, right?
There they go
right there.
He's still
with school.
Shit. Just so they can
spring out that shit pile every day.
Make a good run
at that boy,
he'll be on a corner,
no problem, man.
Yeah, we gonna see.
You hung-over?
Just saying you
look like shit.
You know what you need
at a crime scene?
- Rubber gloves.
- Soft eyes.
Like I'm supposed
to cry and shit?
You got soft eyes,
you can see the whole thing.
You got hard eyes,
you're staring at
the same tree,
missing the forest.
Oh, Zen shit.
Soft eyes, Grasshopper.
Lividity puts the time
of death at 7:48,
- give or take.
- Noted.
You're gonna want
to get a chemstat.
- You think?
- Couldn't hurt.
A CDC, too?
Splatter distance?
Yeah, definitely.
You know, where the hell
did my Q-tips go?
Don't sweat it.
I got mine right here.
Oh, good. It's cool.
You want to take a look?
Won't bite.
Hey, uh, don't forget
the, uh, stippling.
I'm a rookie?
There's something
in his hand.
Oh, yeah?
Give her some
tweezers.
"Tater killed me."
Oh, is it typed?
'Cause that would hold up
a lot better in court.
Phone number in
the other hand.
A standard
confidentiality agreement.
And this one?
Oh, that one
indemnifies us
should you or any of
your staff be injured.
- Who wants to get some learning today?
- This way. Move.
- I roll up front with you?
- You got dibs in the back, little man.
- Come on. Hey...
- Don't worry about him.
- We'll catch him later.
- Yeah, little man's so excited
about what's on that blackboard,
he gonna race us.
What's the line
on us so far?
In the teacher's
lounge, I mean.
They're saying you're
this year's Band-Aid.
Is that how
you feel?
I was hoping for
more than that.
This year's
splint?
Hey, Miss Sampson.
Yo, he police.
I mean, the school
system seems benign.
And I get the sense
North Avenue
might give us some
latitude, if not support.
- You think so?
- You sound doubtful.
You can tell the days
by their faces.
The best day
is Wednesday.
That's the farthest
they get from home,
from whatever's going
on in the streets.
You see smiles then.
Monday is angry.
Tuesdays, they're caught between
Monday and Wednesday,
so it could go either way.
Thursdays...
they're feeling
that weekend coming.
Friday, it's bad again.
This is where
I leave you.
Oh, your class.
Language arts, huh?
Yes.
Anyway, you should
see it without me.
They behave differently
when I'm around.
No doubt.
What do you think
this 20 stands for?
No, it's not the number
of days you've been suspended.
It's not the number
of years you'll spend
in prison if you
don't shape up.
It's 50% below average.
It's 30% below
failure even.
But, really, it stands
for the amount of interest
you're taking in
your own future.
The next question
is worth two points.
Who can tell me why was
Clarence Mitchell, Jr. important
- to the civil rights movement?
- I know. I know.
And I can tell by
Shalanta's smile,
she's gonna win
for the blue team.
Hey, yo, did you see that one
over there? Hey.
Anybody here
DeShawn Price?
Never heard of him.
And what's your name?
Herbert Brown. This
the roundup van, right?
Oh, yeah,
here you go, my man.
Come on.
Oh, no, yo, no.
Yeah, see, "Howard Brown."
That's my brother. He over
on McHenry Street if you want him.
I was just in
school on Friday,
so I'm phat till
October. Sorry.
- Whoa, hold up, my man.
- Nah, he's right.
School gets a certain
amount of money
for each kid that shows
up one day in September
- and one day in October.
- One day?
After that, they don't
lose the government money,
so we done with it.
Nah nah, man.
School is school.
Yeah, well, I'm just trying to
school you, brother.
All right,
which one of y'all still
need your September day?
Get it over with now,
we won't be messing
with y'all later.
What up, Butch?
How do we begin?
You the one
called the meet.
Why don't we begin by you
respecting my time and getting to it?
First of all,
I heard you may be
under the impression
I was somehow involved
with the late Mr. Bell,
in his play against you
with Brother Mouzone.
I was no way involved.
Stringer came at me
to set up the parley
with you.
He used me like
he used y'all,
I feel the need to say.
It's said then.
Tip out on it.
Businessman such as myself
does not believe
in bad blood
with a man
such as yourself.
- Disturbs the sleep.
- Oh, I bet it do.
By way of amends,
a proposition.
I know of a card game
on the West Side--
high rollers,
lots of cash money,
boxcar-sized.
You trying to
set me up, Joe?
You ever known me
to be stupid?
I'm trying to make things
right here with you.
How much we talking about?
If there ain't at least
a few hundred K in that room,
I wish myself blind.
Serious, Joe.
I say again,
have you ever known me
to be a stupid man?
- What are the strings?
- No strings.
- What's your cut then?
- Quarter of the take.
I scope this and it
don't look right,
I'm gonna come back
on you now, Joe.
Where did everybody go?
- Which one of you is Sergeant Hauk?
- Sir.
- And you must be Dozerman.
- Yes, sir.
Welcome to Major Crimes.
I'm Lieutenant Marimow.
I see you just made
sergeant after driving
the mayor around for less
than three months.
You must be
a hell of a driver.
Anyone here?
Greggs? Freamon?
Sydnor and Massey.
And they're on the street,
making rips.
That's what we
do here now.
We get on the street
and we rip and run.
Can you get
with that, Sergeant?
The Western
District way, sir.
- Thank you.
Thanks for seeing me.
I understand you've
already heard from
Mayor Royce and
from Councilman Gray,
and I'd like to thank
you for being able
to join in this process.
I don't expect to walk out
of this room today
with an endorsement from
the lnterdenominational
Ministerial Alliance.
I don't.
But the point is...
I think I can be a better mayor for
Baltimore than the present one.
I voted for Clarence Royce
eight years ago.
I voted for him four
years after that.
I felt there was
promise in the man.
But now
I'm disappointed.
I'm disappointed
and I'm angry
at the crime
and the waste
and the damage done
to so many neighborhoods.
Not just in my district,
but here on the West Side--
Pimlico, Cherry Hill,
Edmondson Village.
Wherever I go, people
want the same things.
They need the same things,
but they're just
not getting them.
I'm gonna change that.
I'm not gonna ask
for your vote now.
Maybe I haven't
earned it yet.
But I am here to say
that when I am mayor,
my door is open to you, regardless
of who you endorse.
And I want you to remember
that I came here today
to say these things.
Thank you.
Councilman.
Thank you for coming.
Okay, I'm gonna need an APB
on a motherfucker named Tater.
"Call Mr. Sweet ASAP"?
Let me guess--
The Gay and
Lesbian Alliance.
Uh-oh.
She's catching on, boys.
Oh, and what do you want?
Another methane probe?
Or some other
"CSl" bullshit that don't exist?
You're the primary
on the Braddock case.
The dead witness.
Norris is back
in the rotation.
What?
You caught your first murder.
Kudos.
Come on, man, damn.
Bam bam, yeah.
Do that to whoever
be snitching.
Who snitching?
Don't know,
but kids be snitching.
Rashid got suspended
for tagging walls, yo.
Y'all ain't heard?
How you know he ain't just
get caught with a paint can?
'Cause Ms. Donnelly came and
pulled him out of the classroom.
Bam.
Yo, I'll see
y'all later, man.
Yo, you going
past the gym?
All right, man.
Peace, peace.
I ain't gonna tell
you again.
Give me the remote.
Did y'all learn
something today?
Y'all learn
Yeah.
What y'all learn?
I said give me
the remote.
- Mmm-mmm.
- Give it.
Math your favorite, right?
Start with it.
I like math.
Yeah, you good
at it, too.
Watched this show
five damn times.
Hey, you good?
All right now.
So, it turns out
the one girl...
200-something stitches
to close her up.
She's looking at a lot of rehab
and maybe more surgery.
The muscles in her face
don't even move right.
How's the class seem?
Like it didn't
really happen.
They're still processing. I know
it doesn't seem so, but they are.
What about Laetitia?
What happens to her?
Nothing worse
than she's already seen.
She'll probably go to
a juvenile facility,
which is only a little
worse than her group home.
She was in a group home?
She grew up
in the system.
Monday-to-Friday angry.
Last year, she was
suspended twice,
and then expelled.
Chiquan wasn't
positive though,
if you're looking for
a silver lining and all.
Excuse me?
She didn't have HlV,
in case you were worrying.
Marcus. Boy, what are you
trying to do?
You trying to
get knocked out?
Drop your head, son.
Left up! Get that left up!
Pick your hand up.
Damn!
Man, that boy
listen to anyone?
All right, all right.
Time, time.
Not bad, y'all.
Not bad, Justin.
Marcus, you got to concentrate,
man. Think.
All right?
Listen, I got tickets
to the fights tonight,
Pikesville Armory.
Now, I was gonna
take Justin and Spider,
but Spider ain't
been hanging out,
and, Marcus, I know you
got your mother, right?
So, Michael,
you want to see
the fights?
- You going?
- Yeah, I'm in.
Yeah, all right.
All right.
Come on, get this
headgear off.
What the fuck
is that?
Souvenir.
What?
Trouble with doing
it this way,
disappearing
'em and shit--
Nobody knows.
I remember when
I was a kid,
if you had a map
of the world,
the playground over
at Baker and Moreland
would be at
the center of it.
And as I got older,
the playground just
kept on getting bigger,
went beyond
the neighborhood.
Everything changes,
you know?
One minute
the ice cream truck
be the only thing
you want to hear.
Next thing, them touts
calling out the heroin
be the only thing
you can hear.
What's that?
Workbook I need
to use with this.
So you read from
the small one
and answer questions
in the big one?
Yeah, ain't no thing.
Yeah, I see that.
I see that.
All right, you see how
he keeping his hands up?
Look at his feet.
Look at their feet.
See how they keep
their feet moving?
See what I'm saying?
See how he stay
in close?
That's how you take
away his power.
Yo, dude is cut.
Yeah, man.
That's discipline.
You take care your body,
your body take care of you.
Yo, I bet his woman
is fine, man.
Yeah, I bet
she is, too.
Flush to the queen.
Full house.
All right, everybody,
Iet me see them
hands, yo.
Hands.
Hey, yo, big man,
back up.
I don't know about cards,
but, uh, I think these four-fives
beat a full house.
Hey, yo, banker,
cash me out, yo.
Boy, you want a head on
that body, you best hop to.
That's my money.
Man, money ain't
got no owners,
only spenders.
I tell you something else--
I like that ring, too.
Boy, you got me confused
with a man repeats himself.
This ain't over.
Oh, that's how you
carrying it, Shorty, huh?
'Cause I can find
your peoples
a whole lot easier
than they can find me.
Wear it in health.
No doubt.
You see what I'm
talking about, Justin?
That's what I'm saying.
That's the real deal.
You keep training, I'm telling you,
boy, you can get there.
See, the last fight
was the best.
The Puerto Rican boy
had a good left.
Yeah, shit was tight.
Oh, this is it,
right here on the right.
All right.
- All right now.
- All right,
- I'll see you tomorrow, Coach.
- All right.
All right, now,
so you live over on--
Hey hey, my boy,
what you doing?
- I'm gonna take you home.
- No, no, thank you.
Michael, come on now,
serious.
Nah, no thank you.
I'm good from here.