Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
...the big fat morning show.
Now, you wanna play
the brand new big fat game:
big fat match game, call us now....
Hello?
Who was that?
-They hung up without saying.
-They hung up without saying?
What you care?
You never use the damn phone
in here no how.
What's up, baby?
I need you to get
them phone lines up out that house.
Out of the apartment? Why?
I'm saying, what Chantay gonna say...
about not havin' no line in her own place?
All right. Got you.
What's up, baby, you got a problem?
-Good.
-I'm just sayin' though, man...
it seem we just goin' past careful, man...
with all of this, man.
Like we buggin' out or something.
You know, like we paranoid and shit.
Naw, I don't wanna use this phone.
We used this phone yesterday.
What you blowing out your mouth for, man?
You act like....
Ain't nobody out to get me, man.
I got no motherfuckin' enemies.
Naw, man.
We all right.
All right, this gonna be so easy...
them Eastside chumps,
they ain't nothing like Avon's people.
Watch, y'all gonna see.
All right, now y'all gonna be here, right?
Hold up.
Yo, Boo!
I'm gonna slide up through here.
Bailey, you gonna cover the alley.
Yo!
Yo, Maurice short, man.
-How short?
-Three.
Tell him to grow a couple of inches.
Where you gonna be at?
That be the trap right there, homes.
You figure they roll
through the alley for sure?
Man, rats always run
to holes in times of danger.
And you him, ain't you?
-Who?
-Danger.
Naw, man, I'm just a nigger
with a plan, that all.
And a shotgun.
For sure.
Sorry I'm late.
Got myself lost down the other hallway.
-That leads to the loading dock.
-Yeah, and deep storage.
So, this is where they put you?
Quite a message they're sending.
-Yeah, and that message is....
-Out of sight, out of mind.
Spoken like a true troglodyte.
Whole lot of dead trees
behind this nonsense.
The foundation of your case, Detective.
You lay it in right, you can build on it.
You lay it in wrong, everything on top falls.
We ready?
Do you solemnly swear and affirm
that the affidavit is true...
and accurate to the best of your knowledge?
-I do.
Then by the power vested in me,
I now declare you man and wife.
-Did he swear already?
-The state's attorney?
Yeah.
I see it.
Second copy is sealed for the court,
and the police get the others.
How's this work?
Same frequency as the one
carried by D'Angelo Barksdale.
He gets a page, we get a page.
-So, we up now?
-It's official.
-You're up.
-Then let the game begin.
Celebrities always seem much smaller
when you meet them in person.
Yo!
Check it out, here he come.
-Somethin' ain't right, yo.
-Watch out, man, he got that boom.
-He's packing.
-Here he come.
Yo, come on, Omar's coming, man!
Oh, shit!
Yeah...
the cheese stands alone.
-How you know?
-'Cause if you could, I'd have been had.
Yo, he saying you can't catch the bug...
just by getting your dick sucked.
Dumb-ass, you gotta be
in some pussy to get it, all right?
Man, wear a coat if you want,
don't nobody like suckin' on a rubber.
How would you know?
Who you trying to fuck anyway?
Arletta Mouzone. Treenee's cousin.
Damn, man, in that case
use a big-ass condom, all right?
You need a trash bag. Fuck that.
I wouldn't run up in that bitch
with D'Angelo's dick....
It's triflin'.
Easy to see why niggers come
around here stealing our shit!
Yo, you know what, nigger?
What?
Forget it.
142 isn't a working telephone exchange.
Six intercepts so far,
and five aren't working numbers?
Something wrong with the recorder?
We're getting what you'd expect,
seven digits of a telephone number...
and a two-digit add-on to identify the caller,
like here, 13.
McNulty, line one.
-Yeah.
-Did youjust get a 142 exchange?
Yeah, that's what we got, too.
-That's fucked up.
-All right, later.
He's got the same numbers
on the readout of the cloned pagers.
So it's not the recorder.
These mopes are using a code
to cover their calls?
-That's pretty damn sophisticated.
-What is?
They've coded the telephone numbers
in their pager messages.
How do you know?
Every time the Barksdale kid's pager
goes off...
this machine gives us a message and time.
McNulty's carrying a cloned pager,
but this is what we use in court.
Same with those pen registers.
Every time a pay phone
in the low-rise court is used...
we get the telephone number,
the time and the duration of the call.
Incoming calls, too.
Spy shit. Very cool.
You say they're using some kind of code?
Yeah, they got to be.
These numbers don't make no fuckin' sense.
-You rang?
-Omar's ride.
Bubbles spotted it.
Different tags, no stolen report,
these come back right for the van...
but Bubs makes it
by the cargo rack on the roof.
Good scope. You wanna take him?
Can't hurt to try.
We pop Omar, get a gun,
he might let us work him.
Anything coming through on the pager?
Eight hits so far,
most of them in some kind of code.
These ain't Baltimore exchanges,
that's for sure.
Three weeks to get Daniels to agree,
a week to write out the affidavit...
and then this bullshit.
How complex a code can it be
if these knuckleheads are using it?
Then again, what does it say
about us if we can't break it?
You wanna run Bubs back downtown,
I'll sit here and wait for you.
All right.
-What'd I miss, girlfriend?
-Not a goddamn thing.
Yeah, boring, ain't we?
How y'all do what you do every day
and not wanna get high?
That's what I be asking.
It's been a little hectic down here,
right, cuz?
String, man, I can't lie.
Them stick-up boys,
they caught us dead up.
And the knockos, shit,
I don't know what the fuck that was.
5-0. Comin' up!
-5-0 comin' up, y'all.
-Time-out.
-C'mon, man, what is that?
-What?
You gotta get your crew
to understand that...
it's the stick-up crews and the creepers...
that give us the most trouble.
When they start thinking like that...
you're not gonna have any more surprises,
you feel me?
'Cause you know, your uncle and me...
we think you got a snitch up in the shop.
-What?
-Someone who tips off the stick-up crew.
And you gotta be on that, right?
You gotta be on that.
I'm gonna tell you what you do.
What day is it today, Friday?
What happen on Friday?
-Payday.
-Not this Friday.
Why not?
No, what you gonna do
is you gonna call 'em...
Iike you gonna pay 'em
and then you crack 'em.
You tell 'em you're not happy...
with what they fuckin' pass
as work down here.
And when you're not happy,
they ain't gettin' paid. You feel me?
Yeah, but String, you don't pay a nigger,
he ain't gonna work for you.
What, you think a nigger's gonna get a job?
You think these niggers
gonna be like, "Fuck it...
"Iet me quit this game here
and go to college"?
Naw, they gonna buck a little,
but they not gonna walk.
-And in the end, you gonna get respect.
-Yeah.
And when that money run out,
they'll come up to you and roll on you...
and ask you for an advance and shit,
when they flat-ass broke.
Them the niggers
that you strike off your list.
But that nigger that stay eatin'...
the nigger that steady rollin',
ain't askin' you for shit...
that's the nigger I want
to hear about. Understand?
Yeah, man, shit, you know how
to play a nigger into a corner, String.
-Yo, take care of this right here.
-You my favorite girl.
Shit, let me handle this, man.
-Yo, Poot.
-Yeah, l--
-Come here, man.
-What's happening?
What the fuck is that? What the fuck is that?
You know the fuckin' rules.
-What the fuck are you doing?
-Copying.
A telephone.
This fucking detail is too much for me.
It's after 3:00.
So, where are the boys at?
Maybe they only come out at night.
I used to have a guy
like Omar working for me.
Guy named Reuben Terry.
Is he good?
Saw the street like we wish we could.
Ain't nothing like a good Cl.
School's out.
Can I use your cell phone?
Yeah, I got that. I did.
I know.
I don't know about this....
-What do you mean, you don't know?
-How can I trust you....
For chrissakes, Elena, I'm their father.
You think I'd let 'em sleep on the floor?
Yes, I got them.
Sheets, pillows, comforters, pillowcases.
I fuckin' got them.
What color are they?
Color, what the fuck do you care
what color they are? Hello?
-Lost her.
-I bet.
You know something?
My ex-wife, the way she acts sometimes,
the way she deals with shit...
you would think a less enlightened man
than myself, cruder man than myself...
a man less sensitized to the qualities
and charms and value of women...
a man like that, not me, but a man like that,
he just might call her a cunt.
You just called the mother
of your children a cunt.
No, I did not call her that.
-Yes, you fuckin' did.
-No, I did not.
Let's just leave this, okay?
I got some stuff to do.
5-0, gotta go.
Whoa, man, get out the way!
Shit.
Not much fighting this time.
You getting tired, asshole?
Still dragging from
the whupping Kima put on him.
Fucked you up like
a cop should, didn't she?
That's one thing about Kima,
she put a hurtin' on you like a man.
Get your monkey ass up.
You're gonna want your
business card back, right?
Come on.
From Bantry Bay to the Derry Quay
And from Galway to Dublin town
Well, I've never seen
My brown Colleen
That I met in the County Down
There's a man in the County Down
First, I go in, play nice.
-Then you come in, play bad.
-I ain't gonna be playin'.
Bracelet too tight?
You rackin' up all kinds of points, ain't you?
First, you put a cop in the hospital,
damn near kill his ass with that punch.
Now, you on the wing from Boys' Village.
Man, I'm 16, all right?
What the fuck they gonna do to me?
That's the least of your worries, my friend.
I got a partner outside who can't wait
to get in here and fuck you up.
Cop you banged was Herc's uncle.
Herc wants off the leash on this one.
And I suppose you
at the other end of that leash?
See, I don't want to play it that way.
I know about comin' up hard and all.
Why, you came up hard?
Flag House projects. Eastside.
Yeah, Flag House?
You know, you remind me of me.
I'm thinking we should work something out.
What do I get?
What you want?
I want....
for you to suck my dick.
I'll beat your fuckin' monkey ass.
You supposed to be the good cop,
dumb motherfucker.
What?
-Hello, may I help you?
-Yeah, we'd like a table.
And you have reservations?
Naw, I thought, you know,
we could just walk in....
Let me see what I got.
That's two?
Follow me, please.
Your coat, ma'am?
-Can we get that one, over there?
-It's Friday night...
those are for patrons
who made reservations.
Let me get your chair for you, ma'am.
-It's okay, man, all right.
-Here you are.
Here you are, sir.
Your waiter will be with you shortly.
You shoulda pushed him, Dee.
Bastards.
Sarge, nobody answers at juvenile intake
and we been calling.
Clearly, they're not
as dedicated as you two detectives.
So what time does
the duty intake consultant get here?
You missed the 8:00.
You got another one around midnight.
-Midnight?
-You think maybe if we left you...
the paperwork, you could put him
in the box 'til intake gets here?
Hemorrhoid.
For the crumbs.
Yeah, right.
-You like your dinner?
-Yeah.
-That shrimp was right.
-Yeah, it was good, right?
Think they know?
Do they know what?
You know. What I'm about.
What you mean, Dee?
Come on, you know, it's like...
we get all dressed up, right?
Come all the way across town.
Fancy place like this.
After we finished, we gonna
go down to the harbor.
Walk around a little bit, you know?
Acting like we belong down here,
know what I'm saying?
So? Your money good, right?
Dee, we ain't the only black people in here.
It ain't what I'm talking about.
It's about where we.... Come on, you know.
I'm just saying, you know,
I feel like some shit just stay with you...
you know what I'm saying,
like, hard as you try...
you still can't go nowhere,
you know what I'm saying?
-Can I interest you in dessert?
-Yes, thank you.
-Can I have some chocolate cake?
-I'll bring the cart.
Boy, don't nobody give a damn
about you and your story.
You got money,
you get to be whatever you say you are.
That's the way it is.
Sir, I'm sorry. These are the samples.
And for you, sir? Very good.
Don't be a bitch, admit it.
Go ahead.
-Admit you're wrong, be a man.
-Yeah, I gotta confess...
this sub beats chink-ass Bob's by a mile.
'Course, you might be all that when it comes
to thumpin' on niggers...
but you can't do shit with that stick, man.
-You'd do better.
-I play.
Says he plays.
He might.
I'm even better with two hands.
I checked it out, man.
Stinkum true on this one.
Except for that nigger, Scar,
from New York...
Edmondson gully is wide open.
What about Tee-Tee's crew?
Naw, them niggers dried up
when they took that federal charge.
Most of 'em laid up somewhere,
gettin' high and shit.
I'll tell you what. You holler at the boy Scar.
Let him know, man, it's time
for him to take a stroll.
If he give you any beef at all,
we'll put Wee-Bey and Bird on it.
-All right.
-And then once we got him outta there...
we'll send in the smokers to run out
all the little poop-butt locals and shit.
Or, if you think
there's some cats in there who got game...
-then we put 'em on our team.
-All right, who you want to run it?
-Send Stinkum up here.
-All right.
He the one who saw the shot.
So, he gets a shot.
All right, okay, not bad.
Can't let the duty officer see that.
You wanna give it a rest, man?
You down $60.
That might be your whole damn salary,
but I clock that shit in minutes.
-Rack 'em and break 'em, man.
-You the guys waiting for juvenile intake?
He's in the squad room.
If I had more time, I'd run you.
Give you a tip, Preston.
You gonna run a hustle,
you best stay with what you know.
Man, fuck you and your
tired-ass advice, all right?
But that sandwich was good.
You gonna move our little thing
down to Edmondson Avenue.
Take the gully.
What about Scar?
Who?
Listen, I'm giving you points
on the package...
so, you make a go of it, you hear me?
You working for yourself, too,
so you gonna put out the strong product...
and you gonna get the locals behind it.
It's as simple as that.
You get your team together, you feel me?
Go and wait for me downstairs.
I'll be down in a minute, man.
-We gonna make this money run in a few.
-Smile or something, nigger.
-Made that nigger's night.
-Yeah, he deserved it, though.
He deserved it.
It's Wee-Bey. We got one.
-You think it's Omar?
-Nah.
-It's one of the young 'uns, I think.
-One down, two to go, right?
Yeah, motherfuckers. Try to rob me, baby.
One, two, three.
-A winner.
-A match? Which case?
The one you just brought me, Bunk.
Casing in that girl shot up in Northeast.
-Kresson?
-Diedre Kresson, right, yeah.
She matches up with two other cases,
both from last year.
-Which ones?
-Toreen Boyle....
-Someone named Ligget. It's in the report.
-It's Toreen Boyd, Roland Leggett.
Yeah, them.
Casings from all three killings go to a .45,
probably Colt Classic.
-That fucker Landsman. How's he do it?
-You like Landsman for these three?
I don't know, Bunk.
As sergeants go, Jay's a sociopath and all,
but I'd have to go with an actual gangster.
Jimmy, you sitting down?
I said it was hot, but ifyou
got these barbecue gloves.
You got a Johnny Weeks up in here?
-Who?
-Johnny Weeks.
-Over in the game room.
-Obliged.
-Any smokes?
-I'm out.
How long have you been here?
You gotta give the medication...
a chance to work in your system, man.
Brought you something.
Yeah, some chicken pieces and some fries.
Bought you a shake,
but I dropped it on the bus.
It comes in a bag, goes out in a bag.
How long you have that for?
-I fucked up, man.
-Yeah, I saw.
There was nothing I could do, you know?
It's like first I got beat, right, then I get this.
What are these for?
They say I got the bug.
The bug?
They checked me when
I was in the hospital--
Are they sure?
Where you been at?
Here and there, I'm at it.
I'd have come past sooner,
but I been on kinda like a mission.
-A mission?
-Yeah. Them hoppers that beat you down...
they got problems now.
Them and the people they sling for, even.
What?
I put the police on their ass.
Police?
-What, you get locked up or something?
-No, come on.
No, I'm not working for them.
I'm working with them.
They don't give me the badge soon enough,
I keep doing like I do.
Why?
What do you mean why?
How can you ask me why?
Why the fuck are you in here, man,
with all these falling-down motherfuckers?
Why you passing shit through a bag?
Why they beat you down?
Why I couldn't do nothing about it?
It's all part of the game, right?
I mean, you taught me that.
What you up to in here, man?
-Doing the meetings.
-N.A.?
Yeah. Twice a day.
That's good, man. It's good,
you give the body comfort, you know.
-Yeah.
-No, you needed a change.
Guess so.
I'll be getting out of here
the end of the month.
It's all right. They got meetings everywhere.
You ain't gotta worry about that.
Bubs.
Who's got the best package now?
-Get the fuck out of here, man.
-I'm coming home, right?
Shit is weak all over, you know?
Got some boys up in Baker
and Calhoun, though.
They had a smoker out
the other day though.
-Yeah?
-Knocked a couple of niggers out.
Ain't you a trip?
Beat down, bagged up,
still ready to rip and run, huh?
I'm a Viking, homes.
"I'm a Viking, homes."
McNulty.
There's something here that needs kissing.
Speak again, toothless one.
I guess you know now why I wear
the stripes in the family.
Good call, Jay. Of course, if Keeley
hadn't fucked the scene up...
you'd have had that casing
months ago, right?
Keeley. Let Keeley be Keeley.
We all can't be princes
of the city, now can we?
Speaking of which...
sit down.
May I ask you a question
that is essential to your career?
-What?
-Who do you serve?
I am asking you to identify for the record
your commanding officer.
-Major Rawls.
-Excellent.
And with that thought in mind, I advise you
to go immediately into the Major's office...
carrying the break
I've given you in the Kresson case...
and kiss the man's ring. Because...
I have talked you right out of the shithouse.
Here's the deal.
You wrap up this thing
with Narcotics in two weeks.
You put yourself back in the rotation
when we go back to night work.
You do that and you're back in the fold.
-Thanks, Jay.
-No problem.
Shit ain't right.
You work, you get paid.
That's what I'm saying.
I'm gonna say something to him, all right?
-You should.
-Truth.
-What's up, Dee?
-What's up, Shorty?
$530, the count is right, man.
Okay, re-ups on the way down.
Go tell Sterling to be ready for it.
All right. Yo, Dee, man.
You know, me and Poot,
we been steady working it, you know?
Nothing sloppy, no troubles, right?
No.
And we was wondering if, maybe you could
let a little something go...
until payday, 'cause you know, right now,
we some broke-ass niggers, man.
Right now, whoever did our girl...
also did Boyd and Leggett a month earlier.
-Leggett.
-And those two are definitely...
straight-up drug executions.
No mention of Dee in either file.
But I did get a fresh number...
-on Tywanda.
-Who?
The girl who called in on Kresson.
-Right.
-She put Dee in for that.
Have you seen this?
Jaybird.
And the bear said, "You didn't
really come here to hunt now, did you?"
-You see Saturday's 24s?
-Sunday morning.
Did you see the one Worden
got on the Westside?
John Bailey, in a Kevlar vest,
lit up by three separate shooters.
Carey Street.
You made the Kresson connection...
you didn't think Bailey might tie in
with Barksdale?
Worden's on the other shift.
I'm trying to work my murders, Jesus Christ.
Tony, Line 3.
What took you so long?
You might've heard, we get a few murders
here in Baltimore...
sometimes we just get backed up.
-You weren't followed here?
-Why would we be followed?
Diedre was playing with scary people.
Who might that be?
You called this in after the murder
and you told the detective...
that you talked to her
the night she was killed.
She called. It was late.
She didn't talk long, she said she had to go.
Dee was at the door.
And that was the last time
you spoke with her?
-Yeah, she was killed that night.
-Dee was her boyfriend?
No, Dee was his nephew or something.
Dee would be D'Angelo Barksdale.
And the boyfriend, Avon Barksdale?
You know Avon?
The question is how do you know him?
You out there running
the street with the players?
I used to be...
but not after this thing with Diedre.
I mean, damn.
We used to go to Odell's for ladies' nights...
and one time he was there with all
his people in one of the big booths...
ordering drinks,
acting like he was king of everything.
And Diedre ate that shit up.
-And you?
-I ain't gonna lie.
I did the club thing for a while, but...
some of those places,
everybody in there's on some kind of game.
But Diedre went with Avon?
She was with Avon for like a year...
and something happened. Toward the end,
she started getting real possessive...
and that didn't sit with Avon,
'cause he has other girls, too.
She started bitching on him one minute...
crying the next minute,
threatening to do all kinds of things.
-She threatened Avon Barksdale?
-The girl was off the hook.
One time, she threatened
to write a letter on him.
-A letter.
-A letter to the state's attorney.
Supposed to be some sort of kin to her.
She said that if he dumped her...
she was gonna tell about the drugs.
-Did she write this letter?
-I don't know.
I tried talking to her about the way she
was acting, but she wouldn't let it go.
She even had it out with him in his club
one night in front of all the people.
What, Avon has a club?
Orlando's, titty bar.
-Does he own it?
-That's what Diedre said.
She said he owned a whole mess of stuff.
-Tell me something, man.
-What's that?
How can you run this place
and not just OD on pussy?
Shit.
You try dealing with all these bitches
and their problems for a few days.
Get so you'd rather be running a goddamn
laundromat out this fucker.
Heard you're doing okay in the Pit.
-Yeah, well.
-What, you ain't getting it like that?
Man, my uncle
still got me working on salary.
Damn, boy.
You ain't the only one
your uncle keeps close.
What?
Come on, man, you ain't making no ends?
I know you getting
something on this by now.
No, man.
I'm just the front,
clean name for the liquor board.
-I'm saying--
-What the fuck?
Is there a problem?
That was for the drink before.
It was for this one.
It ain't like I'm calling your uncle out
or nothing...
but give a nigger a chance.
Plenty of pie out there for everybody.
Believe.
You heard Stinkum gonna be coming off
the clock, right? Getting a percentage.
-What?
-Open up fresh territory.
Take over the corners
down near Edmondson and Brice.
So, my uncle gave that to Stink?
Figured you knew.
Orlando!
Excuse me, Orlando,
can you help me down here, please?
-I already paid for that last drink.
-That was for the drink before.
-Hell, no, that was for this one.
-What's up here?
Look, he ain't paid for that drink
and I took $20 off the bar.
-Look she took $20, then $20 more.
-Hell I did.
Come on, now, why you
gonna do me like this?
I been with you for an hour and a half
buying drinks.
Look, man, this ain't right.
I just spent $1 20 in drinks, $40 in tips.
Now, you gonna take all that
and still try to sneak into my pocket?
-Shit, girl!
-You got to go, get him the fuck outta here.
I ain't done so much as touch your kneecap.
Trying to treat her with a little respect,
and this is the way you do me?
Wait, wait!
Why you do that?
-Did you take his money?
-No, I didn't take his money.
You buying me a drink?
Can I see you sometime?
Like, you know, not in here.
I don't usually see men that I meet in here.
Usually.
What kind of strip joint has
a video camera looking out?
More to it than the girls, maybe.
So, he's got the club,
he's got the warehouse...
he's got the apartment building
by Druid Hill Lake...
he's got the tow truck company...
and that's just what she knew from
what he bragged about to the dead girl.
-Major likes assets.
-The Deputy, too, I imagine.
Nothing like a few property forfeitures
to swell the departmental operation budget.
Check city assessments to see
who owns the club.
Run the company name through
the state corporate charter office.
Also, Homicide picked up one
Saturday night. Might be one of ours.
John Bailey, he's a stick-up artist
I used to know from the Murphy homes.
He was wearing Kevlar, but it didn't help.
39 casings on the scene,
from three different guns.
Overkill for a burn bag...
but about right if he was running with Omar.
Lookit, our buddy.
Just once, I wish they'd use
the right number.
Ain't like him to be late.
Bailey, you fucking dope fiend.
I'm telling you...
them fucking people ain't to be relied on.
Why you always gotta talk like that, man?
-What?
-"F" this and "f" that.
If I give it up,
I lose half of what I mean to say.
Don't nobody want
to hear them dirty words, man.
Especially coming from
such a beautiful mouth.
Wait for Bailey?
Early bird catches the worm, dog.
-I beeped you.
-I didn't get it.
-Let me see.
-You want to see my pager?
Sure, Prez, you want to see my pager?
-I beeped you too.
-You all right, Prez?
714-3432?
I got that. That was you?
You try it?
Yeah, I tried it. Twice.
Non-working number.
It would've worked if you knew the code.
Shit, I'm as surprised as you.
I like word-search puzzles.
You know, where you gotta
find the hidden words?
So, I thought I could do the same thing
with the numbers.
Take the number I sent you.
Now, take the seven
and jump it over the five.
You get three.
Jump the one over the five...
you get nine.
With four you get six.
Three, that's seven, four is six...
a three again...
and two is eight.
Zero switches with the five.
So 714-3432 is...
396-7678.
Our number.
And that's the code?
And it works, because it's all about
where the buttons are on a phone.
If it was a code that involved math...
or algebra or whatever...
these little yos in the projects
wouldn't be able to follow along.
But with this, all you gotta do
is jump the five button.
Ain't no math to it. It's just...
how a phone looks when you look at it.
Prez, you little genius!
-Jesus.
-I could kill you, that's so good.
Your mother keep ragging at me...
to take him outta here and put him
in a private nursing home.
You know, she ain't never gonna let that go.
I keep telling her, man, we can't show
this legit money yet, man...
especially since he ain't got no insurance.
Soon, though.
So, you ain't big on coming here, right?
No.
Tell you something, man...
you about to see your uncle,
you understand me?
-This is family.
-I know.
Family is what counts,
family is what it's about.
Family gonna always be there
'cause it's blood.
Man.
You never figured on this, did you?
Live the life, lead the life. Ain't no big thing.
He used to talk that shit all the time and he
believed it, you know what I'm saying?
What's up, baby, talk that shit now.
You know, you're right.
It's kind of hard to be in here right now.
He scare you, don't he?
-You know, I'm just saying--
-He scares me.
See, if he dead, you know,
I could carry it better.
Coming up the way we did,
you kind of expect that.
Waiting on it.
See...
the thing is, you only got to fuck up once.
Be a little slow, be a little late. Just once.
And how you ain't gonna never be slow...
never be late?
You can't plan for no shit like this, man.
It's life.
Scares me.
They're still using it.
I was by on Saturday night and it was gone.
On your own time?
You still getting your boys?
Yeah, tonight for a sleep-over.
Omar's rolling.
What the hell?
Call for backup?
Not yet.
Let's see how it plays out.
An invitation.
Feel a little lonesome for backup.
Yeah, me, too.
That's nice.
-I'll check the rear.
-I'll watch the boys.
Afternoon, gentlemen.
Saying, if you were gonna use that
you would've been done using it by now.
It's clean.
Got to keep it clean.
We having one of our little parlays like this,
got to keep it clean, right?
Omar with no gun on the street?
Must be a first.
Yeah, sometimes
who you are is enough, dog.
But being as y'all sitting on my ride so long,
I thought I'd save y'all some time.
Come straight on out.
I ain't taking no charge.
You ain't putting me back in no cage.
We're not here to bury you, Omar.
We're pulling you up 'cause
we got a problem in common.
-Problem?
-Barksdale.
-No, he ain't no problem.
-I don't know.
Avon's been chalking up a lot of bodies.
And you being you....
Put it that way,
I guess he could be a little problem...
but I just can't really come out
and help you all.
You know what I mean?
Snitchin' just rubs me wrong.
Personally, I don't think
the game is played like that.
We respect that.
If you do happen to take a charge though...
I'm McNulty, that's Greggs.
You give us a call, we'll sort something out.
Fair enough.
You know, I used to work the homes,
back when your brother was up there.
You get a chance...
Iet him know they blew up
John Bailey last night.
Good man.
Lot of enemies.
Saying, you trying to catch up with Bird?
Word is he dropped a workin' man.
Wait, hold up. Come on, don't play me.
What workin' man, what Bird?
Come on, now,
ain't but one working man, now, is there?
And Bird?
I think your snitch can handle that.
Shit, Bubbles know Bird.
You working late?
A little.
Got a minute?
Sure, have a seat.
No, this is better said standing up.
You know, I've been 13 years on the shelf.
I ain't bitched.
It was me that put me there.
But I'm here now, and I gotta say a piece.
We should've had a tap
on the project pay phones by now.
A wire there will get us the drugs.
Keep pushing,
we'll get a whiff of the money, too.
I know you're serious
about climbing that career ladder...
and I know how slippery
it gets the higher you go...
but for me...
I don't want to go to no dance
unless I can rub some tit.
I appreciate your honesty.
Good night, Lieutenant.
So, what you say to make Dee pay out?
I told him to give it up
or I'm taking him out of the count.
-Shit.
-Look.
I'll pump niggers when I got to.
-That's him.
-That's who?
One of the ones that robbed us.
That light-skinned boy.
That's him?
All right, come on.
I'm the king of this shit.
-So, you want us to wait?
-Yeah.
-All right, we on it, man.
-All right.
There goes Scar right there.
Right there in the blue?
-Number 80?
-Yeah, I'm on him.
All right, you got him?
-Find a phone real quick.
-What's wrong?
It looks like my man Dee
got himself an emergency.
What, he been stuck up again?
What's up, what do you need?
My people are onto one of Omar's
boys down at Greek's.
Word? All right, sit tight.
I'm gonna take care of it.
All right.
Ain't nobody coming.
Dee said wait.
Told you.
-He still in there?
-Yeah, he's playing the games.
All right.
You are sharp, son. What's your name?
-Wallace.
-Wallace, all right.
This nigger's gonna
point him out to us, all right?
Yeah.
It's done. Nice work, cuz.
All right.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org