From the year 1942
to the present time...
you were an employee
of the Genco Olive Oil Company?
That's right.
But in actuality you were a member
of the Corleone crime organization?
We called it the Corleone family,
Senator. We called it the family.
What was your position?
At first, like everybody else,
I was a soldier.
- What is that?
- A button. You know, come on.
No, I don't know. Tell me.
When the boss says "push a button
on a guy," I push a button.
- See, Senator?
- Mr. Questadt.
- You mean you killed people?
- What?
You killed people
at the behest of your superiors?
Yeah, that's right, counselor.
And the head of your family
is Michael Corleone?
Yeah, counselor, Michael Corleone,
right.
Did you ever get such an order
directly from Michael Corleone?
No, I never talked to him.
Mr. Cicci, could you amplify
your answer a bit, please?
Do what?
Could you expand on your answer?
I'm interested in knowing...
was there always a buffer involved?
Someone in between you
and your possible superiors...
- who gave the actual orders?
- Yeah, right, a buffer.
The family had a lot of buffers.
Mr. Cicci,
you may find this very amusing...
but I promise you the members
of this committee do not.
If there's something I could do
for you, you come, we talk.
The rent stays like before.
Hey, what do you think?
God bless America. Big business.
- New York City.
- Would you mind speaking up?
New York City.
- Are you the son of Vito Corleone?
- Yes, I am.
- And where was he born?
- Corleone, Sicily.
Did he, at times, use an alias...
that was known in certain circles
as "Godfather"?
"Godfather" is a term
that was used by his friends...
one of affection,
one of respect.
Mr. Chairman, I would like
to verify the witness's statement.
For years now, a growing number
of my constituents...
have been of ltalian descent...
and I've come to know them well.
They have honored me with their
support and with their friendship.
Indeed, I can proudly say
that some of my very best friends...
are ltalian-Americans.
However, Mr. Chairman, at this time,
I have to leave these proceedings...
to preside over a very important
meeting of my own committee.
But before I leave,
I do want to say this--
that these hearings on the Mafia
are in no way whatsoever...
a slur upon
the great Italian people...
because I can state from
my own knowledge and experience...
that Italian-Americans are among
the most loyal...
most law-abiding, patriotic...
hard-working American citizens
in this land.
And it would be a shame,
Mr. Chairman...
if we allowed
a few rotten apples...
to give a bad name
to the whole barrel...
because from the time
of the great Christopher Columbus...
up to the time of Enrico Fermi...
right up until the present day...
Italian-Americans
have been pioneers...
in building and defending
our great nation.
They are the salt of the earth.
They are one of the backbones
of this country.
The chairman is calling
the meeting back to order.
I'm sure we all agree
with our esteemed colleague.
Now, Mr. Corleone, you have been
advised as to your legal rights.
We have testimony from a witness,
a previous witness...
one Willi Cicci.
He has stated that you are head...
of the most powerful Mafia family
in this country.
- Are you?
- No, I'm not.
The witness has testified that
you are personally responsible...
for the murder of a New York City
police captain in 1947.
And with him,
a man named Virgil Solozzo.
- Do you deny this?
- Yes, I do.
Is it true that in the year 1950...
you devised a murder of the heads
of the so-called "five families"...
in New York, to assume
and consolidate...
your nefarious power?
- That's a complete falsehood.
- Is it true...
you have a controlling interest
in three major hotels in Las Vegas?
No, it is not true. I own some stock
in some of the hotels there...
but very little.
I also have stock in IBM and IT&T.
Do you have any interests or control
over gambling and narcotics...
in the state of New York?
No, I do not.
Senator, my client would like to
read a statement for this committee.
Mr. Chairman,
I think this statement...
is totally out of order
at this time.
Sir, my client has answered every
question asked by this committee...
with the utmost sincerity.
He did not take the Fifth Amendment,
as it was his right to do...
so in all fairness I think
the statement should be heard.
No, I'm going to allow Mr. Corleone
to read his statement.
I'll put it in the record.
"In the hopes of clearing
my family name...
and my sincere desire to give
my children their fair share...
of the American way of life
without a blemish...
on their name and background...
I have appeared
before this committee...
and given it all the cooperation
in my power.
I consider it a great dishonor
to me personally...
to have to deny
that I am a criminal.
I wish to have the following
noted for the record:
that I served my country faithfully
and honorably in World War Two...
and was awarded a Navy Cross for
actions in defense of my country...
that I have never been arrested or
indicted for any crime whatsoever...
that no proof linking me to any
criminal conspiracy...
whether it is called "Mafia,"
"Cosa Nostra"...
or whatever other name
you wish to give...
has ever been made public.
I have not taken refuge
behind the Fifth Amendment...
although it is my right to do so.
I challenge this committee...
to produce any witness
or evidence against me.
And if they do not...
I hope they will have the decency
to clear my name...
with the same publicity with which
they now have besmirched it."
I'm sure we're allquite impressed,
Mr. Corleone...
particularly with your love
for our country.
Committee will stand in recess
until 10:00 a.m. Monday morning...
at which time the committee
will produce a witness...
who will corroborate the charges
which were made against you today...
and at which time, Mr. Corleone,
you may very well be subject...
to indictment for perjury.
I remind you that
you're still under subpoena.
Adjourned.
Ten-to-one shot, you said.
Ten-to-one shot
he would take the Fifth...
and I lose.
You sound like my bookie.
I owe that monkey my life.
Well, just get
a good night's sleep.
- Good night's sleep.
- Got a big day tomorrow.
Got you a new suit,
a new shirt, new tie.
I'm gonna shave you myself
in the morning.
You're gonna look respectable for
50 million of your fellow Americans.
My life won't be worth a nickel
after tomorrow.
Come on.
I saw this thing 19 times.
You got a great home here, Frankie.
The rest of your life, nobody gets
near you, you're not going anywhere.
That's great.
Beautiful.
Some deal I made.
You'll live like a king.
You'll be a hero.
You'll live better in here
than most people on the outside.
Some deal.
Jesus.
Alive.
Pentangeli is alive.
- How'd they get their hands on him?
- Roth. He engineered it.
Frankie went to make a deal
with the Rosato brothers...
and they tried to kill him.
He thought you double-crossed him.
Our people with the New York
detective said he was halfdead...
scared stiffand calling out loud
that you turned on him.
They already had him on possession,
bookmaking, murder one...
and a lot more.
The FBI has him airtight.
He's on an army base,
24-hour guards.
No way we can get to him.
You've opened yourself
to five counts of perjury.
What about Fredo?
What does he know?
He says he doesn't know anything,
and I believe him.
Roth-- he played this one
beautifully.
I want to talk to Fredo.
I haven't got a lot to say, Mike.
We have time.
I was kept pretty much in the dark.
I didn't know all that much.
What about now? ls there anything
you can help me out with?
Anything you can tell me now?
They got Pentangeli,
that's all I can tell you.
I didn't know
it was gonna be a hit, Mike.
I swear to God,
I didn't know it was gonna be a hit.
Johnny Ola bumped into me
in Beverly Hills...
and he said
that he wanted to talk.
He said that you and Roth...
were in on a big deal together...
and that there was something in it
for me if I could help him out.
He said that you were being tough
on the negotiations.
But if they could get a little help
and close the deal fast...
it'd be good for the family.
You believed that story?
You believed that?
He said there was something in it
for me... on my own.
I've always taken care of you.
Taken care of me?
You're my kid brother.
You take care of me?
Did you ever think about that?
Did you ever once think about that?
Send Fredo off to do this,
send Fredo off to do that.
Let Fredo take care of some
Mickey Mouse nightclub somewhere.
Send Fredo to pick somebody up
at the airport.
I'm your older brother, Mike,
and I was stepped over!
- That's the way Pop wanted it.
- It ain't the way I wanted it!
I can handle things!
I'm smart!
Not like everybody says.
Like dumb. I'm smart...
and I want respect!
Is there anything you can tell me
about this investigation?
Anything more?
The Senate lawyer, Questadt...
he belongs to Roth.
You're nothing to me now.
You're not a brother,
you're not a friend.
I don't wanna know you
or what you do.
I don't wanna see you at the hotels.
I don't want you near my house.
When you see our mother,
I wanna know a day in advance...
so I won't be there.
You understand?
I don't want anything to happen
to him while my mother's alive.
There are more people
than a ball game in here.
There's Willi Cicci.
This committee will come to order.
- State your name, please.
- Frank Pentangeli.
- And where were you born?
- Partanego. Outside of Palermo.
Where do you live now?
I live in an army barracks
with the FBI guys.
We have here, finally, a witness
that will further testify...
to Michael Corleone's rule
over a criminal empire...
that controls all of the gambling
in this country...
and perhaps in other countries.
This witness had no buffer between
himself and Michael Corleone.
He can corroborate ourcharges on
enough counts for this committee...
to recommend a charge of perjury
against Michael Corleone.
- Senator.
- Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
Mr. Pentangeli.
Were you a member
of the Corleone family?
Did you serve under
caporegime Peter Clemenza...
under Vito Corleone,
also known as the "Godfather"?
I never knew no Godfather.
I have my own family, Senator.
Mr. Pentangeli, you are
contradicting a sworn statement...
you'd previously made to me
and signed.
I ask you again, sir,
here and now under oath...
were you at anytime
a memberof a crime organization...
headed by Michael Corleone?
I don't know nothing about that.
I was in the olive oil business
with his father...
but that was a long time ago,
that's all.
We have a sworn affidavit.
We have it--
your sworn affidavit...
that you murdered on
the orders of Michael Corleone.
Do you deny that confession?
And do you realize what will happen
as a result of your denial?
Look, the FBI guys,
they promised me a deal...
so I made up a lot of stuff
about Michael Corleone...
'cause that's what they wanted.
But it was all lies--
everything.
And they kept saying...
Michael Corleone did this...
and that Michael Corleone did that.
So I said, "Yeah, sure!"
Mr. Corleone, would you kindly
identify for the committee...
the gentleman sitting
to your left?
I can answer that.
His name is Vincenzo Pentangeli.
- Is he related to the witness?
- He is, I believe, his brother.
Will he come forward
and be sworn, sir?
Sir, this man
does not understand English.
He came at his own expense to aid
his brother in this time of trouble.
He's not under subpoena.
His reputation is impeccable.
Are you saying he knows nothing
about these matters?
To my knowledge, nothing.
I'm gonna find out
what the hell happened here.
Allright, this committee
is now adjourned.
- The witness is excused.
- Senator!
This committee owes an apology!
This committee owes an apology.
Apology, Senator.
- Michael, excuse me.
- Hold on a minute.
The children are outside.
We're going.
What do you mean you're going?
We're all gonna leave tomorrow.
I'll be in my room.
Michael, I'm not going
back to Nevada.
I brought the children
to say good-bye to you.
I want you to know
I'm very happy for you.
I suppose I always knew
you were too smart...
to let any of them
ever beat you.
- Why don't you sit down?
- I'm not going to stay long.
There are some things
I'd like to talk to you about.
Some things that have been
on my mind.
- Changes I wanna make.
- I think it's too late for changes.
I promised myself
I wasn't going to say anything.
You're too late.
What really happened
with Pentangeli?
His brother came, helped him.
I didn't even know
he had a brother.
Where is he now?
He's on a plane back to Sicily.
All he had to do
was show his face.
It was between the brothers.
I had nothing to do with it.
Nobody is going--
not you, not the kids! You hear me?
You're my wife, they're my children.
I love you. I won't allow it.
You say you love me, then you
talk about allowing me to leave!
Things have been going on for years
between men and women...
- that will not change.
- You've become blind!
- Blind to what?
- Look what happened to us.
- Look what's happened to our son!
- Nothing's happened--
- Anthony is fine!
- Anthony is not fine!
- I don't wanna hear about it!
- You will!
Anthony's not fine!
I don't wanna hear about it!
Over!
At this moment,
I feel no love for you at all.
I never thought
that would ever happen...
but it has.
We're gonna leave tomorrow.
Okay? Why don't you take the kids
back to their room?
You haven't heard me.
What do you want from me?
Do you expect me to let you go?
Do you expect me to let you take
my children from me?
Don't you know me? Don't you know
that that's an impossibility?
That that could never happen?
That I'd use all my power to keep
something like that from happening?
Don't you know that?
Now, in time...
you'll feel differently.
You'll be glad I stopped you now.
I know that.
I know you blame me
for losing the baby.
Yes.
I know what that meant to you.
I'll make it up to you.
I swear, I'll make it up to you.
I'm gonna change.
I'll change.
I've learned that I have
the strength to change.
And you'll forget about
this miscarriage...
and we'll have another child...
and we'll go on--
you and I.
We'll go on.
You are blind.
It wasn't a miscarriage.
It was an abortion.
An abortion.
Just like our marriage
is an abortion.
Something that's unholy and evil.
I didn't want your son!
I wouldn't bring another one
of your sons into this world!
It was an abortion!
It was a son! A son!
And I had it killed...
because this must all end!
I know now that it's over.
I knew it then.
There would be no way...
no way you could ever forgive me...
not with this Sicilian thing...
that's been going on
for 2,000 years--
Bitch!
- You won't take my children.
- I will.
- You won't take my children!
- They're my children too.
Fredo, here's this for Grandma.
What are you doing?
Michael, say good-bye.
Can I speak with you
for a second?
- Where's Mike?
- Waiting foryou to leave.
Can I talk with him?
Sorry, no chance.
- Can I see him?
- He's in the boathouse.
Michael, it's Connie.
I'd like to stay close to home now,
if it's all right.
Is Kay coming?
Fredo's in the house with Mama.
He asked for you,
and Tom said you wouldn't see him.
That's right.
Kids, why don't you go outside
for a while?
Please, I wanna talk to you.
I hated you for so many years.
I think that I did things to myself,
to hurt myself...
so that you'd know...
that I could hurt you.
You were just being strong
for all of us the way Papa was.
And I forgive you.
Can't you forgive Fredo?
He's so sweet
and helpless without you.
You need me.
I want to take care ofyou now.
Sit down.
Our friend and business partner,
Hyman Roth, is in the news.
You hear about it?
I hear that he's in Israel.
And the High Court in Israel
turned down his request...
to live there as a returned Jew.
His passport's been invalidated,
except for return to the US.
He landed in Buenos Aires yesterday.
He offered a gift of a million
dollars if they let him live there.
They turned him down.
- He's gonna try Panama.
- Panama won't take him.
Not for a million,
not for ten million.
His medical condition
is reported as terminal.
He's only gonna live
another six months anyway.
He's been dying of
the same heart attack for 20 years.
- That plane goes to Miami.
- Right. That's where I want it met.
Mike, that's impossible.
They'll turn him over directly...
to the lnternal Revenue, Customs
and half the FBl.
It's not impossible.
Nothing's impossible.
It would be like trying to kill
the president. No way to get to him.
You know, you surprise me.
If anything in this life
is certain--
if history's taught us anything...
it's that you can kill anyone.
Difficult, not impossible.
Good.
Why did you ask me if something
was wrong when I came in?
I thought you were
gonna tell me that...
you were moving
your family to Vegas.
And that you'd been offered the
vice presidency of the hotels there.
- I thought you'd tell me that.
- I turned them down.
Do I have to tell you
about every offer that I turn down?
Let's do business.
All right.
Just consider this.
Just consider it.
Now, Roth and the Rosatos
are on the run.
Are they worth it,
and are they strong enough?
Is it worth it?
I mean, you won.
Do you want to wipe
everybody out?
I don't feel I have to wipe
everybody out--
just my enemies, that's all.
You gonna come along with me on
these things I have to do or what?
'Cause if not, you can take your
wife, family and your mistress...
move them all to Las Vegas.
Why do you hurt me? I've always been
loyal to you. I mean, what is this?
What is it that you want me to do?
How would you like it if I taught
you how to catch really big fish?
- Would you like that?
- Okay.
You know, when I was your age...
I went out fishing
with all my brothers...
and my father...
everybody...
and I was the only one
that caught a fish.
Nobody else could catch one,
except me.
You know how I did it?
Every time I put the line
in the water, I said a Hail Mary.
And every time I said a Hail Mary,
I caught a fish.
You believe that?
It's true.
That's the secret.
Wanna try it
when we go on the lake?
Okay.
What else you got?
Things are gonna be okay, Frankie.
Don't worry.
- Did my brother go back?
- Yeah. Don't worry.
He's ten times tougher than me--
my brother.
He's old-fashioned.
He didn't wanna go out to dinner.
He just wanted to go straight home.
That's my brother.
There's nothing...
that could get him away
from that two-meal town.
He could've been big here,
could've had his own family.
What do I do now?
You were always interested
in politics and history.
I remember you talking about Hitler
back in '33.
I still read a lot.
I get good stuff in there.
You were around the old-timers...
agreeing about how the family's
should be organized...
based on the old home allegiance
and called them regimes--
capos and soldiers.
And it worked.
Yeah, it worked.
Those were the great old days,
you know?
And we was like the Roman Empire.
The Corleone family
was like the Roman Empire.
It was once.
When a plot
against the emperor failed...
the plotters were always given
a chance...
to let the families
keep their fortunes.
Yeah, but only the rich guys.
The little guys,
they got knocked off...
and all their estates
went to the emperors...
unless they went home
and killed themselves.
Then nothing happened to them.
And their families
were taken care of.
That was a good break.
Nice deal.
Yeah.
They went home...
and sat in a hot bath...
opened up their veins...
and bled to death.
And sometimes they had
a little party before they did it.
Don't worry about anything.
Thanks, Tom. Thanks.
See you, Tom.
You have to go.
- So pretty.
- Please hurry. He's coming.
Go rest.
Kiss Mama good-bye.
Will you kiss your mother good-bye?
Say good-bye to Mama.
I love you.
Please.
Come here.
Please, kiss me once.
Easy.
He's here!
We're going fishing!
Michael wants to take him
to Reno now!
Oh, shit.
Okay, kid, you gotta go to Reno
with your pop.
Come on, I'll take you
fishing tomorrow, okay?
Okay.
Attaboy.
Hey, Anthony.
Listen. I'll catch one for you
in secret, huh? All right?
Okay, go ahead.
Okay, let's go.
Mr. Roth, you understand
I'll have to take you into custody?
Yes, I understand.
Can you give us your reaction to
the High Court of Israel's ruling?
I'm a retired investor
on a pension.
I went to Israel because I wished
to live there as Jew...
in the twilight of my life.
Hey, Frankie, come on out!
Let's play some hearts!
Is it true you're worth
over $300 million, Mr. Roth?
I'm a retired investor
living on a pension.
I came home to vote
in the presidential election...
because they wouldn't give me
an absentee ballot.
Jesus Christ.
Hail Mary, full of grace...
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed are thou amongst women.
Blessed is the fruit of thy womb,
Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for us sinners.
Hey, everybody,
come on, pay attention. Come here.
This is my friend, Carlo Rizzi.
My brother, Fredo.
- You know Fredo.
- Sure.
Here's my stepbrother, Tom.
That's his girl, Theresa.
This cute little thing over here's
my sister Connie I told you about.
Come on, say hello to Carlo.
He's good-looking, ain't he?
Yes.
Oh, that droopy thing over there,
that's my brother, Mike.
We call him Joe Collar, you know
what I mean? Go on, sit down.
- Go ahead. Talk to each other.
- Sit down.
Hey, Mr. Einstein.
- Here's the cake.
- Hey, get in here.
- Where's your father?
- On a wild goose chase.
- Here.
- Let's see that thing.
- Oh, honey, that's nice.
- That's beautiful.
- Should I put the candles on now?
- Go on. You help her, all right?
Sure.
- What is that, rum?
- Yeah.
Sonny, come on, don't touch
the antipasto till Pop sees it.
What do you think, the nerve of them
Japs, them slanty-eyed bastards?
Dropping bombs on our own backyard.
On Pop's birthday, you know?
They didn't know
it was Pop's birthday.
Well, we should've expected it
after the oil embargo.
What do you mean, expected it?
They got no right dropping bombs.
What are you, a Jap lover?
You on their side?
I understand 30,000 men enlisted
this morning.
- Bunch of saps.
- Why are they saps?
Come on, do we even have to talk
about the war?
You talk to Carlo, all right?
They're saps because
they risk their lives for strangers.
- That's Pop talking.
- You're goddamn right.
They risk their lives
for their country.
Country ain't your blood.
You remember that.
- I don't feel that way.
- "I don't feel that way."
If you don't feel like that,
quit college and join the army.
I did.
I enlisted in the Marines.
- Mike, why didn't you come to us?
- What do you mean?
Pop had to pull a lot of strings
to get you a deferment.
I didn't ask for it.
I didn't ask for a deferment.
I didn't want it.
Come on, knock it off! Come on!
Punk.
- Go on.
- Sit down.
Mommy, Daddy's fighting again!
Go show Carlo the tree.
Nice.
Break your father's heart
on his birthday.
That's swell. Congratulations.
That's right, encourage him.
Go on, get me a drink.
Go on.
I don't understand.
Your father has plans for you.
Many times, he and I have talked
about your future.
You talked to my father
about my future?
- My future?
- He has high hopes for you.
I have my own plans
for my future.
Did you go to college to get stupid?
You're really stupid.
He's here, come on!
Come on.
Stupid.
Surprise!
For he's a jolly good fellow
Which nobody can deny