Now they're on line.
- This is masked as Marlo's
cell number?
How the fuck how?
- Spoofed to imitate
a call stream
like it's
a phone company switch.
We can put any digits in
we want.
Meanwhile, phone company
paperwork on the case
has the cell
we gave to Sydnor.
It's fairly basic shit.
- Now, stick to
the script.
We don't want
any tell-tales.
Even with
the voice modulator,
you're exposed here.
Seven-baker-fourteen.
Bga, go ahead fourteen.
Fourteen.
I got a vehicle
blocking an entrance.
Four hundred pressman.
- What the--
Oh, shit.
Templeton.
Hey, you--
Where do you get off,
you sick little twist?
Sexual?
I'm not sexual with them.
I'm not abusive with them.
How dare you write
that in your paper
without knowing
nothing about me--
What?
- Biting's not sex,
it's biting.
I'm not sick like that.
- Whoa, hang on--
Hang on, hang on.
- Maybe I should
come bite you.
Would you like that,
scotty?
I bet you would
like that.
Am I right?
You write about me
like I'm sick.
You're the sick one,
you know that?
Is that why you like me,
scotty?
Is that why?
Fuck me--
Yeah, this is Holley,
Baltimore homicide.
I need a trap-and-trace on case
oh-eight, h-one-fourteen.
Cell phone is in use
right now.
- I could come bite you;
you tell me how sexual it is.
Okay, hang on.
Who, where are you--
- Well, here's what's
happening now.
You humiliate me
like that?
You mortify me like that
in front of my father?
My father's father?
Listen to me,
smack daddy, crack daddy,
little baby whack daddy,
here's what's happening.
You ain't never
going to find them anymore.
You ait never gonna
see them no more.
I'm sending you
something right now.
You take a good look
at this guy,
because you ain't ver
going to see him no more.
Hey, okay.
Don't hang up.
Can we--
Oh, shit.
Did you get McNulty?
Just his voicemail.
Oh, Christ.
That was--
That was him.
Again!
Nice bawlmer accent.
It's my heritage.
- Has traced
the phone in question
to pier five
on pratt street.
All units respond to that twenty
and detain anyone present
pending the arrival
of a duty officer.
- One-baker-ten,
copy that.
I'm rolling.
- One-ker-thirteen,
I'm almost there.
Kga to all units.
Be advised
that we're looking
for a ten-thirty individual
on a cell phone.
- Anyone on a phone?
- Not that I saw.
Just some people
moving through,
but it could be anybody.
Let's just fan out
and take names.
Go down this road.
Get their names
over there.
Get everybody up
in this area now.
Stop.
What the hell is this?
- Hey, let go of me.
- Get your hands up--
Get on the ground now.
- Get your hands up!
Step out!
- Get everody over there
and get their cell phones.
- I need everyone to take out
yourell phones
and place them on the table
in front of you.
- Stop,
he didn't do anything.
What are you doing?
Sarge, we got him.
- Bullshit.
- I got him on tape.
- The goof
actually called.
- Yeah, yeah,
it was sweet--
Hey, what'd I miss?
- He went off
on a tangent.
Said he wanted to bite me.
- What?
Bite you how?
- Scott, are you saying
that he threatened to--
- Wait a minute.
Hold on a second.
Holy Christ.
- So are we partners
or what?
No, Clay.
I don't pick
so much as a single juror
without a full amount
of my fee being paid.
If you want Billy Murphy
on your case,
you got to pay
to put him there.
- I got a taste for you
right up front.
A good,
five-figure taste.
But you asking for me to pay
a winner's fee right up front,
and you know what?
I ain't a winner yet.
Right now, with the sword
hanging over my head,
I don't have the kind of
financial support at my disposal
that I would ordinarily be
able to rely upon, you feel?
- So the money boys
are laying off, huh?
- Oh, they thinkin' short when
they should be thinkin' long.
Shameful shit.
25,000, 25,000 more
when you seat a jury.
I don't work that way.
- I know you don't, partner,
I know you don't.
And normally, I wouldn't dream
of asking you to suit up
for game day
with my tab, as it is.
- 200,000 when I get you out
from under this mess.
And Clay,
don't fuck me.
Don't even think about fucking me
out of a single part of that fee.
- Oh, Billy, you talk
as if you don't know me.
I'm disappointed.
I am.
My brother,
let's be fair.
I'm providing you
with the opportunity
to go head to head
with the state's attorney
in a case that's gonna be
front page news.
For all that profile?
Sheet, partner,
you should be payin' me a fee.
- Seriously, dawg, for 20,000
cash to my campaign committee,
I'll get myself indicted
federal,
let you go to trial
on that.
Beat the feds
like a stepchild,
an' really make a name
for yourself.
Fuck you?
Naw, son,
I'm gonna make you.
Motherfuckers gonna be
wipin' they ass
with johnnie Cochran's
memory,
and carryin'
your business card
in every damn pocket
before we done.
no.
I already got more rep
than any lawyer would ever nee
why don't you save that
silver-tongued bullshit for the jury?
Right.
No, nothing since.
Alright.
- Me, barlow and kincaid
been sittin' here
like the fucking maytag
repairmen, growing piles.
Nothing, not a call.
Then, bang.
No luck at the harbor.
We were tracking the g.p.s.
Then it just goes dead.
Area of pier five.
Where's McNulty right now?
- He's over
at the newspaper.
- Let's hear
that motherfucker again.
Hey, you-- where do you get
off, you sick little twist?
- Sounds like some gearhead
from dundalk.
- And emotionally,
how was he?
He sounded pissed.
At you, personally?
- Like I told you,
he sd I humiliated him
by writing
that the biting was sexual.
At the end, he offered
to come here and bite me.
I didn't really
respond to that.
Okay.
Did he sound like
the same guy?
What do you mean?
- Did it sound like the same
voice you heard on the first call?
- Oh, right.
Yeah.
No, actually.
I mean, yeah.
It was the same,
but this time I noticed
he had a real thick
bawlmer accent.
Real thick.
- You didn't notice
that theirst time, huh?
- I guess I did,
but I forgot.
Did I screw up
in any way?
- No.
Not at all.
- Listen, we reserve the right
to make this decision,
but that said,
would running these photos
in any way
impair the investigation?
I don't think so.
Fact is, we need
as many eyes as we can
looking for
this homeless guy.
- You don't know
where is guy is, huh?
He could be--
- Could already be
a victim, sure.
Jesus.
That's Charles and conway.
I wonder if he's a regular
out there.
- He had to have used
a different phone though.
Had to have been a cell phone
if he sent you these.
- That's true. But, again,
you can't print anything
about where
he's calling from.
We're trying to get up
on that cell phone.
- What should I do
if he calls again?
- Keep him on the line
as long as you can.
Don't spook him.
Guy likes to rant.
Let him do his thing.
You okay?
me?
Yeah, I guess.
- I wouldn't worry;
he's just using you.
He needs you.
- I kind of resent that,
actually.
Oh, I dunno.
It's workin' out pretty well
for both of you, right?
Gentlemen--
Thanks for these.
- Callin' Vincent
on his cell all morning,
he still ain't answer.
Ain't got time for this.
Re-up time
will come due,
we still ain't picked up
the mannitol.
What the fuck?
Yo, Vincent.
Where you at?
Manny? Manny?
Shit.
Omar.
- Why you still
alive then?
- He say tell Marlo
he out in the streets, waitin'.
Say this whole damn city
gonna know
Marlo ain't man enough
to come down in the streets.
He get the stash?
Yo, cherry.
He blew manny up
as soon as he got inside.
He was gonna do me, too.
- How the fuck
he get inside?
- Manny open up
to go on the food run,
an' this dicksucker
was right there.
He knew
we was the stash.
Ain't need to be told shit.
He just knew.
- Four key of raw;
flushed.
- Hey, yo, cherry.
You gonna untie me, right?
C'mon, nigga,
untie me--
Seriously, steven.
If you can't afford it,
that's fine, I understand.
And if you think this clown
is gonna hold me off
and keep the statehouse,
then I know
you've got to hedge your bets
given how much you're
waiting on fm annapolis.
But if you're gonna choose
a side on this thing,
please, do it early.
That's all I'm saying.
I hear ya, Tom.
You know what, I'm going
to write out a check today,
and send it out the door.
- That's great, steven;
really, I do appreciate it.
Can you, um,
can I ask you to consider--
- I'll double down on that
for my wife, too.
For your wife, too.
That's just great, really.
Yeah, thanks for going
the extra mile on this.
No problem, Tom.
Photographs?
- He messaged digital photos
of the possible victim
to the "sun" reporter.
I've canvassed this guy's
regular corner,
and he has indeed been missing
a couple days.
We got these photos
from the newspaper,
but we want to be able to
intercept any future images--
Hence the amended order.
Correct.
- Can we catch photos
with our city equipment?
Actually, no.
We're still bumping around
in the 20th century.
But howard county
has the right software
on a couple
of their computers.
You need two?
- Yeah, in case
one computer goes down,
we got the other one
as back-up.
We don't wanna Miss our shot
at this nut.
Well, good hunting.
Thank you, judge.
Oh, Ronnie.
You briefed your boss?
And he's calling the mayor,
right?
- And Rawls too,
I imagine.
- Ah, pretty little fella
gets himself elected
on a law and order ticket.
Crime doesn't go down much,
and then, a couple weeks before he starts
gearing up to announce for governor,
some wingnut starts
killing people,
taking photographs,
sending 'em to the newspaper.
You know something?
You may wanna check
the governor's alibi.
You know?
Oh--thanks.
- You couldn't
make thirty?
Twenty?
Ninety-two.
I'm gonna tell you
something.
There are a lot of people
who want Tommy Carcetti
to be their fuckin' governor.
And I can't imagine
what they're thinking.
Ninety-two, Norman,
in a single morning.
It is a new record.
- The motherfucker
killing homeless guys?
He grabbed one
off the street,
wrapped a ribbon
on his wrist,
sent a photo
to the "Baltimore sun,"
saying we won't
find the body.
He--what?
- The newspaper's
gonna run the photos.
Bill Rawls.
I need him
on the line now.
* you rascal you
* I'll be glad when you're dead,
you rascal you *
ah--aw, look at ya,
ya baby-bumpin'
motherfucker.
Look at you.
Let's go.
Deputy wants
as much of my squad
as I can wrangle upstairs
right now.
We're going large Richard
on McNulty's serial killer.
I'm worçing my cases.
- Bunk,
command performance.
The deputy wants bodies.
The mayor's spewing
over this thing.
I'm not going.
- What? You don't see those
on my sleeve?
Plain as fuckin' day,
Bunk.
- I'm doing police work
here.
In fact, I have a fresh angle
on last year's major case,
on which I'm the sole
remaining investigator.
So fuck your stripes
and fuck McNulty,
and fuck your
big-dick red ball.
If you can't work with that,
then just write me the fuck up,
and ship my ass
to a trial board.
- So, for starters, alma
stays with the investigation,
and detectives
downtown.
You don't go home
without checking for updates
before the E-dot
and double-dot editions.
So the case file is McNulty,
with the rest of his squad
as immediate support.
Lieutenant d'addario's shift
will man the wiretap.
- In addition to
alma and Scott,
olesker will have
a column coming.
Fletcher, I want you
on homeless react,
also interviews with
advocates and experts
talking up the problem.
Melody,
you get on the phone
with the whitecoats at
clifton t. Perkins or wherever,
and work up a sidebar
on what it means
when a whackjob
kills somebody
and wants to talk
to reporters about it.
- Greg, I've been
scanning the casework,
and I note that while there have been
numerous field interviews and canvasses;
we haven't done much
with background work
on victims and families.
If you could take charge
of that--
Colonel tomlin,
we're going to need tactical
to provide surveillance cars
and undercover decoys
where the homeless gather.
We need to be
in the street, proactive.
This case is as much about
preventing another abduction or murder
as it is about making
an arrest--
- Thing is, we can't work
this one with the phone.
We need to be in the street,
at eye level--
- We need to keep the media
as part of the equation.
This reporter
that's bn contacted--
He's in the middle of it.
That may be a way
to solve this thing.
- You're in the middle
this now,
so while we're still going to
present this as a first-person piece
on your latest contact
with the killer,
alma's still going to interview
you for the mainbar.
- Now, McNulty's preliminary
checks with shelter workers,
and a canvass
of conway and Charles,
indicates that our victim
is indeed missing,
but when we get
a full I.D.,
we need toun every connection
to make sure this isn't a hoax.
Chief, we're going to need to
pull bodies from district ops
to give homicide
their own surveillance arm.
And having had some experience
in the politics of staffing,
I leave it to McNulty
to pick the people.
- For once, people,
I am assured
that the resources we need
to work this story
will be there for us.
So let's surround this mess
and report the hell out of it.
This one's got legs.
- I am now told,
by the mayor directly,
that there will be
no overtime restrictions,
no staffing limits
on this case.
So put this case down.
- Police work.
Whaddaya know?
Good day.
Six g-packs so far.
New package be
droppin' them fiends.
Yeah.
Probably need
one more re-up.
- Career day
on the corner, hanh?
Step off, nigga.
- Hey, Mike,
check th out.
"certified
hydrotherapist,
"experience with
geri-atric patients,
sinai hospital
outpatient clinic."
Jerry who?
- Whatever, how about this--
"dental front desk,
high quality dental office
seeks front desk."
- What do they mean,
like furniture?
- Like a secretary,
I guess.
- Man, you ain't even
ever been to no dentist.
- "Huhvac maintenance
supervisor."
- What the fuck
is a huhvac?
- "H-V-a-c."
Maybe they spelled it bad.
"systems manager in
a deadline driven environment."
- Man, ain't
nothing there.
And even if there was,
you ain't sixteen,
and y'all got to pick up bug
after three--
- Hey, hey, hey,
hang on, hang on--
"exotic dancer,
"downtown financial district
lunch time hours--
Must be flexible
in body and mind."
Now we talking--
Heeeeeey--
Make it rain on 'em.
Make it rain.
Hold up.
Time out.
Fuck did I do?
- If we don't know,
then you do.
This is bullshit.
Yo, don't forget
about bug.
- As this is an ongoing
investigation,
I'm going to ask
that you direct questions
to the police officials
best equipped to answer.
These new developments in the case
of the homeless slayings in our city
are troubling and tragic
and unacceptable.
We are now doing
everything possible
to locate and identify
the individual
depicted in the photographs sent
to the "Baltimore sun" today.
We are endeavoring to protect
other homeless citizens,
and we are
pursuing the suspect
with every means
at our disposal.
I have made clear
to my police commanders
that they have my full
confidence and the authority
to employ whatever resources
they require.
And let mee unequivocal--
This man
will be brought to justice.
Thank you.
- Mr. Mayor--
Mr. Mayor--
Voice and digital photos.
He calls again,
you'll capture either one.
- I can do those background
checks myself, Jay/
there's no need to--
You heard the deputy.
He specifically
assigned Greggs.
- Greggs
has an open triple.
- And this squad
has your serial killer,
and the case is shit-hot.
- Jay, I don't need--
- Jimmy--
You are the point man on the
motherfucker who's now missing.
You don't have time to be working
backgrounds on the older cases.
It goes to Greggs;
end of fucking story.
Now...
What else do you need?
- I'm gonna need those surveillance
teams as this thing sprawls,
but for right now,
let me pull this guy's I.D.
As fast as I can,
figure what he's about.
And after that,
I'll have more to spin off.
- Voice analysis
of the call?
- Shit, I don't believe
in that shit.
Next thing I know,
you'll want me to go
to fucking Quantico
with this fucking thing.
As a matter of fact--
You don't believe in behavioral
forensics, Dr. Moreland?
- I don't believe in much
of anything at this point.
- Well, it doesn't
fucking matter
what any of us believe
at this point.
You turned on
the fuckin' tap, Jimmy.
They're finally paying
for police work again.
Proud of yourselves?
We're close to Marlo.
A week or two at most.
- How does it feel getting
Greggs pulled off her triple?
How does it feel knong that you
got surveillance teams out there,
and district units,
and tactical--
All of 'em chasin'
bullshit.
- We're gonna use the
surveillance teams, actually.
They're gonna help us
bring in the case, Bunk.
I n't even want to know
whose picture you got
running in the paper,
or where that motherfucker
actually happens to be.
- Names and addresses;
whater you got.
Jimmy--
Don't ll yourself.
Shit.
Don't worry, son.
I got you covered
on all this.
Listen,
one other thing.
I, uh--I'm getting'
my kid for an overnight.
Where do I get
kid's furniture?
Ikea.
Ah, see y'all.
Shame on y'all.
I mean it.
Trace lab.
It's Moreland.
You just called.
- I know,
and I'm callin' again.
I need the tracework
on oh-six-h-two-seven-one,
and I need it now.
- I know, he hasn't been
around to it yet.
Well, tell him I called,
and tell him
I'm gonna keep calling
until he feels
my fucking pain, a-ight?
Gift-wrapped.
Number one.
Fuck.
How the fuck do they expect me
to get this shit done on my own?
Broke ass department
ain't even payin'--
You okay?
It's fucked up.
It's all fucked up, okay?
I could make a red
go to black
'cept for these cheap
motherfuckers--
Whaddaya got?
- Good snitch put the finger on
an eyeball wit been duckin' me.
He lays up at this one girl's
place at athol avenue, right?
Comes in late,
but he leaves early.
so?
- So I don't mind sittin' on the
place all night long an' not get paid.
But it's a garden
apartment.
Parking lots
on both sides,
and if he decides
to park on the street
and walk across the grass,
he still has
the fucking patio doors.
Two more men do it?
Yeah, and two more cars, yeah.
- I got more bodies than
I can use on my serial thing.
Lemme make a call,
hook you up with two tac guys.
You tell 'em you're sitting
on a twenty that I gave you.
I'll write up the hours
under my file.
And you can do that?
Go with God.
- Can you make out
who that is?
Yeah.
Look at you.
Not even blinking.
Not that I blame you
after what this heinous
motherfucker did to you.
Still, this right here
is vicious.
I mean, whoever did this
had a real time;
now you know
what I'm saying?
Now, I know it wasn't you
because with all due respect,
you don't have the physicality
to do this kind of damage.
I mean,
whoever did this
had to be a full-grown
and powerful individual--
A fearsome individual--
You see
what I'm sayin'?
You the murder police.
How the fuck
would I know?
- Is this spot good
for a stand-up?
- Let's go with
a wide shot on this.
- ...say they are hopeful
thathe renewed attention
to their son's death
a few years ago
will lead police to--
Kinda formula, I know.
Anecdotal lede,
nut graf, best quote--
- It works as a sidebar,
but for tomorrow,
let's stretch it some, huh?
Really spend some time with
some of these people, you know?
What I mean is, sometimes,
the weakest stuff in a story
is the shit with
quotation marks around it.
You got a guy telling
how rough it is on the street,
it really doesn't
have much pull.
But if you can describe him
as he really is,
tell his story
in moments.
Look, tomorrow,
get back in the shelters,
and the soup kitchens,
and just be with folk.
I don't even care
if you file copy on it.
I mean, if something
presents itself as a story,
great, but if not,
just spend the day
being with people.
I'm not interested in what can
be quoted or counted on this one.
I'm interested
in what feels true.
- I'm in, thirty inches, with room
for price's stuff from the hall.
Scott?
Five minutes.
- We're coming up
on first edition.
Three minutes.
- We had him in that,
what do you call it,
rehabilitation--
Four times.
We're not rich people.
Henry's on disability.
- We get him out,
he makes all kinds of promises,
but, well, you know--
I'm sorry.
- The last time, we decided
we wouldn't be there for him.
We knew he'd probably
die out there;
if the drugs get him,
we knew that.
But this thing in the newspaper,
this sex stuff.
The biting or whatever.
Jesus, nobody
deserves that.
- You see what I have
a problem with, right?
I mean, the first-person
is one thing.
I know he needs to put himself
in the story--
It's essential.
- But this business about him
being out there day and night
with the homeless--
I mean, this stuff
about sharing their--
Quote, darkest corners
with them, unquote--
- He's writing
more as an essayist.
- We've got a column
from olesker, front metro.
I mean, it's pretty powerful
without being purple.
But this stuff
that Scott's written,
it makes it sound like he's been
ling with the homeless for weeks.
He spends one night
under the j.f.x.,
another half day quoting people
in a homeless shelter.
It ain't exactly studs terkel.
- You don't think the piece
should run as it is?
- I mean, we have him
interviewed about the call
from the killer
in alma's mainbar.
We have his quotes.
But the rest
of this stuff,
he's acting like he's
taking his life in his hands,
he walks another highway
at night?
I mean, this is
our fucking city.
This ain't beirut.
I respect your concerns.
I'll take the piece
and mo it as my own edit.
How's that?
Okay.
- And while they declined
to talk on camera,
the parents of jonathan boland
say they are hopeful
that the renewed attention to
their son's death a few yes ago
will lead police
to his killer.
For channel six news,
I'm Patricia--
Media's going crazy.
City hall, too.
But for once, we're getting
what we need to do the job.
How does it feel?
Forbidden.
I feel like
at any moment,
they're gonna find out
how much we're spending
and shut us down.
You don't have all this
in your head yet?
- I just want to
go over it all again.
We finish voir dire
by lunch,
and then,
it's opening arguments.
- For Mr. Bond.
It's on him.
- He needs
a strong second.
He needs me to know
this case inside and out.
How much longer, Lester?
- If Marlo has a code,
we can break the code.
That's a given.
How long?
Depends on the code,
doesn't it?
- Quicker we bring this in
and shut it down,
the safer
we'll all be.
I mean, Landsman wants me
to go to fucking Quantico,
let the F.B.I.
Do a profile.
- Might learn something
about yourself.
It's not funny, Lester.
This shit's bigger than
I ever thought it would be.
The whole fuckin' city--
Yeah, Jay.
No. No, I don't need
an academy class
to help with a canvass
near this guy's corners.
Well, I don't need
any additional canvassing.
What? You wanna know why?
I'll tell you why.
Because I already know the name
of the missing smokehound.
Yeah, his name,
his d.o.b.
And his last known address
at a city shelter.
Lawrence butler,
3/10/1951,
400 west street,
south Baltimore men's shelter.
- Well, how did you
get all of that?
how?
Police work.
When I have more leads,
sergeant,
I'll be able to use
the extra manpower you give me
and run this shit down.
But until then,
will you back off, Jay?
Yeah,
just back the fuck off.
Trouble with making this thing
into a red ball?
People started treating it
like a fucking red ball.
Jesus!
Get me out of this,
Lester.
As fast as you can.
- Senator--
Senator--
Senator, there have been rumors
of a last minute plea offer.
- How can I plead
to what I didn't do?
- What're you reading
there, senator?
This here?
"prometheus bound,"
an ancient play,
one of the oldest we have,
about a simple man
who was horrifically punished
by the powers that be
for the terrible crime of trying
to bring light to the common people.
In the words of aeschylus,
"no good deed goes unpunished."
I cannot tell you how much
consolation I find in these slim pages.
- One more question,
senator--
- Ladies and gentlemen, I do
believe I have my day in court
and I will see you inside.
- City hall
wants an update.
What do we know
about our missing mope?
What else?
- Sending a tape of the call
down to Quantico,
along with the case file.
They'll review,
then meet with us.
- You gotta hit every downtown
shelter or mission there is--
You want bodies for that?
I'm taking christeson.
The rookie?
- Yeah, he'll ask
the extra question.
He's hungry. He's--
I need more bodies,
I'll let you know.
- Heard what you did
with christeson,
letting him go
on his own case,
while you carry him
and two surveillance teams.
Your shit is right, Jimmy.
Thanks.
- So I got another one
for ya.
You remember
the rape-murder I had?
Bolton hill job?
Brother-in-law
of my rapist--
Last year
wouldn't talk to me,
but now, his wife
just got collared,
and if she gets locked up,
his kids go to family services,
so he's desperate to deal.
The problem is,
he's in the new York system--
Elmira, newburgh,
one of those places.
Anyway, I get a road car
and expenses,
I can put it down.
Jimmy, he strangled
a 20-year-old,
stuffed her
under her bed.
- Okay, give my c.c.
To motor pool.
I'll bury the expenses
and the o.t. In my file.
Thanks, brother.
- Ain't you the lil'
king of diamonds.
Homicide.
Naw, he's on the street
right now.
Call back
in a couple hours.
- On second thought, gonna have Norris
with me on that canvass today, boss.
- And with every single transaction
you've described, detective,
the money was routed through
the senator's personal account
and then
withdrawn as cash--
Yes, sir.
- Often
in the same amounts?
Often the exact amounts,
sometimes
slightly smaller amounts,
but always within a day
of the initial deposit.
- Thank you,
detective Freamon.
Your honor,
no further questions.
- Cross examination,
Mr. Murphy.
- No questions,
your honor.
You got a number?
What?
Number on a slip.
If you get a number,
I might could find you a seat.
It's Mac an' cheese today.
- Uh, no, um,
I'm a newspaper reporter.
- Oh, so you got
what to eat then.
- Yeah, came down here
just to hang out,
and get with
some homeless people.
- How come whenever
y'all be wanting homeless,
y'all come
to the soup kitchens?
- You don't serve
homeless?
Serve everybody.
Homeless, poor folks,
workin' people
tryin' to make it
to a paycheck.
Shit, half the neighborhood be
up here week before check day.
Hey, uh, you're not--
Homeless?
No, I'm down in
my sister's basement,
over at edmondson village.
What you need
the homeless to say?
Talk about the killings.
The thing going on
with the serial killer.
But mostly, I'm just
lookin' for a story
about what it's like
for them.
What life is like.
Hard times out here.
I can't imagine.
- You gonna write a story
about what life's like, huh?
Bubbles, man.
Michael fletcher.
- Sticking for the moment with
the west Baltimore hoops charity,
what were your basic
responsibilities there?
I can't rightly say.
- Yet, you Drew $40,000 a year
as the executive direcr.
nah.
All at money went straight
back to senator Davis.
- Ah!
None for you?
- I got paid through the
district office for drivin' him.
That money I kept.
An' whenever I would
go out to snatch some money
- for the senator--
- Objection.
- Sometimes
kick me back a few.
- Move to strike
all of that.
Sustained.
Disregard
that last comment.
This case is limited to
the charges stemming from
the operation of senator Davis'
non-profit charities.
Other matters
are not relevant.
Here it is.
- What the hell is that--
A meet at five-fifty?
I'm gonna go
get up on monk.
Hmm-hmm.
- You have a criminal history;
do you not, Mr. Price?
Yeah, I did some years.
- And when you last
got out of prison six years ago,
was setor Davis aware
of your criminal record?
Yes, sir.
- And yet,
he gave you a job,
but today, is this how
you repay him?
The testimony you gave
about returning the money
you earned
at the senator's charities,
you say you repaid it
to the senator in cash, correct?
Every time.
- So there's no proof that the
senator ever received that money,
isn't that correct?
I guess not.
You guess not.
- Mr. Price,
you acknowledged earlier
that in exchange
for your testimony,
you received immunity
from prosecution
for any charges
related to this case.
Is it fair to say that
testifying against senator Davis
ensures that you will not
yourself go to jail?
Got-damn right.
Mr. Price.
- I'm sorr--
Oh shit, sorry--
Mr. Price.
- Okay, my b, judge.
Sorry.
- Mr. Price,
do you expect this jury
to take the word
of a twice-convicted felon
over the word of a duly elected
member of the Maryland state senate?
What can I say?
Y'all can play it like
you feel an' leave me be.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I don't get it.
He hasn't moved off this spot
for an hour and a half.
- Alright, well, come
on back then, alright?
- Guy's been hitting
the bus shelters
every third
or fourth night.
We got two wounded
and one dead
going back to that piece
since december.
All I'm asking
is for hours
to stake this asshole out.
Guy's like clockwork.
Spot me an' garvey,
three nights
and the case is fuckin' down.
- I can give you
two nights.
- If he hits
on the third?
One night.
Okay, okay.
Two nights.
- You need to put
my c.c. Number on the ot slips
and you give those to Jay--
- It's cool.
I know the drill.
You do?
- You're doing good here,
boss--
What did you just call me?
What the hell is that?
Office reports.
Families of your victims,
debriefed in full.
And believe me,
it ruined my week.
Rough, huh?
- I'm sittin' there explaining
to the salt of the fuckin' earth
why their eldest,
who is living on the street
because nothing they did
could fix his problems,
but God knows they tried--
Why he met his end being bit on and
fucked with by some sick motherfucker
who used him
for jerk-off purposes.
How the shit
about the bite marks
get in the papers
in the first place?
Gotta run.
I got shit to assemble.
You didn't tell me that part
of it, did you, motherfucker?
Who's up next?
I got one at the corner
of calhoun and mosher.
- Jesus--
That poor guy.
- Wanna take him home
with you?
Shit.
Take me.
What?
- I'm just having fun
with you, man.
- Thanks for bringing me here,
man, showing me around.
nah.
Not about that.
Sure?
- Just--
Write it like it feels.
Fuck.
Shit!
- Rodney, you can't press
a regular for his whole tab.
It just isn't done.
I used to run a bar.
I know how these things work,
remember?
- Gus haynes,
in the flesh.
Well, more of it maybe.
How the hell you been?
Where you been hidin'?
You in vice still?
- Vice? Shit,
that does take me back.
I did eight years
in homicide, brother.
Now it's the western.
Speaking of hiding out,
when you stop comin' round?
Last I saw you was--
- Well, I'm not running
the districts anymore.
I'm an editor now, so--
- Then you can afford
to buy a round.
Hey, Dennis.
Let me pull your coat.
Long time, Gus.
Don't tell me you knew
I'd be here tonight.
- It's a cop bar, you know,
so, if it's not you,
it's some other face
from back in the day.
Theoretical question.
Oh, theoretical.
In that case, a double, rodney,
Gus is buyin'.
Two, rodney.
So...
What?
- I seen you
at the stash house, yo.
Ain't you used to be
with them Barksdale boys?
What they call you, yo?
Savino.
- That's right.
You ain't never
moved no dope.
You was always muscle
as I recall.
Now you musclin'
for Marlo, huh?
I wasn't there.
When they did the old man
like that, I wasn't there.
Chris an' Snoop,
they on that.
- Oh, I know
who was there.
So you innocent, huh?
Let me ask you
somethin' though.
Bein' that youuscle
for Marlo,
what you was gonna do
if you was there, huh?
Riddle me that.
Yeah.
You know what, yo?
Ready?
Yeah.
A-ight.
Yeah?
We got to talk.
I'll come over to you.
hmm.
Does that seem possible?
To go through the court system
with a false I.D.?
- Maybe the first time,
if she's got no priors,
no prints on file,
but after that?
B.p.I. Sheets have
fingerprint characteristics
that are like
an F.B.I. Bar code.
And it's paired
with a photo.
A name's one thing.
But unless||hese women
are twin sisters
and one's been carrying
the other one's hand around
in her purse
for the last twelve years--
Somebody's
yanking your chain.
It's definitely a code.
Definitely not having
much to do with time.
We're at a point where
I'm going to need more bodies,
surveillance cars,
man hours.
We're gonna have to stay
on these guys
until those clocks
start to make sense.
- Well, good news is they giving
me more manpower than I can waste.
Bad news?
- It's all around the office
that I'm giving out hours
and money to people
to work other cases.
I can't help it, Lester.
It's the kind of person
I am.
I give and give and give--
- You know,
if you're not careful,
you're gonna get shit on you,
on us.
Who's gonna complain?
Guys are working cases
and getting paid--
So what exactly
do you need?
Seven men.
No, eight.
And cars.
- Oh shit, they offered me men
from the districts,
and a surveillance supervisor
to run the detail.
- Anyone in the districts
we trust?
- Hmm.
Lemme think on that.
Yeah?
- I don't know how the fuck did
you of all people do this shit, huh?
how?
- You got the right
allen wrench?
God damn directions.
- What kind of scotch
you using?
ow!
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
Piece of shit!
- Yo, so you talked
to Chris, right?
What he say?
He didn't say shit.
He knows I ain't say
a fuckin' word to no police.
- And you heard what little
dermell said to the juvenile master?
Lady ax him like,
"yo, you got a record?"
he's like "yeah, bitch,
I got a record.
My record's so long
I'm about to put out an album."
- Uh uh uh, don't touch
that dial, young'un.
This a Stanfield
corner, huh?
huh?
You know who I am?
You make sure
you tell the boss man
that you know who it is
dropped savino last night.
Ya feel me?
You tell that man
I'ma drop all his muscle
until he get the heart to come
down to the street and dance.
You gonna remone that,
sweetpea?
- That's Omar?
Damn.
Savino dead, yo?
- Shit, man, if he'DA made me from
monk's apartment the other night,
I might be laid out
my own self.
Gimpy as a motherfucker.
- I don't know, senator.
I want to believe you.
I mean,
I'm your lawyer.
But there's all this
up on the board
that Mr. Bond
has on display--
$11,000
to west side hoops,
next day,
$11,000 drawn,
then $11,000 deposited in
your personal banking account--
- You bet
it all went into my account.
It made it easier
for me to do my job.
And at the end of the day?
Not one penny
stayed with me.
- I need you to do better
than that, senator.
Where are your records?
Records?
Yes, records.
For example,
this check for $11,000
dated january 22nd--
That was last winter, right?
So, some went to pay
everyone's b.g.E.,
'cause half my district was
gonna have the heat turned off,
and then, some went
for puff jackets for them
that got children in need.
Let me tell you
something, man.
My neck of the woods,
it's a jungle out there.
Everybody living hand to mouth,
improvising, hustlin',
make do with as little
as you can imagine.
Hell, that, uh, that TV show,
what's that, "survivor"?
Man, they want
some good contestants,
they need to come
around westside.
Folks I know?
Oh, we'd do great
on that show.
Practice every damn day
of our lives.
Hell,
and "fear factor"?
Oh, sheee--
Don't even get me started.
- Forgive me, but I still don't
understand how that justifies--
- Let me tell you something,
brother--
I don't know how they do it
out in Roland park--
Maybe prosecutor obonda
can enlighten me on that.
But my world is strictly
cash and carry,
and I am Clay Davis.
My people need something,
they know where to find me.
Let me tell you, brother,
I step out the door,
hit the corner of mosher
and pennsylvania,
you better believe
my pockets are bulging.
But by the time
I get to Robert street--
Objection!
Objection, your honor.
- Senator! Senator,
take a seat,
and refrain from off-hand
references to Mr. Bond.
- My apologies,
your honor.
- But these charities were
set up for basketball leagues
in city rec centers,
weren't they?
- Yeah, but you give me 20,000or
a basketball and an air pump,
I am pullin' goodly on that
for whatever,
whoever comes at me.
"senator Clay,
I gots to bury my mother,
"bail out my son,
"buy a new shirt
for a job interview,
pay my child's asthma doctor."
Takes me half an hour
to go a hundred yards,
and excuse me if I didn't ask
that old Arthur-itised woman
for a receipt,
or that young mother
needed the similac
to sign
a damned piece a paper
so I don't have to be up here
in this box right now
explainin' to folks who never
been in our neck of the woods
how things truly are.
And if a jury of my peers,
you all deem it right and true
for me to walk out of here
an upright
and justified man?
Oh, I ain't
gonna lie to you.
I'ma gonna do
the same damn thing tomorrow,
and the day after that
and the day after that,
until they got me laid out
at march's funeral home,
and truck me off
to mt. Auburn.
Silence.
Silence in this courtroom.
What about trailers?
Like fema.
We set up trailers to act as
temp housing for some of the--
Some of the shelter
popution.
You know, put 'em down
in war memorial plaza.
- Do you know how much
fema pays per trailer?
- A dozen trailers
for the homeless.
We've got three to four thousand
on the streets, at least.
It's symbolic.
You know, we're doing
what we can
with a civic disaster--
Like new orleans--
Abandoned by the state,
ignored by the federal
government.
- It's bad enough you want to
keep the city shelters open 24/7.
That puts
the health department
a couple hundred thousand
in the red.
You add that to the overage
we're gonna see
for letting
the police department run wild
with overtime
and investigative costs--
There's no choice anymore.
This thing has a lock
on everyone's attention.
When another victim
disappears,
we're gonna be
even more on the spot.
- I'm just telling you, if
this goes on more than a month,
with what we'll be spending,
you're looking at cutbacks
throughout the agencies;
maybe even teacher layoffs
come the end of the fiscal.
- Teacher layoffs...
- By a gubernatorial candidate...
In an election year.
Lovely.
- Hold up, hold up,
whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I just want to say
that despite all the false
accusations made against me,
the people who I continue
to serve have spoken.
What the fuck just happened?
- ...as long as I can
to serve the people.
- Whatever it was, they don't
teach it in law school.
- 45 inches of Clay Davis
playing not just the race card,
but the whole deck,
coming at ya.
- Got it.
Thank ye.
- Someday you're going to have
to explain all this to me, Gus.
After watching that verdict
come in,
I feel very white.
- Well, start with some
James Brown records
and work up from there.
It's embarrassing,
ain't it?
- I can't believe nobody had
sense enough to tone this down.
The hype is bad enough.
But what gets me is
that I can't trust the guy.
I mean, I send him back out onto
the street to own his mistake,
he comes back with some
bullshit about stolen identities.
I don't give a fuck
he gets took.
Everybody gets took
now and then.
I know I did.
- It's about
not owning up to it.
- Gus, this thing with
the woman and the crab cake?
You think the first time
you catch him
is the first time
he does it?
- Lotta guys'll try
to duck a correction.
But the thing with this is,
he was standing
on an outright lie.
And if he'll lie
about a correction--
- Then will he lie to make a
story better than it ought to be?
- I keep thinking about
that kid in the wheelchair
out in front
of oriole park.
The one that only
had a nickname.
A black kid
from the westside,
crazy for baseball?
Basketball, yeah.
Football--sure
I don't wanna call
another reporter a liar.
I really don't.
What's the matter, baby?
You can't sleep?
Let's see--
Let's say good night
to everybody.
Good night, moon.
You say it.
There you go.
Good night, stars.
Good night, po-pos.
Good night, fiends.
Good night, hoppers.
Good night, hustlers.
Good night, scammers.
Good night to everybody.
- Good night
to one and all.
Good night to one and all.