Gotta be somewhere.
You wanna keep goin'?
Officer Smith, ma'am.
We're looking for a man
went after a woman last night
at esplanda apartments,
the ones right behind you.
Heard anything unusual?
- No, sorry.
Oh my God,
that's terrible.
Is the woman alright?
- Huh?
- The woman,
is she alright?
Yeah. Yeah, she good.
- Excuse me, my brother,
Omar little,
came here last night.
He fell out the damn window.
- We don't have
anyone by that name.
- He was kinda,
ya know, high.
Probably messed up his name.
Real dark,
got himself a scar.
Legs should
be busted up real bad.
- No one with that type
of injury came in last night.
- Not a goddamn thing. Been
in every trashcan, dumpster,
vacant for three blocks
'round. Nothin'.
We even checked
down the sewers.
Marlo wanna meet.
- So what you
want us to do?
Which one?
Don't seem possible.
It don't.
- That some
Spiderman shit there.
We missed our shot.
Now he gonna be at us.
- Usually, my staff
tries to keep sharp objects
out of my hands.
You know, it all
started with Charles center and
Tommy d'alesandro and
it continued with William Donald
schaefer and harborplace.
And following that,
there were mayors schmoke and
o'malley with inner harbor east.
Well, today it is my
administration's turn to
lay claim to the middle
branch of the patapsco and
what will soon become
known as new westport,
revitalizing another
waterfront area of
our great city.
Thank you.
- Say g'bye to locust
point south.
Fuck you, Krawczyk.
Yeah, fuck you,
greedhead motherfucker.
Fuck you for tearing down
the port of Baltimore and
selling it to some yuppie
assholes from washington.
- C'mon buddy.
- This is bullshit.
Who the hell's that?
- Oh that's nobody,
Mr. Mayor. It's nobody at all.
- Ya happy now, bitch?
- I am content, yes.
- You called the
reporter, huh? - no, actually.
That asshole's making up
his own shit.
Brass called a press
conference for this afternoon.
They're gonna be shoveling
so much money at
my bullshit it'll make
your head spin.
- What's with all the casework?
- Bodies from the vacants.
- And some of them have
been worked pretty good.
You know what, Jimmy?
I'm gonna go
back to the beginning and work
every one of them again.
Back to square one.
You know why?
Because I'm a murder police.
I work murders.
I don't fuck with
no make-believe,
I don't jerk shit around.
I catch a murder
and I work it.
Working this shit
like I'm supposed to.
- Well, lemme know
if you need anything, alright?
Cars, some o.t.,
some lab work...
Anything you need.
Because in... Three or
four hours the money's
gonna flow on my case.
Whatever you need, Bunk,
I'm probably
gonna have more of
it than
even Lester could use.
- To be that
close to a serial killer.
It must be weird.
Kinda. Yeah.
Wonderful story, Scott.
- Yeah, well, it kinda
wrote itself.
I mean, it's a lucky thing
to have the guy call m
like he did...
- Well it comes
from you pounding the
pavement, right?
That's more than luck.
That's putting yourself in
the place where the story
comes to you.
What do you have for tomorrow?
- For tomorrow?
- This is not the kind of thing
we let go of after a day or two.
- I, um, you know,
I was thinking that if I spent
a night with the homeless,
you know.
Did what they did. Saw what
they saw. That kind of thing.
I mean, if it's
an overnight thing,
I couldn't get it for tomorrow,
but the next day, sure...
That's great.
That could be the perfect
follow. I'll speak to Gus.
- Also, Scott,
we've been taking calls
from some of the national
networks and cable outlets.
They're looking
for you to go on-camera.
- Me? On television?
- I'd avoid the locals,
but if you can do the nationalstuff in a
- sure, yeah. I mean I'm
just not all that comfortable
having myself in the
center of the story like this.
- Of course not. But there is
a way of handling
this responsibly, I think.
Just remember you're an
ambassador for the paper.
Star time.
Yeah.
How 'bout that?
- Homelessness.
- Our coverage should reflect
the diensian aspect
of the homeless.
The human element.
Scott will lead it off,
spending a night on the streets
and
writing from that perspective.
- Scott? He's the
lead on your education project.
I think we need
to get him back on the...
- I don't see the...
The school project as yielding
the same kind of
impact as our attention
to homelessness can.
These murders, the phone
call to our reporter.
It really opens up the
issue, don't you think?
- Yeah, but...
- From now til the end of the year,
let's focus not only
on covering the murders,
but on the... The nature
of homelessness itself.
- The dickensian
aspect of it. Yeah.
- I've reached
a point, detective Sydnor,
where I no longer have
the time or patience left
to address myself to the
needs of the system
within which we work.
I'm tired.
- You're gonna quit?
Not yet. Not just yet.
- So what are you
talking about?
- When they took us
off Marlo this last time,
when they
said they couldn't
pay for
further investigation...
I regarded that decision
as illegitimate.
- Illegitimate?
- And so...
I'm responding in kind.
I'm going to press a case
against Marlo Stanfield without
regard to the usual rules.
I'm running an illegal wiretap
on Marlo Stanfield's cellphone.
Fuck, Lester.
- If you have a problem
with this,
I understand completely
and urge you
to get as far fucking
away from me as you can.
- You remember
this one here?
Backed away from jackin'
the boy up
outta respect for that goofy
motherfucker pryzbylewski.
Wonder what the young man might
tell me a year later, though...
Bunk.
- What the fuck is this?
- Vernon here did a search
warrant on
his dead guy's appliance store,
pulled all of that
out of the desk drawer.
- Grand jury shit?
- Transcris,
sealed indictments...
- Who's your murder?
- Eastside dealer by
the name of Joe Stewart.
Caught one in the back of
his head the other night.
- Somebody finally
touched prop Joe, huh?
Hmm-hmm.||
- you remember when narcotics
indicted Charlie burman last year?
Motherfucker ran a couple
days before the raids,
still on the wing.
- The sealed indictments
are all in there.
Every one of 'em.
- Who don't we trust
at the courthouse?
They put cheese on them fries?
They can. Chili too.
- Alright then.
- You want a drink with that?
- Strawberry lemonade.
- Alright, I'm on it.
- They're back on cellphones.
After more than a year?
That they are.
- Tell me they're
talking in code, Lester.
I wanna go to jail
for snatchin' something better
than Marlo Stanfield's
fucking lunch order.
- There's no code that
I can tell.
I've got a half dozen calls,
all routine. No drug talk,
no numbers, no times...
Nothing but what they seem.
- So he ain't doing
business with the phone then.
So take this mess down.
Let's get the fuck outta here.
I also have five calls,
thirty to forty
seconds duration,
each one picked up
on the first ring,
each one with
nothing whatsoever
said between parties.
You see? When they talk,
it's bullshit.
But there are calls where
no one says a thing.
Thirty seconds,
without conversation.
Is he...
We talked it through,
he knows the risks.
- I'm in.
If it makes the fucking case,
I'm in all the way.
So, what's up now?
They talking dirt?
no.
Lester. Fuck.
Marlo's not gonna
talk dirt on the phone,
but there's
something to this.
I just haven't
figured it out.
We could use some more manpower.
We need a couple of
surveillance teams
to get on these guys to see how
they using the phones.
- You see the
newspaper today?
Headline like that,
the bosses are gonna start
throwing money at
the homeless murders.
When they do, I'll peel
off a couple detectives,
throw them your way.
The homeless murders?
How does that case
tangle in with this?
Hard to explain.
- Remember what the d.n.c.
Folks told me two years ago?
What I needed to do to
take the statehouse?
- Build something downtown
and stick your name on it,
get the crime to go down,
and stay away from schools.
- And keep my
boyish good looks.
- One out of
four ain't bad.
Jesus.
Did we have to schedule
this the same
day as new westport?
My good news isn't even
going to make
the front of the local section.
- The ribbon-cutting
was scheduled two weeks ago.
This homeless thing
no one saw coming.
- First of all, I'm surprised
to see so much media here.
A press event
held earlier today
to announce the
revitalization of yet
another part of our city
was not so well attended.
It would appear that media
attention is always focusing
on the negatives
when it comes to Baltimore,
but you
guys aren't around
when we're making
real progress.
Nevertheless, I'm glad
to see so many of you here.
Some of you representing
not just our local mia,
but national attention
to this problem.
Thank you for caring
enough about
our most vulnerable
citizens to address
yourselves to this tragedy.
Our homeless citizens,
those who have fallen
through the
cracks of our society,
those who command the least
of our attentions and efforts,
they seemingly have little to
endear themselves to politicians.
They don't vote,
by and large.
They don't contribute
to campaigns.
They offer little
to a city's tax base,
and to the extent that our
government is made aware
of their existence, it responds
by trying to mitigate
the damage
done by their presence.
We open a food bank here,
a shelter there.
We try to move them away
from downtown,
away from our communal
areas, away from our schools,
away from our homes.
If you were to judge our
society by the manner
in which we treat
those lost on our streets,
we would have
cause to be shamed.
Well, I am, God forgive me,
a politician.
But I am also someone who
ran for public office because
I believe that there is a
different way of governing.
And I believe that
in the end we will be judged
not by the efforts
we make on behalf
of those who vote
for us,
or those who contribute
to our campaigns,
or those who provide
for our tax base.
I believe that we will be
judged by what we provide
to the weakest and
most vulnerable.
That is the test.
That is my test.
Somebody is killing
homeless men
in this city.
They are taking the lives
of fellow citizens
who do not have the means
or the strength
to properly protect themselves.
They will be stopped.
We will do everything in
our power to stop them.
You have my word on this.
Thank you, Mr. Mayor.
What got into you?
What?
- ...I want to
assure the public
that we are doing
everything possible in our power
to apprehend this subject.
Homicide detectives are
working around the clock.
District officers are in
contact with the agencies
that work with the homeless.
I cannot go into specifics
of the investigation,
but with that caveat,
I will take questions.
- Commissioner,
is there any connection
between these murders and those
in the vacant homes last year?
No conneion.
Commissioner.
Are you asking the F.B.I.
To join in the investigation?
- I think deputy commissioner
Daniels is in a position
to elaborate on that.
- We'll take whatever help
is offered.
Certainly, our detectives
will work closely with
the behavioral analysis
unit at Quantico...
- Deputy, even with all
the resources at your disposal,
isn't it extremely difficult
to catch a serial killer?
- Our ability to
secure genetic material
and the growing
d.N.A. Data bank
are assets unavailable
to us even a few years a.
And our ability to
effectively use resources
has been increased with
the aid of sophisticated
computer software.
And, of course, we have
some of the best criminal
investigators in the nation
working 24/7.
As the mayor made very clear
a moment ago,
this is now a priority
for the department.
- Has a note been found
at any of the scenes?
- I'm not at liberty
to go into any details
of the investigation
at this time.
You want me to hang?
He told you who I am, right?
Son, the thing about murder
is it never goes
off the books.
I mean, we work
on 'em for weeks,
months, years.
We keep on with
it until finally
someone decides
they've had enough,
until we get the right word
from the right person.
And you know what happens then?
When a case does go down...
All those people who kept
quiet about it,
who lied about it,
all of them who thought
it wasn't coming back on 'em,
they end up catchin' a charge.
And they get time behind that.
Time, huh?
You gonna give me time?
- If you know something
about that boy Lex getting shot,
now is your last
chance to speak to that.
You gave a statement
last year...
- Why don't you promise
to get me outta here?
That's what
y'all do, ain't it?
Lie to
dumbass niggers?
Yo, y'all need to get this police
out my face before I bank his ass.
You're a natural, kiddo.
You had them eating
out of your hand.
Shit, I was justfollowing the mayo
he wants a full-court
press, right?
- We can add a detective
or two.
And you can ask patrol toconcentrate
where vagrants congregate.
But other than that, deputy,
the cupboard is bare.
But Carcetti said...
Make no mistake.
He wants us
to solve the murders.
He just doesn't
want it to cost.
Don't look so shocked.
You're runnin' with
the big dogs now.
Isn't it enough that we're
up on the killer's cellphone?
I would think that you
could track him
on the g.p.s. Chip alone...
- He's using a burner and
we suspect he's taking
out the battery
between calls.
- And there's nothing to
stop him from changing phones,
calling the reporter from
a new number.
- So you want to tap
the reporter's phone as well.
- It stands to reason
that we should monitor
this thing from both ends.
It's what we would normally do.
Nothing about this is normal.
A Baltimore sun reporter's
phone is problematic.
We need to strike a
bance between your needs
as investigators and the
first amendment rights
of the sun and its sources.
- The first amendment does not
guarantee privacy, your honor.
Legal
precedent clearly indicates...
- Look, look, I'm
not saying that we can't, but...
But what?
Until we get the sense
that your suspect
is changing phones,
I'm not inclined to look
with favor on tapping
the Baltimore
sun's telecommunications.
- We're afraid
to piss them off.
- Never pick a fight
with anyone who buys ink
by the barrel-full.
Christ.
Very well, judge.
How many enemies do you need?
Deputy.
Where did you get all this?
- Darling, you do not
want to know.
What's up with you?
- Got all twenty-two out of
the drawer, huh?
Workin' the whole mess at once.
I'm tryi to see 'em fresh.
- Twenty-five.
My triple.
It comes back to
Marlo and his people.
For sure?
A good informant tells me so.
Says one of my vics
was talking bad
about Mr. Stanfield,
who took it personal.
Killed him,
his girl, his muscle.
Left the
little kids alive,
so I guess he ain't all bad.
People out there
so scared of this motherfucker.
I can't get close to an
eyewitness on any of it.
- Where you at with
the rest of these cases?
- You know we don't
even have lab work
on fourteen of these bodies?
A year later
and I'm still walking in written
requests into Landsman,
watching him just file
them away in his drawer.
- McNulty would've called
a news reporter on that shit.
I am not him.
- Well, what would the Bunk do?
Take no for a fucking answer?
- We had cutbacks,
you know that.
We lost three of four
trace examiners.
Lost half our clerical.
The freezer went bad,
we lost four months
of blood samples.
Did you know that?
Four months of evidence
and they still haven't
replaced my damn icebox.
- My heart pumps
purple piss for you.
Now, I got the worst mass
murder in b-more history
and you can't get the
tracework back to me
inside of a year?
C'mon, Ron...
Look...
You can't go to the press.
I mean, heads will
roll if this gets out.
It isn't anyone's fault.
In fact, it's a little
bit on you, in a way.
The fuck you say?
- After annette took
retirement, the casework
got backed up
worse than ever, right?
Well, we put in to fill
the lab assistant slot,
but with all these cutbacks,
the best they could
give us was a temp.
- A temp?
- Yeah. No medical. No pension.
A temp hire to get
us over for a while.
Look, I'll show
you mething...
She was assigned to sort
and file the individual
trace elements...
Hair, fiber mostly...
You know, from each
of the fourteen scenes.
So what's the problem?
- Well, in the
initial paperwork,
you guys wrote out all
twenty-two c.c. Numbers, right?
Right.
- But
in the supplemental requests,
you put all the incidents
under the initial c.c.
And then you wrote,
"et Al," remember?
so?
- She didn't know what
"et Al" meant.
And she sorted everything under
the single complaint number.
- You don't fuckin' mean...
- Yeah.
We have no idea which one
of your scenes
any of this shit came from.
We don't have a clue.
Actually, except for this...
shs
Been a pretty good employee.
She's
been a pretty good employee.
Surveillance teams.
- Two each on
twelveour shifts.
I need them to set
up on certain locations
common to our cases.
C'mon, Jay.
You heard the mayor.
This case is a red ball.
That it is.
You can have Greggs,
if you want.
The last
time I offered her up,
you kicked her
back to her own casework.
Other than a second
detective,
you are on your own.
- So it's all bullshit.
- I dunno.
I thought the mayor
gave a very nice speech.
I, for one, was moved.
Much like the bull to
which you just referred.
- Tell you one thing...
- What's that?
- Motherfucker whose
got the connect,
he the one that did Joe.
Oh, no doubt.
- Y'all know the
co-op took some hits.
Joe. Hungry man.
Good people, especially Joe.
Their passin' was for
real, cold blooded.
I ow what you thinkin',
so I'ma put it out there...
I'm reonsible.
A week or so back,
I made a move on Omar,
with Joe's approval.
The faggot ain't
had heart enough to come at me,
so he come at
those close to me.
Now I'm doublin'
the bounty...
Hundred large for
a whiff of that dicksuck.
Two hundred fifty
for his head.
What about the connect?
I got that covered.
And in light of that fact,
I'm a take it upon
myself to conduct this meet.
Slim, I want you take over
hungry man's slice of the cake.
Meanin' no disrespect,
but I ain't cut
out to be no c.E.o.
Cheese, then.
- No problem, man.
Got you covered.
Until we settle up with Omar,
I think it's
best we suspend these meets.
In fact, I ain't really
one for meets no how.
Anybody got a
problem from here on out,
bring it to me,
or sit on that shit.
Those of you on the westside
who need to re-up,
holla' at my man monk.
He gonna handle
supply over there.
On the eastside, cheese.
One more thing.
Price of the brick going up.
Thirty more.
Alright.
Enough of this shit.
What?
- Next year for the schools.
From now until december,
we're all about the
plight of the homeless.
The great whiting has spoken.
I appealed to klebanow
half hour ago but he gave me
the thumbs down.
I'm sorry.
- Check it out, people.
Our metro desk
has some national profile.
- Uh, we're being
careful to cooperate
with the investigators
in every way.
My newspaper has no desire
to get between
the police and the suspect.
- But still, wouldn't you
agree it's an incredible
moment for any journalist
to come face to face
with that type of pure
evil like the son of Sam.
That makes you the
Jimmy breslin of Baltimore.
- Well, no, I wouldn't
say that. I mean...
- But knowing you have been
in contact with a killer,
are you at all concerned
about continuing to report
from the street?
- No, not at all.
I mean, this is what we do.
As a reporter,
you expect to be
in harm's way
at some points.
It's what we do.
- Agreed.
But very rarely does a
reporter end up being
in the middle of a story--
An ongoing story--
About a murderer who
is still at large
and posing a severe and
deadly risk to the...
- You shoulda heard
Phelan this morning.
Too scared to tap
the newspaper phones
they might shit
on him for it.
Fuckin' hack judge.
- What would you want with
more wires?
We got all we need.
I don't want another wire.
It's
the principle of the thing...
It just pissed me off
listening to him.
- Oh yeah,
no surveillance cars.
They won't go beyond
me and Greggs.
You and Sydnor will
have to work
it as best
you can for right now.
Assholes.
They need another body,
don't they?
- I'll call our
man in the southern.
- I can take it from here.
Y'all can bounce.
Alright, boss.
What up, Rick?
Just like ol'
times for me and you, huh?
- Whatever you
want it's yours, alright?
- Tonight, I'm just
gonna take yo' jump...
And leave you with
a little something.
What's that?
My word in your ear.
I'm callin'
Marlo a straight bitch.
I'm sayin' it don't take much
to shoot down a blind man.
And as for him
steppin' to me,
you tell that dude
he ain't got the heart.
Alright.
- You tell that man I'm
in the street, waiting.
Anjust like a little bitch,
he ain't nowhere to be found.
- I'll tell him.
I will.
- Pick up your keys
and go on inside, yo.
You kill Joe?
Hungry?
Didn't think so.
What now?
- There's more than
one way to skin a case.
- Already ran
them for priors, right?
Priors, yeah.
But I'm gonna run every name
you guys developed through
the entire database.
Not just for priors,
but for anything at all
in the miles system.
Court appearances,
parole, probation,
gun permits,
d.o.c., open bails.
- You're playing longshots,
huh?
- Darlin', I'm playin'
the hand I've been dealt.
An h-file?
Who caught the case?
- Worden. Other shift.
- Stepfather.
Beaten to death.
They interviewed the mother,
but no one else
in the household.
- Doesn't exactly fit
with the others, does it?
I mean, a straight
up ass-whoopin'
in an alley doesn't seem
like Marlo staield.
No it doesn't.
- But you're
gonna work it anyway.
- In the pentecostal church
where I was given religion,
it would have been
said that the spirit
was on you yesterday.
- It got good to me.
- Let praises be.
- I don't know.
It just pissed me off
that on top of everything
else I gotta deal with,
some nutjob starts
killing homeless guys.
I mean, fuck already,
how many shitbowls are there?
- He's right though.
You were great.
That passion
was just the thing.
You think, uh...
- We step out on this issue,
it could provide
some national presence...
- Didn't the governor
scrap the emergency medical
and housing program last year?
What was it, temha?
- He did, replaced it
with t-dap, which cuts funding
to anyone who doesn't
qualify for federal support.
It's worse than that,
actually: he froze eligibility
by disallowing new applications,
which put all kinda folks
out on the street.
- So we slam the republican
for sticking it to the poor.
It plays.
Nationally, you're ting up
the cause of the forgotten...
And no one is ever in favor
of homelessness...
- Statewide, you're going
up against the fella who tore
up the safety net.
Homelessness.
I'll be damned.
- Base to twenty-three-oh-six.
- Go ahead, Lester.
- You see anybody using
a cellphone?
Wait one.
Negative.
Hold on.
Somebody's here.
Lester...
Can't get used to how empty
this place feels nowadays.
- True, but you'd be
surprised what you can get done
when no one's looking
over your shoulder.
- You'll need to serve
these. Running out of time.
- I'll get right on it.
- There's a couple of loose ends
I think we should
cover as well.
- Now?
- If not now, when?
The trial date is
coming up on us fast.
- Right.
But it's uh...
- Is it something I said?
- No...
It's, Sydnor is bringing
in a C.I. And if you're here...
Oh, shit.
I'm sorry. Um...
I'll leave you
my list, okay?
- No problem.
We'll get right on it.
I'm sorry, Lester,
if I was intruding.
You couldn't know.
So why you here?
If this about Michael
an' what he into,
y'all should know he don't
live here no more.
- Actually, I'm following
up on your man's case.
You spoke to detective
worden when it happened.
Hmm?
He was your boyfriend,
right?
When he weren't in jail...
Father to my youngest.
But you know how he died.
Beaten bad.
Crime of passion, as we say.
Didn't seem like
he was home long enough
to get somebody
that riled at him.
Unless, of course,
it was over you.
- What, you sayin'
I know somethin' about that?
- Lady, let's put our cards
on the table.
I been in this game
longer than a little bit,
and there's one
thing I know from jump.
You get a murder like this,
there's bound to be a woman
at the center of it.
I don't know nothin'.
- You know my gut
tells me that you do.
And I'll tell you what...
We're gonna
take a ride downtown,
let you talk
to the grand jury.
You're n
straight with them,
they'll slap you with
a material witness warrant.
And you sit
over at woman's
detention for
a couple of weeks.
It's amazing what it does
for the grieving process.
Get your things.
- I ain't goin' no damn where.
It's me or the wagon.
- Detective, I swear,
I ain't in this.
It ain't me you wanna talk to.
It's the boy,
he know.
He runnin' with
them who did it.
- You just tryin' to put me
off the scent here.
No, you gotta believe me.
He told me devar
wasn't comin' home,
'fore we even
knowed he was dead.
- U said he's runnin'
with them?
Runnin' with who?
- Chris, Snoop,
all them gangsters.
Who else doin'
all the killin' around here?
Let me see your camera.
- Add a minute-six
to your times.
Got it.
Here it is. Look at this.
Single ring.
Connection. Silence.
What do you have?
- I took these three.
They're just hangin' around.
What time did monk leave?
One twenty-four.
Two minutes later.
- It's not what Marlo's
sayin', it's what he's sendin'.
Look at monk.
- Yeah.
Text message.
- Text?
Need I remind you, detective,
these young men are products
of Baltimore city schools.
Besides, look how far away
he's holding his phone.
Too far away to
be reading a text.
Naw, son. Pictures.
Pictures...
- What the fuck
you lookin' at?
- You know what
they do, right? They tease you.
They let you get close and
just when you're about to
pull the case, they rip the
fuckin' rug out from under you.
I'm not lying.
We got a fuckin' serial
killer on the loose.
You didn't know that?
It's in the goddamn paper.
What support do I get?
One fuckin' detective.
They wanna play their
simple-ass games, fine.
But I gotta do what I gotta do.
'scuse me.
McNulty.
Yeah, Oscar.
Beautiful.
Absolutely. Where?
On my way.
- Man, you can't let it get
to you like this.
Why don't we go
buy up a bunch of
toys and take
'em to your kids?
You ain't hearin' me.
How can I go near my people
with Omar on us?
- How he gonna find
out about them?
- How we find out
about the blind man?
Omar, yo, Omar!
Hey yo, Omar!
Get.
Omar!
It's Omar!
You too, shorty.
- Omar!
It's Omar!
Money a little late today.
That buckshot in your leg
should help you some you
explain' yourself to Marlo.
As for them other two
they gonna wish
that I'd peppered them a bit.
Now you make sure you tell
old Marlo I burned the money.
'cause it ain't
about that paper.
It's about me hurtin' his
people, messin' with his world.
Tell that boy he ain't man
enough to come down
to the street with Omar.
You tell him that!
- My sergeant and two side
partners got here before me.
Then the
shift commander showed.
Now the duty
officer is on his way.
For a d.o.a.?
- Yeah, well, you and Lester
started some shit here, son.
Now a d.o.a. Call
brings everyone in a heartbeat.
God bless.
Pictures?
Photographs on cellphones.
Now that means new p.c.
To capture the photos,
and new equipment
that could do it.
- How do I write that into my
bullshit homeless killer's m.o.?
When we started this,
you said all we
needed were some bugs,
a camera or two,
and in a couple of weeks,
we'd have them.
That's what you said.
So I cranked up my
bullshit to pay for that,
but no, then you
needed a wiretap.
So I went along with that,
I got you the wiretap.
Then you ask for
surveillance teams,
but before I can get to
that, you came to me with this.
I mean, what the fuck?
I gotta tell you, Lester,
I don't
want to hurt your feelings,
but I can see why Daniels
cringed every time you opened
your fucking mouth.
You're a supervisor's nightmare.
I'm just following the thread.
- Okay, say we get you
the intercept on your pictures,
will that give us Marlo?
- It'll be coded,
probably,
but I'm sure
we can break it.
That'll tell us how they
do business,
and usually, that's
enough. Or not.
But the truth is, I'm running
Sydnor ragged just staying
on a couple of mopes and
monitoring calls.
Now, when
we're up on their code,
we're going
to need more manpower
to run down
a stash or a re-up.
We can't do it all.
- I can't juke
this thing any more than I have.
Last night, half the police
department turned up
at Oscar's crime scene
before I could get there.
We can't make another murder.
Thanks for the milk.
What's a donut without milk?
- So you were
talking about
your second tour...
The bad one, yeah.
Second tour fucked me up good.
But they don't wanna hear it.
- Who doesn't?
- Mostly, it's command and
the Senior E.m.s.
Put it down that marines
don't get p.t.s.d.
But they do.
Can you tell me what happened?
Terry, can you talk about it?
- We had a month
left on the tour,
working an s-and-a mission
outside fallujah.
I was assistant team leader.
Our m-niner, niner, eights were
retritted with up-armor kits.
M-niner-niner-eight?
A humvee, sorry.
They're big on nomenclature.
Anyway we finished our
sweep, headed back in, right?
It was all good.
Then, bam...
Our lead vehicle was hit
with an elevated I.E.d.
The blast
tore the m-fifty gunner in half.
Flipped the humvee
like a matchbox car.
Driver lost both his hands.
Blood shooting out
all over. He's fuckin' laughin',
saying over and over,
"look, ma, no hands."
It's the laughing
I can't shake.
Weird.
'cause he's okay, you know?
I mean, he's better than me.
Got himself a couple
of prosthetic mitts,
eighty thousand apiece.
Wow.
What happened next?
- Nothing really.
We pushed out,
secured the perimeter.
Corpsman did what he could,
an' we waited for the cas-evac.
- Look, I'm not looking
to shit on another guy's copy,
I just wanted to
let you know this was out there.
I'm at a community meeting
in bel air-edison to hear about
school zoning and this woman
talked my ear off about this.
She said the kids
never saw a dime.
Hmm.
- I mean, I'm hoping
this is all bullshit.
- Hey, Scott.
How's it coming?
- Prettyood.
You seen the art?
- Yeah, yeah.
Good stuff, good stuff.
Listen, we got a complaint
about a story you wrote
a couple weeks ago.
The one about the woman
who died from an
allergic reaction to seafood,
you remember?
- What about it?
- Neighborhood ladknows
the dead woman's sister says
our story made a lot of
money for those kids,
a scholarship
fund we wrote up.
- Yeah?
So...
- Well, she says the
sister has a history of fraud,
convictions on it.
She says all the money went
to atlantic city casinos
and kids never saw a dime.
- Christ, who the fuck...
- I know, I know.
It's probably some old biddy
talkin' about stuff
she don't know,
but maybe you should go
back and check with the family,
see if we don't get took
on this, huh?
- No, no. Not now.
After you file.
Just make a couple calls, huh?
This is kidnapping.
- Actually, I'm not sure.
I asked him if he wanted
and talk and
he walked to my car.
You give him the hundred?
Stuffed it in his jacket.
He's fine, Lester.
He's great.
- Think he'll find his way
back home?
Eventually.
By then, we'll be done with
Marlo, we'll have shut
this thing down.
And as far as what happened
to this guy...
They'll write
it off as some fraternity prank.
- Does he know we're cops?
- No.
- And even if he figures it out,
who's gonna believe him?
He's nuts.
- How do you know he's nuts?
- First of all,
just look at him.
He's fucking bouncing
off the walls.
Second of all...
I got his scrip.
I called the university E.r.
It's an anti-psychotic.
So...
I took his I.D., I'll
scratch his
name off the scrip
and leave him with this...
I got that one from E first
homeless death Oscar gave us.
The one that was too rigored.
Donald somebody or other.
It had him in a cleveland,
ohio shelter.
- McNulty, you are deserving
of serious psychological study.
- You need p.c.
To intercept cellphone photos.
Well here it is, right here.
We send photos of this guy
all ribboned up
from a dry cellphone
to that goofy reporter,
along with a message
bitching about his stories.
"I ain't no pervert,"
or whatever.
Now, the killer says,
you ain't gonna find
no more bodies.
Only photos of the victims...
Before they disappear.
Look at this poor sucker.
I don't believe we're
gonna do this.
- He disappears,
the city goes batshit.
You get your photo intercepts,
d by the time we need to
run down one of Marlo's re-ups,
you got all the
manpower you need.
- And Marlo falls.
- Falls hard.
- Don't fucking tell me
you mislabeled ts too.
I want comparisons between
known suspects
and the d.N.A. From this scene.
By the looks of it,
we got a whole
lot of d.N.A. Outta this mess.
Now, motherfucker. Right now.
- Top of my list.
As soon as we work through
all the trace from the
homeless killings.
That's the priority, Bunk.
- The homeless killings.
- Everything is backed up
behind that, sorry.
Your boy McNulty has
everyone's attention right now.
So it's Larry, huh?
Okay, Larry.
You're witgood people here.
It's all gonna be great.
You're gonna like this place.
It's warm, they got nice beds.
And best of all, I gave you
cash money just for
walking in the door.
Come on, Larry.
It's goin' to be fine.
I promise.
- You feel up for trying
Clay yourself?
I mean, it's been
a while since
you tried
a criminal case personally.
It sends a statement, I think.
We should start with our
witness list.
See if we can pare that down
any, out of respect for
the distracted nature
of a Baltimore jury.
- First, there's something
else I need to bring up.
- Old grand jury stuff?
- Sealed indictments.
Sealed transcripts.
Dozens of them.
Pulled from the desk
of a shot-to-death drug
dealer in east Baltimore.
The deputy ops
brought me those.
We have a leak.
- And he showed up,
outside where I work.
He was confused. Lost
I think. So I brought him here.
Donald, where you fr?
Tell the lady, Donald.
Baltimore.
- But he told me he came
from cleveland.
- Donald,
do you have identification?
This does say cleveland.
Donald, why don't
we get you something to eat?
It's okay. Come on.
We're good to go?
It's great, Gus.
It sings.
- Hey, scottie boy.
- Hey.
- Hey. Great piece.
I mean this one really feels
like the real deal.
- It's great work.
Thanks.
- What I like most about it
is that you didn't overwrite it.
No extra color.
No puffy adjectives.
Just
tight, declarative sentences.
And you really let this
ex-marine just tell his story.
- Thanks, Gus.
- Hey, Mr. Slot man,
read it and weep.
And I mean that literally.
Oh, hey, Scott.
Did you get
a chance to, uh,
drop a
couple calls on that complaint?
Yeah, it's bullshit.
I talked to people
in the neighborhood.
Sister's good people, but
there's another woman,
up there, unrelated,
keeps getting arrested
for kiting checks
and stuff, and she...
She uses the sister's name
every time she gets locked up.
She's done it like
three or four times now.
- No shit.
- Yeah, it's crazy.
But sister's clean.
Everyone says so.
Okay.
- Is there anything else
I can do for him?
- No, we've got it.
But thanks for bringing him in.
Most people, they just
ignore them.
I just want to get all of
your paperwork taken care of...