2316.
Yeah, lester.
- Where are you at?
- On monk in east baltimore.
- Who's on marlo?
- No one right now.
- Marlo's been the
hardest to follow.
Too paranoid.
Too much counter-surveillance.
Well, peel off monk
and head out broening highway
to the marine terminals.
Map forty-four,
grid g-as-in-george-ten.
- Forty-four.
- Affirmative.
This is a fresh one.
- If they're going all
the way out there,
then it might just be...
- Damn right.
On it.
Twenty-three-oh-six to
all units on this detail.
New twenty is map forty-four,
grid g-george-ten.
That's forty-four g-george-ten.
Flood that grid and look
for suspect vehicles.
- Twenty-three-twelve.
Ten-four.
Take me a while.
I'm up northeast. You want
me to stay on cheese?
- Negative. New twenty
is a priority.
Think we're on the main stem.
- Yeah?
- Mcnulty? It's on.
- Oh, hell yeah.
Alright...
[telephone
"Deserve got nuthin' to do with it."
- Snoop.
okay, whatchya got?
- Well, we rolled around until
bobby spotted chris partlow
pulled up on a lot two
blocks from here.
So we sat on him until
marlo posted.
They talked for a minute,
then marlo bounced.
And chris goes to the
warehouse gate alone
and a cola white boys
open up.
He's inside now?
- Entrance is around front
from what I can tell,
it's the only working gate.
Everything else is rusted up.
- Who's watching the front?
- Two units.
They're out on foot,
a block away,
with a clear view of what
comes in or out.
- So what do we do
if chris rolls out?
- Let him go.
Partlow is muscle.
He's here to make sure
it looks right.
And if it does, monk or
someone else'll come on down.
Cheese, too, maybe.
So this is a re-up.
Fuck a re-up, son.
This, here, in the
middle of nowhere...
Miles from anywhere
these mopes meet...
This is re-supply.
Other than chris, anybody
else that goes in there...
If it's a stanfield lieutenant
he's coming out dirty.
You follow them back to town.
If he doesn't know you're
on 'em, see where
he takes you.
If he catches a scent, fuck it.
Pull 'em over, jack
'em up and get the dope.
And leander, you want to
snatch the man's cell
before he has a chance to erase
anything that might be on it.
The case is in t phones...
Though we're
gonna need a title three
to take
a look at them.
Where are you going?
Time to 'fess up.
We straight?
I said we straight, right?
Them guns was mine.
- Which guns specifically,
mr. Hill?
- Whatever guns them cops took
out the truck last year.
They mine.
Even though I ain't
touched that iron.
Ain't you got
to do the bit.
- With your limited priors, mr.
Hill, you're exposed to two,
maybe three years, tops.
You'll be well compensated
for the time, I'm sure.
No good to us no how.
You on three legs.
- Familiarize yourself
with the make and model
of the weapons you
left in the truck, Mr. Hill.
The details matter.
- I get shot up
an' then this shit.
Y'all ask a lot, dontcha?
- You can't hack, go down
walmart or someshit.
And see if they take care you
while you laid up for a while.
C'mon, nigga.
- Jeez. In the department,
you take one in the line
they give you light duty
for as long as you need,
then you get to name
your next assignment.
Marlo runs a tighter ship.
Open it.
Six icebox, twenty each.
You count, we wait.
You no count,
we go to lunch early.
- Twenty-three fourteen
to twenty-three-oh-six.
Suspect number three is in.
You sure it was him?
- Been following the
damn truck for a week.
Shouldnow by now.
Copy that.
- Truck. Ticks
have six legs or eight?
- Must have
been a readjustment.
- London was a sweet posting.
I can't lie.
My only regret is I didn't
get the full three-year tour.
Thanks.
- It's no reflection
on you, man.
- Shit, gus, they even sold
the building in kensington.
I mean we bought that sucker
for nothing fifty years ago,
and now chicago sells it off
for a couple million pounds.
- Capitalization they
call it.
- These newspaper-chain
guys
just don't give a fuck,
do they?
- Any idea where they're
gonna drop you now that
you're back in charm city?
No, I got no idea yet.
Klebanow wants to
have lunch, so I guess it'll
come at me, soon enough.
Up for something now?
Depends.
- I gotta problem.
I need someone...
A veteran reporter, quiet,
subtle, discreet.
Good with details,
careful to cover his tracks...
- I don't care
how far we go back, gus,
no way I'm gonna
kill your wife for you.
- You know scott templeton?
City g.a.
- The guy talking to the
homeless killer?
Not really.
He got hired
after I went to london.
- It's better
you don't know him.
No opinions,
one way or the other.
No, no,
i'm not saying anything.
I'm not. I just need
fresh eyes on the fella.
Just a careful look.
- One of whiting's pets,
isn't he?
I said discreet, huh?
I hope you're wrong.
'course you do.
It sticks. Dag.
- Course it sticks.
It's barb wire.
Sticking's what
it's s'posed to do.
Come on.
I ain't got all day.
Hurry up now.
Grab the aluminum
strips there first off.
- How am I supposed
to get back over?
Climb the damn fence.
Do a better job of
it second time, I expect.
Grab them steel pipes quick,
before we get spotted.
Robert ruby.
- Welcome home.
- Thanks.
I need you to give me
a global printout
on everything under scott
templeton's byline.
All of it, every edition.
Hey, I'm a fan.
Twenty-three-fourteen.
Monk is westbound
onto o'donnell.
Cheese wagstaff
is on the way in.
Also, there's
a truck leaving.
The one we saw
back on the loading dock.
That'd be empty.
They've offloaded,
it's all in the warehouse now.
Bobby and me
will stay on monk.
Karen'll follow cheese out,
you guys stay
on the gate.
Forgetting for a moment
our little problem
of the serial killer,
we came in promising
a double-digit drop
in violent crime.
Right up on the
gubernatorial primary,
and we're looking
at another record high.
- Michael, this department
has been crippled
by the budget cuts.
For a year now,
we haven't had
the manpower or the tools.
You have them now.
- Now. But this
thing is a ship,
a super-tanker.
We can't just
turn it around...
Like that.
More foot patrols.
More cars on the street.
Get a handle on it, dammit.
See that's
what doesn't work.
More cops where
people can see them.
More cops on the pavement,
more cops riding past,
more cops showing the flag
so that you guys can say
you're being tough on crime.
Respectfully, sir,
what works
is committing to building
a real deterrent.
We take the time to retool,
to teach our people
not to chase stats,
but to do actual
police work.
- Who pulled your string,
deputy?
I was told by our mayor
at the outset that there
would be no more band-aids,
no more stat games...
- And then we got hit
with the school budget.
And we lost some of the time
we needed to address
the systemic things
you're talking about.
Understood. We will
work back on those,
and we will
support that kinof reform,
if not from city hall
then from annapolis,
if need be.
But now, deputy, right now,
my boss needs the crime
to go down.
Not three years from now.
Not even a year from now.
He needs a ten-percent drop
in the next quarter...
Or no one
is gonna be in a position
to reform anything.
Be creative, gentlemen.
Deputy.
A detective's outside
for you,
says it's urgent.
- Sydnor and I developed
a source
and ran fressurveillances
on marlo stanfield.
And we believe we're
about to catch
his people very dirty.
What?
- We wrapped on that
clay davis
thing and instead of
shutting major crimes down,
we took a couple weeks and
got back up on marlo.
With the right warrants,
he's about to fall.
How the fuck...
- There's no time, cedric.
In an hour or so,
i'm gonna need...
Yeah?
- Lester...
- What's up?
- We pulled up monk.
Dirty as a motherfucker.
Eight keys of the raw.
No, he jersey-rolled a stop and
when we tried to pull him over,
he went rabbit on us.
We ran him down on lafayette,
by the overpass.
You got the phone, right?
Yeah, man. I got it.
Good work.
It's down.
I need teams to arrest
marlo stanfield,
chris partlow,
and cheese wagstaff.
I also need someone
from our s.a.o.
To get on the horn to baltimore
county for an s-and-s
warrant on a middle
river warehouse.
And, oh yeah...
Bunk meland
has a warrant on partlow
for a separate homicide.
He held that back so we could
do this business here.
- Anything else you've neglected
to tell me, detective freamon?
No sir.
I think you're caught up.
- Hello?
- Ronnie, dear.
Hey...
- Are you sitting down?
- Why?
- He was trying to erase
shit when we tackled him.
Secure this location
until we have written
search-and-seizure.
Shit's on t.v, yo.
- With a street value
of almost sixteen
million dollars in heroin,
and charges against high-level
traffickers who were
going to put this poison on
the streets of this city...
- Do this mean I still gotta
take that charge for y'all?
...and perseverance by our
police department.
And while I am told that this
investigation is continuing,
it is my understanding that
there is at least one murder
warrant associated with this
drug organization,
which is believed to have
been responsible for
many of those bodies found
in vacant rowhouses
more than a year ago.
We did not give up on that
investigation
just as we do not give up
trying every day to
address ourselves to the
task of making this city safe
and vibrant again.
And let me just say to all
others responsible
for the drug trade's assault
on the welfare of this city,
a day like this is
coming for you.
Oh, you are so butch.
- I have seen what drugs have
done to baltimore.
Drug dealers do not just
destroy individuals.
They destroy families.
- Don't forget about the
communities.
- They destroy entire
Today the mayor of baltimore,
our state's attorney,
our police department, and
our communities are saying:
we... Have had... Enough.
Thank you.
Deputy.
Alma gutierrez, "sun" papers.
Care to comment?
- It's a good day
for the good guys.
- Could you be a bit
more substantive?
Last time the "sun"
had me in its pages,
you had me doing
things I didn't do.
Regarding?
- Something about me stabbing
someone in the back.
Look it up.
"a source of information
"identified the transmission
of photographs
via cellphone."
Fuck do that mean?
"source of information."
They sayin' somebody talkin'?
Who the fuck even know?
I wanna talk to the lawyer.
And you caught a murder,
too.
says the same shit
on yours, huh?
"from information received,
investigation led to d.n.a.
Analysis of the victim."
They got you on d.n.a.?
My hair, I expect.
- "From information received."
More of that snitchin' shit.
- I'm sayin',
where the information come from?
Onliest people knew 'bout
the deed is us right here.
Snoop knew.
Shit.
- What about your
youngun michael?
Maybe it was him ran his mouth.
He got picked up, right?
I did that thing for him.
Why would he talk about it an'
put hisself in?
- He been tested
on the streets.
Maybe he act different
in the rooms downtown.
- Boy been throwin' up all
kinda backtalk 'bout shit.
Buck' wild about this 'n that.
Like what?
- Cryin' about how june bug
and his people got lit up.
Cryin' about how omar in the
street runnin' his mouth,
callin' for you to step to...
Omar say what?
Nuthin'.
Omar tried callin'
you out by name.
But, shit, it wadn't nothin'...
What he say about me?
- Nuthin', man.
Just talkin' shit.
He use my name?
In the street?
Talk, motherfucker.
He just, ya know...
Say that you need to
step to and that...
I dunno, he just runnin'
his mouth some.
He call me a punk?
It was bullshit, man.
You ain't need
that on your mind.
- What the fuck you
know about
what I need on my mind,
motherfucker.
My name was on the street.
When we bounce from
this shit here,
y'all gonna go down
to them corners,
let them people know.
Word did not
get back to me.
Let 'em know marlo
step to any motherfucker.
Omar, barksdale...
Whoever.
My name is my name.
Don't see the boy snitchin'.
Neither do i.
But you ready to bet
your future on that?
- Ya see that, mcnulty?
Ya see it?
One detective,
working the file,
running a few things
down and bang...
He's got an arrest.
Shit, now that chris partlow's
locked up
we might have some
witnesses coming forward
on those cases in
the vacants.
Clear 'em all on paper.
- We got the one
is all, boss.
- One today, more tomorrow.
And from what?
- From the bunk
just workin' a file.
Business as usual.
But you...
With your
overtime and your cars
and your
surveillance detail
and your bullshit,
where the fuck are
you on your redball?
Nowhere.
Killer stopped calling.
Stopped killing, too.
I admit it.
I'm nowhere.
- From everything
we've given you,
fire should be
shooting out your ass,
but no, there you sit
like a genital wart.
C'mon, mcnulty.
Show me something.
- So what are you
gonna do now?
Keep half a district worth
of manpower on the street,
chasing bullshit?
It'll wind down.
No more killing,
no more disappearances,
no more calls.
Marlo is in cuffs.
Fuck marlo.
Fuck you.
- What's going on in
klebanow's office?
Planning meeting.
Pulitzer submissions.
This early?
- The important thing is
that we build on this
through the end of the year,
with no falloff of coverage.
Exactly.
And scott,
we need to start looking
for the points where the
response to the problem
can be criticized.
The "gotcha." I know.
- At this point,
we can't tell what category
we'll enter with this,
but in public service
especially,
greater weight is given
to stories
that result in
changes to policy,
or new legislation.
- So covering the reactions
to our stories
is as important as
the stories themselves.
- Between now and new year's,
we want to a hammer
at whatever changes
or discussions
or actions result from your
coverage of the homeless.
- And graphics matter.
Our presentation must be
clean and professional when it
goes to the committee.
- You guys really think this
has a shot at a pulitzer?
I do and it does.
Being on the pulitzer board
for a coup of terms,
I've seen the process up close.
There's a way of
doing these things.
Time honored.
Knowing how is why they
pay me the big bucks.
- Alright. What do we
want to say exactly?
With our coverage.
What do we want to say
about homelessness?
I mean, it's bad.
It's very bad, granted.
Buisn't it actually
symptomatic of a much
greater dynamic...
- We want to rediscover
a world
that for too long
has been ignored.
Examine the tragedy
underlying these murders,
the neglect...
The dickensian aspect.
Exactly.
Alma, dearest.
This quote from daniels:
"it's a good day for
the good guys."
He couldn't come up with
anything better than that?
He wouldn't play.
Says we took his name in vain
last time we used it.
When was that?
- When we had him back-stabbing
burrell at city hall, remember?
Do you want me to call
daniels at home?
Try him again?
We're past deadline, gus.
I'll cut the quote.
Alright.
Drink with me, jimmy.
This is what you wanted, man.
- Then why do I feel
like shit?
Postpartum depression, son.
It's the journey,
not the destination...
We got marlo stanfield.
What about the serial killer?
Marlo is he.
Daniels wanted me up there
at that press conference.
Up there with all the rest of
those preening motherfuckers,
congratulating themselves
on a job well done.
Part of the problem,
all of them.
Yet when the bracelets come out
and the dope is on the table...
- We've still got
the surveillance teams.
The districts still have guys
watching the homeless,
undercovers dressed
as homeless...
That shit'll end.
It always does.
Well...
If you ain't gonna
celebrate with me,
you're gonna at least
chauffeur my drunken ass home.
Shardene better be awake, too.
'cause I do believe
lester freamon's
in the mood for love...
- Yo, I'm tellin' you,
it was kenard.
To catch up with him.
Bullshit.
Omar got kilt by them
pimlico boys.
They ran up on him with three
a.k.s an' jus' blazed away.
What up, soldier?
- I don't know.
You tell me.
I mean, everybody locked up,
right?
I mean, damn...
Yeah. 'cause-a that shit,
i'm 'a need you for some
serious business tomorrow, man.
- Anyone I know?
- Big walter.
Big-nose big walter?
- Nah, skinny big walter,
the one be right there
in front of the
cut-rate on calhoun
and riggs all the time.
He witnessin'?
- Marlo say he need
to get got.
So it is, what it is.
You got a problem with that?
We straight.
No need to bring your iron.
I got a clean nine for you
with shaved numbers.
I'll pick you up tomorrow night.
You a-ight?
Yeah, yeah.
A-ight.
- And in the last five years,
the united states has
given fifteen billion dollars
to fight h.i.v. And aids
around the world.
But only part of it goes
to africa,
where there's a huge epidemic
of h.i.v. And aids.
I mean, ten percent of the
population of the world
lives in sub-saharan africa,
but seventy percent of
the new aids cases are there.
In ken,
one in seven people
have h.i.v. And aids,
and in zimbabwe,
one in four people have it,
according to the article in
the "new york human rights
law review."
Plus, the u.s. Surgeon
general has said that
there are twenty-two million
people with h.i.v. And aids
in those african countries.
In the next ten years,
more people will die from aids
in these countries than all the
wars in the twentieth century,
including world war two,
the deadliest war...
How's it feelin', bunny?
- I tell ya,
if I had that boy's
gift for talk,
i'd a really caused a stir.
Look at him go...
Don't sell yourself short.
He's got your way of makin'
an argument.
Lucky for him, though,
he looks like his stepmama.
- And aids in africa
said u.s. Money
can make a huge difference
in africa where even very small
amounts can go a long way.
There seems to be an agreement
that the money should be spent
in two ways: medical treatment
and for education and
prevention.
However, there is not an
agreement on how much money
will be needed and what
programs...
When do we bounce?
I'm working on bail reviews.
Cheese maybe...
On a high surety bond,
if he wants to put up
his mama's house.
Monk, the same.
But with the murder warrant,
there is no bail for chris,
and most likely,
there's no bail for you,
as the charging papers portray
you at the top
of the conspiracy.
- How can they say that when I
ain't go near no drugs at all?
- The full affidavit says
they developed
a source of information...
Bullshit.
- A source of information
who told them that
you communicated with
each other
using photographic transmissions
on cellphones.
Coded transmissions.
- Ain't nobody know
about the code 'cept me,
chris, monk an' cheese...
An' we all locked
up behind this.
No one else even have a phone.
Not even snoop.
No one 'cept the supply.
You trust the supplier?
Well, someone knew
and someone told.
And now they've got
your cellphones,
and they're going for
a title three.
- So they was on our
cell phones then...
- No, the affidavit says
the source told them
the date of your re-supply,
that they followed monk
and others to the warehouse,
followed him out,
and found the drugs.
They're going to get
their title three
and they're saying that by
examining monk's phone,
your phone, and the others,
they're going to prove
the conspiracy.
You see?
They weren't on a wiretap,
but now they're using
the phones and photographs
to link you all together.
So who knew that there
was a re-supply?
Who knew what you all were
up to yesterday?
Snoop.
D you trust her.
Who else?
- Known sex offenders,
southern district.
Three possibles.
- You want us to sit
on them?
A day or two. Yeah.
If nothing shows,
then we'll move on...
Okay.
Dead and homeless.
Jack street in brooklyn.
Christeson's down there.
Strangle?
- Sounds like a beating,
actually.
- Red-ribbon tied
around the wrist?
- Actually, it was more of
a burnt sienna and it
was lashed around his dick.
Fuck do I know?
Get down there.
- Jay, this doesn't
sound like...
Waste of your time, huh?
- That what you have seen
here today is indicative
of the progress that city
schools are making under
this current administration.
Now I know the governor has
had some harsh things to
say about baltimore schools,
but I find that to be cynical
and disappointing.
The fifteen-point jump in
third-grade test scores
is a trend that
can't be ignored.
- But we've seen third grade
scores rise before, Mr. Mayor.
And it doesn't seem as if any
gains in that grade can be
sustained into fifth and
seventh-grade scores.
- Kathy, you know,
we are committed to
substantive change in baltimore.
The kids that you saw today in
this citywide debate...
They are achieving at
a high school level and
disproving any negative
stereotypes about the city
school system.
Could you excuse me for
a moment, please?
Major colvin.
Just colvin.
- You know,
I always wanted to say
how sorry I am
how things turned out.
There wasn't anything that
I could have done
with your experiment
in the western district.
There wasn't anything
that anyone could have
done with that.
- Yeah, well, I guess,
mr. Mayor, um...
There's nothing to be done.
- Mr. C, you know
the mayor, too? Dag.
- I can't even believe
i'm talking to you, gus.
After that shit you pulled.
See that's how you all do.
Slam somebody an' then
come back the next day
like it never happened.
It's jus' bidness, nerese.
It was your turn to read
about yourself.
Now, if carcetti's governor
and you become mayor...
Is bond gonna run against ya?
Or is he done?
What do you think?
- After the clay
davis farce...
He smells like he's done to me.
There's rumor that keiffer
want the job, too.
- I'll deal with that
as it comes.
- What about this
daniels fella?
You think he's ready
to run the copshop?
It's kinda ugly the way
he kept puttin' a knife
to burrell like that.
I mean...
- You know I read that and
wondered where the hell
you people got it from.
What do you mean?
- I was behind burrell
until the moment I wasn't.
And if he had someone
backstabbing him
at city hall...
I'd've heard about it.
Daniels wasn't even
on my radar.
- Daniels didn't
undercut burrell?
- Shit, at the end,
after his name was floated,
daniels went around saying
he didn't want the job.
Talk about it.
- Well, he's been beat
pretty good,
but I've got neck bruising too,
so it could be
an attempted strangle.
- No ribbon?
- Nope.
- Bite marks?
- Not that I can see.
This fuckin' guy stinks.
He probably evacuated.
- What?
He left and he came back?
No, he shit himself.
It's not my guy.
Sorry, rook.
He's all yours.
- And does the governor
think that's a problem,
that it's something that
needs to be addressed?
Hold on a sec...
- You got the military records
back from the marine corps?
- Three weeks at least,
they said.
Sorry about that.
- Hey steven,
I gotta little problem.
- Well, it's common
in men your age.
- I need to get into
walter reed.
I gotta talk to
a vet down there.
The fella that was with
our homeless vet
when he saw that firefight.
The one templeton was
writing about.
- Why do we want to
go back on that?
- I just want to talk
to a guy.
Homeless fella gave me the name
said he's in-patient down there.
- Afr the "post" series
blew up walter reed's shit?
If you tell them you're
a journalist,
you're dead to them.
Yeah, I know.
You know somebody
down there, right?
Not at the hospital.
A neighbor of mine
is with a-w-two.
What?
- The army's wounded
warrior program.
She could get you in,
if you're not actually
writing a piece.
I'm not.
What are you doing, gus?
Scratching an itch.
- I do Miss the
shift-change parties.
No you don't.
You never missed a
fucking one of them.
- That was one sweet bust you
people put on marlo stanfield.
My number right?
I mean, it definitely
smells like a lester
freamon wiretap.
I watched the news,
all that dope on the table.
I swear, carv,
I was fully erect.
- Your dick got hard?
How could you tell?
- 'Cause the head was
poppin' out of the back
of your neck.
Seriously, it was a
wiretap, right?
- Seriously, I couldn't fuckin'
tell you if I knew, herc.
- So what're you saying?
My phone number wasn't shit?
- Ah, what do you want me
to fuckin' say, herc?
You're the tits.
Without your little
contribution,
the whole fucking city
slips into the chesapeake bay.
Better?
So you grew up there?
Well, when did your family
move to baltimore?
- Reginald.
You down there?
yes.
Come to the steps.
Got a coupla things for you.
Soap, deodorant and the like.
- 'Preciate that.
Usin' the washer basin
to clean up.
And to pee in.
- Don't worry,
I rinse it out.
I was wonderin'...
I got this anniversary comin up,
at the meetin' place.
Sometimes kin folk
come along
to show support.
I was wonderin',
maybe you could...
- It's hard for me to make
plans with my schedule
at the hospital.
- We got a little
celebration after.
Thinkin' I could cook us
some dinner.
I mean wouldn't be
a fancy thing,
mac and cheese, like that,
but I guarantee it'll
be good to you.
We'll see.
Okay.
My sister.
She good people.
Been through a lot though,
you know?
Levy.
'scuse me?
Levy. The lawyer.
I know who he is.
I'm not looking for
any lawyers.
I'm following the money.
Follow the lawyers.
Levy, bronfman,
silverstein, cray...
All those guys who take
the high-end drug work.
They don't just make money
off the criminal fees.
- How's he...
- The lawyers?
They the ones who make
a path for all this
street-corner money.
They showin' all these
kingpin motherfuckers
how to sd it overseas,
bring it back,
invest the shit.
They the ones who
these ignorant ghetto
motherfuckers always
listen to when
it comes to cash money.
And levy, man,
he got the most grease.
- So levy routes
it through who?
- Anyone who got a project
or a game in need of cash.
Developers, people lookin'
to capitalize,
elected folk like myself.
Shit, there's a lotta people
out here need a dollar
now an' then...
- And the lawyers
take their cut.
- On both ends,
though I got to say,
he gonna let you rob one
of his clients only so much.
I mean once you get
a barksdale or
a joe stewart on the hook,
you want to go deep
on they ass.
Levy'll let you get a taste,
but he won't let you run wild.
'cause once you get past these
motherfuckin' lawyers,
yocan really play the pimp.
This one time,
I had this fella named bell
hooked up on this howard
street condo thing,
got him so that he
wasn't runnin' his shit
past the lawyer...
Boy, I tell u,
we bled that mother fucker...
Lawyers, huh?
- Oh, most definitely,
detective.
me?
Shit, I'm just small potatoes.
Just a workin' politician
from walbrook junction,
tryin' to make his way
from this world into the next.
- What else can you
give me on levy?
- Nothin' other than
what I have.
I ain't up in his
business or nuthin'.
I just takin' what he throws.
Bullshit.
You got something
solid or I'm on my way
to the u.s. Attorney.
- You ain't nuthin'
but a shakedown artist.
How's this...
Levy got someoneat the courthous
oh, hell yeah.
Levy been buyin'
papers now for years
and sellin' 'em to
whoever needs an early look.
And don't think there ain't
no real money in that.
A prosecutor?
- I don't have a name.
Truly I don't,
but it seems to me,
you start lookin' at
the people hangin'
around the grand jury,
you'll find I'm right.
Now I know I've said
enough to buy my case back.
You know, you could
buy a round, too.
I get you?
Nah, feels good, hubert.
You dig in there,
you got a mind to.
You admiring my hand, si
oh, call me gus.
- It's hard to
get out the habit.
- That's pretty
damn lifelike.
Yeah.
Prosthetic digits.
Five of 'em,
individually controlled.
I got my key grip...
And my power grip...
My precision grip...
And my index point.
These new models got a
thumb that rotates,
which makes
all the difference.
Used to be you just had
this one grip,
right here for everything.
- You got your...
- Not yet.
- Brave new world.
- Yeah.
Do you mind if I...?
- The a-w-two lady says
you weren't writin' no story.
- No, I'm just verifying
details of one we already
printed in my newspaper.
Profile of your buddy.
- Terry.
- Hmm-hmm.
- Yeah, he come down
visit me every coupla weeks.
He takes that peter pan bus
down from baltimore.
Walks a couple of miles
down georgia avenue
from the silver
spring terminal.
He's having some
trouble as you know.
Did you read the article?
Yeah.
Man who wrote it got
some stuff right.
Terry was pissed,
I tried to play it off,
make him good with it.
- What did the story
get wrong?
- Well, that day wadn't
no black hawk down thing.
You know, when shit
went bad...
After I lost my hands,
them habudabi
motherfuckers weren't
even around after
the shit went off.
That's how they do.
How you doin', marino?
Outstanding.
Let me ask you this.
Could terry have exaggerated?
Why not?
If he got wound up say...
nah.
You lie about combat
because you weren't there.
And terry was.
Two tours.
He's got stories
if he wants 'em.
Just not on that day.
He ain't lie,
y'all did,
sorry t'say.
- Kima, what the fuck
are you taking about?
- I'm sayin' you made a
mistake letting mcnulty
run your people from one case
to the other like you did.
Why? What's the big deal?
- Their run sheets,
office reports.
Mcnulty covered them, right?
- So fuckin' what?
They did police work.
They did good fuckin'
police work, in fact.
Your guys...
You coach 'em good, ellis.
You let them know when
i.i.d. Comes callin'
that their answer is
that they didn't know
anything about it,
that they did what
they were told and they
turned in clean run sheets,
and they don't know
what anyone else sent
upstairs for staff review.
Know about what?
- When you spoke up
on colicchio...
How did that feel?
- Like shit.
You okay with it?
It was a forced move.
Tony lost it.
He was around the bend.
But are you okay with it?
Ninety-two q jams.
The most hip-hop and r & b.
It's your girl neke here...
We got our peoples
in the street.
They big, they fat,
and they gorgeous.
What up, porkchop?
- What's up, neke,
it's your boy porkchop...
We just gonna sit,
I should cut it.
With what they be chargin'
at the pump,
don't make sense to idle.
You can go.
Where to?
- Sayin' you can leave
the car with me.
You rent by the night, right?
- I ain't seen no
medium of exchange.
Look, when you done,
leave my short on the street
where I pick you up at.
Hmm-hmm.
- Oh, my god.
Look at this.
Bubs.
Walon, man...
This here's
my boy fletcher.
Newspaper writer
been followin' me 'round.
- Well, you're welcome
to sit in.
But I have to ask that
you respect the privacy.
No notetaking,
no recorders,
what you hear today
stays in the room.
- Not a problem.
I'm just here with reginald.
Reginald?
- I'm his fuckin' sponsor
and I don't believe
I ever got a christian
name out of him.
Reginald.
Hot shit.
See what you done?
What, man?
Come on.
My name is...
Reginald.
Round the way
they call me bubbles.
Hey, bubbles.
I'm a drug addict.
Celebratin' my anniversary.
My people couldn't
make it here tonight.
I left a trail
of fire behind me.
Time gonna make it right
with them, I guess.
That's right, it will.
- Same thing get me
right with myself.
Couple a days ago,
I took a walk down
in druid hill park,
right wh the sun
was goin' down.
You know how that
time be like,
with the sun throwin'
shadows an' all.
Got me thinkin'
'bout when I was a young man,
sittin' in that park.
You know, watchin' the girls,
smokin' on a little herb,
drinkin' a cold beer.
You know where this is goin'.
I had this moment where,
you know,
I was wantin' to
feel that way again.
I remembered,
what y'all said,
if the urge was to come,
call a group member
up and talk.
First thing I called walon up,
him bein' my sponsor an' all,
turns out he's on a ride
with his motorcycle club.
So I pulled out that sheet
that got passed out...
Dialed a few numbers,
couldn't get an answer.
I left a coupla messages,
but nobody called me back.
You didn't call me.
'cause I would have got up
with you, reginald.
You can believe that.
Well, anyway...
I didn't get high.
See, I knew if I did
I wouldn't get that
good feelin' back that
I was daydreamin on.
- That's right.
That's right.
- It got me thinkin'
about a friend of mine...
Boy named sherrod.
I been carryin' his passin'
for a long while.
Like that memory I had
about those summer days
in the park.
Thinkin' on that make me smile.
With sherrod,
it's more of a hurt.
But not as...
Not so bad like it was.
Ain't no shame in holdin'
on to grief.
As long as you make room
for other things, too.
It's alright.
So thank you for listening.
Thank you for
lettin' me share.
Thanks for sharing.
Where my gun?
- In the trap.
You get it when we set up.
- A detective is here
to see you.
Greggs, I think she said.
What? What's the matter?
- How you all even know
if Walter behind everybody
gettin' jacked?
I mean, ain't you
all ever wonder
if he even deserve
any of this shit?
- Deserve got nuthin'
to do with it.
It's his time that's all.
- Yo, pull over in that
alley right there.
I gotta piss sumpin' fierce.
- You better piss in that
cup right there on the floor.
- Man, I'm gonna
need ten cups.
Yo, pull over, Snoop.
- What now, motherfucker?
You shy?
Smart nigga.
You always was.
How you know?
- Y'all taught me.
Get there early.
Why? What I do wrong?
- Chris locked up behind
somethin' he done for you.
You downtown with the police.
I ain't say a word.
Yeah, that's what you say.
But it's how
you carry yourself.
Always apart.
Always askin' "why"
when you should be doin'
what you told.
You was never one of us.
You never could be.
How my hair look, Mike?
You look good, girl.
- They're sayin' the
only o.t. That anyone
has been sing has been
through getting
detailed on the
homeless killings.
They say that's the case.
And no wiretaps up?
I asked about that.
And I'm hearing,
off-the-record kinda,
that it was a wire.
And it makes sense,
'cause that's how Lester works.
He gets hold of a number
and works it to death.
Ere he would get the
number I have no idea...
- But a wiretap is hours,
and you say no one
is making any money...
- Fuckin' department's
more fucked up than even
I remember it.
Where you been at, Mike?
You gotta see this.
There's a serial killer,
but he only be killin'
other serial killers...
- Yo, yo.
We about take a ride.
You ain't got no whip.
- Just gather your stuff,
both of y'all.
Come on, we gotta move quick.
Come on. Let's go!
Okay.
- But that means...
All the calls to
the newspaper.
The photographs
of the missing man.
We have a wiretap...
McNulty has a...
On a cellphone.
Jesus Christ.
He wouldn't dare.
What's the number?
It's on the paperwork...
Come on.
Where...
Evidence control.
- I always thought you
were bullshittin'
'bout havin'
an aunt out here.
She expectin' him.
An' what's in this box.
It's nice here, huh?
Let's go, bug.
Wish't I was going with you.
You gonna have your own room.
She probably got one of
them plasma t.V.'s, too.
Them joints is wet.
Let's go.
OK, give that to aunt Carla.
Tell her there's more behind
it when she finds the need.
A-ight?
Make sure she cop you
some fresh things, too.
I don't need you going
to a new school lookin' all...
Come on, now.
A man don't be sheddin'
no tears.
Go on, bug.
- Bring it up front for
re-seal when you're through,
would ya, sir?
Thanks, augie.
Augie...
Glad you landed okay.
Yeah.
Beats workin'.
Why here?
Why you wanna mix
with their kind, man?
They give me work.
Who you talkin to?
I know what they be doin'
in there, duke.
- I could still hang with you,
then.
You know I'm too hot.
- You remember that one day,
summer past?
When we threw them piss
balloons at them terrace boys.
You remember? Just before
school started up again...
Y'know, I took a beatdown
from them boys,
I don't even throw
a shadow on it.
That was a day...
Y'all bought me ice cream
off the truck.
You remember, Mike?
I don't.
See you 'round, Mike.
See you, duk