_
Reginald Ledoux, 35.
Did a bit for manufacturing
meth and LSD.
He's a cook, you know,
like a chemist?
He said that there's this place where all
these rich men go to, uh, devil-worship.
Reggie got this
brand on his back,
like in a spiral?
He says that's their sign.
Marty!
You don't get to do what
you did to me last week.
She came to my home.
Our daughters saw her.
You blew up my life!
Reggie Ledoux.
Where is he?
He only cook
for one client now.
Some bike gang.
That bike club, I know 'em.
I had deals with 'em when
I was working narco.
We can get to Ledoux.
Keep this handy and be listening to
Beaumont police channels.
You got it?
I got it. Are you
gonna be all right?
I need a good soldier.
Now, you do this with us,
we talk about
puttin' you with my man.
Don't fire.
Do not--
[Gunshot]
[Grunts]
What are you doing, man?
Marty, I need you.
90 seconds!
Go, go, go!
[Tires screech]
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
[The Handsome Family's
Far For Any Road playing]
♪ from the dusty May sun ♪
♪ her looming shadow grows ♪
♪ hidden in the branches ♪
♪ of the poison creosote ♪
♪ she twines her spines up slowly ♪
♪ towards the boiling sun ♪
♪ and when I touched her skin ♪
♪ my fingers ran with blood ♪
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ when the last light warms the rocks ♪
♪ and the rattlesnakes unfold ♪
♪ the mountain cats will come ♪
♪ to drag away your bones ♪
♪ and rise with me forever ♪
♪ across the silent sand ♪
♪ and the stars will be your eyes ♪
♪ and the wind will be my hands ♪
True Detective - 1x05
"The Secret Fate Of All Life"
♪
[Coughs]
Uhh...
What happened to your face?
Pool game the other night.
Called the wrong dude
on cheating.
You got to watch that.
What do you want again?
I'm repping some people.
Yeah. They want to get
to the good cook.
They'll trade you
or the IC Brotherhood,
however you want to do it,
coke for crystal.
Why am I not talking to Miles?
Oh, me and Ginger go way back,
boosted together.
You ain't saying much.
I figure I let my man
give you the details.
Look.
This shit I got,
you can step on it 5, 6 times.
It'll still kick.
Just means you got
to cook a little more
for a lot more profit.
Nah.
I ain't go no use for it
or your money.
What, money don't spend?
I can see your soul
at the edges of your eyes.
It's corrosive, like acid.
You got a demon, little man,
and I don't like your face.
It makes me want
to do things to it.
Ginger, you call me again,
I'm setting Miles on you.
I see you again,
I'm putting you down.
There's a shadow on you, son.
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
♪
[Beep]
Marty, you got him?
You fucking better, the
shit I've been though.
HART:
I do. I got him.
We're on empty roads now.
So I got to drop back,
or he'll spot the tail.
Okay. That's
Reggie Ledoux's
cook partner Dewall.
Birddog him, Marty.
You got it.
COHLE: What's
your location?
Just south of I-10 along
the Creole Nature Trail
heading towards Carlyss.
Hurry up, man.
Copy that.
On my way.
[Car horn honks]
How we doing
back there, Ginger?
Fuck you, motherfucker.
[Tires screech]
- Aah!
- Yeah.
GILBOUGH: How'd you
get onto Ledoux?
One of my old CI's
tipped me off
to the location
of his cook house.
So I came back on the job.
Didn't want anybody else
to catch him, bring him in.
Look. You want my help?
Just show me the rest
of the file.
Why are you so hot to see
the new discovery file, man?
Well, why are y'all...
so hot to not give it to me?
It's supposed to be like
a consultation, right?
Yeah, but you go first.
You take me through it,
and I'll let you
see what we got.
I'll hold you to that.
[Engine stops]
HART:
Where's Ginger?
Wrapped up in a ditch.
What you got?
Well, lost him and then
had to double back
a few times till
I found the exit.
That's his truck there.
We're gonna have
to call this in, Rust.
Eh, we don't want to do that.
Troops will come,
flood these woods.
They could scatter.
[Sighs]
All right.
We ain't gonna
find him from here.
You ever been hunting, Marty?
Uh, yeah--
10-point buck
year before last,
50 yards.
I'm not talking about
sitting in a treehouse
waiting to ambush a buck coming
to sniff your gash bait.
Talking about tracking.
Jesus, you're a prick.
Look. We find the place.
We come back here.
We call it in.
One of us stays
surveillance, yeah?
I can live with that.
Let's go.
GILBOUGH:
Now, you got a tip
where Ledoux cooks,
and Cohle came back
from wherever he was.
You knew it was
gonna get here, man.
Just the once,
the way you tell it.
I'll tell it the same way
that I told the shooting board
and every cop bar
between Houston and Biloxi,
and you know why the story
is always the same
17 years gone?
Because it only went down
the one way.
♪
Now, Rust's dad taught him
bowhunting.
You know, you had
to track game till you got
within maybe 30 yards of it.
HART: Now, this enabled us
to discern the suspect's path
while sidestepping various
anti-intruder devices
they installed.
Tripwires back there.
Clearing is probably mined.
All right.
How you want to do it?
You go back. Call it in.
I'll wait here.
You're gonna hold position?
Yep.
COHLE:
Do it now, Marty.
Fuck you.
You ain't doing this
without me.
All right.
Stay low.
COHLE: We were just about
to turn back,
call in parish, state, whoever.
I mean, we had the location.
We had our suspects identified
at the location, you know?
Might as well
just leave the shit be
and hand it off.
That ain't what happened.
Hmm.
No. As soon as we started
to back off, man...
Blam!
Bullets cut through
right near Rust's head.
We dove opposite ways
into the high growth,
but they'd already spotted us,
and they had something
high-velocity.
Boom! Blew apart this tree
between us.
I mean, it was on.
COHLE:
[Imitating automatic arms fire]
♪
Hmm.
Heavy shit--
like ferns and whatnot
bursting all around us,
bark flying off of trees.
I mean we were
in a bucket shitstorm.
Shit.
[Door slides open]
[Door slides closed]
State police.
Put your hands on your head.
Put them on your head now.
Don't even think about it.
Put your hands
on your head right now.
Intertwine your fingers.
Do it.
Back up toward me.
HART: Down on your knees.
Go on.
[Handcuffs click]
It's time, isn't it?
The black stars.
Shut the fuck up.
[Handcuffs click]
HART: They'd spotted us
before we crossed the forest.
So all we could do
was duck for cover, dig in,
try getting closer.
It was chaos.
[Wings flapping]
The black stars rise.
Why the antlers?
[Creak]
Freeze, motherfucker.
Put it down. Hands up.
State police.
Set it down.
LEDOUX: I know
what happens next.
I saw you in my dream.
You're in Carcosa now with me.
He sees you.
COHLE: Marty!
You'll do this again.
Time is a flat circle.
Listen, Nietzsche.
Shut the fuck up.
Put it down. Marty!
There you go.
Black star.
COHLE: Put your hands
on your head.
[Click]
COHLE: While I was hunkered down
behind this old, decrepit boat,
Captain America Marty Hart
decides he's gonna run
deep into the woods,
flank around the back
of the house
where Ledoux is firing
at us, right?
Well, he sneaks up
behind Ledoux
and just as Ledoux turns,
bam, popped one off in him--
head shot, clean--
dropped him.
Now, his buddy Dewall,
he made a run for it,
and his homemade,
cracker-ass security system
took care of the rest.
♪
Oh, fuck.
Get the cuffs off him
before his blood settles.
We got to make this look right.
Goddamn. Fuck.
[Handcuffs click]
What do we do, Rust?
Oh, fuck him.
Good to see you
commit to something.
Now go see to the kids.
Don't bring them out
until I say so.
COHLE: After we confirmed
two deaths
and searched the rest
of the premises,
that's when we found
the two children.
I mean, we got very lucky.
We just as easily
could've been chewed to pieces
by an AK on approach.
COHLE: I can say that I walked
away from the experience
with a greater respect
for the sanctity of human life.
Yeah.
MAN: Thank you,
Detective.
I believe I speak for the board
when I commend you
on the heroism
displayed by you
and Detective Hart.
♪
No. We were doing
our jobs, sir.
COHLE: There were
the twig sculptures
and the LSD on hand matched
that in Dora Lange.
Everybody was pretty satisfied
that we got our man.
COHLE: The boy
had been missing since January.
He'd been dead less than a day.
The girl, she hadn't been
reported yet.
She was from St. Landry,
catatonic when we found her.
[Lighter clicks]
Why should I live
in history, huh?
Fuck, I don't want to know
anything anymore.
This is a world
where nothing is solved.
COHLE: Someone once told me,
"Time is a flat circle."
Everything we've ever done
or will do
we're gonna do over and over
and over again...
Good job, y'all.
COHLE: ...and that little boy
and that little girl,
they're gonna be
in that room again...
and again...
forever.
Cohle, you couldn't
manage to get shot?
Next time.
Thanks for not doubting us.
Never did.
WOMAN: Here they come.
Marty, our hero.
Way to go, boys.
Little extra pouring
while I finish this up
with the semicelebrities?
HART: There's plenty
of news stories
if you care to find them.
I got promoted
to detective sergeant.
Rust got a commendation
for bravery,
basically because I insisted,
and things were pretty good
for a while, I guess.
♪
Come on.
Get your speed up.
Ooh. All right.
HART: Maggie came around.
Just, you know,
a lot of talking, counseling,
and maybe being in a shootout
kind of opened her up
to forgiveness
or the possibility.
Right to the wall.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Oh!
Oh, thank God.
All right.
Go take off your skates.
- It's time to go.
- No, no.
Please, please, Mom?
One more time.
- Please.
- All right.
One more time around,
you take them off, okay?
Is Daddy coming home yet?
One more time around.
Go on. One more time.
One more time.
Okay.
Thanks.
I needed that.
I think they did, too.
- Were there others?
- What?
Besides her, were there others?
No.
No...
and listen.
That was a different person.
I lost it, you know,
just a little.
I--
I'm back.
I'm begging.
I keep begging.
I'll go to my grave
begging you.
It's not just the affair.
You used to be a good man.
Cut the booze, 5 weeks now.
I'm in a program--
Promise Keepers.
You have a long road to climb.
Yes. I do.
A few years,
good ones.
♪
HART: Down the line,
one of those setups
Maggie was so intent on
finally hit,
doctor, no less.
Yeah. She and Rust
had a thing, few years.
[Laughter]
WOMAN: He's
conflict-oriented.
So when I deny him
small arguments,
it builds up his energy.
- Wow.
Yeah. Are you ever
a match for this dude.
HART: Look.
You know about Rust.
During those 7 years,
he probably pulled more assists
than any other detective
in the state.
Word got around quick.
You want a confession,
see if State Detective Cohle
is available.
GILBOUGH: Your
interview technique.
Sure there isn't some
secret you can pass on?
Look. Everybody knows there's
something wrong with them.
They just don't know
what it is.
Everybody wants confession.
Everybody wants
some cathartic narrative for it,
the guilty especially...
oh, but everybody is guilty.
♪
HART: You know the good years
when you're in them,
or you just wait for them
until you get ass cancer
and realize that the good years
came and went?
Because there's a feeling--
you might notice it sometimes--
this feeling like life has
slipped through your fingers...
like the future is behind you,
like it's always
been behind you.
HART: You know, I cleaned up,
but maybe I didn't change,
not the way I needed to.
MAISIE:
Give it back.
Give it back!
HART: Remember what I said
about the detective's curse?
Solution to my whole life
was right under my nose--
that woman, those kids--
and I was watching
everything else.
HART: See, infidelity
is one kind of sin,
but my true failure
was inattention.
I understand that now.
[Cans clatter]
- Hey, Audrey...
- Audrey...
[Laughter]
PAPANIA: So when do you
think things started to,
how you put it, change again
with Detective Cohle?
Early on, 2002,
but that was his life.
Mine was steady, like I said.
I'm just trying to understand.
What is it you're going for?
What's the message?
There is no message.
It's just me.
It's just--
Well, what's
just you--
your hair,
your clothes, your--
I mean,
I look at Macie--
AUDREY: Women don't
have to look
like you want them to, Dad.
No. Women,
but I'm talking
about my teenage daughter,
and I'm not trying to tell you
what to wear or anything.
I'm just trying
to understand it.
Well, who told you
you had to understand?
Why would you?
So...
I hear you made cheerleader.
Yeah. There are,
like, 10 other girls
who didn't get it.
Hmm, I didn't know they had
eighth-grade cheerleaders.
Well--
Same as there's
football players.
♪
[Changing TV channels]
GILBOUGH: Tell us what
you know about his girl.
Yeah. Laurie. Yeah.
She became chief of something,
Lafayette General, I believe.
GILBOUGH: You know what
happened there between them?
What always happens
between men and women?
Reality.
[Exhales]
Dad--
Tell it to your mother.
[Door opens]
[Keys clatter]
Deputy found her
parked in a car with two boys.
Come here.
Get over here.
What?
Yeah, in states
of undress, you know...
like fucking.
Boys are 19 and 20.
Got them in holding
for the night,
haven't decided whether to
press stat. rape charges.
What?
You can't do that.
I can do anything I
goddamn want to those boys.
You think about that.
Audrey, look at me.
Look at me.
What are you
thinking? God.
What the fuck is wrong
with you, huh,
or is this one of those things
that I'll never understand,
you know, being the captain
of the varsity slut team?
Marty!
Fuck you.
♪
AUDREY:
Get in your fucking room.
MAISIE: Ow!
[Door slams]
Mom, she hit my head.
Go to bed.
This isn't about you.
Audrey, open the door.
Open the door, Audrey.
Audrey, it's just
you and me, honey.
See...
you need to tell me
what's going on.
Audrey, open the door, please.
COHLE: Years.
You ever heard
of something called
the M-brane theory,
detectives?
No. That's
over my head.
It's like in this universe,
we process time
linearly forward...
but outside of our spacetime,
from what would be a
fourth-dimensional perspective,
time wouldn't exist,
and from that vantage,
could we attain it...
we'd see...
our spacetime would look
flattened,
like a single sculpture
with matter
in a superposition of
every place it ever occupied,
our sentience just
cycling through our lives
like carts on a track.
See, everything
outside our dimension...
that's eternity,
eternity looking down on us.
Now, to us,
it's a sphere,
but to them...
it's a circle.
Mr. Cohle?
Mr. Cohle, what
happened in 2002?
COHLE: Guy Leonard Francis.
They say you killed two people
in Livingston.
They say you're
a drug store robber.
You know they already
got a nickname for you?
Southern Fried Pharmacy
Firearm Thief.
You like that?
Got a nice ring to it,
a bit of a mouthful.
Fuck, telling you, man,
the shit they got
these days--
technology,
fingerprints, DNA--
you got to be a fucking genius
to get past that shit.
Let's face it, Francis.
You ain't no fucking
genius, are you?
First, you come in and say,
"I got the drugs
from somewhere else."
Then you say, "No.
I don't remember.
I don't remember
where I got the drugs."
You're making it
too complicated.
You're creating
a maze for yourself
that you ain't never
gonna get out of.
They got you.
You just got
to change your play.
You got to plead impairment.
You know what that means?
That means that you
cannot be held
accountable for your actions.
Well, I don't think
I ought to be blamed--
well, entirely blamed--
for things I did
when I was under the
influence of anything.
I don't think
you should, either.
That's what I'm saying.
PCP. Stuff makes
a man crazy.
One time, famous case,
guy, he cut off his own
face on that shit.
- For real?
- Hell yeah.
You mix that with meth,
that's an insanity defense
if I ever heard one.
How you gonna say a man
who's not on anything
is insane because he
did something crazy
but a man who's on something
that made him crazy is sane?
You know what I mean?
- Works both ways.
- Yeah, exactly.
I mean, I'm not even saying
that I remember anything.
I was shit hammered.
There we go.
That's your play right there.
Fuck this amnesia story.
That dirt don't stick,
but an insanity defense,
that's your ticket.
That's your way out, all right,
because you're sobered up now.
You got your mind right.
You back.
You got to show them
the difference
between that madman
in that pharmacy
who blew them two people away
and the man who's
sitting here right now.
You got to show shock,
terror, and
re-fucking-morse.
I am. I do. I'm--
- I'm scared, sir.
- Oh, yeah.
You should be, right?
Yeah. What'd you say
to the pharmacist?
I said,
"Give me everything."
And then what?
Boom. Boom.
Blew that fucker
away, didn't you?
You want forgiveness for that?
- Yeah.
- Say it.
- I want it.
- You want what?
Forgiveness.
You see what you just did?
You just copped
to a double murder.
They got you now.
But--
I want to make a deal.
A deal about what?
I know things.
Oh, what you know
now all of a sudden?
I know--
I know who you are, and I know
about that woman y'all
found out in the woods
way back, the antlers.
Hmm.
That don't mean shit.
That was in the newspaper.
What you know?
You don't know shit, do you?
No. Y'all never caught
the man that did that.
He's been out there killing.
You're talking
out your ass, boy.
You don't know a fucking thing.
You're just trying
to buy some time,
ain't you?
I met him once.
There's big people
who know about him,
big people.
Ah, ain't no deal
because there ain't no people.
You make me a deal.
You deal with me
with these murders.
Ain't no deal.
You ain't got nothing
because you're full of shit,
and there ain't nobody alive
that did none of that killing.
He's dead, boy.
I'll tell you about
the Yellow King.
What the fuck you say, boy?
Give me a name.
Give me a fucking name.
You want to fucking play, boy?
The Yellow King!
Oh! Aah!
Get the hell off me!
Get off me!
Get off of me!
Deal with me,
you son of a bitch.
You deal with me!
I want a deal!
Easy. Come on, man.
Calm down, dude.
Now take a deep
breath, all right?
You got the confession.
then you made it inadmissible.
What do you fucking mean?
He's still talking.
Shucking and jiving.
He knows exactly who you are.
You called me in here, huh?
You did.
I know, and if we need
anything else,
we'll let you know.
We appreciate the
assist, Detective.
What the fuck is going on here?
We have to salvage
a double murder
confession, is what's going on.
If he wasn't just
running you in there,
you'll get anything we get.
You have my word.
Come on. Ease up, baby.
Calm down.
And I'll be back...
Oh, I got it.
...tomorrow.
Stay the fuck back.
I got it.
♪
COHLE: In eternity,
where there is no time,
nothing can grow.
Nothing can become.
Nothing changes.
So death created time
to grow the things
that it would kill...
and you are reborn
but into the same life
that you've always
been born into.
I mean, how many times have we
had this conversation,
detectives?
Well, who knows?
When you can't remember
your lives,
you can't change your lives,
and that is the terrible
and the secret fate of all life.
You're trapped...
by that nightmare
you keep waking up into.
[Footsteps]
You all right?
We got to go to Abbeville.
Well, I got a deposition
this afternoon.
Aw, push it.
I got somebody
we need to talk to.
I'll tell you on the way.
Come on.
HART: You really
think he's serious
about having something,
and if so, then what?
Reggie Ledoux deserved
to die, Marty.
That was justice.
I'm not ruling out
other agencies.
Mm-hmm.
What does that mean?
Guy Francis and Charlie Lange
both say the Yellow King.
Dora Lange
said the Yellow King.
Okay. Look.
If the killer
is still out there,
why haven't there
been more killings?
Well, maybe there have, Marty,
and we just don't
know about them,
hadn't put them together.
Ever wonder why that task force
was so hot to take
the case back in '95?
[Laughter]
Are you telling me you
think the task force
was in on it?
♪
COHLE: Fuck.
COHLE: How the fuck
does this happen?
MAN: He knew what he was looking
at with the double murders.
Guess he thought about it
and made a choice.
You got a camera feed?
COHLE: Here.
Go back. Play this.
MAN: Took a phone call
at 7:15, his lawyer.
You got audio on this, sound?
Nah, just the vid.
That's it, just
3 hours of nothing...
till you see the blood.
We don't know what somebody
might have told him
on that phone call.
I want to see your
incoming call logs now.
All right.
What are the two
officers' names?
Childress and Mahoney.
Give me their files, please.
Yes, sir.
♪
Terrence, get prints on this.
Yes, sir.
Prints?
That's a public phone.
No kind of lawyer
makes calls from here.
Francis have relatives?
Yeah-- sisters, a few
nieces, nephews.
Connects to the suicide how?
Somebody might have
told him something,
gave him no choice.
Well, great.
GILBOUGH: So when he got
going on this thing again,
did he mention
Billy Lee Tuttle?
You know that he did.
PAPANIA: Tuttle died a
couple years back, 2010.
Yeah. Yeah.
What was that,
mixed medications? So what?
Right after Cohle showed
back up in the state.
Fuck this.
Fuck this bullshit.
You tell me right now
why you're all over Cohle,
or I'll walk.
♪
_
[Thunder]
His record, his reports,
his stories, they don't add up.
So talk to him
about it already.
Stop pissing in my ear.
We did.
- Oh, you did?
- What?
Well, if you two
talked to Rust,
you weren't getting
a read on him.
He was getting a read on you.
♪
_
This is all you got?
Fuck, I already know all this.
That what we have so far.
You hadn't checked
old unsolveds.
PAPANIA: Maybe you
stop dancing with us.
Tell us what you
really been up to,
how you spend your time.
I already told you
how I spend my time.
Except you've been
bullshitting us
all afternoon.
Excuse us for
one minute, please.
♪
[Door opens]
These are from the crime
scene in Lake Charles
once folks got word.
Recognize anybody in there?
PAPANIA: Lake Charles
is a bit out of the way
for you, ain't it?
How did you keep her
out of the papers?
Maybe you got some friends
in high places?
Your truck and a man
fitting your description
was spotted in the vicinity
of our crime scene 5 times
by 5 different people
over the last month.
GILBOUGH: Now, besides
people seeing him
and his truck around
the location for weeks,
you know he was off the grid
after he left in '02,
didn't show up anywhere
till 2010-- Louisiana.
Got his driver's
license renewed.
Nobody knows what
he's been doing
in the meantime.
PAPANIA: Got a storage
shed near Church Point.
He won't let us see
what's inside.
PAPANIA: How about
you let us see
what you're keeping in storage?
Fuck no. You can't see
my storage unit.
Get a warrant.
Christ, try working a case.
GILBOUGH:
We are working it.
Yeah?
See, how we work it is,
we think way back,
you put the case
on Rianne Olivier,
put it on her old boyfriend.
I don't know.
Maybe the Ledoux boys knew you.
Maybe you traveled
the same circles,
got the same hobbies.
Maybe they had
something on you.
PAPANIA: You just kept
pulling the right old murders,
take the case wherever
you wanted it to go.
You're a juicer.
Ever black out?
Ever wake up, don't
remember what happened?
Look. Y'all want to arrest me,
go ahead.
If you want to follow me,
come on.
You want to see something,
get a warrant.
Thanks for the beer.
Beyond that, you wasted
my fucking day, company man.
GILBOUGH: Now, he
bartends 4 days a week,
this roadhouse,
has a little
apartment behind it.
No other accounting
of this time.
Says he drinks.
You're wrong.
Nobody could change that much.
You are dead wrong.
GILBOUGH: Hey, you've
been telling us all day
about the kind of shit
he'd think up,
the way he'd talk.
We got a good earful
of that, too.
PAPANIA: Are you
gonna tell me
that's a stable individual?
Left a burnout, junkie rumors.
Do you think 10
years on the sauce
has made him more reasonable?
GILBOUGH: Think about this.
You said it.
He'd been there 3 months,
and you two catch a heater
like you've never
had before or since,
one that he shines on.
You're saying he did
such a great job.
Didn't he get you
every bit of evidence?
Didn't he push you
where he wanted it to go?
PAPANIA: He brought
you Rianne Olivier.
She wasn't one of Ledoux's.
She was one of his.
What'd he say,
"Life is a disease"?
When he heard the Abbeville
prisoner Francis
knew something, he got on it.
He shut it down.
You ever thought if he made
that phone call
to the prisoner,
like-- I don't know--
the guy was trying
to blackmail him?
He got on that, too, didn't he,
the idea that the Lange
killer was still out there?
Yeah.
Yeah. He did.
Looking for a new patsy, maybe.
HART: Y'all given me
a lot to absorb.
PAPANIA: Goddamn right
it's a lot to absorb.
- So help us out.
- Yeah.
Whatever you can tell us
about, you know,
from when he got
on the Lange killer
you up to when
you two had your altercation.
Whatever that was about.
♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player