_
You know, she's always been
in some kind of trouble.
I thought things
were getting better.
Got away from Charlie.
She called up here
for you not too long ago.
She come out
she's going to become a nun.
What'd you do last night?
I was out with girlfriends.
I can't meet a nice man at home.
There is nowhere else
I want to be.
I wonder if you even
know you're lying.
Come on!
I got a whodunit where
my two detectives are stalling,
and I got a task force
wants to take it off our hands.
So Cohle didn't want
to give it to the task force.
- Did you?
- No.
I heard of this place.
Kind of trailer park.
Called "The Ranch."
Something happened to a girl.
We need to know if
any of you knew her.
Yeah, that's Dori.
You got any idea where she might have
been staying the last few weeks?
She'd been going to church.
I was hoping maybe she
just turned things around.
_
Place is trashed.
This ain't no kinda anything.
Marty.
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
[The Handsome Family's
Far From Any Road playing]
♪ from the dusty May sun ♪
♪ her looming shadow grows ♪
♪ hidden in the branches ♪
♪ of the poison creosote ♪
♪ she twines her spines up slowly ♪
♪ towards the boiling sun ♪
♪ and when I touched her skin ♪
♪ my fingers ran with blood ♪
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ when the last light warms the rocks ♪
♪ and the rattlesnakes unfold ♪
♪ the mountain cats will come ♪
♪ to drag away your bones ♪
♪ and rise with me forever ♪
♪ across the silent sand ♪
♪ and the stars will be your eyes ♪
♪ and the wind will be my hands ♪
True Detective - 1x03
"The Locked Room"
♪
[Camera shutter clicks]
MAN: You were as blind to Him
as your footprints in the ashes,
but He saw you.
He saw you
in those dark corners.
He heard you--
Oh, my brothers,
He heard those thoughts.
Yes!
Preach it.
- Amen!
- Yes!
Yes.
Glory.
You are stranger to yourself,
and yet He knows you...
- Amen.
- Yes. He does, sir.
...and when your heart hardened,
made you liken to the stone,
and broke you from His body,
which is the stars
and the wind between the stars,
He knew you.
- Yeah!
That is forever.
Amen, brother!
This world is a veil...
- Amen.
- Yeah.
- Tell them.
- Hallelujah.
...and the face you wear
is not your own.
HART: Parish FD said
the church burned down
4 months earlier, no prints,
put out an APB
on Friends of Christ.
Week later,
we were in Franklin,
um, Revival Ministry,
old-time religion.
You can imagine what
Mr. Charisma thought of that.
MAN: It is merely the limitation
of your senses.
COHLE: What do you
think the average IQ
of this group is, huh?
Can you see Texas up there
on your high horse?
What do you know
about these people?
Just observation and deduction.
I see a propensity
for obesity, poverty,
a yen for fairy tales,
folks putting what
few bucks they do have
into little, wicker baskets
being passed around.
I think it's safe to say
that nobody here
is gonna be splitting
the atom, Marty.
You see that?
Your fucking attitude.
Not everybody want to sit
alone in a empty room
beating off to murder manuals.
Some folks enjoy
community, the common good.
Yeah? Well,
if the common good
has got to make up fairy tales,
then it's not good for anybody.
Your sorrows
pin you to this place.
They divide you
from what your heart knows,
and there are a lot
of good hearts out there.
I'm looking out there.
I'm seeing a lot
of good hearts out there.
I see a lot of joy out there.
HART: I mean,
can you imagine
if people didn't believe,
what things they'd get up to?
Exact same thing they do now,
just out in the open.
Bull...shit.
It'd be a fucking
freak show of murder
and debauchery,
and you know it.
If the only thing
keeping a person decent
is the expectation
of divine reward,
then, brother, that person
is a piece of shit,
and I'd like to get
as many of them out in the open
as possible.
I guess your judgment
is infallible
piece-of-shitwise.
Do you think that notebook
is a stone tablet?
What's it say about life, hmm,
you got to get together,
tell yourself stories
that violate every law
of the universe
just to get through
the goddamn day?
No.
What's that say about
your reality, Marty?
When you get
to talking like this,
you sound panicked.
PAPANIA: You figure
it's all a scam, huh,
all them folks?
Mm-hmm.
They just wrong?
Oh, yeah.
Been that way since one
monkey looked at the sun
and told the other monkey,
"He said for you to give
me your fucking share."
People so goddamn frail
they'd rather
put a coin in a wishing well
than buy dinner.
MAN: Jesus Christ, Jesus Christ,
Your arms open and close.
The echoes of my life
could never contain
a single truth about You.
You move the feather
in the ash.
You touch the leaf
with its flame.
- Amen!
- Amen.
COHLE: Transference of
fear and self-loathing
to an authoritarian vessel.
It's catharsis.
He absorbs their dread
with his narrative.
Because of this, he's effective
in proportion to the
amount of certainty
he can project.
- Yeah! - Yeah!
- Yeah.
Certain linguistic
anthropologists think
that religion is
a language virus
that rewrites
pathways in the brain,
dulls critical thinking.
Well, I don't use
$10 words as much as you,
but for a guy who sees
no point in existence,
you sure fret about it
an awful lot,
and you still sound panicked.
At least I'm not racing
to a red light.
MAN: ...every self-doubt
because he knows it.
COHLE: See, we all got
what I call a life trap,
this gene-deep certainty
that things will be different,
that you'll move
to another city
and meet the people
that'll be the friends
for the rest of your life,
that you'll fall in love
and be fulfilled.
Fucking fulfillment,
heh, and closure,
whatever the fuck
those two--
Fucking empty jars
to hold this shitstorm,
and nothing is ever fulfilled
until the very end,
and closure--
No. No, no.
Nothing is ever over.
HART: Minister Theriot,
do you recognize this girl?
I don't know for sure.
Wonderful sermon.
Well, thank you for coming.
- Thank you.
I want to say it's--
Thank you.
I don't remember the name,
came pretty regularly
when we was in Eunice,
but I can't be sure.
We get around since then.
You? Oh, hello.
No. You're right.
We saw her in Eunice.
Tina might know her.
Mm-hmm.
HART: How long
were you in Eunice?
About 6 months.
Widow in Opelousas
leased us cheap.
We left when it caught fire.
HART: Any idea
how that happened?
Your people said
criminal mischief.
If I was to lay odds,
maybe one of the widow's sons
wanted us off the land,
but we move on.
We seek no title
nor retribution.
I'm gonna go find David.
Okay.
Yeah.
Great preaching.
How long you been doing this?
Been preaching almost 20 years.
We've had Friends of Christ
for the last 8.
You with a church before that?
Independent evangelical.
I came up under
Billy Lee Tuttle,
went to his college in
Baton Rouge a couple years.
HART: So back in Eunice,
who painted the mural
on the church wall?
Children from our
congregation painted it.
I'm sorry.
Something happen to this girl?
You looking for her?
Mr. Theriot, can we see
the identification
of your staff members?
HART: You ever see her
with anybody?
WOMAN: Wasn't she with
someone the one day?
You remember?
The tall man.
TINA: Yeah,
but I don't know
if she was "with him" with him.
Well, can you describe him?
I just saw them talking.
I didn't get close or anything.
He was hunched forward
talking to her,
kind of a strange face,
I think,
skin shiny around his jaw.
Ah, what, like burned?
Uh-huh.
So did she leave with him?
Yeah, maybe like that.
WOMAN ON POLICE RADIO:
Arrested 10/89 on a 314,
spent last year in solitary
after a gang altercation.
Print and hold.
Thank you.
Copy that.
[Children laughing and shouting]
THERIOT:
Everything check out?
For the most part.
Burt, you spent two
years in Angola--
indecency, public exposure,
whacking off outside a school.
They gave me bad medicine.
I didn't know.
I paid for that.
Can you account
for his whereabouts
December 25 through January 3?
Yeah. Christmas
to New Year's,
we was in New Roads.
Shouldn't be a problem
to find people
who'll vouch for
Burt's whereabouts.
We had a good turnout there.
Good turnout in--
Detective, what is it
you think happened?
Someone killed this girl,
made a big show of it...
left a painting
of the crime scene
on one of your old churches.
[Scoffs]
"I am the resurrection
and the light
for those
who believe in me."
Was she raped, Detective?
Why would you ask that?
If you speak to Burt alone,
I believe you'll be
adequately convinced
of his innocence, Detective.
Okay. Let's do that.
Burt, go with the Detective.
COHLE: The ontological fallacy
of expecting
a light at the end
of the tunnel,
well, that's what
the preacher sells,
same as a shrink.
See, the preacher,
he encourages
your capacity for illusion.
Then he tells you
it's a fucking virtue.
Always a buck to be had
doing that,
and it's such a desperate sense
of entitlement, isn't it?
"Surely, this is all for me.
Me.
Me, me, me. I, I.
I'm so fucking important.
I'm so fucking important,
then, right?" Fuck you.
GILBOUGH: Excuse us
for a second.
[Telephone rings]
[Door closes]
BURT: I didn't know.
COHLE: Easy. I am not
gonna hurt you.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
BURT: Oh.
[Sighs]
Compassion is ethics,
Detective.
Yes. It is.
COHLE: I ran checks
on all of them.
Everyone has got a clean
record except for Burt.
HART: I could see
this being some kind
of retard job--
pays for it, gets ashamed,
overreacts,
tries to redeem the act,
like, you know?
That's not bad, Marty...
Well, yeah.
I got all the way there
without your help.
...but it's not him.
He did a deuce at the farm
for dick wagging.
Should've been in
a mental ward to begin with.
Give me the second half.
Angola.
Some Bloods caught him
in the shower,
took his balls off
with a razor.
They were sloppy about it.
Oh, Jesus.
Still--
I braced him.
He shit himself, literally.
We can put some
troopers on this place,
have them surveil it,
but I think we should move on,
the tall man.
Well, that could be bullshit.
One threw it out,
and the other one
picked up on it.
No. Burt knew.
He saw the tall man, too.
This,
that Marie Fontenot thing,
there's no way Lange
was his first,
no fucking way.
♪
THERIOT: Rosie, can you
help them get out, please.
[Engine revving]
HART: We haven't
matched any signatures.
One guy in the fed
database used crowns,
another a set
of antlers--
Michigan lifer.
Then he called
the signature wrong.
[Zip]
We don't know that
there's any connection
to Marie Fontenot.
Yeah, but the lattices,
the symbology--
some kind of culture
to it, Marty.
I mean, he wanted
us to find this one,
like he was showing off.
That cane field is our stage.
Make a suggestion, then.
We start at zero,
they're gonna hand it
to the task force.
Well, somebody
missed something.
We need to go back,
check all files.
Any DBs in state
the last 5 years,
we start there.
We don't have the hours.
Shit, man. Look.
I've noticed you have
a tendency toward myopia,
tunnel vision,
blows investigations.
Vision skews, twists evidence.
You're obsessive.
You're obsessive, too,
just not about the job.
Not, me, brother.
I keep things even, separate,
like the way I can
have this one beer
without needing 20.
People incapable of guilt
usually do have a good time.
Try not to be
too hard on myself.
Well, that's real big of you.
You know the real difference
between you and me?
Yeah. Denial.
The difference is
that I know the difference
between an idea and a fact.
You are incapable
of admitting doubt.
Now, that sounds
like denial to me.
I doubt that.
[Clears throat]
We'll put out an APB
on any tall man
with facial scarring...
Okay.
...telex the hospitals
for patients that fit.
Good.
♪
[Engine starts]
PAPANIA: So Cohle was trying
to keep it from the task force.
Looking back,
you ever think maybe
he tried to push things
where he wanted them to go?
No. We went where
the case led us.
But you took it up, though,
his serial theory.
Well, as arrogant
as he could be,
he was right.
I mean, that's how
we got our man.
♪
COHLE: Uh-huh,
but I like it
this way, you know?
It's steady.
MAGGIE:
Bullshit, really.
Look. I did all the
counseling and stuff.
This is just the way
things are.
No. Things don't
stay the same.
Pick up what you keep, and
you leave the rest behind.
People get better.
Well, that's the thing.
I think I am better.
You really think so?
Uh, trust me.
Maybe you just think
you prefer it this way
because it's
what you're used to.
Your life accommodates you.
You don't have to be
afraid of loss.
Those are the guys
I was telling you about.
They get a dog, fish,
what have you.
You start with that.
You live with it.
[Car door closes]
Hell, I suppose
you could set me up
with a nurse, get me
some of the good drugs.
Mm-hmm.
[Door closes]
New start.
[Keys clatter]
- Daddy.
HART: Hey, kids.
Hey, honey.
How you doing, Marty?
What's going on, Rust?
Brought the mower back.
Mow my yard?
Yeah. I saw
it needed mowing,
returned the favor, borrowing.
We got etouffee,
trying to get Rust
to stay for dinner.
Oh, yeah?
Stay for dinner, Rust.
Nah. I think
I got to get.
Maggie, thank you for the tea.
Sorry to hear that.
See you Monday.
I'll walk you out.
Hey.
Hey!
What?
What the hell do you
think you're doing, man,
at my house when I'm not here?
Returning the mower.
You know what I mean.
You mow my lawn? Hmm?
Just what'd you think
I'd be doing over here
when you're not around, Marty?
What's our problem, you and me?
No problem.
I just don't ever want you
mowing my lawn, all right?
I like mowing my lawn.
[Engine starts]
HART: Oh.
That is your team, Daddy?
Yeah, baby. That--
I want them to win.
[Clears throat]
Uh, hey, Audrey, your mom and I
want to talk to you
a minute about
those drawings you
did in school, yeah?
Mace, run to your room.
Why?
Because I said so.
Run to y--
Go. Go on.
Go.
Go. Run.
Look.
You don't have to get
upset, honey, okay?
We just want to talk to you.
Where'd you see that
before, hmm?
Why'd you draw that?
Because other girls liked it
and they thought it was funny.
That's all.
Yeah, but where'd you
get that idea, hmm?
The girls dared me to do it.
Oh, God.
That upsets people, Audrey.
It's ugly.
It makes something
that should be nice
ugly.
I'm sorry. Oh...
Shh. That's okay.
It's okay.
[Whimpers]
It's okay, sweetie.
HART: Well, I'm not saying
that I got any room to talk,
but do you know what it means
to be a father?
It means you are accountable
for other people.
You are responsible
for their lives.
Now, past a certain point,
there's a futility
in responsibility.
Hey.
That's the extent
of your concern?
Well, no.
I just don't know what
looking at it any more
is gonna do.
It's her.
I'm concerned.
Well, she's just trying
to get attention,
and the other girls--
Jesus, how do they even know
about that stuff yet?
Girls always know before boys.
Why is that?
Because they have to.
Listen to me.
She's withdrawn.
She asks about you,
and she wants to know
why you're working so much now.
Well, I should be working less.
Task force is gonna
take that case,
and I'll be around more.
Last week?
[Clears throat]
I'm sorry about that.
I should've begged off.
We were having a good night.
Don't stop me. Talk.
I'm close, Marty.
Do you hear me?
I'm close.
Um, they're gonna
pull that case from us,
and I'll be around more,
and we'll do things.
Why is there all this
space between us, Marty?
I don't know what you mean.
You do know what I mean,
and you won't say,
and that's it.
That's what I'm talking about.
This last year, you've
been a sulky teenager.
You know it.
I'm trying to be
your friend, Marty.
[Sighs]
I'm just not good
at... you know, expressing.
We change, don't we,
and sometimes not for long.
And here I'm thinking people
don't really change at all,
not who they are at heart.
You know, I try to remember things
because I feel
like I should, like it's my job
or something,
you know, early days,
and I'm tired of
trying to remember.
Part of this--
and I'm not talking
about the part
that's all my fault--
but part of it, it's just life.
We used to spend weekends
without leaving my room.
- That's not what I mean.
- Remember that?
Of course we don't
screw like we're 19.
God, you want low expectations.
You know, you put a ceiling
on your life,
on everything, because
you won't change.
You were so much smarter
when I met you,
you know?
I'm sorry, Maggie.
I'm sorry
for everything--
for not being here,
for taking all this
for granted.
What have you been
doing, Marty?
I--
Work, home, cases.
Just--
I get to feeling like--
Look. I can see 40...
and it's like I'm that coyote
in the cartoons,
like I'm running off a cliff,
and if I don't look down
and keep running,
I might be fine, but, um...
I think I'm all fucked up.
You are.
Yes. You are.
♪
[Kiss]
[Exhales]
PAPANIA: Marty?
Anyway, well, we pulled
a few hospital patients--
tall, scarred, sex offenders.
One kid did B&Es.
He had to tug one out
before he could leave a scene.
Phew. Yeah.
A lot of room work then.
Which one of you guys
is the box man?
You, yeah?
I used to be pretty good
in there myself,
not as good as Rust.
COHLE: I know, son.
I can read this off you.
♪
You're not bad.
It's not you.
There's a weight,
and it got its fishhooks
in your heart and your soul.
[Sobbing]
Now, what you did
is not your fault.
It's not.
You was drug to the bottom
by that same weight,
the same weight
that won't let you
get along in a job,
and same weight that
wouldn't let you
get along at school...
same weight that
wouldn't let you
have a mom.
I know these things, Chris.
I'm weak. I'm sick.
I get into the houses,
and I can't leave
until I go
all over the drawers.
Listen to me, son.
You got one way out,
and it's through
the grace of God.
You're only how
the Lord made you.
You are not flawed.
We, you, me, people,
we don't choose our feelings.
[Chris sobbing]
There's grace in this world,
and there's
forgiveness for all,
but you have to ask for it.
I do. I do.
I want that.
I want it. I want that.
I'm asking. I'm asking.
Tell me. Tell me.
Please just tell me
what to say.
I want to confess.
[Chris sobbing]
GILBOUGH:
Sorry about that.
[Door closes]
Your assist record, man,
that's something else.
PAPANIA:
Any pointers?
Oh, I never really
found it that hard.
You just look at somebody
and think like they think,
negative capability.
I mean, I guess it's a skill.
Most times,
you don't even need that.
You just look them in the eyes.
The whole story is right there.
Everybody wears their hunger
and their haunt, you know?
You just got to be honest
about what can go on up here,
a locked room....
[Cuts can]
but then again,
I'm terrible at cards.
Ha, ha!
Yeah. So while we were grilling
B&E jerkoffs and burn victims,
I decided to put insomnia
to good use.
♪
_
COHLE: People.
I've seen the finale
of thousands of lives, man--
young, old.
Each one is so sure
of their realness,
that their sensory experience
constituted a unique individual
with purpose, meaning...
so certain that they were
more than a biological puppet.
Well, the truth wills out,
and everybody sees
once the strings are cut,
all fall down.
[Beeping]
♪
WOMAN:
Maggie says he's shy.
I wouldn't say that.
Definitely not shy
about speaking his mind.
Well, that's not what I mean.
His personality.
He's edgy.
Yeah, intense,
more like, introverted.
WOMAN: I don't want
another drunk.
The last cop
you showed me--
HART: No. Wait. Steve was going
through a tough time.
He threw up in my lap.
Don't worry about that.
Getting him near you lap
is gonna be the challenge.
Oh, hey, speak of the devil.
- Hey, Rust.
- Martin.
- Hey, Maggie.
- Hi, Rust.
- Jennifer.
- Rustin.
Nice to meet you.
Well, you walk over here?
[Clears throat]
Well... okay.
♪
HART: Just when I thought he
couldn't get any stranger.
Are you serious?
He tastes colors.
So what is synesesia?
COHLE: Synesthesia.
It's a misalignment
of synaptic receptors
and triggers--
alkalis, colors,
certain metallics.
It's a type
of hyper sensitivity.
One sense triggers
another sense.
Sometimes I'll see a color,
and it'll put a taste
in my mouth.
A touch, a texture, a scent
may put a note in my head.
MAGGIE: I've heard that.
It can be a side effect
of a statin.
It's not a side effect.
So when something feels good,
does that mean it
feels twice as good,
like from two different ways?
COHLE: It could.
Yeah.
MAGGIE: The waitress
will bring them, babe.
HART: Why wait?
I'll be right back.
HART: Refill and two rums.
Ohh...
Hi. Can I have
another beer?
Thank you.
♪
What are you doing?
What's it look like?
I'm on a date.
Aren't you?
Heh.
So are you gonna go home
with this guy? Huh?
It's really none
of your business.
Do you fuck your wife?
What do you
want me to do? Look.
Is this your way of
trying to talk divorce?
My God, Marty,
I don't want to marry you.
That's my whole point.
It's just run its course.
No, it hasn't. Come here.
Have a shot with me.
WOMAN: Gonna play
a little something
everybody should dance to.
♪
Hey, I didn't just
come here to drink, you know.
Let me just set this down.
It'll be fun.
Yeah.
What?
Oh, nothing.
Thought I saw a guy who
supposed to be in parish.
So what's Alaska like?
It's beautiful.
It's not Paris, but it's clean,
and it's clear.
You've been to Paris?
For a month.
What'd you do in Paris?
Mainly just got drunk
in front of Notre Dame.
♪
COHLE: Each stilled body
so certain
that they were more than the sum
of their urges,
all the useless spinning,
tired mind,
collision of desire
and ignorance.
You asked
about the interrogations.
You want to know the truth?
I never been in a room
more than 10 minutes
I didn't know whether
the guy did it or not.
[Sniffles]
How long does it take you?
Rust spent a lot of off duty
running DBs,
weeks of it,
coon hound in another life.
Coon hound?
I meant raccoon hound.
Everybody is a fucking
drama queen nowadays.
Jesus. Look.
If working his theories,
if his job
was his idea of himself, fine.
I mean, the rest of us
had families,
people in our lives,
good things.
People give you rules.
Rules describe the shape
of things.
[Pounding on door]
MAN: Come on!
Fuck you!
Fuck, Marty, get out of here.
"Fuck, Marty." Is that
all you got for me?
Stop it. Go home.
I don't want this anymore.
You got that little
shitbird in here?
Go away.
I'll call the cops.
Well, let's see how that
works out for you.
- I know other cops.
- Okay.
LISA: Get out.
Marty, get out.
But she said she was single.
Marty, God!
Stop! Stop it!
Did she suck your dick, huh?
Stop it!
She suck your fucking dick?
Get out! Get off.
Get off!
Yeah.
You try it?
Oh, you tell me, or I'll have
some Ninth Ward prison queen
wearing your face for a condom.
Did she suck your dick?
Just for a little bit.
Get off.
Please stop it.
HART: Sorry I got
in your face, guy.
I wouldn't have really
done something like that.
I'm not a psycho.
HART: That's why I always said
I think Rust needed a family.
It's boundaries.
Boundaries are good.
[Traffic passing in distance]
[Telephone rings]
[Ring]
This is Cohle.
MAGGIE:
Rust, you're home.
- It's me.
- Yeah. What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Steve Geraci said
he caught something.
He needed help.
I almost called the station,
but what's the point?
You know they lie.
I got to put you on the spot.
You know if it's true?
I didn't hear anything,
but then again, I wouldn't.
I mean, Geraci
wouldn't pull me.
He hates me.
[Clears throat]
You drop Jen at home?
Yeah. I walked her
to the door.
You didn't go in?
You don't have to fall in love
at first sight, you know.
Yeah. I know. Look.
She's nice, pretty.
There's comfort there, Rust.
I think you guys
would be good together
if you gave it a chance.
You guys don't
give things chances.
I don't know why that is.
That's because we
know what we want
and we don't mind being alone.
Go to bed, Maggie.
Marty'll be home.
Take care.
[Beep]
[Clears throat]
FAVRE: Holy shit,
3 days in a row.
Is that a new personal record?
HART: Fuck off.
I will take my first shit
through your sunroof.
Hey, hey, I found one, I think,
another girl from earlier.
Come here.
3 years ago,
a flood in Abbeville,
they pulled this girl
out of the river.
Hold it.
It says here that her
death was accidental--
drowned, water in the lungs.
How's that him?
Coroner says the branches
and debris from the flood
caused these injuries,
all right?
I understand the ribs and
the arms, but the hyoid?
- Still--
- No fucking way.
Look at this,
lacerations to the abdomen,
plus she was positive
for meth and LSD.
They said she
was high, fell in.
Hmm.
Look at the posterior.
- Holy shit.
- Yeah.
IDed
as Rianne Olivier--
22, lives in Pelican Island,
population 300.
Grandpa is still there,
got a phone at the dock.
I don't know if I
can sell this shit.
Two days, we dig
in this direction.
If this is his, it's
some kind of archetype.
QUESADA: DB, Ville Platt,
machinist. You're up.
Hey, we caught a break
in the case, boss.
I thought you were
handing that off.
What break?
KA of the victim.
Might've known the killer, boss.
Might've seen him.
We follow up.
We still got a few days.
Two days, and it
goes to task force.
You two catch again.
We'll try that serial
theory out on him,
he will pull you
just for spite.
Pelican Island
is two hours away.
Here we go.
♪
[Radio static]
MAN ON RADIO:
Put your hand in his hand.
[Radio static]
DIFFERENT MAN:
The good church teaches
that the Christian church
does not teach that,
the Catholic church does not--
[Radio static]
[Switches radio off]
Hey.
Mm-hmm?
Think a man can love
two women at once,
I mean, be in love with them?
I don't think
that man can love,
at least not the way
that he means.
Inadequacies of reality
always set in.
This pipeline is
carving up this coast
like a jigsaw.
Place is gonna be
underwater in 30 years.
[Sighs]
Do you think--
Do you wonder ever
if you're a bad man?
No. I don't wonder,
Marty.
World needs bad men.
We keep the other
bad men from the door.
That's him.
HART: When's the last time
you saw your granddaughter?
She left 4 years ago,
like her ma.
Wasn't surprised they
found her like that.
Yeah. Everybody
think they gonna be
something they not.
Everybody, they got
this big plan.
She had a boyfriend
you know about, a man?
Eh, she took up with
that Ledoux fella--
older boy,
shit family--
run off with him.
I ain't never had nobody
ask me about him before.
He just tell me she
died in the flood.
That Ledoux family,
they still live around here?
Oh, maybe a cousin or two.
Been shrinking every year.
Hurricane Andrew wiped most
of the folks out around here.
So you got a full name
on that Ledoux boy?
Reggie.
Reggie Ledoux.
Father
is Bart Ledoux--
works offshore, drunkard.
I heard he died.
Heh.
So where'd Rianne go to school?
Light of Way when it was open.
Kids either went there
or they were bussed
to Abbeville.
State said a kid
got to be bussed
two hours away to school.
I ain't too big on
them God botherers.
Between them
and the government--
How about her parents,
other relatives?
Father is a merchant seaman.
Mother is in California,
last I heard.
Do you have
anything of hers--
possessions,
anything that'd give us
an idea what he
might have been like?
What you boys looking
all this up for?
I was told she drowned
in the flood.
Now, I ain't no idiot.
You telling me she
ain't done drowned?
We don't know that, sir.
We're just looking for a man
who might have known her.
Who?
That's what we're trying
to figure out.
HART: He ended up having
a little box of her stuff,
had her last yearbook,
tenth grade,
not a hint of feeling
from the old man,
kind of got blinders,
but why'd he keep the box, huh?
Did he ask himself?
Anyway, I guess,
that's one way to do it--
keep your eyes
on the crab traps.
Kind of reminded me
of Rust a little bit.
This school is small,
grades one through 12.
Rianne Olivier.
Here she is, tenth grade.
Hmm.
_
This school was part
of Tuttle's foundation.
[Mower running]
_
[Mower stops]
Good afternoon.
Afternoon.
This place shut down
'92, right?
Yeah, the way I heard it.
What'd you hear?
Oh, Andrew blew it out.
Guess they didn't think
it was worth cleaning up.
Do you work here, then?
No, sir. I work
for the parish,
cover several properties.
WOMAN ON POLICE RADIO:
I-23?
I-23. Go.
I've got comeback on your R&I.
Reginald Ledoux--
DOB 11/13/60.
You know anybody who went here
or worked here back then?
Mm, no, sir.
I only been coming here
the last few months.
Parish added it
to my work order.
[Car horn honks]
Thank you for your time.
HART: Who walks
that fucking slow?
What you got?
R&I just came back.
Reggie Ledoux skipped
parole 8 months ago.
He's got a stat.
rape complaint,
charges dropped,
but '93, he's busted
in connection
to a narcotics lab
used to make meth and LSD,
which Dora Lange and
Rianne were full of.
Right.
Ledoux did two years
at Avoyelles,
and guess who his cellmate was
the last 4 months.
Charlie Lange.
I got to give you this one.
I started to believe
you were going
a little off your nut.
I mean, you're bonkers,
just not on this.
All right.
Where was Ledoux?
Getting a list
of relatives, KAs.
Been out of pocket
since jumping parole.
We'll find him.
This makes sense.
Looks good, baby.
All right.
We are on our way.
To Avoyelles.
Fuck, yeah, Martin.
Let's go.
I'm calling the interstate APB
and the US Marshals on this.
I-23 to dispatch.
WOMAN ON POLICE RADIO:
Come in, I-23.
What can I say?
I thought for a minute,
you just liked looking
at pictures of dead people.
I need an all-state APB
on one Reginald Ledoux.
R&I came back with info.
All US Marshals
and Highway Patrol,
be advised, detain
on sight, over.
WOMAN ON POLICE RADIO:
Roger that, Detective.
We've got that sent now.
COHLE: Mm, mm, mm.
♪
And finally, we arrive
at Reginald Ledoux. Heh.
HART: Come on, man.
You want to ask me,
ask, goddamn it.
You ever been in a gunfight?
No.
♪
Well, then how the fuck
you gonna know
what I'm talking about?
COHLE: Man, that place--
I never--
That day, it reminded me
of my pop talking about 'Nam
and the jungle thing.
Look. Me talking about
what happened back then,
that ain't gonna do you
any good now.
This--
This is what I'm talking about.
This is what I mean
when I'm talking
about time and death
and futility.
There are broader ideas
at work,
mainly what is owed
between us as a society
for our mutual illusions.
14 straight hours
of staring at DBs,
these are the things
you think of.
You ever done that? Hmm?
You look in their eyes,
even in a picture.
Doesn't matter
if they're dead or alive.
You can still read them,
and you know what you see?
They welcomed it,
mm-hmm, not at first,
but right there
in the last instant.
It an unmistakable relief,
see, because they were afraid
and now they saw
for the very first time
how easy it was to just let go,
and they saw--
In that last nanosecond,
they saw what they were,
that you, yourself,
this whole big drama,
it was never anything
but a jerry-rig
of presumption and dumb will
and you could just let go
finally now that you didn't have
to hold on so tight...
to realize that
all your life--
you know, all your love,
all your hate,
all your memory, all your pain--
it was all the same thing.
It was all the same dream,
a dream that you had
inside a locked room,
a dream about being a person...
and like a lot of dreams...
there's a monster
at the end of it.
♪
Sync and corrections by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player