Previously on "Vikings"...
Earl Ragnar,
you seem to forget I am king.
Ragnar Lothbrok wants to be king.
His fame eclipses even yours.
I'm supposed to be eternally grateful
to my husband's killer.
Everything that I was
has been stripped away from me.
I want my old position back.
I helped Ragnar rise
and now he is earl.
Earl Ragnar.
And our little world waits upon him
and eats from his hand.
King Horik understands the gods
better than Ragnar.
There is something about him.
You talk about trust. You!
I am a trustworthy person.
We know the things we like
and those we hate.
I have a proposition to put to you.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ More, give me more ♪
♪ Give me more ♪
♪ If I had a heart I could love you ♪
♪ If I had a voice I would sing ♪
♪ After the night when I wake up ♪
♪ I'll see what tomorrow brings ♪
♪ I... I... I... ♪
♪ If I had a voice I would sing ♪
Sync & corrections by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
That's it, my boy.
Show your brother
how to tighten them.
I must help your father.
Klaus! Hurry!
Erik, come here.
We have some work to be done.
What is it?
Floki.
Floki, it's me.
Helga!
Hey...
We have a child, Helga.
Yes, we have a child.
- A beautiful girl.
- A girl!
You did not come,
so I brought her to see you.
A girl!
- I don't want to drop her.
- You won't drop her.
A girl...
A beautiful, beautiful girl.
How is it possible?
Take her back.
What shall we call her, hey?
Angrboda.
- The name of Loki's first wife?
- Yes, yes.
But she's...
What's wrong with that?
They thought she was evil.
They had monstrous offspring.
She was a great giantess, Helga!
Will you come back with us?
Will you get to know your daughter?
No. I have to stay in Kattegat.
But you, you must go home.
Can't I stay awhile...
You don't understand, Helga!
You have to leave!
Leave! Leave!
Oh, there!
They're here, father!
- Father!
- Let's go!
Hey! Erlendur!
Welcome! Welcome to Kattegat!
Sisters.
Darlings!
Are you well?
Yes, all of us are well now.
Come! Come, family!
I want you to meet Ragnar. Huh?
Are you hungry?
Welcome!
Ragnar Lothbrok, my friend and ally,
and all your family gathered,
let me properly present to you
my wife, Gunnhild,
and my children.
Ragnar,
you and I have formed an alliance
on which the future of our country
and its people depends.
In this endeavor,
I see you more than ever as an equal.
Between us...
and, of course Earl Ingstad...
we have already accomplished so much.
We have land and opportunity
in Wessex...
But that is only the beginning.
We know already there are
many other worlds to discover,
and we shall do so together,
united even more
by the bonds of family...
for you have many sons
and, as you can see,
I have many daughters.
It is our custom to celebrate
such an alliance
as the gods celebrated theirs...
with feasting and with pledges.
Yeah!
You must be the famous
shield-maiden Lagertha.
Oh, you are more famous, Gunnhild.
The poets talk of your exploits.
They tell how you killed
Swein Forkbeard
when he invaded Gotaland.
And they say that you are
now an earl in your own right!
How did it happen?
I killed my husband
when he invaded me.
- What is it?
- Don't you remember?
You were going to put
a proposition for me?
Was I?
Yes! And I am still waiting!
The thing is, Floki,
I'm not entirely sure I can trust you.
Over here!
I have something for you!
Bring it with you!
Porunn,
you are a free woman now.
What will you do with your freedom?
I will use it to choose.
- To choose what?
- You don't understand.
When I was a slave, I loved you.
You were the first to treat me
as if I was not a slave.
But now, I have choices.
There are plenty of other women here.
That is your first mistake.
Hey! Hey!
Ah, Torstein...
Up to your usual tricks I see.
These two beautiful women
approached me.
They chose you for the size
of your silver pouch
and nothing else.
I don't think about it too much.
If these women don't love me,
what do I care?
They will still make me happy.
Here! Have some more!
Siggy.
I am pleased to see you.
I would like to know your plans
while you are here.
My wife is here,
and my children are here.
That's all you need to know.
You again! You again!
Why did you come back, priest?
Nobody wants you here.
You betrayed the gods!
You betrayed all of us.
It's your fault Rollo's going to die.
Forgive me, Floki.
I know I should trust you,
but I need proof.
- Proof?
- Yes.
Prove to me I can trust you.
Prove to me you are on my side.
How can I prove it?
Kill someone. Someone who matters.
Erlendur!
Take your time, Torstein.
You missed it!
Yeah!
Floki!
Have you made up your mind?
Yes.
I know who I will kill.
Next summer,
I say we should return to Wessex,
claim our land from King Ecbert.
Those who wish to farm should do so,
and divide the land between them.
What should the rest of us do, hmm?
Those who do not wish to be farmers.
Those can join King Ecbert
and Princess Kwenthrith
in the battle for Mercia.
I am sure they will be rewarded well.
I agree with you.
I think we should claim the land,
but I do not like the idea
of being Ecbert's handmaiden.
I still have a score
to settle with him
and unlike Ragnar,
I do not trust him.
But isn't it best to test him
to see if he is honest?
I believe he is telling the truth.
Then you are still innocent.
So you agree with me?
No. I agree that those
who wish to farm should do so
and also ask
for King Ecbert's protection.
But for some of us,
those of us who still want to raid,
we will go elsewhere,
explore and discover new places.
How is he?
He's alive.
Will he ever walk again?
Only the gods know.
Do you watch over him
day and night?
Listen.
I'll stay with him for a while.
- You get some sleep.
- No, I...
Go get some sleep, Siggy.
You deserve it. I will watch him.
Thank you.
You put me in a bed
like this once, Rollo.
Do you remember?
I brought you something.
Look!
It's the food of the gods.
Eat!
- Catch me again!
- I'm warning you!
Ubbe!
Give this gift to Torstein.
Say that they are
from his good friend Floki.
Oh! And one more thing.
You must never tell anyone
that it was me who gave them to him.
That must be our secret.
Do you agree?
Good. Because if you don't
keep this secret,
something terrible will happen to you.
Do you know what will happen?
I'll tell you.
When the God Loki had done
something terribly bad,
the other gods took him
to a nasty dark cave.
And there they chained him
on three sharp rocks,
and above him
they fastened a vile snake
so that its poison would
drip, drip, drip
forever on Loki's face.
Now, you wouldn't want that
to happen to you, would you?
Well, go and give my present
to Torstein,
but keep the secret.
My friend Torstein has been murdered.
I swear by all the gods,
whoever did this
will pay a heavy price.
We'll find the guilty one!
And we shall flay the skin
from his body
and use horses to tear him apart!
You did well.
Now I know I can trust you.
So, what is your plan?
I will kill them all.
- All?
- Yes, all.
- Ragnar?
- Of course Ragnar.
And Lagertha, and Aslaug.
All of them.
All their bastard children.
I will wipe his family
from the face of the earth.
And Bjorn? What of Bjorn?
Bjorn Ironside.
He is difficult to kill.
Perhaps the gods are protecting him.
You must find a way to kill him.
I have no doubt you will manage.
I know you will manage.
When?
Tomorrow.
Be prepared, my friend.
The gods are coming.
I know.
It's not goat. It's mutton.
- Two more?
- Yeah, two more.
How many do you want?
Porunn.
Forgive me for what I said.
I don't want other women.
I want you.
What do you want from me?
Respect.
You know I respect you.
I worship you.
I don't want to be worshipped.
I spent my life as a slave.
Your words are ridiculous.
What can I do?
You can fight me.
- Fight you?
- Yes.
It's no use!
Don't give up.
What do you care if I give up or not?
Do you want an honest answer?
I don't know.
But I think you might
still be useful somehow.
To whom?
Shouldn't you be with your wife?
Doesn't she have need of you?
- Don't play games.
- There are no more games.
Yes, there is,
and this is the final one.
You once promised you would
tell me Ragnar's weaknesses.
I don't ever remember you
delivering on that promise.
Well, you wasted
all your seed on a promise.
Tell me now.
Is it not obvious?
Ragnar's weakness is his children.
Then this is what you must do.
You must go to the Great Hall
at sunset
and you must kill
Ragnar's young sons.
What do I get in return?
I will marry you.
Gunnhild is my only wife
at the moment.
I will take a second.
I will make you a queen.
You will rule again, as you once did.
What was that?
Porunn! Please, stop.
Please what?
Porunn!
Porunn, I'm sorry!
It was an accident!
Porunn! Where are you?
Porunn!
This is the Sword of Kings.
One day, if the gods will it,
this sword will belong to you.
Today we must do
something extraordinary.
We must overcome the magic
of Ragnar Lothbrok,
which threatens our power
and survival.
The gods have spoken,
and I have listened.
We must cut and kill in such a frenzy
none can survive.
For, believe me, if even one
of that family survives,
then the day will come when
he will rise again and destroy us.
Put yourself in the hands
of the gods, do their will.
And then, for certain,
they will grant you this sword,
and a kingdom.
Come.
I've seen you praying
to your God.
Will you teach me one of your prayers,
so I can learn?
Our Father, who art in Heaven...
Hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come. Thy will be done,
on Earth as it is in Heaven...
Thy kingdom come, thy will be done.
Give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us our trespasses,
as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
And forgive us our trespasses,
as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
Boys! Come with me!
And lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from Evil.
Forever and ever, amen.
Forever and ever...
Amen.
- Bring it here, girl.
- Yes, mistress.
Erlendur!
And deliver us from Evil.
Floki, where have you been?
Looking after you, Bjorn...
like I promised your father.
Earl Ingstad,
you should leave now.
I have orders from Earl Ragnar.
Ragnar Lothbrok!
Floki, you have betrayed the gods.
No, King Horik,
I only betrayed you.
I was always true to the gods.
And Ragnar.
Ragnar, if you can find it
in your heart,
spare my son.
Go.
Sync & corrections by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player