We have built a new boat.
For the first time,
we can go west.
Countless riches await us.
Our enemies are everywhere.
They cannot prevail.
The Earl knows nothing
about our new boat.
He could kill us
for disobeying his orders.
Have you got the balls
to join us?
They have set sail.
They'll never be
heard from again...
What if Ragnar is right?
There are no lands to the West!
- They've come.
- They're here.
Who is here?
Hell - and all its devils!
How do you speak our language?
Why have you not killed
this one?
He is worth more alive.
Take what you will.
This is what we came for.
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
♪ More, ♪
♪ Give me more ♪
♪ If I had a heart
I could love you ♪
♪ If I had a voice
I would sing ♪
♪ After the night
when I wake up ♪
♪ I'll see
what tomorrow brings ♪
♪ I... I... I... ♪
♪ If I had a voice
I would sing ♪
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Hello!
You are Ragnar Lothbrok's son,
Bjorn.
I remember you from the thing.
Yes.
Where is your father?
Bjorn? Who are you
talking to?
I was just asking your son
where Ragnar Lothbrok might be?
He's gone fishing.
Oh! Fishing.
Yes, fishing.
When will he return?
I don't know.
In which case I must take
someone back as surety,
just in case.
In case...?
In case your husband
has not gone fishing!
You! Come!
Come!
You have to come with me.
If you don't obey this order,
the Earl will never give you
an arm-ring!
I'll come.
Good.
Then let's be on our way.
What are you doing?
Where are you taking my son?
He'll be quite safe, woman.
I bid you all a good day.
We did it, brother.
Yes, brother, we did.
Let's just hope the Earl
sees it that way.
Yeah.
What is your name?
Athelstan.
I am Ragnar Lothbrok.
What was that place called?
Lindisfarne.
England?
Yes.
It was foretold
that divine punishment
would fall upon God's chosen
people for all our grievous sins,
and so it has happened.
And that is why I am here.
No.
You are here
because I spared your life.
Why did you spare my life?
I don't know yet.
Ragnar Lothbrok!
What is it?
Brother cenwulf here,
beside me,
I think he's dead.
You're right.
Leif.
May God rest your soul,
brother cenwulf.
E nomine patri, e filii,
et spiritus sancti.
Amen.
Yeah!
We'll drink well tonight,
my friend.
Ahhh.
Erik!
Oh, thank the gods!
And not alone!
Look!
We've brought slaves to sell.
But there's more, woman.
More things of gold and silver
than you and I have ever
seen before,
nor anyone else here
in Kattegat.
Ragnar Lothbrok, welcome back.
We know you sailed West
across the open ocean
and found land and plunder,
as you promised.
So let no man say any more
that it is not possible,
and we salute and praise you.
Knut.
You're too late.
You missed the boat.
I came to tell you that
Earl Haraldson summons you
to attend him
in the great hall.
It will be a pleasure.
Well done, Ragnar!
Are you coming, Knut?
My Lord,
it was easy to take
all of these things.
The priests in their temple,
they had no weapons.
They were like babies.
Here is one of their priests.
We captured several of them
to sell for slaves.
It must be true
that there are many more
such holy places in England
and other lands to the West
likewise filled
with such treasure,
and to sail there
will benefit us all.
How did you find this place
of great riches
when all before you had failed?
My Lord,
we were more fortunate
than others.
We had Thor on our side.
Thor. Thor. Thor.
Yes.
Then you were indeed fortunate.
But you understand that
all this belongs to me,
by right.
My Lord, me and Floki paid
for the boat.
Surely we are entitled to...
some reward, and my crew...
You want me to pay you
when you took these things
as easily as from babies?
Here's what I've decided
to do...
Each one of you
can take one thing
from this haul.
One?
Yes. And you'll still be richer
than you were before.
Now, all the world can see
how magnanimous and generous
is your Lord,
especially since you
disobeyed me.
So, Ragnar Lothbrok,
what will you choose?
I will take the priest
for my slave.
The priest?
Granted.
Why did you do that?
Why did you give everything away
so easily?
We wasted our time.
I never should have
believed in you.
He was looking for an excuse
to kill us.
Why would we go to Valhalla
after such miserable
and pointless deaths?
Brother, believe me,
this is not the end,
it's just the beginning.
Well...
At least we didn't give
everything away so easily.
That's your one thing?
How should he ever find out?
You idiot!
Would Odin expect us
to do anything so stupid?
You have your Odin
and I have mine.
Why don't you go get drunk,
spend all this on whores.
Make sure the Earl really finds
out that you stole from him.
What a hoard is this!
What a hoard it is.
See what you've done, my Lord?
Never doubt your power.
With just a few words,
you stripped Ragnar Lothbrok
of all his treasure.
He's nothing to you,
and you are all power,
all authority.
You can have whatever you want.
They told me you'd come home!
Father! You're home!
Little man...
Did you reach the West?
So...
Where's all the treasure
you promised?
The Earl took it all
for himself.
But I found it,
and it filled the boat.
I believe you.
You ought to believe me.
This is a priest
from the temple to prove it.
Priest!
This is my family.
His name is Athelstan.
Although he's a foreigner,
he speaks our language,
don't you?
A little, yes.
What is wrong with your head?
When we become monks,
they cut our hair.
It marks us out.
If you're a priest,
which God do you like best?
There is only one God.
Here, you can touch him.
Are we keeping him?
Hello.
I've missed your smell
and your body.
Why do you wear this?
All monks do.
Look at his feet.
Athelstan.
Athelstan, we want to ask you
something.
Come and join us, priest.
Come on.
Don't you want to?
You'll enjoy it.
I am a monk.
I have taken vows of celibacy.
I cannot touch a woman.
I never have.
Wouldn't you like to?
It would be a sin.
Who would know?
God would know.
What if he looked
the other way?
Go to sleep then...
with your God.
Is this what you wanted?
There are so many...
Bjorn, where are you going?
Time for breakfast.
Agh!
What age are you, boy?
Thirteen.
The age my boy would have been.
The men will soon be going
on the summer raids,
are you looking forward
to joining them?
I dream of it.
I'm already a good fighter,
like my father was.
That's why I chose you,
because you're broad
and strong.
That's deep enough.
Come.
Why are you burying
all this treasure?
Don't you know anything, boy?
Odin promises that a man
will have the use
of everything he has hoarded
up after he is dead
and wakes up again in Valhalla.
But the hoard needs protection,
somebody to look after it...
In this life...
and the next.
You've already seen enough
of this life, boy.
Aghhh! Oh!
No more.
We don't like those
in our house
to go hungry or thirsty.
I am very curious
about England.
Does it have one king
who rules over
the whole country?
There are four kingdoms
with four kings.
You landed in the Kingdom
of Northumbria.
The king of Northumbria
is called Aelle.
He is a great king.
A powerful king.
Then why did his men
not protect your temple?
Before you came,
we had no need
to protect our monastery.
We lived in peace.
Everyone respected it
as a place of God.
Why does your God need
silver and gold, hmm?
He must be greedy...
Like Loki!
We have greedy gods too.
My God is not greedy.
His kingdom is not
of this world.
Then why is his kingdom
so full of treasure?
Christian people
give away their riches
to the churches and monasteries
in order to save their souls.
What are their souls?
I want to learn
some of your language.
Will you teach me, priest?
You. Come.
Ragnar Lothbrok.
My Lord.
And how do you find
your new slave?
Hmm...
I find him very useful,
as you will discover.
So what do you want?
I want to sail West again.
I have spoken at great lengths
with my Christian slave.
He is not a stupid person,
however stupid his God is.
He has traveled a great deal,
and he has told me that there
are many countries to the West.
He has also told me
about his England,
about his kings
and his customs.
And what are we to do
with his customs?
He has informed me
of a large town,
near to the temple
that we raided before.
And in this town there
are other temples,
and surely other riches.
No! I was lying!
There's nothing there!
Shhh!
You see?
This town is clearly
worth a visit.
Give us back our boat.
Let us go there and find out.
What do you have to lose?
Any plunder we take
will be yours to do with
as you please.
I could go there myself.
Ragnar yes, you could, my Lord,
but why put yourself in danger?
Why not leave it to someone
who has more... experience
of this journey,
and someone who is
more expendable?
Very well.
I sanction this raid...
On one condition:
a warrior I trust
goes with you.
Knut.
You will go with him
for my sake.
Trust me, Lord.
I will take very close care
of your interests.
O Lord, forgive me
for what I have done.
You will not regret this.
He's found a new way
to navigate the sea.
Find out what it is.
Run away if you want.
I have the Earl's permission
to sail back to England.
I want to leave
as soon as possible.
How soon is that?
Tomorrow.
We all wish you success.
We will sacrifice to Odin.
Are you not coming?
What?
I want you to come with me.
But the farm, the children.
Bjorn is still too young,
although he can help
on the farm.
But who is to be in charge?
The priest.
I will leave him with a key.
Father! You cannot place
a slave above me,
your natural son.
I don't regard him as a slave.
He's a responsible person.
Please, Ragnar Lothbrok,
don't do this.
What do you think, Gyda?
I don't mind.
I like the priest.
Hmm...
Then it is decided.
If any harm befalls
my children,
I will tear the lungs
out of your body, priest.
Oof!
Answer me this, Knut:
are you really with us?
Understand this!
A war band lives...
and dies together.
If you cannot trust the men
to either side of you,
or in front of you,
you are already a dead man.
I am with you.
I made a mistake before -
I did not come with you.
Now I fear Odin will make
a bad judgment of me.
For me, that's as important
as it is for you.
Just wanted to ask.
Ungh!
Ragnar!
Ha! Hi-yah!
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player