Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Agghhh!
Ungh!
Ohhh!
Agghhh!
Agh! Ugh!
Agghhhh!
Ragnar!
Agggghhhh!
Ungh! Ungh!
Agh!
Ungh!
Agghhh!
_
Odin!
Ragnar!
♪ More, give me more ♪
♪ give me more
♪ if I had a heart
I could love you ♪
♪ if I had a voice
I would sing ♪
♪ after the night
when I wake up ♪
♪ I'll see
what tomorrow brings ♪
♪ I... I... I...
♪ If I had a voice
I would sing ♪
Sync and correction by GeirDM
www.addic7ed.com
_
come on. Let's go home.
Watch.
Agh!
What are you two doing?
I'm taking Bjorn
to the thing tomorrow.
Not yet. He's not old enough.
He's twelve years old.
Take him next year.
Next year is soon enough.
He'll need a silk ribbon,
Lagertha.
You're a handsome boy.
Funny ears, though.
Don't sleep with
lots of women in Kattegat.
I can do without it
for a few days.
Is that another way
of saying you love me?
Huh?
I always dream of you.
Last night,
I dreamt you were feeding me
blood pudding.
What does that mean?
It means you're giving me
your heart.
Get your dog, boy.
Frodi! Come on, boy.
What will happen at the thing?
The Earl will deal
with some criminal offences
and then, we'll discuss
the summer raids.
And where will you go?
The Earl decides.
He owns the ships.
He'll send us to the east,
as always, to the baltic lands.
But I want to know
what is to the west...
what cities and gods
are over there.
See, I'm not satisfied...
With this.
Odin gave his eye
to acquire knowledge,
but I would give far more.
And will Earl
Haraldson let you?
Good.
Like this, nice and tight..
And on three.
One, two, three.
Very good, Gyda.
Gyda, feed the goats.
Go on!
What do you want?
We know you're all alone here.
All the men are gone.
If you're thirsty,
I will give you a drink.
If you're hungry,
I will feed you.
Otherwise, you must go.
We will eat and drink after
we've satisfied our other needs.
I don't want to kill you,
woman.
You couldn't kill me
if you tried
for a hundred years.
Aggghhhhh!
Out!
I went to
confess my love to her
but I was set upon by a bear
and an enormous hound
who guarded her home.
I killed the bear with my spear
and I managed
to strangle the hound
with my bare hands.
And that is how I gained
her hand in marriage.
Did she tell you
the same story?
Just about.
Are you ready to receive
your arm ring
and become a man?
Yes.
And what does a man do?
He fights.
And...?
He looks after his family.
That's right.
Could you look after
our family?
What do you mean?
You look after us.
Say I wasn't there.
I have a big decision to make.
It may change many things.
Now, go to sleep.
You have a big day tomorrow.
Arrggghhh!
Bjorn!
So, here you are, brother.
Rollo.
By frey and all the
gods how you've grown.
Hello, rollo.
Are you here for the thing?
You're a real man now.
Come, let's get a drink.
Looking a little pale, Bjorn.
Why don't you go lie down, hmm?
So where do you think the
Earl is going to send us this year?
Those bastards to the east
are as poor as we are.
I know.
That's why we should sail west.
I've heard such tales, rollo.
Great towns, and cities,
and treasures;
Hordes of gold and silver,
and... and a new God.
I've heard those stories too.
But what does it mean?
We can't sail across
an open ocean.
I believe there's a way
to go west.
I have something
that will change everything.
What?
What is that?
Now just listen.
A while back, I met someone,
a wanderer.
He told me that it was possible
to go west, over the open sea,
using this.
It's a sun-board.
It needs to sit in water.
Another wanderer?
This time is different.
Now tell me, Ragnar,
this-this wanderer of yours,
has he ever sailed
west himself?
Just get some water.
Now, this candle is the sun.
Every day...
The sun rises up into the sky
until noon.
See how the shadow shortens?
At noon, it is at its shortest.
That only tells me how
far South I have travelled.
Didn't I just tell you
to listen?!
The day before sailing
you mark a circle around
the pointer
where the shadow
is at its shortest at noon.
The next day at sea,
you place the board
back into water around noon
and watch the shadow.
If the shadow only touches
the circle...
Your course remains true?
Yes.
And if it passes outside
the circle, like this...
Then you have drifted
and you must steer
further South.
Yes.
And what if it never
reaches the circle?
Then you are too far South
and must steer more
to the north.
That's it!
Keep the noon shadow
on the circle
and your course will be true,
west.
But what if there is
no sun, hmm?
How can the board
help you then?
How could you find your way?
Using this.
Follow me outside.
They call it a sun-stone.
Oh! You see?
There is the sun.
Now we go west.
Come on. Come on.
Silence!
Olaf Anwend.
You have pleaded guilty
to the charge of stealing.
Tomorrow, you will run
a gauntlet of stones and turf
as punishment.
Yes, lord. Thank you, lord.
Let it be known
a fine is to be paid
by anyone who fails
to throw something.
Bring in the next accused.
There he is! Murderer!
Eric Trygvasson,
you are accused of the murder
of Sigvald strut
this January.
How do you plead?
It wasn't murder, lord.
I killed him in self-defense.
Liar!
If it wasn't murder,
why did you not declare
your crime
to the first person
that you met afterwards,
as the law obliges?
In fact, you passed by
several houses
before you reported it.
I thought the
relatives of the dead man
might be living in them.
The law allows
you to pass two houses
in such circumstances,
but never a third.
You murdered
my brother in cold blood!
It's not true!
We argued about
some disputed land.
He pulled out a knife.
You wanted
that land for yourself!
You're a liar and a coward.
Who says I'm a coward?
I'm not a coward!
Silence!
As the normal procedures
were not followed,
this killing cannot be
atoned for
by compensating
the victim's family.
Murder is a dishonorable deed
amongst our people.
Carried out in secret,
unacknowledged,
and likely to give rise
to a series of revenge killings
that would involve
your own family.
Lord, you knew about that land.
You knew I had a claim to it...
enough!
I ask you to look
to the accused.
If you think that he is guilty,
raise your arms.
The decision must be unanimous.
Eric Trygvasson,
you have been found guilty
of murder.
Yes! Justice!
How do you wish to die?
By beheading, lord.
Your wish is granted.
You shall be executed tomorrow.
After which we will shall feast
and talk about the summer raids.
You have to.
Yeah! Yeah!
Why is he smiling, father?
He wants to die
well, without fear,
to atone for his sins.
You must watch, for his sake.
It's his only hope
of reaching Valhalla.
Feed him to your pigs!
And I curse him.
May he never enter Valhalla.
May he never feast
with the gods.
Why did he do that?
He should not have done that.
Someone told me he
wanted that land for himself
and he knew Trygvasson
had the best claim to it,
but refused to sell it.
You hear that, boy?
This how things are done
around here.
Olaf, son of Ingolf,
Bjorn, son of Ragnar.
May you accept this gift
of salt and earth
to remind yourself
that you belong to both
the land and the sea.
These arm rings bind you
in loyalty to me,
your lord, your chieftain.
Any oath that you swear
on these rings
must be honored and kept.
Do you understand
and swear to this?
Yes, lord.
And do you
freely give your fealty to me,
your lord, your chieftain?
Yes, lord.
Good.
You may put on the arm rings.
Come here.
Wooooo!
Let us feast!
My lord,
we all want to feast,
but we also want to know
where we will be raiding
this summer.
Can't it wait, Ragnar?
No. Tell us.
We want to know.
We have a right to know.
Very well.
We will raid east again,
to the Eastlands,
and into Russia.
Every year
we go to the same places!
But there is an alternative...
If you choose.
Oh yes, yes. Choice, yes.
I have heard of these rumors,
these stories;
That if we travel west,
that we will somehow
reach a land
that is rich and plentiful.
But I tell you that
I will not risk my ships
or my reputation
on such a deluded fantasy.
They are my ships -
I pay for them...
and they go where
I tell them to go.
Now that's the end
of the matter.
Let's feast!
Let me see!
It's a fine ring.
Ragnar Lothbrok,
Earl Haraldson wants to
speak with you...
in private.
Stay with your Uncle.
Ragnar Lothbrok...
Sit down.
Are you hungry?
Yes, lord.
You want to feast in my hall?
You want to sail in my ships?
Anything else you want from me?
Lord...
You keep
talking about the west...
what do you know of it, hmm?
Why are you so certain
that it's a land
of great riches, hmm?
I can't be sure.
But I believe that...
I don't care what you believe.
You insulted me out there,
and not for the first time,
but, believe me,
it will be the last.
Who told you you could go?
You are a farmer.
You should be content
with your lot.
Farms are few
and in great demand,
and there are many people here
who would like to possess
your land.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
I understand.
Then don't ever stick your nose
in my face again.
I don't trust him. Watch him.
Where are they?
Where are my sons?
You said you'd found them.
Where are we going now?
I'm so tired.
To talk to the gods.
It's what we do.
Why don't you come in?
I'm waiting.
Sit.
What do you want?
I want to know what
the gods have in store.
For you...
Or for the boy?
I'm more interested in myself.
The gods desire you
to have a great future.
I see that.
But they can withdraw
their goodwill
at any time.
To have this great future,
must I challenge the law?
You must convince
the gods to alter the runes
so they work in your favor.
But the laws of men
are far below the workings
and shapings of the gods.
So I should take
the laws of men
into my own hands?
Answer me.
You already have your answer.
No I don't.
Well, then go
and ask the gods yourself.
What are you afraid of?
Wait outside.
All right.
You haven't helped me at all,
ancient one.
Perhaps you asked
the wrong questions.
We have someone
special to visit.
His name is Floki.
Floki?
Like loki the God?
Yes, only different.
How is he different?
He's not a God.
Why didn't he come
to the thing?
Because...
Because he's shy.
Floki,
this is my son, Bjorn.
Hello.
How are you?
Well. Thank you, sir.
Let me see.
Ah!
You have your father's eyes...
Unfortunately.
Why unfortunately?
It means he will be like you,
and therefore he will want
to do better than you,
and you will hate him for it.
How can you tell that
by just looking at my face?
Oh, it's the same with trees.
I can tell which trees
will make the best planks
just by looking at them.
I can look inside the tree.
Floki is a boat-builder...
Among other things.
Hmm...
This is one.
Inside this tree are two
almost perfect planks.
They will bend, then curve,
like a woman's body
from the thighs to the back.
When I split this tree
I will find them.
You can see that?
Do you think I'm joking?
I joke about many things,
son of Ragnar,
but never about ship-building.
Do you imagine ships
are just dead things?
So... what about our boat?
It will be lighter
and carry a bigger sail.
The construction is different.
It's built with
a strong central plank.
The two strakes above it
are nailed
directly onto the knees
of the frame.
But the ones below - look!...
are cleated and lashed
onto the frames,
not nailed,
so they can move in relation
to each other.
This means the boat won't butt
against the waves like a goat,
but move over them
like a ripple.
Hmm.
The hull is deeper. How
will my men set their oars?
I will cut them
into the sheerstrakes,
and the ports can be closed
when the boat is at sea.
And you think it could handle
long sea voyages?
That's why I'm building it.
But will it be strong enough?
We won't know that
until we try.
For the anchor.
It's all I have left
from last summer's raids.
Don't worry.
We'll soon be as rich
as dwarves!
I missed you.
Did anything happen
while we were away?
No.
Hmm.
Did you miss me?
I ached with love longing.
My belly was empty of laughter.
Is that what you want? Hmm?
You want me to make you laugh?
I don't want to laugh now.
I want to ride you,
like a bull.
Like a wild bull.
Hello, young Bjorn.
Hello, rollo.
Where are your parents?
They are having sex.
Well, uh...
I guess we'll have to wait.
So, Gyda,
is your mother teaching you
how to use a shield?
Yes, I know how
to use a shield.
Your mother was a famous
shield-maiden.
Was?
Is a famous shield-maiden.
Come on, children, to bed.
Do I have to?
Let's leave the men.
But I'm a man. I have a ring.
Let him stay awhile.
To bed!
Say good night.
Good night, my children.
Good night.
Hey!
Shhhaaaaaa!
Tell me your news.
What about the boat?
It's nearly ready.
I won't go under your command.
I won't go
unless we're all equal.
We are brothers.
You and I will always be equal.
Then we must find a crew.
Not many men will go against
the wishes of Haraldson.
Many will be afraid,
some may even go to him
and betray us.
I must go piss.
Yesterday, I was
with a girl from the town.
Thank you.
A good-looking girl too.
But when she shouted out
in pleasure,
I didn't see,
I saw yours.
Lagertha...
Don't talk like that.
Why not?
I think about you all the time.
That's too bad.
Don't insult me, shield-maiden.
No.
I would never insult you.
You're too great a warrior...
But perhaps not so great a man.
I saw something.
What did you see?
A sign.
It made me certain
we're doing the right thing.
Good night, brother.
Set the sail.
Floki! The sail!
She'll sink.
No she bloody won't!
I shouldn't have
pretended to build such a boat.
It's beyond
my humble capabilities.
I'll set the sail.
Floki I'm sorry, Ragnar.
I've wasted all your money.
It was all a joke.
Shut up, man.
Ha!
Now it runs on its cool keel.
Oh, it's beautiful.
Why didn't you believe me?
I told you I could do it!
Ah?
Now it's all up to you,
Ragnar Lothbrok.
Sync and correction by GeirDM
www.addic7ed.com
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player